I've been waiting for you.
Don't be so wary of me.
The thing is,
I want to help you.
Why wouldn't I?
After all, you're innocent.
I understand that Akizumi is targeting me.
But what is there for him
to catch in the first place?
I had almost forgotten.
It was unnecessary for me
to worry about you,
the fair and strict Judge Seko.
I beg your pardon.
I've come today to thank you.
This is about
Diet member Tomita, isn't it?
Naturally, as the prosecution,
we were hoping he'd confess
with a little more pressure.
But you held back.
I owe you for that.
However…
Wouldn't it have been
more convenient for you…
if you could get rid of Tomita?
What do you mean?
If you put in the wrong kind of effort,
you might find yourself in trouble.
It must be tough for you…
trying to please everyone.
Tatsuya Kazaki
is the current State Minister of Justice.
For Seko, who's eyeing
the position of Supreme Court Justice,
Kazaki would be a valuable ally.
As I've mentioned before,
Tomita and Kazaki belong to rival factions
within the same Mineito Party.
However, with Tomita out of the picture,
Kazaki faces no opposition.
The next Minister of Justice
is almost certain to be him.
Consequently, to Kazaki,
Ms. Sawahara became a nuisance
for covering many of his scandals.
So, he instructed Ueda
to pin the information leak on her.
With his influence
over the higher-ups in the justice system,
Kazaki swayed the presiding judge
to ensure Ms. Sawahara's conviction.
Namely, Judge Seko.
It's frightening
to think individuals like them
are politicians and judges.
This is so wrong.
Those who gain twisted power
lose themselves
in their desperation to cling to it.
They fail to recognize what they're doing
is morally wrong as humans.
Wait, when did you two
find out about Seko?
Am I the only one who was in the dark?
As we were digging,
we pieced together Mr. Akizumi's plan.
Well, either way, if we want to secure
an acquittal for Ms. Sawahara,
we have no choice but to uncover the ties
between Judge Seko and politicians.
This will also pave the way
for winning a retrial for Mr. Matsunaga.
And…
I will make Seko get what she deserves.
What she deserves?
An impeachment trial.
An impeachment trial?
You mean the one where
you can remove a judge from office?
It would mean a judge,
who usually passes judgment on others,
faces judgment themselves.
True. If we pursue this,
we can legally remove Seko
from her position as a judge.
But only a few judges
have ever been impeached.
It must be a difficult process.
Naturally, evidence is crucial.
That's the law in our legal system.
We need proof that Seko and Kazaki
are unlawfully connected.
NARUMI SEKO
TATSUYA KAZAKI
A world built
on money and lust is fragile.
Like a paper tiger,
it will collapse…
with one small puncture.
When you're the guest speaker,
State Minister of Justice Kazaki,
it's no surprise people gather.
So, what did you want to discuss?
There's this bothersome attorney.
He's handling
Maki Sawahara's defense and--
You mean Akizumi?
Ueda has briefed me.
He's also the one
who took down Diet member Tomita.
JAPAN ECONOMICS AND LAW FORUM
EARLY SUMMER GATHERING
Now, we'll have today's guest speaker,
Mr. Tatsuya Kazaki,
the State Minister of Justice,
to deliver his speech.
State Minister Kazaki,
please take the stage.
It seems it's starting.
As introduced just now,
I am Tatsuya Kazaki,
the State Minister of Justice.
Hey, do you think Seko had
political backing 12 years ago?
No, at that time, Seko was just
an ordinary judge in the Chiba office.
She wasn't on a fast-track career path.
In that case,
maybe Seko began to rise to success
after that incident 12 years ago.
Some time ago, I had the chance
to review Mr. Akizumi's past case files.
But they were all unrelated
to the incident from 12 years ago.
Suddenly,
Mr. Akizumi started to take action…
I wonder what prompted him.
He's here!
Mr. Akizumi, he's here.
He's heading your way.
Right. Good work.
Now, shall we begin soon?
As Japan's economic society
becomes globalized,
free competition is advancing…
What a coincidence, Judge Seko.
What are you up to?
What do you mean?
As I've said before,
you shouldn't deliberately
engage with the presiding judge.
It's extremely inappropriate.
I'm simply attending this event
as a legal professional
who is concerned
about the future of our judicial system.
What about you?
Is it appropriate
for an active judge to appear at an event
clearly endorsing a politician?
I'm here to greet a Ministry of Justice
acquaintance who has helped me before.
You have no right to criticize me.
Leave immediately.
This isn't a courtroom,
and you have no right
to order me to leave.
…that is my sincere wish.
Thank you very much, everyone!
Sir, please stop!
Shut up!
Let go of me!
Sir, please--
Seko!
Where the hell is Seko?
Why?
Tomita?
He's been arrested, so why is he here?
It appears he was released the other day.
He's a nuisance. Get rid of him.
Right away.
-Seko!
-Sir!
Sir!
Seko!
So it's true!
After all I've done for you…
you repay my kindness with evil.
What is this about? I don't understand--
Don't pretend you don't know!
What's this about?
Let's discuss this outside. Come.
You stay out of this.
Mr. Tomita, let's speak over there.
It's all right.
-Everything is under control.
-This way.
Let's go.
Everything is all right.
Please don't worry.
What is going on? What did I do to you?
You're the one who set me up.
What are you talking about?
You wanted to drive me out of politics
because I became a hindrance.
You colluded with that corrupt attorney.
You set me and Shoichiro up together!
That's not true!
You're already here to curry favor
with the next Minister of Justice.
You misunderstand me.
Have you forgotten the lengths I went
to secure your release?
Even that…
seems doubtful now.
I'm at this event as an individual
for social reasons,
not because I wanted to be here.
The only one
truly fit to be Minister of Justice…
is you,
Mr. Tomita.
You're not the kind of person to end here.
I believe that.
That's why I pulled strings
within the prosecution
to get the indictment withdrawn.
I intend to do everything I can
to ensure your return.
It's just as we thought.
Seko was involved in Tomita's release.
To Seko, her connection
with Tomita is now a blemish.
Yet, there's a reason
she can't simply discard him.
There's something she can't risk
Tomita exposing about her.
To Seko, Tomita is a ticking bomb.
But how did you trick Tomita?
The best way
to make someone believe a lie…
is to use the person
they believe is most loyal to them.
DETAINED
Why wouldn't I?
After all, you're innocent.
You want to help me?
What a joke.
It's all your fault that Mr. Tomita was--
Have you heard that Tomita was released?
He must've used every connection he had.
It might be a matter of time
before the charges are dropped.
But what about you?
Why didn't Tomita get you released
along with him?
There's only one reason.
It's a trick politicians often use.
"My secretary acted alone."
That one.
I'm truly sorry.
I caused a scene at your important event.
Tomita is the one to blame.
You just had some bad luck.
I never expected him
to be resentful toward me.
Good grief.
He was only going to embarrass himself
by marching into enemy territory.
I wonder how he managed to get in.
Indeed.
You wanted to drive me out of politics
because I became a hindrance.
You colluded with that corrupt attorney.
There's no question
that there was bribery…
between Tomita and Seko.
But Tomita must have been
careful about this.
He didn't let us secretaries get involved.
So, you don't have
any evidence to prove it.
Is that right?
Yes.
Well then, Mr. Kosugi.
Do you know something about this case?
Six months ago,
Mr. Masato Matsunaga
was convicted in a trial.
One of his friends confessed
that Diet member Tomita
was bribing people to alter testimonies.
You're aware of this, aren't you?
Please tell us the truth.
Don't worry.
Tomita instructed me, and…
I distributed the money.
Could you…
testify to that?
-I can't--
-Mr. Kosugi.
Think very carefully…
about who can protect you right now.
Very well.
I'll testify.
Good day.
Are you sure…
everything is all right?
If you let me handle everything,
you have nothing to worry about.
All right then.
Mr. Matsunaga!
It seems we can petition…
for your retrial.
Every testimony at your trial
was dishonestly manipulated by Tomita.
We've found someone
who will testify to that.
This time for sure…
I'll secure your acquittal.
Please do.
I will.
As I suspected, Akizumi was
behind the secretary's release.
All right. You may go.
What will you do now?
What else is there to do?
Right?
This is the Akizumi Law Office.
Mr. Akizumi.
This is Akizumi. What's the matter?
Um…
The other day, I said I'd testify for you.
Yes.
I want you…
to forget I said that.
What?
I take back everything I said.
Also, I don't need you
to defend me anymore.
What are you talking about?
This isn't what you agreed to.
Anyway, that's what I've decided.
-Mr. Kosugi!
-Well then.
It seems Kosugi has joined
the Kazaki camp as a secretary.
Kosugi couldn't hope for a better
opportunity than joining the Kazaki camp,
the most powerful faction right now.
It's pointless to try to persuade him.
But why the sudden change?
Perhaps our actions were leaked to them.
It's possible Seko pulled some strings.
Ms. Sawahara.
I need you to do something for us.
Damn it!
Mr. Kosugi won't answer.
What are you here for?
To assist you.
Huh?
You must realize by now
who your true enemies are.
Seko and Kosugi.
They were planning to set you up
from the beginning.
Seko already intended
to wash her hands of you and join Kazaki.
That's why she used Mr. Shoichiro's trial.
Shoichiro's trial?
The footage that incriminated you
is the evidence.
You remember who it showed, don't you?
This is your reward for providing us
with the dashcam footage.
But I can't--
…orchestrate things
in your business's favor.
I trust you'll work with us.
Kosugi intentionally
recorded that footage.
As a result, he was arrested too.
However, his plan
was to pin all the blame on you,
and to have Seko exonerate him.
But Seko secured my release…
Her decision to release you was merely
a tactic to lower your defenses.
Now, it seems she's pulling strings
within the prosecution
to have you rearrested.
Rearrested?
Impossible.
How could you have that information?
You see, one of my clients is a reporter.
This is Ms. Sawahara, the former
vice editor-in-chief of Taiyo Weekly.
She specializes in politics.
According to my source,
the authorities will come
to search your house within a few days.
Like that's possible…
You've committed many other crimes.
And Seko has covered them up.
Is that what you thought?
But Seko has a connection
with the prosecution's head.
If they wished,
they could issue an arrest warrant
for you at any time.
They're trying to bring you down again
with what they have on you.
For what?
Isn't it obvious?
To solidify Kazaki's position.
You stand to lose everything,
while they continue to profit at leisure.
Even your son, Mr. Shoichiro, is caught
in the crossfire of this power struggle.
Will you let this continue?
You can still prevent this.
Strike first before they do.
Even if it means risking everything.
You possess the means to do so.
People make mistakes.
But they're also capable
of correcting their mistakes.
I hope you'll face your errors, repent,
and become the latter.
I was listening to your ruling today.
You seemed genuinely concerned
about the accused.
It's nothing so grandiose.
By the way…
you met Chief Prosecutor Datehara
the other day, right?
As his aide, you don't miss much, do you?
What did you discuss?
It's rude to pry into a conversation
between a man and a woman.
I've come…
to confirm something one last time.
One last time?
Won't you come clean about everything?
About your crimes?
Ridiculous.
You volunteer at that children's home.
The children admire you.
You're just, kind…
and compassionate.
They see you as a judge worthy of respect.
Can you face them…
with your head held high?
"People make mistakes."
"But they're also capable
of correcting their mistakes."
That's what you said earlier.
I am a judge.
I may pass judgment on crimes,
but I never commit them myself.
Is that so?
I bribed Judge Seko.
The total was over 20 million yen.
She covered up my son's crimes
and did other favors for me.
In return,
we agreed that I would support her
to become the Supreme Court Justice.
How did you transfer the money?
I handed it to her personally in cash.
Compare this
with the contents of Seko's safe.
Everything is recorded here.
Wow.
He confessed everything,
even how he bribed her
and the total amount.
I'm surprised he took such a big risk.
Mr. Akizumi,
you pushed Tomita into a corner
so that he would do this.
His secretary betraying him
was also part of the plan.
Actually, there's been a man
hanging around the office lately.
He's Prosecutor Kikuchi,
a subordinate
of Chief Prosecutor Datehara.
Chief Prosecutor Datehara?
Everything Kikuchi reports
also reaches Seko through Datehara.
Is that why you called Kosugi
to our office?
All right then.
You deliberately wanted to demonstrate
your connection with Kosugi.
Upon hearing Kikuchi's report,
Seko must have felt uneasy…
knowing that someone aware of her secrets
was within my reach, of all people.
I could expose them at any moment.
This is why Seko turned to Kazaki,
and brought Kosugi around.
And that's why Tomita…
When people feel isolated and suspicious,
they often reveal their vulnerabilities.
Everything…
was done to bring down Seko.
The indictment request
for your impeachment trial
has been accepted.
The Committee will review it soon.
Who initiated this?
The request was submitted…
by Seiji Tomita.
The agent…
is Masaki Akizumi.
MR. KAZAKI
A cornered animal is a dangerous foe.
This situation seems to be exactly that.
You have influence even over Diet members.
Make them drop this indictment request.
What?
Right now…
I'm in deep shock.
You were supposed to be
the epitome of a fair judge.
Instead, you were blinded
by position and money.
And you were convicting innocent people
to further your own career.
What are you saying?
You dragged me down this path!
You introduced me to politicians.
And pushed me to accept bribes.
Did I?
Don't play games.
I never wanted to gain this position
using such methods, not in the slightest!
You never wanted it?
How strange.
You disregarded my advice
and took steps
to safeguard your current position.
That's how it appeared to me.
It seems…
there's nothing more I can do for you.
I see.
So, you're not concerned?
I might reveal everything at my trial.
Including what happened 12 years ago.
I wonder how many people
will believe your words now?
It's a lonely thought.
To think…
I'll never see you in the courtroom again.
There's no longer a place for you there.
How dare you.
You've brought this upon yourself.
You've just destroyed
everything I've worked so hard to build.
What you've built
isn't a legacy of achievements,
but stacks of bills
tainted with corruption.
I needed power.
Overwhelming power
that would silence all dissent!
A man like yourself
could never understand.
The frustration of never being
acknowledged solely for your skills
simply because you're a woman.
Nor the humiliation
of being underestimated
by less competent men.
In the Diet, the Cabinet,
and even within the realm of judges,
there are far too few women
represented in this country.
I needed to climb to the top
and deliver results!
I have a mission.
I only did what was necessary
to bring about change in this country.
You might have a point.
Currently, in this country…
many women are having
their dignity crushed
and enduring humiliation.
That includes Ms. Maki Sawahara.
She tried to do
what was right as a journalist.
However, because of men
who saw her as an obstacle,
she was framed as a criminal
despite her innocence.
You were supposed to understand her
better than anyone else.
Yet, instead of aiding her,
you attempted to bring her down,
just like those men.
You only desired power.
Perhaps initially, you acted on a whim.
But people become accustomed to it.
They descend down a dark path,
and as they immerse themselves
in its tepid comfort,
their senses grow dull.
To the point
where they irrationally believe
that it's acceptable to convict
an innocent person.
The men who have trampled upon your pride
and yourself at this moment…
Who is worse, I wonder.
Yata no Kagami.
The mirror that reflects
clear, unclouded truth.
Your conscience has been clouded
by selfish desires.
You no longer have the right
to wear that badge.
I offered you a final warning
the other day.
Perhaps I wanted to believe.
"Behind sad incidents,
there are suffering children."
"I want to be of some help to them."
I wanted to believe
that at least you meant those words.
That when you said them
and looked toward the children…
your eyes weren't clouded.
It seems I was mistaken.
I'm disappointed.
So, in addition to suppressing evidence
and hiding criminals,
you're also admitting
to bribing Judge Seko?
Absolutely.
I want to apologize
to the citizens I've betrayed
and to my son whom I've implicated.
Thanks to Tomita admitting his corruption,
public opinion has shifted significantly.
Yes.
That's why Judge Seko's impeachment trial
is moving forward
with unprecedented speed.
…and your date of birth.
Are they correct as stated
in the grounds for indictment?
Ms. Sawahara's second instance…
This is the decision.
…was delayed because of Seko's indictment.
The accused…
I'm glad she was found innocent.
Yes.
Next…
Mr. Akamine.
Let's go.
Now, defense counsel.
Please deliver your final argument.
Mr. Matsunaga…
is a victim.
A sloppy investigation
by the police and prosecution,
negligence and abdication
of responsibility by the defense counsel,
and unlawful dealings by the judge.
Many people contributed
to Mr. Matsunaga's wrongful conviction.
Mr. Matsunaga's dignity
was deeply harmed by these individuals.
The evidence speaks for itself.
But I urge…
everyone involved in the law
to take this opportunity
to reflect on their own ethics.
We are the ones…
who robbed the light
from Mr. Matsunaga's life.
It is his natural right…
to walk with his head held high.
And it is our duty to protect that right.
This is for Mr. Matsunaga,
and to prevent…
others from suffering as he did.
I am determined…
to overturn this ruling…
with responsibility and resolve.
Mr. Matsunaga is innocent.
That is all.
I will now deliver the verdict
on the accused, Masato Matsunaga,
regarding the injury case.
The decision.
The accused…
is found innocent.
I'm…
truly sorry.
If only I had more skill…
It took…
It took so long.
I'm so sorry.
For so long…
I thought my life was over.
I had given up,
thinking I could never trust anyone.
But you made me believe
that I could trust someone again.
Thank you.
I see.
So, you're reporting for Tokyo Chuo?
Yes.
Thanks to you.
No.
Without your help,
we couldn't have secured
Mr. Matsunaga's acquittal.
This experience
has made me realize the issues
of Japan's justice system firsthand.
I want to shed light on them in my own way
for other victims of false accusations.
Is that so?
In that case,
I have some information for you.
Hey, put them away.
Honestly.
TOKYO CHUO NEWSPAPER
FALSE ACCUSATION
IN ITOI FAMILY MURDERS?
Judge Seko has handed down
a death sentence in a trial
concerning the Itoi family murders
12 years ago.
The condemned criminal, Yusaku Shimizu,
had maintained his innocence at the time.
Now, 12 years later,
doubts are emerging
regarding the correctness of--
Saya!
The incident took place in 2012.
Makoto Itoi, an office worker,
his wife Eriko, and their daughter Natsu…
Here you go.
Thanks.
It's finally moving forward.
Mr. Akizumi must've asked Ms. Sawahara.
He's trying to secure a retrial
for Mr. Shimizu using the mass media.
All the cases following Shoichiro's
are connected to the false accusation
against Mr. Shimizu.
There's just one thing.
Hiyama, right?
FALSE ACCUSATION
IN ITOI FAMILY MURDERS?
You're behind this article, aren't you?
Yes.
I told you I didn't want a retrial.
Why not?
I've made up my mind
to die quietly without causing trouble.
Is that for your daughter?
The last time you saw her…
was before the incident.
When Ms. Saya was five years old.
Stop it.
She's now 17.
She's very sweet and smart.
Stop!
I have no right…
to hear about her.
Put it away.
-Now!
-Look at her.
This is your daughter who's grown.
Stop!
Because if you see it,
your desire to see her will be too strong?
You must've imagined
what kind of woman Ms. Saya has become,
who she's living with,
what expression she wears.
These 12 years,
you must've imagined it all this time,
again and again!
You must want to know.
You must want to see her.
You must want to see her right now
and hold her!
Because you're her father!
And Ms. Saya must be feeling the same way.
No!
There's no way she wants
to see her father who's on death row!
I've committed a crime.
A very terrible crime.
Stop coming.
You might die tomorrow.
Once the sentence is carried out,
Ms. Saya won't ever see you again.
She won't be able to touch you
or hear your voice.
But that's not all.
She won't ever know your innocence.
She'll have to go on living
as the daughter of a murderer!
And that might even be
a crueler fate than your death sentence.
You're the only one who can protect her!
I know I'm asking for much.
But please,
think about it.
I promise…
to secure an acquittal for you.
I'm calling it a day.
See you.
CHILDREN'S HOME
YUMEMIRAI
Any progress?
Yes.
Could you spare a moment sometime soon?
I know where Egoshi is.
Well then,
come to the office tomorrow.
I'll inform you of the time later.
FALSE ACCUSATION
IN ITOI FAMILY MURDERS?
ITOI FAMILY MURDERS CASE
TO AKIZUMI
You saw the news, didn't you?
What are you doing?
I've come…
to apologize to you.
Everything that happened…
is my fault.
I'll tell you everything.
Everything that happened…
12 years ago.
Who's Egoshi?
This person is connected
to Mr. Shimizu's case, right?
And you're trying to locate this person…
in exchange for getting an acquittal.
Tell me everything.
HIYAMA
I won't let you get away again.
Subtitle translation by: Ai Matsuoka
I've been looking for you for so long.
Do you remember
what happened 12 years ago?
Mr. Shimizu was wrongly accused.
I didn't do it.
I killed the boss.
Ms. Saya!
Mr. Akizumi will accept it.
I'm truly sorry.
Mr. Akizumi.
Let me prove your innocence.