SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
My god, that's some bad design.
No one will come to us
with words like that!
That's all I can come up with
for a budget of 30,000 yen!
But this too provocative!
Being truthful is very important
as a bodyguard.
But it's important to create some buzz!
-It's important to stand out online.
-"Buzz"?
You know, bodyguards are just there
to support others behind the scenes.
MASAYA TAKANASHI
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
But you got one.
See? It's a customer.
-It says "Urgent."
-Move aside.
That means everything's going to be fine
if you follow my suggestions.
If you secure a client with my ad,
make sure to give me my share.
"Please save me!"
"I'm being targeted by someone!"
"I can't move!"
"Daisuke Ikuta."
It doesn't seem like a prank mail.
Hello? Are you Mr. Ikuta?
This is Shimazaki Security.
Could you please hear me out?
I'm going to ask you some questions.
Please answer either "Yes" or "No."
By the way,
are you able to talk now?
Yes.
Is it a life-threatening situation?
Are you being confined somewhere?
Yes.
Are you injured?
No.
So is someone keeping watch over you?
Yes.
We'll send help right away.
Could you tell me your current location?
Machidashi, Fujinomiya, 5-3-2.
The room facing south on the second floor.
Please don't inform the police.
ETA: 40 MINUTES
We'll need around 40 minutes to get there.
The client does not want the police
to interfere in this matter.
There are clients who are
unable to reveal their entire situation.
If the situation looks suspicious,
contact the company immediately
-and wait for our decision.
-Yes, ma'am!
All okay.
-All right!
-Okay!
That was amazing, Ms. Suganuma!
Thank you.
Next, the group over there!
SEITARO SAWAGUCHI
BODYGUARD, KICKS GUARD
You were impressive.
If you have time to tease me,
-go write up your training report!
-Okay…
The same goes for everyone else!
-Yes.
-We'll be placing a camera here.
Hey!
Sorry about that.
All right.
I don't think it's good
to rely so much on Suganuma.
What do you think?
KOUMEI RYU
PRESIDENT, KICKS CORP.
She's young and a woman no less.
And she was suddenly promoted too.
You can be direct with me.
There are rumors spreading
that I'm favoring her, right?
As a woman.
No, I haven't heard any of that.
I wonder…
I'm interested in her
in a personal capacity.
And that serves as
a form of motivation in my work.
I'm making good use of her in my business.
-Check the container's surroundings.
-Got it.
No suspicious vehicles.
No suspicious people around the building.
I see the curtains in the southern room
on the second floor.
Commencing contact.
Who is this?
Excuse me. My name is Shimazaki.
Is Mr. Daisuke in?
Do you need anything from Daisuke?
He's in, right?
-We're heading up to the second floor.
-Who the hell are you guys?
Hey, wait!
This is Shimazaki Security.
NO ENTRY
DAISUKE IKUTA
I'm Ikuta.
-I'm Shimazaki from Shimazaki Security.
-I'm Takanashi.
Nice to meet you.
I chose the smallest security company
I could find on the Internet.
If it's a big company,
they might charge more.
They probably wouldn't protect me either.
You said you're being confined.
I thought you guys
would come immediately if I said that.
Excuse me.
why did you request our services?
There's a place I have to go.
I want you to protect me
until I reach that place.
I can't stay outside for too long.
"For too long"?
Excuse me, but what's your occupation?
I've never worked before.
I have a home,
and my parents cook food for me.
I can live even without a job.
I'm not proud of it,
but I've been like this since the summer
of my second year in high school,
so this marks the 20th anniversary
of me being unemployed.
But I'm not embarrassed.
As you can see,
I'm connected to the world.
Excuse me, but where is your destination?
Please excuse me.
My elementary school is closing down
since fewer children are attending,
so they wanted to have one as a memory.
I'm impressed that they came up
with something like this at this age.
A class reunion.
It's tomorrow.
Let me put this straight.
I don't want to attend.
The problem is…
It's written at the bottom of
the card, right?
-Time capsule?
-All the students had those.
Everyone wrote their dreams for the future
and placed them into a box
to commemorate our graduation.
I would rather die than have my letter
read in front of everyone else.
That's why I'm going there
to ask my teacher
if I can retrieve my letter first.
What did you write in it?
I wanted to be
a top player in the J.League.
-That's a great dream as a child.
-You're annoying.
-I don't want it to be read.
-I'm sorry.
You know…
I'm being targeted.
Is that so?
Could you tell us the details?
Someone punctured the tires of my bicycle
and even pushed me from the back
in front of the railway crossing.
When did those happen? Could you give us
specific dates and times?
The bicycle incident was around the 20th,
and the railway crossing incident
was around the 30th, I think.
About bodyguards…
You'll be my shield, right?
You'll put your lives on the line, right?
I'm counting on you.
Oh, so he's being targeted?
What bullshit.
He's just coming up with nonsense
because he doesn't want to work.
He's just the boy who cried wolf,
except that he's in his forties!
Stop it, dear.
Daisuke is struggling too.
Isn't it all because
you buy everything for him,
that now, he's a parasite at home?
It's your fault, to begin with!
I'm sorry.
-It has nothing to do with you.
-No…
But 20 years…
It must have felt extremely long
for Mr. Daisuke,
as well as the two of you.
Are you a train operator, Mr. Ikuta?
I was just made to
retire early from my job.
Corporations are cold-hearted.
When I think about seeing
my middle-aged son
and living with him
in this small house up till now…
sometimes I even think about
killing Daisuke
and ending my own life as well.
Excuse me, but I'm counting on you.
If he meets his old friends
from the class reunion,
it might create some opportunity for him.
-I'll pay the money.
-No.
We'll receive the payment from Mr. Daisuke
since he's the client.
There's no way he can pay.
You saw him.
He's using a children's desk,
and all those toys…
People like that are called
"parasite singles."
But he's the client, right?
There's no way we can receive
the money from his family.
Then let's refuse this request.
It's just like what his father said
about him being targeted
as complete bullshit.
I trust my client.
What if we don't receive
any payment this time either?
-Aren't you going to keep us fed?
-That might be impossible…
-Maybe you should leave while you can.
-What?
Why are you saying
such irresponsible things now?
-Did you call him?
-I didn't.
That guy…
Sushi delivery!
We didn't call for one.
You're so cold as usual.
It's a present from me.
Aren't you guys hungry?
I welcome such generosity with open arms.
-How is this?
-It looks delicious!
It feels suspicious
that you're treating us.
Well, just think of it as a celebration.
-For what?
-For Suganuma.
Suganuma has been promoted
to executive officer.
With President Ryu's
recommendation, that is.
Why should we celebrate?
What? I thought
I should let you know, Takanashi.
About what?
Rumors have been spreading
around the company.
People say President Ryu and Suganuma
seem suspicious.
-Is it a life-threatening situation?
-This will be good PR for us.
-I'm glad that I recommended you.
-To secure the position of bodyguards,
you need appropriate judgment
-and make your move based on that.
-Can I ask you something?
Right…
My story was interrupted the last time.
For today, let's talk about why
I'm interested in the security industry.
Yes.
I lost the woman I loved to violence.
Five years ago,
a burglar entered my home in Los Angeles,
and my fiancé was shot by a gun.
Three months later, she died.
Actually, I had engaged a bodyguard then.
But that guy…
he didn't prevent her from getting shot.
And that's why
you thought about training bodyguards?
Unfortunately, no.
After that incident,
I realized that even if
bodyguards fail to protect their clients,
they aren't held accountable.
So I thought to myself that
this would be a profitable business.
Your fiancé…
you loved her, right?
This and that are different.
You shouldn't judge me
using normal standards.
The destination
is Fujinomiya Elementary School.
The class reunion commences at 1:00 p.m.
The distance is approximately 2km.
This is the shortest distance
we ever had to cover in a job.
Excuse me.
We're not yet on duty.
You can take it if it's a personal call.
Shimazaki, please call Shun's school.
It seems like he got injured.
What?
I'm really sorry!
It appears that he had a conflict
with one of his classmates.
Is that so?
How is he now?
He bruised his elbow.
I'm sorry.
-I'll check if he's being bullied--
-Give me the phone.
What?
SHUN SHIMAZAKI
AKIRA'S SON
This is nothing. I'm fine.
You should go get checked at the hospital.
Right. In Shiroyama General Hospital,
there's a doctor called Ms. Kasamatsu.
You can count on her.
What?
See you.
He said it's nothing.
Are you really his father?
Hey,
why would he have your contact details?
We talk sometimes.
What? I've never heard about this.
Why would he be honest
with an irresponsible father?
-Hey, that hurt.
-Oh, sorry.
It's time!
It's 10:51 a.m.
-Synchronized.
-Mr. Ikuta.
-Yes?
Let's go.
If we don't hurry,
everyone else is going to arrive first.
Oh, if you like…
Please wear this.
Don't do things I didn't tell you to do!
This attire…
-I'm fine with it.
-Please excuse me.
Please wear these, if you like.
How did you know my shoe size?
I checked it yesterday.
Is that also a bodyguard's job?
Daisuke…
You always look
as if I'm giving you two trouble.
I'll check the surroundings.
IKUTA
We're going in through the rear,
you handle the front.
Understood.
Let's go.
We're keeping a close look all around you.
You have nothing to worry about.
I look just like an ex-convict
who was just released after 20 years.
No, quiet!
You can't do that!
Aren't you the boy from Ikuta's place…
Daisuke?
Oh, my…
I haven't seen you for a long time,
so I was really worried!
How have you been?
How sarcastic.
I know everyone in this neighborhood
makes fun of me!
I'm sorry.
Good boy.
Is this where you were pushed?
You probably think I'm lying,
but it's true.
Were you looking at the train?
Why do you think so?
That's the train
your father used to operate, right?
You did your research.
I was staring at his train,
wondering if I should jump in front of it.
Being the ostentatious person he is,
he thinks I'm a shame to the family.
So…
I thought about doing him that favor
in the best manner.
However…
I suddenly realized something
after I was pushed.
Even parasites have the right to live.
Isn't the school over there?
It's been a while,
so I want to take the long route.
It's not broken.
-Your elbow's just swollen.
-Yes.
You can go home after applying a compress.
No medications?
You're still young.
You don't need any pain relievers.
Now I understand why my dad told me
to come to you.
Why?
Because you don't seem like a doctor.
My dad's a bodyguard,
but he hates going to the hospital.
He's scared of injections and medicines.
Really? That's surprising.
I thought your father
wasn't afraid of anything.
He's a different person when he's working.
I see.
Is he weak at home?
He's weak, lame, and pathetic.
That's why Mom left him.
I see.
-So he was abandoned.
-Right! With no hesitation!
I feel sorry for him.
He deserved it.
After he gets tired from work,
he just comes home looking all cold.
Well, his job requires a lot of
physical and emotional energy.
But it's wrong to bring it
into your personal life.
But he isn't the kind to cut corners,
personality-wise.
You know my dad very well.
Hey. Take care of yourself.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
What?
You're Ikuta, aren't you?
It's been a while!
I'm Taniguchi! Tani!
Hey!
This is my wife and son.
I left home after I got employed,
but I returned for the class reunion.
You're going too, right?
Hey. Shall we go together?
Who are these people?
They're my bodyguards.
What?
Bodyguards?
I deal with stocks, and I earn
an annual income of 2 billion yen…
so things can get dangerous around me.
Things are too different between us!
He found a job,
and even has a wife and kid.
As if I could talk with someone like that!
Getting married doesn't put you
on higher ground.
I'm not married either.
So what?
I'm just stating facts.
You know…
You're really bad at consolation.
How are you still in the service industry?
I'm sorry.
-We're moving to the underpass.
-Understood.
He even lied just to get away from me.
It must have really scarred him.
He said he's earning
an annual income of 2 billion yen.
That was a lie, right?
I can't reveal anything.
That Ikuta…
He didn't go to university
or even work a part-time job.
You seem to know him very well.
I thought of myself as his best friend.
Could you please relay my message?
Tell him to attend the class reunion.
I understand.
Please excuse me.
I'm heading over now.
I'm over here!
Papa!
Mr. Taniguchi wanted to attend
the class reunion together with you.
Now he's suddenly acting like my friend.
I don't need his pity!
No, but he thinks of you
as a close friend…
Suspicious person spotted at 12 o'clock.
I see him.
What? Is someone following us?
I'll check it, just in case.
I lost the suspicious person.
-Tracking aborted.
-Understood.
It's fine now.
I'm going home.
What about the time capsule?
I don't care anymore.
I knew it. I'm being targeted.
No… What?
-Mr. Ikuta…
-Daisuke!
And he returned after 30 minutes.
Oh, you can leave now.
Our mission is not complete yet.
To think that an unemployed person
would request bodyguard services…
How laughable.
Pardon me, but…
are you really that short on cash
that you would be the bodyguard
of a piece of trash like him?
Please do not say that about my client.
I've been betrayed so much by him.
You never know.
You know,
because of my family's circumstances,
I wasn't able to attend university.
I was proud of my work
as a train operator.
However, I wished for my son
to attend university,
wear a white shirt,
a neat necktie,
and become someone capable
of changing the world.
That's why,
I taught him as much as I could.
I even brought him everywhere.
I understand
your expectations for your son.
Don't say it like you mean it.
No.
I also have a son myself, so…
if Mr. Daisuke requested
bodyguard services,
doesn't that mean
he does want to leave the house,
even for a little?
You're right.
It was just 30 minutes for you.
But to your son,
I believe it might have been
a tiring adventure for him.
That's the end of your mission.
You can go home now.
-But we haven't done anything yet.
-What?
We accepted your request
because you sent an SOS message to us.
-Just leave him alone!
-Mr. Ikuta…
No matter what he does, it's useless!
Please don't refer to him so rudely!
You know…
He's a liar.
He's irresponsible.
And there's nothing you can do about him!
Listen up.
Stop trying to hide
what you put in the time capsule.
Just go to the class reunion
with your head held high!
You're just worried about appearances.
Are you really that scared
of everyone laughing at you?
Please go back, you two.
As his parent, I'll pay for him.
You'll be fine with that, right?
-Just--
-Shut up.
You have no right to talk to me like that!
Mr. Ikuta…
Mr. Ikuta!
I'm sorry.
You had to play the part of the bad guy.
Excuse me.
Will he…
really be able to take a step out?
FUJINOMIYA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
GRADE 6 CLASS 3 REUNION, 1995 GRADUATES
If you're worried about your attire,
I can find you one.
That's fine.
I don't think I should be here.
I haven't been to a class reunion
or an alumni meeting myself either.
What?
When I was young,
I thought get-together sessions
like this were dumb.
And when I was in my thirties,
I made a huge blunder in my work
and didn't want to see anyone.
Now that I'm in my forties,
I started to feel nostalgic,
but it feels too strange
to attend one now.
I attended one a few years ago.
So you attend these things?
But I went home immediately.
Some people didn't remember me,
and that hurt my pride.
I've been waiting for you.
Ikuta.
Shall we go to the science lab together
before everyone else arrives?
Sure.
Come on, let's go!
What?
Are the bodyguards coming along?
Well…
Just here is fine.
-Let us escort you to the lab.
-Here is fine.
Your work is done.
I'll transfer the money to you later.
-Let's go. Come on.
-Okay.
Aren't you curious?
Yes, I am.
Oh, it's the anatomical model.
I used to be scared of this.
That was during your lower years, right?
Back in sixth grade,
you destroyed the lab specimens
and were reprimanded harshly.
Did that happen?
I don't remember that at all.
You stole some hydrochloric acid
and caused a huge ruckus back then too.
It felt like that happened…
I remember it all too well.
It's over here.
I stole it because you made me.
You lost in the punishment game,
so I want you to steal
the hydrochloric acid in the science lab.
HYDROCHLORIC ACID
You really don't remember that?
The police even came,
and it caused such a huge fuss.
You know you shouldn't do that, right?
But you…
Until the end,
you never confessed
that you ordered me to do it.
So you finally remembered.
Because of that incident,
I flunked my middle school exams.
I had to go to cram school
and study harder.
After that, my mother
became mentally ill.
And during my high school years,
she committed suicide.
And you just forgot about that?
Do you think
that I will ever forgive you?
Apologize.
Apologize! Come on!
Apologize!
What are you doing?
Just some entertainment
before the class reunion.
Just go back. Your work is done, right?
We can't go back.
It appears that Mr. Ikuta
was being targeted by someone.
Do you have any idea who it could be?
Are you suspecting me?
You seem very knowledgeable about
Mr. Ikuta's circumstances post-graduation.
In fact, you seem to know too much
for a mere classmate.
I'm his best friend.
So I tracked him down.
And that's why you followed him today?
Today?
I didn't today.
But I did give him a few surprises.
Of course, I would!
Because of you,
my life is in shambles!
But don't you have your family?
I…
I divorced my wife a year ago.
I was just supposed
to meet my child today.
Ever since you deceived me that day,
I had been unable to trust anyone!
Personal relationships…
It never went well for me ever since!
And yet
you pretend as if nothing happened,
and live as a shut-in!
I don't think I can forgive you
unless I punch you!
If that's the case,
you can punch me instead.
This has nothing to do with you!
Please go ahead.
Have you ever punched someone?
You have to clench your fist tight.
And aim here.
But let me say just one thing.
It wasn't Mr. Ikuta's fault
that you couldn't trust anyone.
The problem lies with you!
Shut up!
Stop it.
Stop!
Please stop!
Please…
I'm sorry.
I didn't know anything.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry that I forgot!
If you want to,
then punch me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
It's been a while, Taniguchi!
How long has it been?
You seem flashy as usual.
And you don't hold back, as usual!
-You've changed a lot!
-You haven't changed one bit.
-Hey, Yuki.
-Look over there.
Isn't that him?
-That's…
-It's amazing.
Look at how he's dressed.
No way! How disappointing!
Hey, Ikuta!
What's with that getup?
Are you trying to make us laugh?
Oh, right!
He always tried to joke around!
You…
You always wanted to stand out,
didn't you?
-Yes, he's right!
-All he did was just mess around.
-He was always like that!
-Yes.
He's just weird that way.
Hey! The time capsule is here!
Ikuta!
This is yours!
TO ME, 25 YEARS LATER
Please excuse us.
Please look at this.
TO ME, 25 YEARS LATER
I'M A REGULAR MEMBER OF THE SOCCER CLUB.
WILL I BE ABLE TO CONTINUE PLAYING
IN THE FUTURE?
I LOVE LOOKING AT DAD'S TRAIN.
HE'S SO COOL WHEN HE OPERATES HIS TRAIN.
I WANT TO BE A COOL TRAIN OPERATOR
LIKE MY DAD.
I'LL DRIVE MOM AND DAD AROUND
IN THE TRAIN.
I said I wanted to jump
in front of my father's train,
but that was a lie.
I…
As long as I had time,
I always went to look at his train.
Dad!
To tell you the truth,
I looked up to my father's profession.
However, my father told me
to study hard and enter a good company.
He said that instead of moving trains,
I should become someone capable
of moving people.
He was so stern,
I couldn't say what I felt.
That's why…
I always lied and said
I wanted to be a J.Leaguer.
That was the only time I went against him.
But in the time capsule,
you wrote down
what you really felt, didn't you?
I didn't want to lie
to my future self after all.
The one who was hung up about appearances
was me.
I'm sorry.
What's with this all of a sudden?
Daisuke,
you should
leave this house.
Daisuke!
How much was it?
It was eight hours,
so it'll be 80,000 yen.
Oh, I see…
It's quite expensive.
You can pay in installments too.
Oh, it's fine. I…
I brought my entire savings here.
Ever since I was young,
I saved up all my New Year allowances.
Here, 80,000 yen.
I've received the payment.
Excuse me…
Thank you.
You protected my memories.
I'm sorry.
-For what?
-About Mr. Ikuta.
He didn't lie.
You won.
It wasn't about winning or losing.
I'm concerned about one thing.
What?
If Mr. Taniguchi wasn't following him,
then who was it?
It's him, right?
Why did you keep quiet about it?
I sowed the seeds, so I'll reap the--
-Stop that!
-What?
I didn't follow you here
just to keep myself fed.
Then what? You ran here
because you were dumped by a woman?
-You really know everything about me.
-You're easy to read.
What?
Just shut up and finish your work!
Thanks to Ms. Suganuma's contribution,
we've received a bodyguard request
from the governor Sakiko Takabe.
I look forward to your performance.
Do your best too, everyone.
-Yes, sir!
Dr. Kasamatsu treated my injuries.
You aren't asleep yet?
I'm glad it wasn't anything serious.
That doctor's quite rough.
I guess all surgeons are like that.
But she was worried about you.
What?
I think she's really conscious of you.
What in the world are you saying?
Go to sleep.
DR. KASAMATSU
Hello?
How is Shun?
I think the swelling should subside soon.
Oh, thank you for taking care of my son.
It's fine.
That was payback for last time.
I…
Yes?
Are you currently outside now?
In a ramen shop, perhaps?
What? How do you know?
Well, it's just an occupational habit.
I just heard a waiter saying "Welcome."
At this hour, there is no suitable place
for a woman to be alone.
I…
Then next time…
shall we eat together?
My treat.
Don't misunderstand.
I wasn't trying to invite you.
Goodbye.
What?
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your extra-special ramen!
Stalking is a despicable act.
I did my best
to become a first-class secretary.
I don't want to give up
because of something like this.
You still haven't apologized!
What have you been saying?
It feels much more intense than hate.
I'm always prepared.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu