Okay.
Help me!
Oh, hello?
Good morning. It's me.
I haven't heard from you in a while.
How's Shun?
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
HINODE PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
He's still asleep.
You sure are treating me like a stranger.
Well, we are strangers now.
So who's this person
that needs guarding? A friend?
Well, it's me actually.
If you're joking, I'm not laughing.
I thought you'd say that.
I've been getting
a lot of silent crank calls lately.
-Silent calls?
-Yes.
So Hitomi...
I mean, on your mobile phone?
Maybe someone hates you.
You're so mean.
You're heartless, as usual.
Hello? This is the Samejima house.
Hello?
Aya.
Did my enemy say anything?
No, nothing.
If he calls again, shame him.
Say, "Give your name, coward!"
-Okay?
-Dad.
Aya's just a child.
The SP people are here to see you.
Come in.
Prime Minister Samejima,
it has been an honor working for you.
Your protection under the SP
will end tomorrow at 6:00 p.m.
I asked for it to be extended!
This is the government's decision.
If anything happens in the future,
please call the police.
Goodbye.
So I have to call the cops from now on?
Grandpa.
You're not an important person anymore?
The client is Kyoichi Samejima,
76 years old,
the former Prime Minister.
During the coalition government,
his harsh comments earned him the nickname
"Man-Eating Shark."
Give us the truth!
Don't former prime ministers get SP?
If the government decides
that he's no longer important,
they end protection.
-They said they're done with him?
-Yes.
That poor guy.
It's only natural.
Protecting a former prime minister
is a huge waste of our taxes.
But why did he decide to hire bodyguards
out of his own pocket?
He's been getting
silent crank calls at home.
Silent calls? Is that all?
I get them all the time.
Are you bragging that you're popular?
What? What gives you that idea?
Now, now.
It's hard for a former prime minister
to give up his SP.
Let's work seriously on this.
Okay, who will be the BG this time?
Shouldn't it be "Zaki" this time?
-Hey!
-You're right.
An experienced bodyguard is best
for a former prime minister.
Can I ask you to do it, Shimazaki?
I'll work on-site as your partner.
Well, I guess if you insist.
Quit acting so humble.
You know you're totally confident.
We all know you were the bodyguard
of the famous Junya.
If you're going to do it,
knock us out with your skill.
-Okay, fine. I'll do it!
-All right.
In fact, I'll guard him so well,
the SP will be surprised.
Okay. It looks like
we're getting paid quite a lot for this.
Once this mission is over,
let's all have a drink together.
We also haven't had
a welcome-back party for Takanashi.
-Good idea.
-Yes.
Sir, you'll pay for us, right?
-I'm not so sure about that.
-I'll go if I don't have a date.
Count me out. It's a waste of time.
Quit acting all embarrassed.
It's a waste of time.
It's your own welcome party!
I'm sad to say that
our time to part ways has come.
We're proud to have successfully
protected you for 25 years, sir.
As the representative
for the 110 SP officers who protected you,
I bid you farewell.
Take care, sir.
Dad, you should thank them.
Hello!
Thanks for coming. I was expecting you.
Good evening.
What's going on here?
Can't you tell?
I've hired bodyguards to replace you SP.
Excuse me, but do you believe
private guards can replace the SP?
It's a little late for that!
Even though I've said that I'm in danger,
the police still refused
to extend my protection.
So I hired private bodyguards
to protect my life and my honor.
Mr. Ochiai,
leave this to us.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll protect your life and honor,
Prime Minister Samejima.
-Good morning.
We'll be accompanying you today.
I'm counting on you.
I'll be attending
Secretary-General Igarashi's
70th birthday celebration.
I'm a little worried about
my daughter and granddaughter.
I'll take care of your daughter
and granddaughter.
Okay.
Hold on.
These weren't here when we came.
They're just stones. Four of them.
My enemy is warning me.
Warning?
He senses that I no longer have
the SP's protection.
Four stones.
Four means death. He wants me to die.
-What about the rocks, Grandpa?
-Nothing for you to worry about.
-Be careful on your way to school.
-Okay.
Don't cry if you're bullied.
It's your chance to find out what
your enemy's weakness is.
-I'm not being bullied.
-Good.
-See you.
-Bye.
-I'll walk her to school.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Do you know who might be after your life?
Isn't it obvious?
The people who were hurt by my comments.
Back then, I was attacked by
the people who lost money
when my comments stopped construction.
From now on and forevermore...
Darn you, Samejima!
The guy who did it
got out of prison long ago.
Samejima!
But that was when
you were serving as Prime Minister.
It's the fate of politicians to be hated,
no matter how many years have passed.
Leave me be. I'm still pretty strong.
I'm sorry.
Your grandpa really loves you,
doesn't he, Aya?
Well, I'm his poor granddaughter.
Poor granddaughter?
You heard, right?
My mom and dad got divorced last year.
You answered the crank call
yesterday, right, Aya?
Yes. But they hung up fast.
You know,
I wish you wouldn't call me "Aya."
What?
That's how superiors address
the people below them.
You're just a bodyguard
that Grandpa hired.
Certainly, Mistress Aya.
That sounds so artificial.
A "Miss" would suffice.
Should private security be guarding him?
That old geezer Samejima always says
someone's after him,
but he has never been attacked.
It was over 20 years ago
that he was almost stabbed.
But if we miss the final attack,
the last 20 years will be for nothing.
If he's attacked...
we should welcome it.
Welcome it?
If he gets attacked the moment
the bodyguards take over,
it'll prove to people that
nobody is better than the SP.
If you want to get promoted,
you need to think like that.
I do want to be promoted...
but I won't be underhanded
with a private company.
Who the heck are those guys?
Those Hinode-whatever people.
They must be pretty formidable
if they've got you so upset.
This way.
Hello.
You all look well.
I had almost forgotten
what you looked like.
Thank you for coming,
Prime Minister Samejima.
I'd like to retire soon myself.
Prime Minister, your seat is here.
-Right.
-Thanks.
It seems the level of beauty among
female politicians has improved.
When I was in the Diet,
there was no such thing
as a beautiful Diet Member.
AIKO TACHIHARA
HEALTH, LABOR, AND WELFARE MINISTER
Sir, you know how tame
the world has become, right?
You can be charged with sexual harassment
if you make jokes like that.
Hey, now.
Someone, help me!
Sir! You can't do this!
Get out of my way!
-Someone, help me!
-Let me through!
What's the commotion all about?
Please!
You have lots of enemies,
Secretary-General.
I'm the target.
What?
Actually,
my life has been in danger
for a while now.
Is that so?
I told the SP,
but they hardly looked into it.
They said old people don't need security,
and then abandoned me.
That's why I hired expert bodyguards
that are better than the SP.
Isn't that right?
Minister!
Don't move! We won't let anyone through.
Detaching.
Stand back. This can be dangerous.
The target is my client.
-Someone, help me!
-Let me through!
Hey!
Let go of me!
It's you!
Minister!
Minister Igarashi!
Oh, my. It appears the target
is the Secretary-General.
Minister Igarashi!
What?
Minister!
-You...
-Minister!
Why are you avoiding me?
Get out of here now!
You told me you'd take care of me!
I took the blame for everything!
You broke your promise to me!
-Cut it out!
-Hey!
I've had enough of you!
Minister!
-Hey! Settle down!
-Come with us!
Minister!
-Minister!
-Sorry for the trouble.
The front guard
let your former secretary through.
We'll be more careful.
The intruder has been taken away.
Returning.
Roger.
1. SECURITY TARGET
KYOICHI SAMEJIMA, AGE 76, FORMER PM
You know, it seems like
things are going well.
We only just started this one.
That's not what I mean.
I'm talking about
the Personal Security team.
"We're finally working as a team."
"I think we can get along."
Were you going to say that?
Yes, I was.
I mean, you've come back,
and we found out
about Shimazaki's brilliant past.
It's like the rain has lifted.
It's "the fog has lifted."
But you do understand what I mean.
It's not going to be that easy.
But...
the boss has a secret too.
You noticed?
I may not look like it,
but I watch people closely.
Of course, I watch you too.
How come you have such great muscles?
I'm a bodyguard. It's only natural.
You need to drink some protein yourself.
The Ginza office is taking over.
Relieve some of the team.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
There's no need to hurt a man that much
when he's unarmed.
Personal protection means
completely eliminating any threat.
Is your definition different?
I'm not sympathizing with him.
You must be careful with someone
that angry, or they could retaliate.
Let's go.
Don't take that from this jerk.
Did he just call me a "jerk"?
Why...
I've checked the perimeter.
Everything is safe.
Thank you. I'll get you some tea.
Thank you, but we can't have any.
We'll need to use the restroom if we do.
I see.
I'm sorry for all the rude things
that my dad says.
It's all right.
After Mom died,
he became even more stubborn.
He gets out of hand.
I'm sorry.
It's all right. A bodyguard will also
listen to your complaints.
-Have a seat.
-Thank you.
Dad will get angry if I speak too freely.
Even if that wasn't so,
since my marriage failed,
he doesn't appreciate me.
I heard you got divorced last year
and came back to live here.
That's right. My husband...
He had his own business,
but he was swindled
and his company went bankrupt.
Dad paid off his debts
in exchange for divorcing me.
I guess I'm spoiled.
No. Money is important.
If I didn't have the financial need,
I certainly wouldn't be a lady bodyguard.
You're very interesting.
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
By the way, didn't Aya only have
a half-day of school today?
Yes.
She's a little late.
I'll go pick her up.
Please don't.
I don't want her to be like me
and not be able to decide things
for herself.
She'll come home on her own.
Don't tell anyone.
-I like that stuff!
-It was the first time I went.
Those SPs from earlier
including Mr. Ochiai
are people I know
from my time with the police.
You were in the Security Bureau?
Right.
I only told you
I was a former police officer.
Sorry. You don't have to tell me this.
I'm not trying to hide it.
You told us about your past after all.
I made such a poor SP.
I couldn't bring myself to tell you.
You're exactly the kind of person
who's usually very talented.
No.
I quit
because I made a terrible mistake.
A mistake?
It was over ten years ago.
I was guarding the foreign minister.
When he was attacked by a radical,
I fired my weapon.
Your pistol?
I meant to scare him,
and nobody was injured.
But the attacker didn't have a gun.
I was criticized
for unnecessarily firing my weapon.
It became hard to stay at my job.
I wasn't cut out
for being a police officer.
Are you sure?
What?
When I quit my job as a bodyguard...
I kept telling myself
that I wasn't cut out for it.
But now I'm back at it again.
I really believe that
my work is much better now.
Coordinating a group of people
with so much individuality
is far more rewarding.
Excuse me.
It's from Suganuma.
Hello, Shimazaki here.
What? Aya?
-Kiwako!
-Dad!
She still hasn't come home
an hour after school was let out.
-Did you search the area?
-I've looked everywhere.
What was the point of having you around?
I'm sorry.
I told her that she didn't have to
go pick her up.
How can a mother
put her own child in danger?
This is a kidnapping!
I'll call the police.
Don't!
I can't trust the police.
If we call the police,
the victim usually isn't returned!
Excuse me. Have you seen this girl?
-No, I haven't.
-Thank you.
What are you doing? Relax, would you?
But I have to find her, no matter what.
That's what I love about you.
What?
That cleared your head, right?
What a jerk!
-Check over there.
-Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
-Can I ask you something?
-Okay.
Do you know Aya Samejima?
Yes. She was just at Mosaic Park.
-Is Mosaic Park that way?
-Yes.
Thanks.
-This must be it.
-Right.
There she is.
Who's that?
Miss Aya!
-After him!
-Got it!
Are you okay?
Who said you could touch me?
Sorry.
What did you talk about
with the man in the park?
Nothing.
He just asked for directions.
Where did he want to go?
The station.
But you've never seen him before, right?
Even if I knew him,
I'd say the same thing.
Miss Aya.
Why did you go to that park?
I was just wondering why
you were sitting all alone there.
Who cares? I can do what I want, right?
Aya! I'm sorry.
Aya!
It looks like my fears
turned out to be right.
We avoided the kidnapping,
but my enemy is trying
to put my family in danger.
Strengthen security tomorrow!
Yes, sir.
I'm home.
I'm home!
I've been meaning to tell you
that you could at least say
"welcome home" when I arrive.
Welcome home.
If you hate me that much,
then why don't you go back to your mom?
She called me.
She said you're welcome home anytime,
so come back home.
And that guy,
Odagiri.
Her new, young, and rich husband.
He also wants you to come back.
I don't mind going back, but I'm only here
because you'll be lonely.
What?
Who said I'll be lonely?
Who cares?
I guess you dealt with a lot
when we got divorced, didn't you?
Do you want some fried rice?
Sure, I'll eat your food.
You'll eat my food?
Then I'll cook for you.
Thank you so much.
It brought tears to my eyes.
You just smiled, didn't you?
You smiled. I know you did.
No, I didn't. Quit bugging me!
All right! That's what I call
a rebellious child!
Do I still have any? Oh, there's plenty.
Because I will get lonely.
Okay. Here we go.
So are you striking first this time?
Sorry to call you when you're so tired.
I have early morning duty tomorrow.
Keep it short.
Okay, I'll be direct.
Can you tell me anything about
the former Prime Minister Samejima?
Do you think I can?
I understand your position.
However, I was just hoping
you could give me a hint
that would make it easier
for us to protect him.
You mean, you want me
to return an old favor?
If I was in a position
to make that kind of deal,
I never would've quit the police force.
I'll be clear with you.
I never asked you to,
but you took the blame for me and quit.
That wasn't part of your duties.
I have no intention
of cooperating with you.
He didn't even drink anything, did he?
-Was it good?
-It was.
Hello? Good evening. It's Shimazaki.
I have an idea
about tomorrow's bodyguard job.
SAMEJIMA
Hold on a moment.
One stone.
No listening devices around the perimeter.
Same inside.
-I checked the family albums.
-I researched the past incident.
Thank you.
There was one stone.
Let's proceed according to the plan.
Time is 7:22 a.m.
-Synchronized.
-Synchronized. Everyone, into position.
Excuse me.
Everything is normal
inside and outside the house.
-You were very thorough, right?
-Yes, sir.
There will be three of us
guarding your home.
Also, since Aya will be going on
a field trip to a television station,
we'll accompany her.
No. No school for you today, Aya.
What? I want to go to the TV station.
Aya,
you were almost kidnapped yesterday.
I was looking forward to this.
We'll stick very close to her.
No!
Sir.
You hired bodyguards
so you could live your life normally.
I'll hold you responsible
if anything happens!
Yes, sir.
-It's big.
-Yes, it sure is big.
I wonder if we'll meet anyone.
That would be cool.
This way. Come this way.
This way. Make a line.
Okay, now this way. Let's go.
-Yes, ma'am.
It's Matsuo!
Hello! Welcome!
-You're so pretty!
-Thank you.
Look at this.
BID-RIGGING FELLED IN A SINGLE STROKE
You were attacked in 1998, right?
Fortunately, SP shielded me,
so I wasn't injured.
The perpetrator got out of prison
a long time ago.
Only in Japan are you despised
for doing what's right.
-This TV station is cool!
-It sure is.
Let's stop for a moment, kids.
-Okay!
Look to your right.
-Wow, cool!
-Cool!
This is a recording studio
where we make TV programs.
-Look at that!
-Next, we'll go to the sub.
-What's a "sub"?
-Good question.
I wonder what's there?
I'm excited to find out.
Keep quiet here. Everyone is working.
That's Minister Tachihara.
This is the sub.
Amazing!
I want to be on TV.
I can't let you.
-Really?
-I want to be on TV too.
Talk with him. If you mention
my grandpa's name, he'll let me on.
But everyone is working.
I thought a bodyguard would do
anything I asked.
I can't let you bring your grandpa shame.
You're useless.
What about you?
Today's economy troubles me.
What do you think?
Well, I'm not optimistic about
the current state of the economy.
I would agree.
WRAP IT UP
Cut! You're hopeless!
-What's wrong?
-Do it in this order.
-Why?
-We're doing this part now.
If you don't say this part...
No, you need to do that.
I'll return to the studio later.
Thank you.
So you even came here
to guard his granddaughter?
It's my job to stick by her side,
no matter where she goes.
It's okay to talk now.
Mr. Ochiai and the others are
in the waiting room while I'm on TV.
Sorry, but I'm working now.
Shimazaki.
Excuse me.
Miss Aya!
The teacher will be angry
if you go off alone.
Stay away from me!
Okay, let's go.
Let go of me!
Let go!
Help!
Help me!
Hey, you!
-No, you've got it wrong.
-Who the heck are you?
I'm with Personal Security
at Hinode Security.
Aya!
I'll report you as a peeping tom.
Peeping tom?
Use another one.
I'm Aiko Tachihara.
Don't you remember me?
We met at your grandpa's retirement party.
You were a very cheeky granddaughter.
I'm not criticizing you.
If you're cheeky,
it means you're intelligent.
But don't you think locking yourself
in the restroom
is awfully childish?
It's good to see you again.
Thank you.
I guess there are places
that you can't go.
This is 02.
I've caught the perpetrator.
Roger.
We caught the perpetrator.
It was you? You troublemaker!
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry!
I told you not to come around here again
once I took care of all your debts, right?
I'm terribly sorry, I just...
I wasn't able to give Aya
her birthday present.
Her birthday was long ago.
You're slow at everything you do.
And you're so easily deceived.
Cut it out, Dad!
You still like this moron?
Don't you remember
all the pain you went through?
Excuse me. This is for Aya.
Aya.
How did you contact him?
You don't have a mobile phone.
Was it that call?
Hello? This is the Samejima house.
Aya. It's Dad.
I'll be waiting for you
on Wednesday at Mosaic Park.
Okay.
Hello?
-Aya!
-You used the stones
as a signal to her, right?
Four stones meant you'd call at 4:00 p.m.
One stone meant you'd meet at 1:00 p.m.
Such impertinence!
Sir, I'm a useless person.
But I want to do whatever I can for Aya.
A debt-ridden father has no right
to see his child!
-Sir!
-What do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry.
You gave us an order.
You ordered us to protect
your life and your honor.
Prime Minister,
you made a request for an inquiry.
We investigated the criminal
who attacked you in 1998.
He died ten years ago.
The organization that suffered losses then
no longer exists either.
You aren't being targeted.
That's all I have to report.
Goodbye.
I'm not being targeted.
Not by anyone.
It's good to know you're safe.
Isn't that
what's most important?
The most important...
I'm sorry.
Grandpa.
Do you want to hold him?
Mr. Ochiai!
What's with you? You won't even stop
when you hear me calling.
Mr. Samejima seemed saddened.
Being targeted by someone
was like proof that he still existed.
Once someone has attracted attention,
they're not easily forgotten.
That's why I told him the truth.
That's very kind of you.
Don't flatter me with cheap comments.
That was "cheap"?
At any rate,
I never want to see you
where I'm working again.
-Nice work.
I'm glad the plan worked.
Come to think of it,
when did you realize it was her dad?
She wasn't the least bit scared
when we found her at the park.
And there was no evidence
that he was targeted.
Also, kids
unexpectedly want
to protect their parents.
I'm only here because you'll get lonely.
-Isn't that right?
-Yes, it is.
I'm just checking,
but you're paying, aren't you, sir?
You're worried about that?
I'll pay, but please refrain
from ordering expensive stuff.
We sure aren't paid much
to put our lives on the line.
You're so right.
I wish that were different.
-Lobster with caviar sauce.
-You're going for that?
Then I'll have the Mexican chips
with avocado salad.
Wimpy food for a wimpy guy.
I'll have pickled mackerel carpaccio.
-Thank you.
-They have that?
-Yes, they do.
-That's so refined.
Filet mignon.
-What?
-Filet mignon?
Where do you see that?
Oh, I get it.
Wait, I thought you said
this was a waste of time.
Right. He did.
This is part of the job.
Can't you be honest?
You know you wanted to be with all of us.
-Roger.
-Anyway, let's take a picture.
What?
Why? Act your age, will you?
Come on. Why not?
Count me out.
There you go, ruining things again.
Leave him be.
Could you please
take the picture, Takanashi?
Right, take the picture.
Come on. Hurry up.
Take the picture.
Excuse me. Take a picture of us, please.
Sure.
It's ugly if something is missing.
Synchronized.
I don't understand what you mean.
It's all right. Okay, let's go.
Oh, all right.
Ready, go!
-Synchronized!
Sorry. Were you waiting long?
Don't talk like this is a date.
-Is this about Shun?
-No.
Then what is it?
Well,
I just happened to do a job
related to silent crank calls.
So it made me think about you.
You're kind even to strangers.
Can you give me the details?
-You won't laugh?
-No.
Someone
is targeting me.
I want you to protect me.
I'll handle it.
It's a good chance to show her
that he's a real pro.
Did we talk like this six years ago?
Things are different when you're divorced.
Don't turn around.
It's all that woman's fault!
I'll never forgive her! I'll destroy her!
A SHOCKING FAREWELL