Don't you dare shoot yet!
There's one thing I want to say
before I die.
27 HOURS EARLIER
Sorry. Were you waiting long?
Don't talk like this is a date.
I just happened to do a job
related to silent crank calls.
So it made me think about you.
Can you give me the details?
-You won't laugh?
-No.
Someone
is targeting me.
When did it start?
About three months ago, I think.
I see.
-Three months ago, isn't that...
-Yes.
It was right when Shun started
staying at your place.
Because of that, I didn't stop Shun.
Protect me.
Your ex-wife?
Yes.
But I'm still not sure
if someone really is after her.
It's troubling though.
I'd like to take the job
and protect her, but...
I hate to be rude,
but what about the payment?
I doubt that'll be a problem.
But can I ask someone else
to be the BG for this?
Why?
She asked you personally.
I understand that,
but it's kind of hard to do this
for my ex-wife, you know.
-Why are you ashamed?
-I'm not ashamed.
I can't be wholly professional.
I get it! If you protect her well,
your love will return...
No, it won't! She's remarried.
An affair with your ex-wife
would be quite novel.
-I'm sorry.
-Now, now.
I understand how Shimazaki feels.
Even surgeons don't want to operate
on their own family.
The client is a woman,
so Suganuma is the best choice.
-Okay.
-First, I'll go and talk to her.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-I'll take care of it.
-Thank goodness.
-What's your ex-wife's address?
I'll get it.
-Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too.
Just as I thought.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
I didn't think he would want
to do this himself.
Will that be a problem?
No.
I only asked him because I don't know
any other security companies.
Let's get started.
May I ask why you feel threatened?
All right.
Sometimes I get mysterious calls,
and it's like someone
is following me when I go to work.
Where do you work?
I do flower arranging
for many different shops.
How exquisite.
How nice it must be
to live in a lovely home
and arrange beautiful flowers
for a living.
Arranging flowers takes
a lot of energy, you know.
The flowers in my garden were destroyed.
As soon as I replant my flowers,
they get destroyed like this.
At first, I thought it was done by cats,
but this is the third time in a row.
It frightens me.
I see your husband runs a biotech company.
-That's right.
-What does he think?
I haven't told my husband.
He's working overseas right now.
It's hard to tell him that
something strange is happening
while he's away.
I don't have definite proof
that someone's after me either.
I thought it was best
to talk with Shimazaki,
then maybe I could get
some kind of clues to work with.
This way, please.
It's awfully unusual for you
to invite me out.
I didn't invite you out.
I just want to talk.
That's still inviting me out.
Oh, forget it.
What do you want to talk about?
-Two beers.
-Got it.
-You already know.
-I have no idea!
No. You already know.
Is this about my wife? I mean, my ex.
You should be her BG.
Can I order?
After we talk.
You know, it's like you're always
angry about something.
But you're angrier than usual now.
-Your wife is frightened.
-My ex-wife.
How can you be a pro
if you can't protect a frightened lady?
What?
It's just...
I never thought a guy like you
would say "lady."
-Is it strange?
-No, not at all.
Whether a lady has status or is athletic,
ladies are still physically weak
and cannot be compared to a man.
They have to be protected.
Well, I guess you're right.
Here you are.
We're still not done.
You can say anything you like
about male superiority,
but that's reality.
You're a real romantic, aren't you?
-Cut that out.
-Sorry.
Anyway, thanks.
I'll think it over.
I'm glad to hear it.
Is it all right to order now?
Go ahead.
By the way, the best food here
is the cheap stuff.
What do you recommend?
I recommend...
this stuff, like chicken skin.
Chicken skin?
-Chicken skin.
Nomoto is done for.
-He got carried away.
-You're so right.
We need someone from your side
to be his opponent.
Okay.
I want the newscaster Kawakami to run.
He may not look like it,
but he's easily seduced by women.
It's time to do your thing.
If I succeed,
I expect a big reward, you know.
Excuse me.
Minister, are you feeling all right?
YOSHIAKI OCHIAI
SECURITY BUREAU (SP), MPD
No matter how high I go,
I always feel like
I'm just a party hostess.
You must be wondering, Mr. Ochiai...
why it took me so long to realize that.
No.
"No"?
Please be frank with me.
Tell me, "Don't be weak."
Or even, "Quit if you don't like it."
Tell me anything.
I believe I understand your feelings.
However, I'd like to keep
my personal opinions to myself.
You're quite admirable.
You never break the rules.
You become vulnerable
when you break rules.
My duty is to keep you safe, Minister.
Good evening.
What?
Please come in.
I'm sorry.
Come in.
My silly son will be home
from cram school soon.
It's all right.
-Here, Shimazaki.
-Yes?
Oh, thank you.
I'll get you something to drink.
Thank you.
I spoke to Hitomi Odagiri.
Okay.
It appears it's not just her imagination.
INVESTIGATION REPORT
If we provide private security
for several days and try several methods,
I think we can solve this issue.
This is a difficult request,
but Hitomi is depending on you, isn't she?
Don't you think you should
respect her wishes?
Welcome home.
Nice to meet you. I'm Murata.
I work with your dad.
Hey, at least say hello!
It's all right. Actually...
I bought some steamed meat buns,
so don't you want to try some?
I'm Shun Shimazaki.
Thank you.
Not all of them. What are you doing?
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
He's in his second year of middle school.
Even my son is still rebellious at age 19.
In fact,
my wife once asked me for a divorce.
They say a bodyguard is only
a real pro after he gets divorced.
I'm surprised you stayed together.
The amount of effort it took
would make you weep.
Really?
Actually,
all I did was work as hard as I could.
Let's have these while they're hot.
Thanks.
This place makes delicious ones.
Thank you.
Oh, that's good.
Everyone, with regard to
Hitomi Odagiri's personal security,
I'll handle it.
-Thank you, Shimazaki.
-Yes, sir.
We'll also be starting
the Overlook Coop security today.
That's yours, Takanashi and Suganuma.
-Yes, sir.
-Understood.
SATOSHI ODAGIRI (HUSBAND)
I'll be running backup for you,
so please check in every hour.
Roger.
The time is 9:35 a.m. and 52 seconds.
Wait! What?
-What?
-You're off. Is your battery dead?
Why today of all days?
Is something wrong?
No. Nothing.
Use mine. I'll be here all day.
Thanks for this.
-See you later.
-Bye.
Bye.
-Ta-da!
-What?
No way!
That's a necessity for your work, right?
Yes, but...
Come on. Try it on.
What?
What? You're acting funny.
Why are you silent?
What is it? What's wrong?
-Actually...
-What?
I want to...
protect you forever.
-What did you say?
-You heard me.
You are so darn ordinary!
Okay.
I want to protect you forever.
-What?
Look, you're angry now.
-No, I'm not angry at all.
-Yes, you are.
-I'm not angry at all.
-You're really angry.
Look at you.
You're angry. Oh, you scared me!
Oh, you!
-I'll do the protecting.
-Then protect me.
I'm Shimazaki
from Hinode Security Service.
Thank you, Mr. Bodyguard.
I'm Hitomi Odagiri.
-You'll be going out to work today?
-Right.
I'll escort you everywhere.
Don't you worry.
This feels kind of weird.
Anyway, thank you.
I also have a request
to help me protect you.
What's that?
Cooperation from your family is essential.
Please inform your husband
that we're providing you with security.
My husband spends all his energy
on his work every day.
I don't want to cause him any undue worry.
Then...
if you're in danger,
please allow me to contact your husband.
All right.
I have a request too.
Yes? What is it?
By chance,
if anything should happen to me,
I want you to take good care of Shun.
Understood.
Personal security commencing now.
-We're going to Meguro.
-Roger.
Estimated time of arrival, 2:05 p.m.
Roger.
There.
-Shall I carry this?
-It's okay. This is for my work.
Take these.
All right.
After becoming a freelancer,
I carried this all around
and got more clients.
I met my husband at his company
when I provided them arrangements.
You must be happy you've been blessed
with a wonderful husband.
Is that sarcasm?
I heard from Shun.
He's young, rich, talented, and kind.
I bet he said
he's the exact opposite of you.
That's exactly right.
Time to get started.
-Can you wait here?
-I'll be over there.
All right.
My apologies. I'm working now.
Really? It's not personal business?
I often go to that restaurant.
I wanted to apologize to you
for being rude the other day.
I was going to treat you
to some wine and lunch.
How about dining with me once?
We're a different class of people.
Oh, my! You certainly have
a high opinion of yourself.
I don't like comments
meant to toy with a man.
Don't trouble yourself. Goodbye.
Mr. Shimazaki,
do you enjoy your work?
Is it fun being a bodyguard?
I mean, you exert
all this effort for others,
but not for yourself.
You work in their shadow.
But...
don't you do your job
for the benefit of others too?
I'm sorry. It was rude of me
to compare myself to you.
My apologies. Goodbye.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
Okay.
You're going to a flower shop
in Ebisu for supplies next, right?
You really know your stuff.
It's like a groper is after me.
Don't turn around.
Keep walking.
You were second in the prefecture
in the 1km run back in high school, right?
It was in the 800 meters run.
Why do you remember that?
Turn right at the stairs,
then turn at the next corner.
-I'll carry this.
-What? Why?
Please pick up your pace.
-Go down.
-Okay.
-Left!
Stop here.
Wait here.
What do you want?
Who the heck are you?
What are you to that woman?
"That woman"?
That woman, Hitomi.
She's a thief who stole what was mine!
Calm down.
You're the one
who's been following Hitomi,
making silent crank calls,
and destroying her flowers, right?
Am I wrong?
You see, it's all that woman's fault!
That hurt!
I dated Satoshi for three years.
I could understand
if she was a young woman,
but why did he marry
an older woman with a kid?
I'll never forgive her!
I'll destroy her!
Stop it!
Stay back!
Let me talk to her.
Please calm down.
You're Shoko, aren't you?
He told me your name.
Give him back.
-I met Satoshi after you two broke up...
-Give him back!
I can't do that.
Satoshi isn't an object
that belongs to me.
He doesn't belong to anyone.
Why are you patronizing me?
What's wrong with you?
Would you like to file charges
with the police?
No.
If I were her,
I wouldn't come after me again.
Understood.
At least it didn't turn into
anything serious.
Is your mission complete?
I'll take you home.
Is it possible to add an extra service?
An extra service?
MESSAGE: YOU, MOM, AND I ARE HAVING
DINNER TOGETHER IN MEGURO. DAD
What?
Roger. Report received and acknowledged.
By order of the client,
Shimazaki will be dining with her.
I see.
Well then...
This could be bad
if they hit it off again.
I mean, she's married to a rich guy.
Zaki will be in big trouble.
Cut that out.
-If you insist. Thank you.
-Please.
I haven't seen Shun in a while.
Has he grown?
Actually, just now,
he said their practice is running late,
so he wants us to start without him.
Thank you.
Can I give you an order?
What?
During dinner, talk normally with me.
You're being too stuffy.
Yes, ma'am.
I mean, okay.
Order anything. I'm paying.
No. I'll pay.
No, it's all right. You saved me today.
-That's my job.
-Okay, then we'll go Dutch?
I can't do that either.
I'm his father after all.
You said "after all," didn't you?
Right?
You've really matured.
Did we talk like this six years ago?
No.
I didn't think so.
You should tell your husband everything.
You're right.
But he's six years younger.
I have to act more mature.
Being divorced doesn't help either.
Is that anything to tell your ex-husband?
Well, things are different
when you're divorced.
-Any reservation changes?
-None, sir.
-Good. Proceed.
-Thank you.
-So can I order?
-Oh, sure.
You are here on personal business
just as I thought.
No.
These are beautiful flowers.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to cause you this trouble.
No one knows who might be listening
if we used the usual restaurant.
Are you serious about this?
Yes.
Please allow me to leave the party.
What do you think you can do
if you leave me?
I want to...
become a politician.
That was Minister Tachihara, wasn't it?
Do you know her?
-I know her through work.
-As a bodyguard? For a minister?
Amazing!
No. She's the amazing one.
I just work in her shadow.
Why are you so amazed?
You're amazing.
You do so many amazing things.
CHIEF MURATA
INCOMING CALL
HINODE BUILDING
Really? A date with his ex-wife?
The boss got angry when I said that.
This is an important mission.
It's a good chance to show her
that he's a real pro.
Men have a hard time getting over things.
Especially guys like Shimazaki.
This place is on my way home.
What?
-I had it repaired.
-You didn't have to do that.
I thought this watch
was important for today.
You figured it out?
Actually, my wife gave me my watch
as a present too.
Then...
Synchronized?
Synchronized.
Thank you. You've been a great help.
Boss.
That guy...
Minister!
-Someone, help me!
-Let me through!
Minister Igarashi!
You told me you'd take care of me!
I took the blame for everything!
The Secretary-General
and Minister Tachihara are meeting
on the second floor.
I doubt this is a coincidence.
-Where's the SP?
-On standby upstairs.
Minister Tachihara is in a meeting.
Okay. Sorry, but can we talk for a moment?
See the man at the table
on the first floor wearing glasses?
Thank you for the information.
Let's get out of here.
What?
We just ordered.
I know that.
What? Why the serious look?
It might not be safe here.
It might not be safe?
Excuse me.
Allow me to see Mr. Igarashi.
I can't do that.
I want to apologize for the other day.
I know you're here!
I just want a moment. Let me apologize.
I don't need your apologies.
Go away!
Mr. Igarashi says he won't talk to you.
Please leave.
Then...
can I die here?
What are you talking about?
I wanted to apologize to him.
Then if he apologized to me too,
I thought I could continue living.
Quit talking nonsense.
Go on. Get out.
I wonder...
what I should do to assure my death.
It wasn't easy to get this.
Tell me what's going on.
Shun still isn't here either.
What? What is it?
I'll explain after we leave.
Stay calm.
I won't let anyone touch you two.
Get down!
Get to the corner!
Why? Why do I have to be
the only one to die?
I was tricked.
It's insane.
It's totally insane.
I'll aim for the leg.
No! Don't you dare shoot!
Shooting is a last resort.
I'm on my way.
So is anyone willing to die with me?
No!
Quit making such a ruckus!
Excuse me.
Can I talk?
I won't do anything, so take it easy.
You're SP, aren't you?
No! I'm not.
I'm a private bodyguard.
I'm here on personal business.
I'll do whatever I can to help you.
I want to talk with Mr. Igarashi.
It's all right.
Okay. All right.
If that's what you want,
then you won't mind
if everyone here leaves, right?
They're not involved, right?
There's no need to needlessly
make your crime worse, right?
I'll make sure you talk to Mr. Igarashi.
Bring him here now!
Okay.
All right. I'll bring him.
Just keep pointing that right here.
But don't you dare shoot yet!
There's one thing I want to say
before I die.
Actually, I was going to
have dinner here today
with my ex-wife and son.
That may not have anything to do with you,
but it's the first time I'm having dinner
with my whole family in six years.
It was meant to be special.
Who cares? Hurry up!
Sorry! Okay!
So you see...
my wife, I mean my ex-wife...
I want to apologize to her.
It was all my fault.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I was a terrible husband to her.
I made a mistake at work,
got depressed, and went nuts.
I took it all out on her.
It was only natural that
she got sick of me and got rid of me.
I never once
apologized to her.
What's wrong with people?
Even when we know we're wrong,
we can't apologize.
Hurry up!
You've got to be kidding me!
You still don't get it, do you?
I didn't get sick of you.
I'm not that cold a person.
I only left you to put a scare into you.
You wanted to put a scare into me?
-That's right.
-What?
I said that's right.
I thought you never wanted
to see me again!
You were wrong as always!
You're the one
who said you wanted a divorce!
I went away for your sake and Shun's!
You just wanted an easy life. That's all!
You're not even wearing
the watch I gave you!
-Yes, I am.
-You're right. What?
It happened to be broken,
and I got it back just now.
"Happened to"?
So it returned just in time for me?
What a lucky coincidence.
Yes, just like us,
things go wrong at the wrong time!
-That's so right!
-Quit your arguing!
Who cares about that right now?
Sorry.
Put your gun down.
-Go!
-This way. Stay calm.
Go!
This way, please.
That's hot.
That's odd. He missed his hourly check-in.
Maybe he and his wife are hitting it off.
Oh, come on.
He's working with a client, you know.
-But it's his wife.
-His ex-wife.
That guy is the type who would contact us
even when it's unnecessary.
Okay, I'll call him.
Let me hear what you have to say.
You're pointing a gun at me.
How can I talk to you?
All right.
I'll put my gun down.
Put your gun down too.
You're the one who...
Hey!
I've had enough of you!
I'm sorry for what I did.
If you really feel that way,
bring Mr. Igarashi here.
I'll give him your message.
In the corruption scandal four years ago,
Mr. Igarashi made a promise to me.
That's why I took all the blame!
It was the typical "My secretary did it."
But he didn't keep his promise!
You tricked me, Mr. Igarashi!
Of course, you should apologize to me!
Hurry up and bring him here
and have him apologize to me.
After I see that, I will die.
Can I apologize instead?
No!
I'll apologize for my rudeness
the other day as well.
I apologize.
I'm terribly sorry.
Is that still not enough?
I told you, there's no point
in you apologizing!
Stop this foolishness, Ueno!
Remember what I told you four years ago?
If I took the blame,
it would throw politics
and the people into confusion.
It's the secretary's job to prevent that.
You did a good job!
You're lying!
You pinned the blame on me
and then abandoned me!
The least you can do is apologize!
You should apologize!
Take responsibility
for this outrage by dying!
Sir!
What's wrong?
Isn't that why you came here?
The only thing a shameless man
like you can do
is die a quick death!
Don't talk like that, sir!
I won't allow pointless deaths!
Apologize!
Come with us!
I'm sorry!
Boss?
Boss!
-I've been shot.
-I'll stop the bleeding.
Are you all right?
Thank goodness it wasn't my heart.
The 40-year-old male perpetrator
was arrested at the scene.
But as you can see,
the area is still bustling
with activity by police-related personnel.
Someone has just exited.
MAN ARMED WITH PISTOL TAKEN INTO CUSTODY
Secretary-General Igarashi just exited.
Civil Party Secretary-General
Igarashi just exited.
I think that's Minister Tachihara too.
-That's Minister Tachihara.
-A man fired a gun at someone.
Coming through!
Just now, emergency medical
personnel are coming out.
Emergency medical personnel
have exited pushing a stretcher.
There appears to be a male victim
on the stretcher.
According to employees at the scene,
the male victim was shot in the leg
and has bled quite a lot.
His life could be in danger.
Thanks.
Thank you.
What happened?
There has been mass confusion.
I'll explain everything later.
Are you okay?
I'll be all right.
Thank you very much.
Thank you too.
-Thank you for what?
-What?
Thank you for what?
Mission complete.
Goodbye.
Take care of your mother.
Excuse me.
Even though we were here,
we allowed a civilian to be injured.
I'm terribly sorry.
It's okay.
Nobody died.
Don't worry about it.
Excuse me.
The gunshot wound to his leg
damaged an artery
and may have fractured his femur.
We're taking him
to Dogami General Hospital.
Dogami General Hospital. Okay. Thank you.
Let's go.
He's going to Dogami General Hospital.
-Let's go.
-He was shot...
He was shot means he was shot, right?
-I can't believe this.
-Pull yourself together!
That's what being a bodyguard is!
Let's go.
Boss.
I've informed your family.
Thank you.
Your son answered.
He said they'll be on their way soon.
You said he was being rebellious.
He was actually very proper.
He even thanked me.
Really?
Is that so?
I hope my Shun turns out like that.
TOKYO FIRE AND DISASTER MANAGEMENT AGENCY
Shimazaki.
Yes?
Is your watch
all right?
Yes. It's working perfectly.
-I'm glad to hear it.
-Thank you.
The time is 6:14 p.m...
and five seconds.
Synchronized.
Can I cover him with this?
You told me
to be the bodyguard for my wife.
I'm glad I did it.
I realized
that our time as a married couple
doesn't disappear.
Thank you.
Sorry.
What's going on?
Let me check the electrodes.
-Cardiac arrest!
-Okay!
-I need to sit there.
-Okay.
-Get ready.
You must be kidding.
Boss!
TOKYO FIRE AND DISASTER MANAGEMENT AGENCY
FINAL CHAPTER
Can you make public
what happened that day?
I didn't see the moment of the shooting.
The recording on the day
of the shooting has been deleted.
The only thing I did was
I just stuck with the police.
We don't have status, power, or weapons,
but the one thing we had
was stolen from us!