You chased him away?
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
Yes. I gave him a stern warning.
I'm used to people taking revenge.
Stop this already!
If you provoke him,
he's only going to take it further.
They're getting closer to us.
It's better to increase protection
around people close to you, to be safe.
This person never listens to anyone.
-What?
-Yes?
Make yourself clear
if you have something to say.
I do listen to my employee's opinions.
I have nothing in particular.
I'm glad that Shun is safe.
Oh, don't worry about that.
I wasn't with Shun.
What?
Well…
in other words…
I was eating with Dr. Kasamatsu.
"In other words"?
Just say you were with her.
Don't be embarrassed, Mr. Divorcee.
-I don't want to hear that from you.
-Dr. Kasamatsu, right?
I see…
Hey, about that Napolitan…
-What did you order again?
-I didn't!
Sorry to keep you from waiting.
I'm from Junction Café!
You guys haven't had lunch yet, right?
This is spicy cheese curry.
We didn't order any curry.
This is a takeout menu item.
You know, I stopped searching for
an office position
and started working in cafés
immediately after graduation.
In this era,
getting an office job
doesn't guarantee security anyway.
When I look at you guys,
-I think freelancers sure have it easy.
-We have it easy?
It's quite hard, you know. I have to
think about my employees and such.
If you don't get along with your partner,
it feels like nothing but hell.
Don't worry.
I'm good at personal relationships.
Give me your feedback on it later!
-Go ahead.
-Have it.
-No, you.
-You go.
-Then I'll--
-I'll have it then.
There's nothing else…
-Thank you.
-Give me some too.
Actually, there's something
I've been thinking about.
I've seen that man somewhere before.
Maybe he was following you
and appeared near the hospital.
He's not that dumb
to get himself discovered.
Please.
Hello, this is Shimazaki Security.
Oh, hello?
Are you a bodyguard?
Yes.
We receive requests
for personal protection.
Can I request for your service
even without a referral?
Yes, that's fine.
Even if I'm not rich?
Can I hear about your request first?
Then can you come over to my house?
I'm really bothered that
I can't make any curry.
Curry, you say?
Over there.
CURRY CAFETERIA
CURRY CAFETERIA SAKUMA
Are you the bodyguards?
Yes. We're from Shimazaki Security.
It's horrible, right?
No matter how many I tear down,
they'll put them up again.
WARNING
EVICTION ORDER
WE ARE UNABLE TO CONTINUE
OUR CONTRACT WITH YOU ANY LONGER.
SHIROYAMA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Stop it already!
-Come in.
-Excuse me.
-Here are your afternoon appointments.
-Good work.
Hey.
Do you remember
if we had a patient in his thirties,
around 180cm in height, with a big build,
and has a slight scary expression on him?
Dr. Kasamatsu, do you know
how many patients we see every day?
There are more than
100 of them that fit the bill!
I guess she's right.
Please come in.
-Please excuse us.
-Come in.
-Sorry that this place's a little cramped.
-Excuse us.
This shop is really well-decorated.
I've been making curry here
for the past 40 years.
Oh, this jar stinks.
Are those sour-sweet pickles?
Yes, it's a secret recipe from my husband.
I've had customers scoffing at me,
saying, "The curry is nothing much,
but the pickles are incredibly good."
Where is your husband?
He was killed.
I might end up like him too.
Excuse me.
Can I ask how your husband passed away?
Last month,
he was talking to the landlord's son…
and he suddenly had a heart attack.
He died so suddenly.
What? You said he was killed,
but there was no violence, was there?
There was violence!
Those people, they kept on cornering us,
telling us to get out.
That was the reason
why he had a heart attack!
My husband was killed!
So he was cornered,
and that cost him his life.
This place…
It's a rented space.
-I see.
-But…
we've never failed to pay
our monthly rent these past 40 years.
That's why the landlord told us,
"You can stay here forever."
Their family often came here to eat curry.
And those pickles too?
Their son, who was still in kindergarten,
even laughed and said
the pickles were delicious.
However, when the landlord died
and his son took over…
he told my husband
that he was going to sell off
this building and the land.
It was quite a shock.
He said he won't renew
our rental contract.
There was even a lawsuit.
And by tomorrow…
I have to move out.
All the shops
around this area have closed…
The ramen shop, bakery,
and even the café…
They all cried and left
after the sudden notice.
But my husband bowed and begged them.
"This is different
from what we discussed."
"Please let us continue to stay here!"
He begged over and over.
And then…
that incident happened.
Are you still there, old lady?
Let's abide by the laws, okay?
We'll be in trouble if you don't come out!
Is the tallest one the landlord's son?
-Yes.
-How long are you going to stay there?
He went down the wrong path,
and the landlord was really upset.
He even got in trouble
with the police a few times.
Hey…
You can't even make curry alone, right?
They're acting like
those old-fashioned land sharks.
It's better to report it to the police.
The police won't do anything!
They just told us to discuss it
with the other party!
I don't mean to be rude,
but do you have any other family members
that you can confide in?
We didn't have any children.
My husband and I got this far,
just the two of us.
Please, my husband
protected this place with his life.
Please! Protect our curry!
Hey, old lady!
We'll have to file a claim
if you don't listen to us!
Hey!
Come out now!
What the…
Hey, what are you doing?
Aren't you guys committing
an illegal act here?
Shut up!
Tomorrow's the eviction deadline.
-Deadline?
-Hey, pass me my bag.
If she doesn't leave,
we're allowed to destroy the building.
It's useless clinging on
to this small restaurant.
Let's continue.
Old lady!
BODYGUARD REQUEST
TAKASHI KUWATA
The house of Mr. Kuwata,
Special Aide to the Prime Minister,
is 660 square meters wide.
There are a total of four exit points.
There are windows facing the road.
It has a Level 2 risk.
It's a casual meeting with journalists,
so there will be many outsiders.
Please exercise extra caution.
-Yes.
About this…
SEITARO SAWAGUCHI
BODYGUARD, KICKS GUARD
Why would he want to hold
the press conference at his residence?
Wouldn't it be safer if Mr. Kuwata
held the event at his headquarters?
Rumors are spreading that in order to
become the Prime Minister's special aide,
Mr. Kuwata deliberately leaked the scandal
regarding Assemblyman Otonari's wife.
He's having this close-up interview
in order to prove his innocence.
That's just a front.
He's treating them to some delicacies
in his house,
and ask them to write
something positive about him.
KOUMEI RYU
PRESIDENT, KICKS CORP.
This is Mr. Kuwata's forte.
The mass media…
They're all gathered there.
So if we do a good job of protecting him,
it'll help build our reputation.
Is that so?
Exactly.
You've shown remarkable progress,
Sawaguchi.
Only huge companies can be hired
for the ruling party's personal security.
I'm expecting good results.
Yes, sir. I'll be careful.
-Please excuse us.
-Excuse us.
This is tough.
The law is on the landlord's side.
If we obstruct the progress,
we'll be arrested
for breaking the law too.
It smelled really good.
-You mean the curry?
-No, the pickles.
I would like to try it someday.
Why are you being so nonchalant?
-You might be attacked here!
-I won't let them have the chance.
But if anything happens,
I'll leave it to you.
What?
-No. I refuse.
-I was joking.
I won't actually need your help.
Yes.
AKITO SASAKI'S FUNERAL CEREMONY
We're having curry in the morning?
You can tell?
The smell's so strong.
I made this from scratch using spices.
It's authentic curry.
Is your work really that dangerous?
You should choose your work.
I'm digging in.
Let me say this first.
Now…
I'm being targeted by a man.
It might be someone who had a grudge
over my past assignments.
This is what he looks like.
I don't know much about him though.
You should make sure to close the doors
and be careful when going home.
He looks pretty strong.
Can I take him down?
I learned karate online
during my school vacation.
-They taught quite well.
-Online…
What is he doing…
I wonder if he'll come for me?
I'll defeat him and help
your weak security office!
Try hitting me.
If I was that man,
I would just continue with this
and render you unconscious.
-Do you get it?
-What do you mean…
Human bodies are extremely susceptible
to sudden movements. Remember that.
I got it already!
Just eat your breakfast.
Don't open it immediately.
It's Dr. Kasamatsu!
What kind of joke is that?
I'm telling the truth!
Just stop it already!
What the…
Shouldn't you open the door?
I'm trying to understand what's going on!
So much for an adult…
-Good morning.
-Oh, good morning.
Sorry to come here suddenly.
-What's the matter?
-Well…
-I just passed by, so I came to visit.
-I see.
Oh, this is for Shun.
Thanks, you didn't have to.
This is farm-fresh with no preservatives
and comes with vitamins C and K,
both essential for growth.
-Oh, since he's still growing…
-Yes.
You're here to see Dad, right,
Dr. Kasamatsu?
-What?
-Good going for you!
What are you saying, you idiot?
Well, I'm off to school.
-Please make yourself at home.
-Hey!
-The curry was delicious.
-I'm glad.
I'm sorry.
But as Shun said,
I'm here to see you, Shimazaki.
There's something I would like to say,
which is hard to convey via phone.
Sure.
-Excuse me…
-We'll be starting soon.
I hope that all of you
treat the journalists kindly.
-Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
Please come over here.
-I'll take over.
-Thank you.
Sorry. My place is a little untidy, so…
It's fine.
I see…
You really had curry early in the morning.
Smells good.
Well, I came across
a curry restaurant while working,
so I thought of letting Shun
have some curry.
Oh, I would like to have some too.
Well… sure.
Before that…
Oh, sorry… the main topic.
Well, it's about the man we saw last time.
I see…
Here you go.
-I said I saw him somewhere before, right?
-Yes.
I thought he might have been my patient…
Did you remember something?
Yes.
He came to my husband's funeral.
Your husband's funeral?
Hey. Did something happen
between you two, Shimazaki?
-I can help you investigate his--
-No.
Please don't do that.
I can't tell you any details,
but it's quite dangerous.
I was a police officer's wife.
I'm not scared.
But you were so scared back then…
Oh, that's because it was too sudden.
I'm asking you nicely here,
so how about you being nicer?
Don't pressure me with that.
It's my problem and
it's got nothing to do with you.
Don't be so full of yourself!
I'm not thinking of
being in a relationship with you.
Wait… I didn't say anything about
going into a relationship with you.
-Isn't it the same?
-It's very different.
"Going into a relationship…"
What was that about?
-I'm digging in.
-Please.
Please excuse me.
Hello?
I arrived at the place earlier
just in case…
This case is much more troublesome
than we expected.
What?
Ms. Sakuma!
Old lady!
It's the promised deadline!
Ms. Hanae Sakuma!
In accordance with the court ruling,
you are required
to vacate this place by today!
I'm Nakano, an attorney!
I represent Mr. Mitsuru Tamai,
the owner of this land.
Did you hear me?
EVICTION NOTICE
THE CURRY HERE IS ILLEGAL
-Hey.
-Got it.
Wait a minute!
-Isn't this too sudden?
-It's not sudden at all!
I've been telling her to leave.
She was the one who ignored the law.
Excuse me, but are you
Mrs. Sakuma's representative?
I've never seen you before.
Which law office are you from?
I'm Shimazaki. I'm not an attorney.
I work as a bodyguard
for Ms. Hanae Sakuma and her late husband.
A bodyguard?
When a law is in effect,
mere bodyguards
can't do anything about it.
Or are you going to
chase us away by force?
Ms. Hanae is all alone.
We are here to
help facilitate negotiations.
Don't misunderstand.
There is no room for any negotiations.
Good morning.
Are they really planning to
destroy this building?
Those guys are capable of doing anything!
I will not cave in to their threats!
If I can't fulfill our promise
with the previous landlord…
I refuse to take a single step out!
What the… Hey!
Hey, old lady!
CURRY CAFETERIA SAKUMA
Hey, why did you close the shop?
Open up!
Hey!
This is just like a siege.
If I want them to understand,
I have to show them my determination!
You two will be with me, right?
What the hell are you doing?
Open up!
Hey!
I appreciate everyone coming here.
Today, I intend to answer every question
with full transparency.
Please do not hold back.
-Please begin.
-Yes.
Please go ahead.
This is Ezaki from Maicho News.
There's an article stating that
Mr. Kuwata is responsible
for leaking the scandal
on Mr. Otonari's wife.
I read the article.
It pains me to hear that my appointment
has led to such a misunderstanding.
But this is completely untrue.
Regarding Mr. Otonari's
wife's private life…
…there is no way
I would know about that.
Also…
Is something troubling you, 04?
Is your vision failing, 01?
This is 01.
I'm leaving my position for a moment.
Say something, old lady!
I'm not extending the deadline any longer!
KANAGAWA POLICE
We received a complaint call
from the neighboring area.
Who's the one in charge of this area?
Oh, go complain to the old lady
who holed herself inside.
We're doing this
in accordance with the law.
Who are you?
I'm just a mere bodyguard,
and my name is Shimazaki.
The Sakuma couple have been operating
their curry restaurant here
for the past 40 years.
We seek your understanding that
she is unable to come to terms
with the sudden eviction notice.
And like I said, it's impossible!
Do you still not understand?
We applied for an eviction notice
through legal means!
The one taking reckless action
is Ms. Sakuma!
It may be true, based on the law.
However, Ms. Sakuma came this far
based on a promise with your father.
At least let her have a chance
to negotiate, please.
You're not even her attorney, so stop
interfering with other people's matters!
Any further act of barbarity
would only destroy the image that
the restaurant worked hard to build up,
don't you think so?
OWNER OF LONG-ESTABLISHED CURRY SHOP
STAGES A SIEGE!
AN EVICTION PROTEST?
-Good work as always.
-This is Suganuma.
A concerning individual has appeared
at Assemblyman Kuwata's press conference.
Is he troublesome to deal with?
He was the one who tried
to attack Assemblyman Kuwata
during his 20th-anniversary celebration.
I heard everything from Sawaguchi.
The reason why Shimazaki left Kicks Guard
was that he found out
I planned the attack during that event.
President…
Don't tell me you're planning
the same thing again?
You really don't know how to hold back.
As expected of the woman I acknowledge,
as a bodyguard and as a woman.
Is this the time to joke?
Please tell me.
Why is that man here?
Unfortunately, I don't know.
Be extremely cautious of him.
However,
do not let the other bodyguards
know about this.
President! Just who is he?
You don't have to know.
GUESTBOOK
POLICE-RELATED VISITOR LIST
Thank you very much.
-Thank you very much.
It got a little hot there.
How was it? I hope all of you liked it.
-Yes.
Well then, we'll end it here for today.
-Thank you.
-Please excuse me.
Oh, please take the souvenirs!
Wow, thank you!
-Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
Here you go.
You think you could actually
bribe people with these?
Please step back.
Assemblyman.
Did you buy information with money?
This battle could have been easily won
if you knew about their private lives.
Please tell us the truth.
Please come over here.
It's fine.
But…
It seems like you have something to say.
Shall we talk?
It's dangerous. Please stay back.
It'll be fine.
If we have a good talk,
the misunderstanding will be cleared up.
All right. Over here.
Assemblyman…
Isn't your eviction method too coercive?
It's not.
I heard that this restaurant has
a good reputation around this area.
Don't you feel that it's too cruel to
do this to the owner so suddenly?
We're bothered by it too.
If we can't sell this place,
I can't pay my taxes.
Stop making us
look like the bad guys here!
I'm sorry.
Come over!
What's up?
-You should go back!
-What?
I'll deal with the rest.
I got it already.
It won't do us any good
to continue this siege any longer.
Not yet! I won't lose to them!
There are people
who understand how I feel, right?
People might be sympathizing with you now,
but you don't know
when it'll turn into criticism.
People might say that you're trying to
force them into caving in.
It's almost summer…
What?
I mean, if I recall,
the season for pickles
is almost over, isn't it?
Yet you didn't make any this year.
Ms. Sakuma.
Haven't you already accepted that
you can't continue to operate
the restaurant any longer?
I mean, you didn't even prepare
any curry either.
And what's wrong with that?
Oh, I'm sorry if I was wrong.
But didn't you stage this siege
in order to create a commotion?
Mr. Bodyguard…
I thought you were just
all brawn and no brains…
but surprisingly, you have good intuition.
It's my job to take a close look
at my clients after all.
That's right.
I wanted them to know.
Please excuse me.
This place belongs to me,
so I'm coming in.
Wow, as expected of a bodyguard!
You guys look strong!
If you try anything reckless,
I'm calling the police!
Your late father would be sad!
-Hey.
-Got it.
Oh, I'm not doing anything reckless here.
We're just doing a search.
Excuse me.
This place belongs to me.
So I'm free to do whatever I want here.
Young sir…
Please look at this!
That time, you and your father…
the two of you complimented
this place happily, didn't you?
I was happy.
My husband and I wanted to see
the smiles on our customers.
That's why we did our best for 40 years!
No matter what, rain or shine,
we would prepare
the curry and the pickles.
No, it wasn't just us.
The same goes for everyone
who had their shops here too!
But then,
our everyday lives
were taken away from us.
It was so hard on all of us.
I'm not doing this
just for my own restaurant!
I wanted someone… anyone to
understand how we shop owners felt!
Wow, how admirable!
But it's not good to lie.
Old lady!
You went to the Sugihara Law Office
in the shopping district, didn't you?
Did something happen
between you and that attorney?
I'll say it then.
She asked how to get the maximum
compensation in the event of an eviction.
Then the attorney told her to
just kick up a fuss
and refuse all negotiations.
Am I wrong?
It must be hard on you two
since you don't know what's going on.
This old lady?
She doesn't care about
this run-down place!
She was after the money!
Stop… Please stop!
No matter what our client is after,
our duty is to protect them.
-Please stop this!
-Let go!
Takanashi!
Enough already…
If people knew that
all I wanted was
just to receive more compensation,
it would bring shame to my late husband.
I'm closing…
the restaurant.
So you finally get it.
Get out of this place now.
Yes.
Please give me until the evening
to pack my belongings.
If you continue to stay after that,
I won't let you off so easily.
Let's go.
Got it.
Hurry up.
Dammit…
Stop staring.
Are you really fine with that?
You never had the intention of trying to
get more compensation, did you?
You just wanted to grab at any chance
in the hope that you would get to
stay here forever, right?
How amateurs like you think…
It's just no good.
It's all over.
I did my best until now…
My husband…
I'm sure he'll forgive me.
Why are you giving up?
Even if the place changes,
your husband's cooking
can still continue elsewhere.
What are you saying?
I'm already over 70!
It's impossible for me to
open up a new restaurant!
You said it yourself, Ms. Sakuma.
"Please! Protect our curry."
It doesn't matter where you set up shop.
It doesn't matter who eats it.
Your everyday life, making curry…
can still continue.
Have some curry, you two.
I'm sorry there are no more pickles.
The two of you did well.
I'll treat you both to
our restaurant's curry.
We'll just accept your thoughts.
We can't eat while we're on duty, so…
And you call yourselves bodyguards?
It's your job to listen to orders, right?
There, it's done!
Sakuma-style curry!
What are you doing? Go on, sit down!
-No, we really can't eat while--
-Yes, ma'am.
-Here you go!
-I've been a bodyguard for 25 years,
and I've never eaten while I'm on duty.
-You don't know when to give up.
-What are you saying?
"You're on duty"?
What the hell are you saying?
You're just a geezer
who doesn't want to break the rules.
You're such a stickler for rules.
I'm sorry.
All right, good. Here you go.
Please eat it while it's hot.
Mission complete.
Current time, 11:30.
Time, 11:30. Synchronized.
Sync…
Synchronized.
-Mission complete…
-I'm digging in.
Mission complete…
-I'm digging in!
-Delicious!
It's good.
The carrot's really good.
It's delicious.
You two really make a good combination.
-No, not at all.
-It's the complete opposite.
I'll try making curry seriously
for a month,
and see how it goes.
Thank you, Mr. Bodyguards.
You protected my everyday life.
Can I have a second helping?
Of course!
-You finished already?
-Hey, you're still eating!
CURRY CAFETERIA SAKUMA
It's getting late.
-Assemblyman!
Are you all right, Assemblyman Kuwata?
Behind you!
Stop him!
-Please check on Assemblyman Kuwata!
-Yes!
-I'll take the other exit!
-Assemblyman Kuwata!
Stay still!
I…
was asked by President Ryu to do this.
He told me to silence Kuwata.
-Suganuma!
-I'm fine. Go after him!
Yes!
We were talking about
some political issues.
I don't know what irritated him,
but he just suddenly charged at me!
So I started to fight back.
What were his bodyguards doing?
-I'm truly sorry.
-No, it's fine.
They did a really good job.
I…
This happened because of
my selfish request.
You were the last one who saw him, right?
Did you notice anything?
You have to be honest here.
He said it was a request.
He was told to assault Mr. Kuwata.
It was a request? By whom?
Ms. Suganuma. Are you all right?
By President Ryu.
Welcome back.
President Koumei Ryu, I presume?
Yes.
We would like to speak with you.
Please accompany us to the police station.
And may I ask by what right?
I've been paying my taxes.
In Assemblyman Kuwata's assault incident,
the perpetrator said that
you requested him to do so.
And I'm the president of the company
that provided him with personal security.
We're just going to have a talk
to understand the details.
-Please.
-This is ridiculous.
-This is a request.
-Mr. Ryu!
Hey, stop!
What are you doing?
Hey, hold up!
Stop!
POLICE SCANDALS - 2017
APRIL 18: METRO POLICE SP-AFFILIATED MALE
ASSAULTS, SERIOUSLY INJURES SUPERIOR
Hello?
Sorry to call while you're not on duty.
Are you injured again?
Oh, I'm not injured today.
This morning…
I was too arrogant.
So you're here to reflect
on your mistakes?
In my line of work,
there are some things that I have to say
while I can still say them.
I see.
I have to apologize too. I'm sorry.
You stopped me,
but I still did my own investigation.
About that man, I mean.
It doesn't seem like
he was close to my late husband,
but…
he was his junior at work.
Which means, he was a police officer.
Seems like he was a passionate individual
in the Security Police Division.
However, he resigned three years ago
due to an incident.
Thank you.
But…
please forget about this matter.
I got it.
I won't ask any further.
Sorry.
In exchange…
promise me.
Don't treat your life poorly.
I know you're dealing with
something very dangerous.
And I know you tend to be
really reckless as well.
As expected of my attending doctor.
That's right. I know you very well
since I'm your attending doctor.
You're not immortal.
Got it.
The curry this morning was delicious.
All right!
So that's how happy you feel.
Well, if that's the case…
maybe I should've made it
for my ex-wife at least once.
Oh, sorry.
I always talk about things in the past.
It's fine.
Me too.
I should have made some delicious curry
for my late husband too.
Isn't it fine?
Both you and I
are here because of our pasts.
It's beautiful.
I mean, look at that.
You can see the tip of the Tokyo Tower
poking out there.
Sorry.
What?
It's from a junior that
I have an estranged relationship with.
You have to take it.
Excuse me.
Hello?
I thought you wouldn't call me ever again.
I…
didn't plan on calling again.
But…
things have turned troublesome.
What's the matter?
It's still not out in the news yet.
Assemblyman Kuwata was attacked.
The one who did it
was a man by the name of Kato.
He was the waiter from that incident.
Before Kato escaped…
I was asked by President Ryu to do this.
He told me to silence Kuwata.
The president was asked
to cooperate in the investigation,
but he ran away.
News of President Ryu's escape
is not out yet.
So far, there's only
the article on Kuwata.
What is going on?
Could this be real?
President Ryu going
after Assemblyman Kuwata, I mean.
Hopefully, our prediction is wrong.
Hello.
It's me, Ryu.
I was just talking
with Takanashi about you.
Perfect timing.
I didn't do it.
But it seems like…
I know too much.
This may just be what I deserved.
Why are you calling me?
There's only one reason.
Protect me.
Protect you?
Kuwata has connections
with the Metropolitan Police.
They probably won't believe
that I'm innocent.
I plan to leave Japan.
I'm requesting you
for my personal security.
I'll give you as much money as you want.
Why would you request for my service,
when I don't like you?
I might report you to the police.
No.
You won't do that.
You…
You're a bodyguard that protects
his clients, no matter who they may be.
Please reconsider this.
I'll be waiting
at North Toyosu Park at 11 p.m.
Don't tell me…
you're going to accept his request?
-He betrayed us bodyguards!
-But he needs help now.
I'm opposed to this assignment.
-It might be a trap.
-We don't know until we go.
Today…
at the curry restaurant,
when you chased those guys away,
it was frustratingly easy
to keep up with you.
I thought that
it meant we could really work together.
It was the first time I felt that way.
I see.
If you're going to protect President Ryu,
I will resign from this office.
Let's go!
-Over there!
-After him!
Search for him!
Search thoroughly!
The last episode!
Prove to me that bodyguards
can really become their client's shield.
He's back, right? Let me talk to him.
Get rid of him.
You should tell the truth.
This is an order from your client.
Let's silence him.
-Shimazaki!
-Shimazaki?
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu