The ace of Japan's national
soccer team, Junya Kono,
has made a dashing entrance.
The scoring champion
three years running for Kamakura Regulus,
Junya has transferred to
the famous Italian club, Piedmont FC.
-Thank you.
-Japan has high expectations...
Mr. Kono!
Junya!
FROM: HITOMI
IT'S HITOMI
I WANT TO RAISE SHUN HERE WITH US.
MY HUSBAND AGREES.
COULD YOU TALK TO SHUN ABOUT THAT FOR ME?
I HEARD YOU'RE WORKING
AS A BODYGUARD AGAIN.
BE CAREFUL.
HITOMI ODAGIRI
So you're Mrs. Odagiri now.
A bill to increase lump-sum benefits
for childbirth and childcare
has been introduced to
the ordinary session of the Diet.
This is part of the government's
social welfare reforms.
Apparently, the submission of this bill...
-Morning. You're up early.
-was due to the reversal of opinion
by Chairman Sakiyama of
the Japan Federation of Physicians.
Chairman Sakiyama stated that
this law affects
the children of Japan
on whom Japan's future rests.
I was thinking about
watching one of your matches.
What's the point? I'm not a regular.
Really? Are you that bad?
Shut up! I'm not bad.
I just get nervous in real matches.
What about breakfast? You'll get hungry!
MHLW Minister Aiko Tachihara
displayed resolve to pass the bill.
The declining birth rate is
a critical issue facing Japan.
Not even a "thank you"?
I've introduced this bill to...
You've really done it this time!
Did you think you could hide this from me?
OSAMU HIKAWA
CHIEF, SECURITY BUREAU (SP), MPD
A serving minister escaped
under the watch of her SP guards!
What's worse,
private bodyguards helped her!
I've never heard of such a thing.
I'm terribly sorry.
I don't think I'll ever hear a report
from you that I'm pleased with, Ochiai.
I'll clear this up.
YOSHIAKI OCHIAI
SECURITY BUREAU (SP), MPD
-Good morning.
Everyone, there's good news.
Really? A special bonus?
Thirty days of paid leave?
We have a new job.
-What a letdown.
-Now, now.
The client heard about
our excellent reputation,
so he insisted on hiring us.
We've been depending on
the President's personal contacts,
but we got this one on our own.
He "insisted" on hiring us?
That's actually kind of scary.
He's not a dangerous client.
BRINGING JOY TO CHILDREN THROUGH SPORTS
PURENESS FOUNDATION
I know this. It's that famous charity.
I doubt we'll attract any attention
from the police this time.
Now, as for the BG...
MASAYA TAKANASHI
HINODE PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
I think Shimazaki would be best.
What?
What's wrong?
Well, I mean, instead of me,
wouldn't it be better for Sawaguchi
to be the BG for the first time?
Well, if you insist so much,
I'll have to accept.
He only said it once.
Then this is your first chance
to be BG, Sawaguchi.
Yes, sir.
I'll be the backup.
I think you're up to the task.
Don't get so cocky.
-Do your best.
-I will.
-I'm going to the restroom.
-I'm counting on you.
Thank you, sir.
BG Sawaguchi.
We have a new team starting today,
and I'll be handling
your security personally.
Personnel changes have been made
by order of the Security Police.
Are you increasing surveillance on me?
Please refrain from contacting
private security firms in the future.
I'd like to exclude
any interference in your security.
"Exclude"?
You sound like you want
to destroy Hinode Security.
Here is the security schedule
for the week.
AFFINITY
PURENESS FOUNDATION
Please come in.
I'm Junya Kono,
a representative of Pureness.
Of course, we know who you are.
-Hey!
-This way, please.
I mean, this is Junya.
To people my age, he's a god.
The Japanese Whirlwind.
You scored through four defenders
at the Youth Championships.
The boys in my class went wild
when we heard
you were going to
the big Italian club, Piedmont.
You're being rude.
It's all right.
I haven't been called "god"
in a while. It's nice.
When I played, that nickname put
a lot of pressure on me.
Can you tell us more about this job?
Sure.
Let's see. From the 18th to the 20th,
I'll be at a charity auction in Milan.
I'll be auctioning autographed balls
and other goods I collected
from athletes around the world.
I need security on the way to the airport.
Could you be targeted by someone,
like a crazy fan
or a thief hoping to make money?
No.
These are precious, so I just want
to make sure they're safe.
Please help me deliver
the dreams of the children.
Don't you worry. I'm Sawaguchi.
I'll be in charge,
and I will protect you with my life.
Actually, I'd like to make
one personal request.
He wants me?
He said you used to be friends.
That's amazing. Is that true?
Why didn't you tell us?
Probably because
he's too secretive. Right?
So was there some trouble between you two?
With that star soccer player?
-Maybe they fought over a girl.
-Quit joking around.
It appears there's something
bothering you.
Everyone has troubles in their past.
Even I do.
It's all right if you have problems
accepting this.
I won't ask why.
We'll turn this job down.
No!
I'm sorry if I never told you.
Up until six years ago,
I was Kono's bodyguard.
So you were lying when you said
you're a novice bodyguard?
Novice? He's a total expert.
I always thought it was odd.
You were always way better than you acted.
Unbelievable.
Hey.
Did you know about this?
More accurately, I figured it out.
Then why didn't you say anything?
Keeping silent makes you just as guilty!
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
I'll take the job Kono wants me for.
However, unnecessary info will interfere
with his security.
After we've completed this mission,
I'll tell all of you everything.
Okay! Let's get to work!
Yes, sir.
FORMAT PC
FORMATTING...
Hello?
Shiraishi here.
How are the preparations going?
I'll clear the room out for you.
I've taken care of everything.
I knew you were a fast worker.
Brilliant stars are a cut above.
Don't say that.
I'm not a star anymore.
To us, you're a big star.
Goodbye.
Kamakura Regulus!
Go! Junya, go!
FORMATTING COMPLETE
Zaki, try these on.
-No, it's okay.
-Come on. Try them.
They look great on you.
-You can have them.
-Thank you.
Excuse me!
Thank you.
Stand back! Don't push!
-Autograph, please!
-Don't push!
It's dangerous! Don't push!
-Junya! Autograph, please!
-Don't push!
If you're going to do this,
then give it your all.
Make up for keeping silent.
You bet.
Well, it sure has been a while.
How have you been?
Hi. Yes, it's been a while.
I always wondered
how you'd been doing, Zaki.
Thanks.
Where's the luggage
you're taking to the airport?
It's these two.
It's precious. Take care of it.
Certainly.
Protect me until I leave this time.
Yes, sir. I promise to protect you
until you depart.
Why didn't he tell us?
There must be something
he really didn't want us to know.
Providing backup is more important.
Check traffic conditions and social media.
Yes, sir. Sorry.
There are no congestion
or accident reports.
You sure recovered fast.
What else can I do?
He never told us anything
because he didn't want to.
Really? I guess your brains finally
caught up with your mature looks.
What's this?
JUNYA WILL BE AT THE WINTERIS SOCCER EVENT
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW!
Junya's supposed to be
at a soccer event in Todoroki
the day after tomorrow.
JUNYA KONO, FORMER NATIONAL TEAM
AND KAMAKURA REGULUS MEMBER
Five o'clock.
-Can we have your autograph?
-No! Stand back!
-What? How scary!
-Excuse us. Let me have that.
Sorry, but since I retired,
I haven't given autographs.
Will a handshake do?
-May I?
-All right!
-I hope you make a comeback!
-Me too!
Your foot is better, isn't it?
-Here you are.
-He's so cool!
That was amazing!
-Minister.
-Hold on.
You're Junya Kono, aren't you?
Hello.
We met at a charity event
for international education.
It wouldn't have been a success
without your support.
Excuse me.
Let's go.
I wonder if Junya Kono
is escaping overseas.
"Escaping"? What do you mean?
Politicians often act like
they know nothing
when actually, we know an awful lot.
Shimazaki.
A soccer event the day after tomorrow?
He's scheduled to appear for sure.
Without Junya,
the crowd will get pretty upset.
Oh, that? I'll cancel that later.
You're canceling an event for
the day after tomorrow now?
The media will demand an explanation
when you return.
I won't be coming back for a while.
I only said I'd be gone for two weeks.
I might never return.
Anyway,
when I was still playing, I got
a permanent resident visa over there.
Then what about
the charity event in Milan?
There is no charity.
-Why did you lie to us?
-Why did I lie?
-Well...
-Give us an explanation.
-What's going on?
-You sure are pushy.
It's all a lie.
It's all a lie?
Almost none of the charity money
has been used for kids.
I was just a PR front,
making money for my backer.
Your "backer"?
After I retired,
they covered my bills
when I went through rough times.
You could call them my sponsor.
Then why are you going to Italy?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm disappearing before people find out.
All evidence of wrongdoing is in those.
That's why I got bodyguards,
just in case anything happened.
-We won't help you flee.
-Quit acting so self-righteous!
I'm your client, you know.
Zaki can't refuse me, right?
No matter what I ask.
That's why I asked for you.
Get going! Drive!
Right now! That's an order!
Shimazaki...
Shimazaki!
They're going to the airport.
They can't do that!
We're helping him flee the country!
What am I supposed to do?
Shimazaki is just following orders.
But we have to stop him!
We're in danger
of losing our license again.
Even if we drop this job,
Kono will go to the airport
on his own anyway.
Maybe Shimazaki is taking him
so we can stop him.
CURRENT LOCATION: NEAR BAY TRUST HOTEL
Minister Tachihara's information
was right.
There are suspicious rumors
about Junya Kono.
He's under surveillance
by the Organized Crime Squad.
Inform them that
he might be fleeing the country.
Wouldn't it be better
if Kono fled the country?
Since Hinode Security is involved,
a charge of assisting escape
will harm their reputation.
It's the perfect excuse to terminate
their security business license.
I won't pull nasty tricks like that.
I'll destroy them head-on.
My bags.
You call yourselves bodyguards?
Are you sure about this,
"Zaki"?
Get out of my way.
Junya...
you said you wanted me to guard you
until you depart.
So carry these!
You call this a departure?
You...
were a star...
no, in fact, you're still a star.
Anyone who has inspired
other people's dreams
should never flee, no matter what happens.
Not just once, but twice...
you're going to interfere with me
going abroad?
Mr. Kono,
can I have a moment of your time?
Those might be police detectives.
Did you leak this?
We'd never betray a client!
The police may already have
an arrest warrant for you.
No, that's impossible.
All the evidence is here.
I'm leaving before an investigation...
Hold it right there!
They're asking questions
at the Milan departure desk.
There are detectives
EMBARKATION, TICKET SALES
The headlines will say,
"Former soccer star Junya Kono
falls from grace."
"The man called the god of speed
fed off the dreams of children!"
Let go!
Let go of me!
Whose fault was it
that I turned out like this?
Come on! Say something!
Did you forget it all?
It's collapsing!
Junya!
It hurts!
I'd be better off dead.
That forced me to retire.
Even after my injury healed,
I lost my chance to go abroad.
That put an end to my soccer career.
You have a lot of nerve,
working as a bodyguard.
I lost everything.
Shimazaki quit being a bodyguard.
He did road construction security
for six years.
He never once spoke about you
or about his past.
And now,
he obeys the client's orders
to the letter.
Even now, for you, he's--
-It's too late for that!
-No, it's not.
Mr. Kono,
turn yourself in before you're arrested.
We'll take you there.
Are you lecturing your client?
Who knew you'd all be alike?
Junya, when I left your side then,
I failed at being a bodyguard.
Why are you apologizing?
If you hadn't saved those kids,
they would have died!
My client was Junya.
Hold on a second.
So even if we see someone about to die,
we shouldn't leave the client?
That's what it means to be a bodyguard.
You're paid to protect my life!
It can't be helped
if you're on the job.
-I'm supposed to watch people die?
-That's not what I mean!
My client was Junya.
That's no reason--
My client was Junya!
You're such a bunch of idiots.
What's the point in talking about this?
I'm sick of dealing with you.
I'll go to the police.
But before that,
I have to tie up some loose ends.
We'll accompany you anywhere.
No.
I only want Zaki to come along.
Okay.
I won't leave your side again.
That's what I promised.
Thank you for the information earlier.
Junya Kono has some
very shady people backing him.
In fact, they once offered
to give me a contribution.
Naturally, I refused it.
Fortunately, he's still in the country.
The Organized Crime Squad
is investigating.
Was I of some help to you, Mr. Ochiai?
Yes.
I see.
Out of consideration for me,
will you please take it easy
on Shimazaki and the others?
I cannot do that.
Why not?
"Why not"?
It's the police's duty to censure mistakes
made by the private sector.
It seems to me that
this has nothing to do
with the public and private sector.
I think you simply hate Shimazaki.
No, that's not right. You don't hate him.
You're jealous of him.
Or is that even possible?
The mighty SP would never envy
a plain old bodyguard.
I'm sorry.
It's time for a shift change. Excuse me.
SHIRAISHI ARTS MANAGEMENT
If I turn myself in,
the people who took care of me
won't take it lightly.
I can't just betray them.
I'll accompany him to Shiraishi Arts.
Be very careful.
The Investigation Department checked him.
Gozo Shiraishi has been arrested
for fraud and bribery.
There's something fishy.
Junya said he put all the evidence
in his suitcases,
but the police are carrying
everything out.
That bothers me.
Come back out in 30 minutes.
If you don't contact us,
we'll call the police.
Roger.
Time is 3:58 p.m. 12 seconds.
-Synchronized.
I wish you success.
SHIRAISHI ARTS MANAGEMENT
Is the chairman here?
Kono is here.
Okay. This way.
This is a surprise.
I thought you were already on a plane.
Sorry, especially after
all you've done for me.
Who's that?
-He's my bodyguard.
-Bodyguard?
If you wanted a hired gun,
I would have gotten you one.
A hired gun?
I should have done that.
This guy lectures me
even though he's only a hired gun.
He told me to go to the police.
-The police?
-Yes.
What a joke.
Turn myself in? Don't be stupid.
Did you think I had a change of heart?
Of course not.
Thanks to him, I missed my flight.
That's so cruel.
-We'll have to take care of that.
-Please do.
Do anything you like.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I've had it with this guy.
It's been 20 minutes. Still no word.
Right.
Your client, Junya Kono is
under police investigation.
SECURITY POLICE
Evidence indicating private use
of charity funds
was found in his hotel room.
Cooperate with us to arrest him.
What if we refuse?
Most likely,
you'll be charged with a crime
and immediately lose
your security business license.
Thank you for the warning.
I'm on duty now. Goodbye.
Are you sure it's okay?
If Junya Kono escapes,
we won't get away with just a warning.
I'm counting on Shimazaki.
You trust him too, right, Takanashi?
That's why you always worked with him
even though you knew about his past.
And I think Shimazaki
trusts you as well.
So even though he realized that you knew,
he worked with you without any complaint.
It's been 30 minutes.
You're going too easy!
I'm not a hero or a star anymore.
These past six years,
my life has been worthless.
-Hurry up and get him out of here.
-Yes, sir.
Hold on.
Any last words?
Fire me.
What? I can't hear you!
Fire me, please.
What are you talking about?
You've been fired long ago.
Why you!
I'm not your bodyguard anymore!
What are you doing?
You've been double-crossed.
What do you think you're doing?
I've had it with this guy.
Stop right there, you jerk!
Hey!
-Takanashi!
-Yes, sir!
-Stop! Darn you!
-Stop!
They double-crossed me?
DON'T THROW IT AWAY!
The police found evidence
in the room that you said
was empty of everything.
They planted evidence that would
make you take all the blame
after you fled the country.
What's this?
A star that has fallen from grace
is better off dead.
Don't think you've caught up with me.
I told you.
I wouldn't leave your side.
When you hit me earlier,
you hit me with all your might,
didn't you?
Yes.
I haven't hurt that bad in a long time.
Sorry.
You gave your son
the ball I signed, right?
Yes. He still treasures it.
Here, Zaki. For your son.
What?
-Thank you.
-Wish him the best.
I will.
TO SHUN,
JUNYA, KAMAKURA REGULUS
He says that...
he's too nervous to be a starter
in a real match.
I see.
He should try kicking the ball
with his eyes closed.
Close his eyes?
When you realize how helpless you are,
you won't be so tense.
Okay.
I guess my time's just about up.
That's right.
You're Junya Kono, right?
Yes.
Isn't that Junya Kono?
Seriously?
-Wait.
-It's really him!
-Let's get his autograph!
-Can you wait a second?
No. Stop.
Let me have your pen.
-You want me to sign these?
-Yes, please.
-There you go.
-Thank you!
There.
-Do your best. Keep practicing.
-Thanks!
-That's fast!
-Keep it up!
-Hang in there.
-Thank you!
-Look at this!
-See you.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
My injury from that accident
didn't end my career.
To be honest,
I was afraid I couldn't perform abroad.
The injury was an excuse to retire.
I couldn't overcome my own fears.
So...
you leaving my side
and saving those kids
was the right thing to do.
Thanks for staying with me until the end.
See you later, Zaki.
Thanks for all your help.
We avoided the loss of our license.
That was a heck of a run.
You've been beaten to a pulp. How pitiful.
So...
can I call you "Zaki"?
No.
I can't?
-Goodbye.
HINODE BUILDING
Are you all right?
Yes.
When I saw you at the hotel today,
I couldn't talk to you because...
Mr. Ochiai told me not to have
any more contact with you.
Is that so?
But when I'm told something like that,
it makes me want to talk to you even more.
Be careful.
Politicians
surprise others
to make them do what they want.
Bye.
That hurts!
You're so devoted.
You're still not drinking
because of your work?
Mura.
I'll forget about what happened today.
But there won't be a next time.
Our final warning. How frightening.
A beer and a pork cutlet sandwich.
You're getting used to
the private sector, I see.
Yes.
It's not always easy, but everyone
on my staff is very interesting.
They're the kind of people
that I'd do anything for.
Is that a declaration of war?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm home.
TO SHUN,
JUNYA, KAMAKURA REGULUS
By the way, Shun.
I heard that it's good to practice
kicking the ball with your eyes closed.
What?
That way you won't feel so tense
during a match.
-Are you nuts?
-That's what I heard.
Who said that?
-God.
-Don't be stupid.
I HATE TO ASK YOU THIS,
BUT THERE'S SOMEONE I WANT YOU TO GUARD.
HITOMI ODAGIRI
The client is the former Prime Minister.
They said old people don't need security.
I'll guard him so well,
the SP will be surprised.
-Someone, help me!
-Let me through!
So you even came here
to guard his granddaughter?
-I can't let you bring your grandpa shame.
-You're useless.
Help!