-Assemblyman!
Assemblyman Kuwata was attacked.
The one who did it
was a man by the name of Kato.
I was asked by President Ryu to do this.
He told me to silence Kuwata.
Seems like he was a passionate individual
in the Security Police Division.
You're not immortal.
Could this be real?
President Ryu going
after Assemblyman Kuwata, I mean.
Hopefully, our prediction is wrong.
I didn't do it.
Protect me.
I'm opposed to this assignment.
-It might be a trap.
-We don't know until we go.
If you're going to protect President Ryu,
I will resign from this office.
Let's go!
-Over there!
-After him!
Search for him!
Search thoroughly!
Head over there!
Where are you going?
Please stop.
-Stop!
-Hey!
-He's getting away!
-Stop him!
We're at the east exit.
To the left!
The other side!
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
NO CALLER ID
This is Shimazaki.
If you're President Ryu,
please knock the receiver once.
The police are searching for you.
Don't stay around the places you frequent.
Also, please make sure
the surveillance cameras can't see you.
YOU GOT A NEW MESSAGE
TO: AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
NO PROBLEM
KANTO KURI WAREHOUSE 2-A,
KACHIDOKI, 7:00 A.M.
Reach Kachidoki by 7:00 a.m?
MESSAGE DELETED
Excuse me…
the President…
Currently,
we are unable
to establish contact with him.
Is it true that he ordered the attack?
Indeed, the culprit said so.
But it doesn't mean that it's the truth.
Then why did he run away?
President Ryu should've known full well
not to interfere in an investigation.
What's going to happen to the company?
Won't our bodyguard licenses
-be suspended?
-No way!
-That's impossible!
-There's no way that's happening.
-But…
-Calm down!
Until we know the details,
everyone is to resume their duties
as a bodyguard of Kicks Guard.
Those who have bodyguard duties tomorrow
should focus on their assignments.
Concentrate on your work.
Yes, sir.
SHUN SHIMAZAKI
AKIRA'S SON
What?
Oh, sorry.
I'll be heading off to work now.
You don't have to tell me everything.
Hey, for breakfast…
have some raw egg with rice.
Just put one egg over white rice,
one teaspoon of soy sauce,
and five pieces of seaweed.
There's nothing better than this.
Make sure to eat.
A raw egg with rice is the best?
Shimazaki?
This is a video from a surveillance camera
in North Toyosu Park
we extracted from Koumei Ryu's phone GPS.
Over here, sir.
It really is Akira Shimazaki.
Why would he be there?
Could he be protecting Ryu?
Impossible.
Shimazaki resigned from Kicks Guard
after a conflict with President Ryu!
However,
for better or worse,
he's a pretty gutsy bodyguard.
I've heard about the Civil Party incident
two years ago.
Koumei Ryu is a man who would employ
anyone useful to his own advantage.
I shall arrange for the Riot Squad
to deal with any unforeseen circumstances.
We'll capture him no matter what.
Please
make sure that everything
doesn't come out for anyone to see.
Yes, sir!
To think that the president of
a 60-billion-yen company would run away…
Now that it has come to this,
I would rather him die as a fugitive.
It'll help wrap things up easier.
The Prime Minister would be very furious
if I had to resign at a time like this.
The same goes for you too, right?
Hello?
Assemblyman Kuwata told me
to call this number.
I'm sorry,
but he asked me to cooperate with you.
I…
don't know where President Ryu is.
Are you scared?
You haven't changed.
Not since you've been the chief
of the Security Police Division.
CHUO WARD, TOKYO
KURI WAREHOUSE, KACHIDOKI
MASAYA TAKANASHI
Oh, sorry about this.
You're sleeping, right?
Of course.
I'm not even wearing anything now.
What?
I see, you sleep naked. How wild.
Are you with President Ryu?
Not yet. Soon though.
Where are you?
MASAYA TAKANASHI
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
Though I have no intention of helping.
Takanashi…
thanks for everything.
You've been a reliable help. I mean it.
What the hell is that?
Also, I've calculated your salary so far.
Well, it's nothing like severance pay…
SALARY
…but I've included as much as I could.
Listen,
I didn't come with you to help you.
I couldn't make up my mind.
Things in the SDF didn't go well,
and I never thought
that I was meant to be a bodyguard.
That's why I wanted to know the reason
why you're able to do this job
without any hesitation.
So why did you accept that job?
Any incidents involving politicians
always put you in harm's way.
Or worse, you may end up dead!
Have you forgotten…
what happened to Chief Murata?
There's no way I would forget.
I wish us all success.
Boss!
Are you all right?
Mr. Murata!
Don't you think it's stupid to
expose yourself to danger for your enemy?
Don't tell me you're after the money.
-Sorry, it's time to work.
-Hey.
No one ever comes back
to life after death!
-Well then…
-"Well, then"? What do you mean?
How would I know what you want to say
if you don't finish it?
Hey, Akira Shimazaki…
just go die if you want to!
KOUMEI RYU
PRESIDENT, KICKS CORP.
Not a bad disguise, right?
From a bodyguard's standpoint…
wearing clothes that don't suit you
makes you stand out instead.
I see.
Then teach me, as a professional.
I still haven't accepted your request.
Indeed, I'm coercive
when it comes to business, but…
I've never exacted violence
in that manner!
Then why did Kato lie?
That man…
He resigned from the police force
after getting injured
and was picked up by Assemblyman Kuwata.
He is used to doing dirty work.
This time…
he was probably used to set me up.
Set you up?
Of all methods, why do you think
Assembly Kuwata used
the same as the one back then?
He did it to show
that I was the one who devised the plan.
It was a warning.
Nothing surprising,
coming from the world of politics.
He's probably planning to shake off
all the benefits I've given to him.
I'm sure you can understand.
As a bodyguard,
you must know how those in power think.
But if you're innocent,
you could have just proven it.
It's so unlike you to run away.
If I were to be arrested,
I don't think
I would receive fair treatment.
In the past, when there was a huge scandal
surrounding Kuwata's public office,
one of the secretaries killed himself
during a public announcement.
Do you really intend to escape overseas?
I…
don't have Japanese citizenship.
And while Japan is my mother's homeland,
it gave me nothing other than money.
I don't think the police
would be the only ones after you.
One of my acquaintances has prepared
a small airplane for me
in one of their private airports.
You just need to take me there.
What's wrong?
Don't you accept all requests,
no matter who the client is?
If I manage to escape safely,
I'll reveal to the public
that I've leaked security data.
And you…
why don't you prove that bodyguards
can really become their client's shield?
You're asking me to prove it,
but I have no interest
in things like this.
However,
your life is in danger,
so I'll accept the request...
as a bodyguard.
OMOTO, MIYAGUCHI
After his escape, all we know is that
he hid in an apartment he purchased.
Well, I'm just an employee.
I don't know anything.
I heard that
you were close to President Ryu.
Only as a subordinate.
-I've been serving him closely.
-Suganuma.
The president is a suspect on the run.
You would be breaking the law
if you're covering for him.
I really don't know!
You surprised me.
That's my line.
Sorry to pop by so suddenly.
The door was open, so…
You're not with my dad?
Yes, I guess.
I thought bodyguards
were supposed to have a buddy system?
Don't tell me you quit?
You're easy to read, Mr. Takanashi.
What do you want?
It's the first time I'm seeing you here.
He seemed strange this morning.
It's like we're never going to
see each other again.
Did he say that?
No.
He prepared a raw egg with rice
for breakfast,
and even made freshly-cooked rice.
I think you probably don't understand,
Mr. Takanashi,
but he only prepares a good breakfast
when he's on a dangerous task.
It was a simple breakfast,
but it still felt a little strange…
You're right.
This time, it's…
a very dangerous task.
You would actually tell me it's dangerous
when I'm his son?
I'm easy to read either way, right?
How dangerous is it?
Assuming that the average score is 50,
is it around 60 to 70 points?
It's over 90.
I see.
But with that said, it doesn't mean
anything will happen for sure.
As a bodyguard,
your father is highly experienced
and highly skilled.
You don't have to cheer me up.
If he dies, I'll just go to Mom.
See you.
Shun!
My apologies
if I had to conceal you there.
We can be tracked using the N System
if we use the expressway,
so I'm opting
for the public highways instead.
HANDLE WITH CARE
PRECISION MACHINERY
I came to Japan
and made my company grow so big,
and to think that
I have to escape in such a small box…
Life is truly interesting.
Please bear with it a little longer.
By the way, what happened to Takanashi?
Talk to me to kill some time.
He resigned.
Was it because of my request?
I should have released him sooner.
He's still young.
Instead of doing small jobs with me,
he should be pursuing
that bright future ahead of him.
I should be impressed by your friendship,
but it's useless.
I know that when humans
get in contact with one another,
all they want is to benefit themselves.
And that is the reason why
I made use of people.
-Dr. Kasamatsu?
-Yes?
A patient insists
on having a consultation with you.
Since it's outside your duty hours,
should I just reject him?
The person's name is Shimazaki.
What? Now?
I see.
What's the matter?
Dr. Kasamatsu,
what do you think about my dad?
What?
I'm sorry to ask
something so strange suddenly.
But I want to hear the answer now.
Let's see…
Well…
He's passionate about his job
and is a good father.
No, I don't mean as a father!
Do you like him? Or is he not your type?
Hey, Shun! What's the matter?
I'll put this straight.
My dad is on a dangerous job now.
He might die.
If you like my dad,
maybe you should stop him.
That's all I wanted to say.
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
The number you are trying to reach
is unavailable…
He said he'll help us.
Takanashi, I mean.
Someone from Shimazaki Security will help?
I can no longer follow
Shimazaki's beliefs.
That guy…
Do you know if he's with President Ryu?
I resigned because we were conflicted
over President Ryu's request.
-Conflict?
-Do you know where they are now?
No.
But both Shimazaki and President Ryu
are the worst.
They bring shame upon our occupation.
The police predict that President Ryu
will be escaping overseas,
so they have stationed forces
at both Narita and Haneda Airports.
They are also conducting
inspection checks in Shizuoka.
FUJIGAWA
What do you think?
There are some airports in Shizuoka.
I've used those a few times
while I was still with the SDF.
These are airports that can accommodate
small planes for private use.
It sounds like something
the president would use.
All right.
-Gather all available personnel now!
-Please wait.
You're dealing with Akira Shimazaki.
Even if you outnumber him,
he still knows what you're planning.
If so…
Are you going to track him,
even though he's your friend?
That's in the past.
I'm borrowing a wireless transmitter.
Takanashi.
If you find both of them,
contact me first.
There are people within the police
that cannot be trusted.
In order to protect the company,
I'll hand them over to someone reliable.
Got it?
NEW MESSAGE
NAGIKO TSUNODA
NAGIKO: ARE YOU OKAY? I SAW THE NEWS.
SEI: YES. WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NAGIKO: DO WHAT YOU HAVE TO.
OKITSU
It's a police checkpoint.
They must have realized that
you might be heading for Suruga Airfield.
Japanese police are quick to think.
Are they tracing your GPS?
3 MISSED CALLS
DR. KASAMATSU
LOCATION SERVICES: OFF
Please relax.
I've already turned off mine.
I don't intend
to start a car chase with this vehicle.
Hey! Stop!
Turn around!
Please stop!
STOP
-Good work.
-Your license, please.
Sure.
May I know your occupation?
Oh, I have a delivery company
called Shimazaki Transport.
I'm currently on a delivery,
but I kind of lost my way
and I'm not sure where to go, so…
Could you let us
check the contents of your delivery?
Sure.
These are combustible products
with their inspection reports,
as well as some medical supplies.
They are rather bulky.
These, well…
It's medical machinery.
Could you let us check the contents?
No, I was told that this kind of machinery
is extremely sensitive
to conditions like tremors,
so I'm not allowed to open it.
It's true, I'm telling you!
This scary doctor warned me
countless times.
Wait, just take a look at this.
Here, I'll show you the number.
She's Dr. Kasamatsu,
a surgeon from Shiroyama General Hospital.
What? From the police?
Hello? This is Dr. Kasamatsu.
This is Ogawa, a police officer
conducting an inspection at Shizuoka.
Did you request Shimazaki Transport
to deliver some medical machinery?
Oh, right!
Shimazaki Transport, right?
Yes, I did.
Is it true that it's a precision machine
that cannot be opened?
Oh, I see…
It's a large precision machine, right?
I need that for an experiment.
If it's damaged,
it'll cost a few hundred million.
-Thank you, that's enough.
-Oh, please excuse me!
Hello? Good work today.
-Hello--
-Sorry to bother you, Dr. Kasamatsu.
-Hey, where are you--
-Okay, I'll deliver it safely. Yes.
-What?
-Sorry, I was held up at the inspection.
-Where are you--
-Got it. Please excuse me.
I'm closing the trunk.
It's safe now.
From my experiences in Hinode Security,
you're being watched by the police
as well as private security.
It's only a matter of time
before you get exposed.
-That was a mistake.
-Sorry.
We're abandoning this vehicle.
Suruga Airfield is just
at the other end of that tunnel.
-Let's hurry.
-Wait.
Maybe it's because
I've been cramped inside for a long time,
but I can't move my legs.
Please hold on to me.
DEAD END FOR WHEELED VEHICLES
To think that my last memory in Japan
would be of you protecting me…
It's too late to regret that.
I never regret what I do.
Money never smiles upon
those who look back after all.
It's just that…
there's something
I haven't accomplished yet.
That is, I failed to woo Mayu Suganuma.
You can report me for sexual harassment.
I won't.
SAFETY FIRST
God shows his love upon the virtuous…
but you and I…
we're nothing but pathetic beings
abandoned by God.
After this job is completed,
you should go play with a woman.
I have a woman I like.
Is that so?
Sorry about that.
She's an unpretentious and honest woman.
Please get behind me.
Please run!
The police are right behind us.
You guys won't escape.
The same goes for you too.
Pardon me.
No, it's fine.
President Ryu!
Please go to the police with me.
You should reveal the truth.
I'm not going to the police.
If you run away…
What will happen to Kicks Corp.
if you run away?
At the very least,
the bodyguards won't get paid.
You might be able
to set up another company.
But what about the bodyguards?
They'll lose their jobs!
This "business" you speak of,
is this how it works?
-Shimazaki.
-Yes.
Get rid of him.
This is an order from your client.
Hey…
That hurts. What the hell--
What is with you?
What?
President.
Let's silence him.
Hey…
Has Takanashi contacted you?
I've called him a number of times…
I knew it was a bad idea to trust him!
Wait, we still don't know
if he betrayed us. Please don't panic!
We have to find them before the police,
no matter what!
I CAN'T TELL ANYONE.
I TOOK TAKANASHI'S LIFE.
EVERYONE WON'T FORGIVE ME.
PREPARE HIM A FUNERAL.
SING A SONG THAT HE LIKED. RYU.
I TOOK TAKANASHI'S LIFE.
Suganuma knows something.
Sawaguchi.
You always look at the bigger picture.
You know what you should do, right?
Please wait.
Please keep your body low.
Let's split up!
92-18…
92-18… There you are.
2 MISSED CALLS
DR. KASAMATSU
SPARKS CAR SHARING
RESERVATION DETAILS
Hello?
What was that call just now?
You used me,
and you're not going to explain yourself?
I'm sorry. I'm in the middle of work, so…
I'll apologize to you on another day.
Let's have proper sushi next time,
not conveyor belt ones.
Shun came over.
-He asked if I liked you.
-What?
What is that kid doing skipping classes?
Wait, don't get mad.
He told me that you're on a dangerous job,
and that I should stop you if I like you.
I guess I couldn't give him
a proper answer.
Well, that's a given.
I'm sorry. Really.
Shimazaki…
don't be reckless.
I have the right to say this.
Losing your life while working…
is just the worst.
I apologize
if I'm getting ahead of myself.
It's more important
to have sushi with a girl you like,
rather than prioritize your job.
You aren't getting ahead of yourself.
Thanks.
I gained a lot of courage from that.
Wait, I didn't say that
to boost your courage!
That courage won't help with anything!
But for me right now…
it's extremely important.
You're way too bad with tailing!
I know that
you've been following me by car.
It was deliberate.
I didn't want to use
any underhanded means.
And in that sense, you've matured.
What's this?
This must be a lie.
There's no way that Takanashi is dead.
I can't accept the fact if I'm alone.
Would you come with me?
The coordinates point to this area, but…
You were really rough…
Shimazaki.
That's what I usually do, President.
Enough with this.
If you guys hadn't come,
I would've been in deep trouble.
This.
The first character of each line
says "dummy,"
meaning a decoy.
We used this back in Hinode Security
when we were protecting a popular singer.
It's a code we use.
Just what in the world is happening?
Shimazaki.
Get rid of him.
Hey.
Don't fall, okay?
President.
Let's silence him.
You'll switch with Takanashi.
Please leave this place.
I've requested Suganuma to assist us.
How considerate of him
to arrange a last meeting with you.
As expected of him.
Bodyguards are indeed
in the service industry.
I…
didn't want to meet you in this manner.
Don't say that.
These words, at the very least,
I wanted to say them myself.
I'll be leaving Japan.
If everything goes well,
I'll probably never return.
Take me to the location
Shimazaki has prepared.
Is that…
an order?
Yes.
What else could it be?
SURUGA AIRFIELD
OFF LIMITS
SHIZUOKA CITY, SHIZUOKA PREFECTURE
SURUGA AIRFIELD, SHIMIZU WARD
Sorry for all the trouble.
We have 20 minutes
until the aircraft arrives.
I'm sure the police must have
their sights set on this place too.
We'll keep watch to the very end
and escort you to the plane
immediately when it arrives.
-I'm counting on you.
-Pardon me.
Are you really going to do this?
Me too.
I just happened to come along,
but I can't accept it.
Are you really going to escape, President?
The President promised
to reveal the truth behind the data leak
once he returns to Los Angeles.
Are you stupid?
I don't believe that
President Ryu will reveal it willingly.
He swore to do that,
and that's why I accepted his request.
He's not someone you can trust.
I'm leaving.
Takanashi.
You should leave too
if you don't agree with it.
Takanashi.
You wanted to ask me, right?
The reason I get so serious
about being a bodyguard.
Probably…
because this job questions
whether I can trust another person or not.
I mean, we meet
different clients every time,
and we do our best to believe in them,
no matter if we like it or not.
Even if…
that person could be our enemy.
To believe and protect them…
By protecting our clients,
we protect their future.
Isn't that what our job means?
Though I still don't really know.
But if he betrays our trust,
we would be covering for a criminal!
This is just reckless.
He has lost his trust in bodyguards.
If this backfires,
we may be forced to resign.
You trust everyone so easily.
Aren't you the one underestimating
our job, Shimazaki?
It seems like
you're at a disadvantage, Shimazaki.
So you'll trust someone if they're serious
and have a good reputation?
You'll trust someone
if they're nice and kind to you?
if they've never done anything wrong?
We never know if they're lying or not.
That's why we have
no choice but to trust them!
Otherwise…
we won't be able to
protect them with our lives.
Shall we leave it at that?
Can I change my request?
I won't run away.
I'm changing my destination.
That is,
if all of you are willing to find out
if I'm a person
that can be trusted or not.
I will follow my client's orders.
Shimazaki will be the BG,
and Takanashi will be the backup.
We will take the lead,
and Sawaguchi will do a route check.
Suganuma,
you're on standby at the destination.
-Understood.
Check your transmitters.
Be on alert. Please communicate in secret.
We'll be leaving
the onsite decision-making to you.
It's been a while.
The estimated time
is 4 hours and 30 minutes from now.
The current time is 3:40 p.m.
-Synchronized.
I wish us all success.
-Yes.
What? You lost them?
I caught up with their car when they broke
their way through the police checkpoint
and I went ahead to cut them off,
but they never showed up at the airfield.
I'm also sorry
for leaving a scratch on your car.
-What about Takanashi and Suganuma?
-I don't know.
It's possible that they pretended
to head toward Suruga Airfield
-but went somewhere else instead.
-Find them immediately!
I'm very sorry!
I entrusted that task to him.
How could you trust your subordinate?
This was the reason you couldn't
go up the ranks back in the police force.
I will not let things end like this.
I have my own pride too.
We've arrived, President.
-Good work.
-I'll check on the situation.
This is 02, to 03. What's the situation?
This is 03.
There's no one stationed
around the rear car park.
Only Chief Omata's company vehicle
is parked here.
This is 04.
I'm on the lookout near the courtyard.
It seems like there is no one
watching over or patrolling the area.
This is 02. Acknowledged.
Assemblyman Kuwata is at home.
There are two police officers
at the entrance.
I believe he has been inside
ever since the assault incident.
I see.
President, will you enter from the rear,
or from the front?
What would you choose if it was you?
If you're prepared
to meet the police later,
it would be wiser to take the front.
I would take the rear.
No matter what place, it's always easier
to enter from the rear entrance.
That is what I learned in life.
However,
we must always be aggressive
when it comes to business.
You better pray.
Everything's fine here.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
What's wrong with your neck?
My neighbor's cat scratched my neck.
Is Assemblyman Kuwata at home?
What?
Shimazaki is…
Assemblyman, sorry for approaching you
without an appointment.
I happen to be with that person,
so I was wondering if we could meet you.
I see.
I was thinking
of having a talk with him too.
Please wait at the nearby car park.
Someone will show you the way
after five minutes.
Please let the police know
that private security is sufficient
and tell them to go back.
Also…
This is 02. We'll be entering.
To achieve his own objectives,
that man thinks of
other people's lives as nothing.
I understand that
because I'm similar to him.
But Assemblyman Kuwata…
says that he would like to meet you.
Let's proceed.
Please.
Gunshots heard coming from eleven o'clock.
It's not the police.
So the front gate
wasn't open to me after all.
-Please wait here.
-What are you planning to do?
He's back, right? Let me talk to him.
He's an ex-police officer.
He's familiar with firearms.
-I'll go.
-I'll go!
You have Shun to think about.
-Dr. Kasamatsu too--
-You have Suganuma too!
She's already…
No. She always…
had you in her heart, Takanashi.
Shimazaki.
You should go.
-You'll put your life on the line, right?
-Please wait!
I've been thinking about this.
Why did you ask Shimazaki to protect you?
Don't tell me your motive
is to expose him to danger!
You're wrong.
That's because…
I believe in Shimazaki too.
-Protect him.
-Shimazaki!
Hey, can we talk for a bit?
Haven't we known each other long enough?
He fell for it all right.
I heard that…
you were quite the passionate person
back in the SP, Kato.
I don't know what happened to you
when you were with the police,
but don't do anything
that goes against your own feelings.
Let us pass.
I'm begging you, Kato.
Don't call me by that name!
What are you waiting for?
I know! I'm a former police officer!
Takanashi!
This is 02. We're heading in!
We…
couldn't win against
the unarmed guys, even in the end.
Excuse us.
Please go ahead.
Why did you come back here?
It's a little late, but…
I wanted someone
to place their trust in me.
The crime that you and I committed
is stored right here.
I will be turning myself in to the police.
Won't you come with me, Assemblyman?
Or rather…
the fact that
I'm standing here and talking with you…
proves that you've lost.
Do you know what you're saying?
This is going
to implicate the Prime Minister!
Assemblyman.
You're not seeing anything.
Allow me to warn you…
as a friend.
-Shimazaki?
-Shimazaki!
Are you all right?
I'll call for an ambulance!
Hey, Shimazaki!
-This is an emergency.
-I'm fine.
-I'm at Setagaya…
-Shimazaki?
-Shimazaki!
-…Akira Shimazaki.
-Isn't it cold here?
It's likely that he collapsed
-due to a gunshot wound on his leg.
-Shimazaki!
Shimazaki!
Hey! Akira Shimazaki!
-Hey!
-Please hold on!
-We're entering the room now.
-Yes.
Oh, you came?
-Mr. Takanashi called me.
-I see.
What the heck?
Your complexion looks way too good.
The bullet…
kind of went through my leg, so there was
no need for serious surgery or anything.
You had serious surgery, you know?
A gunshot wound to your left thigh…
If the wound was just off by 1cm,
you might have suffered
from major blood loss.
Please give him a good scolding!
Sure, leave it to me.
Also…
please take care of him forever,
if you can,
Dr. Kasamatsu.
See you.
Sorry.
Once I'm discharged,
let's have sushi, not conveyor belt ones.
I'm fine with conveyor belt sushi.
Isn't that good enough for us?
I'm saying that
we don't need further progress.
You're angry, right?
I've come to understand…
that I'll never be able to tie down
a man like you.
Do whatever you want.
But…
make sure you don't die.
Got it.
The police questioning
is going to be troublesome later.
Oh, that goes for you too, Dr. Kasamatsu.
I'm sorry about that.
Seriously…
-What? No way!
-You're so troublesome.
That hurts!
Hey…
Yesterday, Special Aide Takashi Kuwata
of the Civil Party turned himself in,
and after police interrogation,
has admitted to all his crimes,
including the assault
during his press conference,
as well as the misuse of political funds.
This morning, he submitted
a letter of resignation--
The suspect behind Assemblyman Kuwata's
assault during his press conference
has been arrested
and identified as Kazuma Kato,
a former officer
in the MPD's Security Police Division.
He is also suspected
of being involved in an assault incident
during Assemblyman Kuwata's
20th anniversary…
Oh, you're here.
Have you seen it?
Seen what?
As a way of atoning for my sins,
I wish to further my business
based on this entire experience.
As I got myself involved
in the security industry,
I learned that there are bodyguards
who will risk their lives
to protect their clients.
Knowing that people like them exist…
was an invaluable experience for me.
Well…
I guess that's part of their job,
but I hope to thank them
personally someday.
Thank us now.
And in person too.
Oh, and Sawaguchi
already transferred the money to you.
-Oh, for Ms. Tsunoda's case?
-Yes.
It seems like Sawaguchi and Suganuma
will be staying in Kicks Guard,
but the company owner will be changed.
Omata managed to get himself a job
in another security company too.
I see. What about you?
It has nothing to do with you.
I guess so, right?
This is Junction Café!
-Did you order something?
-I didn't.
We didn't order anything.
I quit my job,
so here's a farewell present.
You quit?
Weren't you betting your entire life
on opening up a café?
It's hard to make a living
as a freelancer during these times.
I'm looking to find work
in a listed company.
-You change really fast.
-I had no choice.
My girlfriend said she would break up
with me if I didn't have a stable income.
Thanks for everything. Take care!
So that's how youngsters
in the Reiwa era are.
Scary, indeed.
Testing.
All good here.
I'm staying here.
Oh, you have no right to refuse,
by the way.
All this talk about "rights" again…
Copy.
Let's expand our work scope
from here on out.
We could cooperate with big companies
and that could give us
more possibilities too.
And you're suddenly giving orders
like you're some big shot here?
That Reiwa-era youngster mentioned it.
I would need a stable income
to settle down.
Hey, wait. Really? With whom?
-Suganuma?
-Wait…
-It hasn't been decided--
-That's great! Congratulations!
-Congr--
-It hasn't been decided yet.
Well, it's just my imagination as usual.
Imagination? That's sad.
In any case…
this is the situation I'm in.
And that's precisely why
I should be able to work
by being useful to others.
Your reply?
-This is 01. Synchronized.
-Synchronized.
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
The pizza's just sitting out here,
it's unsanitary.
NEW MESSAGE
RE: BODYGUARD REQUEST
I will check the positions
for today's assignment.
-Bodyguard is 01, Sawaguchi.
-Yes.
Backup is 02, Suganuma.
-Side is 03, Kawazu.
-Yes.
-04, Shirai.
B1 will proceed first
and check the interior of the building.
Yes.
And as additional support,
we will be cooperating
with Shimazaki Security this time.
Please guide us.
-We'll do our best not to get in the way.
-Same here.
It's almost time.
-Well then, I'm counting on everyone.
-Understood.
We will be in charge
of your personal security today.
-I look forward to working with you.
-Pleased to meet you.
-We're in position.
-Understood.
We'll lead the way.
This is 01.
Mr. Ichikawa has entered the main hall.
Congratulations!
Team C will switch with B2.
Please move to the rear entrance
and proceed with your security duties.
Understood.
THE WORLD CHANGES DRASTICALLY OVERNIGHT.
THOSE WHO CAN STAND UP TO IT
ARE PROFESSIONALS WITH THE RIGHT SKILLS.
THE NEED FOR PROTECTORS HAS ARRIVED.
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu