Why are you a bodyguard?
WAIHA BEER
What?
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
HINODE PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
There's no reason to do a job
where you could get killed.
You know, you're right.
You're not even listening.
GORO MURATA: ASSEMBLE IMMEDIATELY.
WE HAVE AN URGENT JOB.
Now?
Next week on Music King...
WAIHA BEER
I have an urgent job. Bye.
Quit playing with that phone.
Lock the door.
Take a bath.
You haven't had one for two days.
You'll never get girls that way.
I don't want to be that popular.
Cheerfully full-bodied.
Delightfully smooth.
It's Kanon! She's so hot!
Waiha!
Sorry to call you here so late at night.
-Good evening.
I was out with a woman.
I just got a beer out of the fridge.
That's the worst.
We'll get late-night pay, right?
GORO MURATA
MANAGER, PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
Your first concern is money?
There he is.
What? He really did come back?
Yes. He's returning to us for this job.
The manager said he needs my experience.
That's why I said okay.
That's good.
I wanted to work with you.
I mean, for the marathon job
we had the other day,
he ran away at the last minute.
-What?
-That was a shock.
Now, now!
As bodyguards, we have to work together.
Also, to build a good team,
you need to be able to disagree.
Let's all get along, okay?
Now, for the assignment.
If you have a single sip...
No way!
-...it's a taste of the tropics.
-That's Kanon!
-Waiha!
-I'll do it!
I mean, I'll take the job.
Why now? You usually avoid work.
I can't let this one go.
I'm a huge fan of hers!
I'll do anything. Be her gofer.
Carry her bags.
I'll guard her with my life!
Sawaguchi, I hate to break the news,
but we're not guarding her.
What?
This time, we'll be guarding...
one hundred million yen.
NEW PRODUCT!
WAIHA BEER
Can you give us more details?
It's Kanon's bonus.
Oh, really? One hundred million yen?
Out of the blue,
she said she was quitting.
I reminded her that she was still bound
to her contract, but then she vanished.
Anyway, have a seat.
Thank you.
She left without a word?
It's so pitiful.
I worked so hard to get her this far.
I can't let her miss work,
so I did my best to contact her.
Then she goes and says,
"Boss, if you bring me 100 million yen,
then I'll come back."
Waiha!
So you're doing as she says?
A hundred million is a fortune.
I hired bodyguards
exactly because it's a fortune.
I wouldn't normally walk around
with 100 million, you know?
Is there a special reason
you're doing this?
The day after tomorrow,
there's an announcement
for a movie project.
She has a coveted leading role.
THE SONATA OF MEMORIES
I have to get her back
by tomorrow by all means.
Understood, sir.
We'll take responsibility
for protecting this money
and make sure it gets to her.
Let me introduce myself. I'm Takanashi.
I'm Shimazaki.
I'm experienced with carrying cash.
Don't you worry.
I'll handcuff the bag to your wrist.
Excuse me.
HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES 2ND CONGRESS
YOSHIAKI OCHIAI
SECURITY BUREAU (SP)
Madam, why did you do this?
There's no need to get so angry.
You left your home
without telling your security, right?
Yes. I had a personal errand,
so I didn't want to bother them.
What?
Did you want to make me look bad
so I would get fired?
Is that why you disappeared
at the marathon too?
AIKO TACHIHARA
HEALTH, LABOR, AND WELFARE MINISTER
Don't be silly.
You're doing a great job, Kiyota.
In fact, it's almost too great.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
But could you please
step out for a moment?
I need to properly apologize to Ochiai.
Certainly.
I think you can see
why I can't trust Kiyota.
I'm terribly sorry.
His sense of duty is so strong
that his emotions often show through.
I'll warn him about that.
Ochiai...
I don't need your protection anymore.
As you may have guessed,
I'm in a perilous position
as a politician.
I've always been in perilous positions,
but this one is for real.
It exacts a toll when I don't get along
with the 24-hour security guards.
I've requested security
from a private security company.
-Private security?
-Yes.
You know Shimazaki, the bodyguard I met
at the Sumida River Marathon.
I spoke to him directly.
He agreed and said he would be glad to.
That's insane.
He's barely an experienced security guard.
He can't protect important people unarmed.
Your subordinate didn't even notice
that I had left.
He sounds much more inept.
Politicians are reclusive.
Particularly lady politicians.
SP are too haughty
and proclaim their duty is to the country.
A private company can provide
much more sensitive security.
What I need right now is
more caring security.
Yes, sir.
We're on the Central Circular Route
crossing the Shiomi Bridge.
When will you arrive at the destination?
Since we don't know our destination,
I don't know.
You don't know your destination?
We'll be contacting her
when we arrive in Hachioji.
I'll inform you when we find out.
Roger.
I wonder what this is all about.
What? Are those two already fighting?
Why did you pair them?
Well, because I think
they make a good pair.
How come? They don't get along at all!
Hold on.
What bothers me aren't those two.
It's the fact that
the destination isn't clear.
They're carrying 100 million yen,
so doesn't it seem odd?
Yes, it does seem odd.
Kanon would never greedily demand
100 million yen like this!
You're just a fan. What would you know?
I mean, look at her interviews.
"It's not money that I want."
"I want to be loved and be a good wife."
She always says so.
You must be stupid.
That's how she sells herself!
She's not selling herself!
She's not a product!
Forget it! Get back to work!
You don't know anything about Kanon!
Sir, we've pulled off
at North Hachioji Interchange.
Please keep on driving around
until Kanon calls me.
I thought you were going to call
once we got closer.
No, I'm waiting for her to call.
What?
Excuse us for a moment.
-Let's drop this job.
-Why?
Maybe you haven't noticed,
but he's hiding something.
It's dangerous to transport money
when we can't trust him.
But we've already taken the job.
It would be irresponsible to drop it now.
Why are you talking in secret?
-We're talking about your security.
-Sir.
Why does it have to be cash?
You could give Kanon a check
or wire her the money.
Giving her cash is dangerous,
so why would you do it?
Well...
there's a tax issue...
and I don't want Kanon to change her mind.
So I'll offer her a stack of cash
she can use right away.
I've always worked like this.
I see. So that's why it's all used bills.
If you withdrew 100 million yen
from a bank, they'd give you new bills.
But it's all in used bills.
It does feel immediately spendable.
Yes, that's right.
The entertainment business runs on cash.
KANON
Yes, it's me, Bando.
Where are you now?
Nakase Bridge Park.
You haven't told the police, have you?
Of course, I haven't.
How prudent.
Go to the Tama Shopping Mall
event area in 20 minutes.
Let's go to the Tama Shopping Mall.
Sir!
I apologize if I'm wrong, but...
has Kanon been kidnapped...
The kidnapper called me
yesterday at 12 noon.
"I have Kanon.
I'll return her without a scratch
if you pay 100 million yen."
"Return"?
I'll notify the police.
No! Don't!
He said he'd kill Kanon
if I tell the police.
A kidnapping?
The 100 million yen is the ransom.
What about the police?
Mr. Bando has requested
that we don't tell them.
I think we need to notify them right away.
We should request
immediate assistance from the local MPD.
I'll notify them.
Don't! Don't you dare tell the police!
I hired bodyguards
because I can't tell the police!
Manager, can you please give us some time?
I'll speak to Mr. Bando.
We should probably inform
the police, but...
Shimazaki told you
not to tell the police, didn't he?
If we tell them secretly,
we'll betray him.
I have important information
regarding Asami Yukinaga.
I'll wait for only 30 minutes.
Contact me immediately after that.
A kidnapping...
Will Kanon be killed?
Wouldn't it be best to notify the police?
I'm leaving it in their hands for now.
Let's prepare to notify them immediately
if we need to.
-Prepare the documents.
-Yes, sir.
Don't just look like a man. Man up!
I'll check her social networking accounts.
I may find a clue.
Hurry up and drive.
We need to be there by 10:00 a.m.
Please relax, sir.
It's five minutes to the mall.
There's still time to notify the police.
How many times do I have to tell you?
If you ignore the kidnapper's demands,
Kanon will...
You're the one who'll regret it
if the worst happens.
If the public finds out
that Kanon has been kidnapped...
it'll harm her image.
It'll end her career as an entertainer!
What's more important?
Her life or her value as an entertainer?
Her life, of course.
Kanon is my treasure.
But she dreamed of being a star
and has worked hard.
I made her give up on romance.
She has probably lost friends too.
She sacrificed a lot to make it this far.
Just saving her life isn't enough!
Please!
It's my duty to help her
achieve her dream!
Let's go to the mall.
It's Mr. Bando's orders.
It has already been 20 hours
since the kidnapping occurred.
Statistically, they're likely dead
24 hours after being kidnapped.
That's why I'm doing this.
Mr. Bando doesn't want
to cooperate with the police.
If we inform them,
it'll cause confusion and eat up time.
We're going.
They have 18 more minutes.
No, 19 minutes.
Manager, is it okay to keep silent
about the kidnapping?
No.
In the worst case, we could lose
our security business license.
-Hurry up!
-I know. I'm on it.
SECURITY POLICE
HINODE SECURITY SERVICE
Ochiai, I'm sure you know that
I won't tolerate
Minister Tachihara's antics.
I can't let her make a fool
of the SP again.
Maintain the same level of readiness.
And don't replace Kiyota.
But compatibility is important.
To achieve proper security,
we should accept some of her requests.
That's unlike you.
You sound like a civilian.
Hello?
Bando here.
You lied, Mr. Bando.
What?
You promised not to tell the police.
I haven't told them.
Then who are those two with you?
They're...
managers who work at my agency.
I have a weak heart,
so I had them come with me to
make sure the money was delivered.
Please believe me!
Then bring the bag and your phone to
the coffee stand at the mall's event area.
Sir.
Hello, this is one of
the managers speaking.
Now then, about the money,
if it's stolen, then we'll have nothing.
So would it be possible if
we accompanied him with the money?
Sure, Mr. Manager.
Don't look too mean. We're managers.
I thought people in show business
looked mean.
Sir, is it true that
you have a weak heart?
Yes, it's a chronic disease.
I almost died a few years ago.
Hello, Bando here.
Keep going south,
then climb the stairs to the fourth floor.
Kanon is unharmed, isn't she?
Just a little farther.
Shall I carry the bag?
No, I'll take care of it.
Are you okay?
I'm doing this for Kanon.
It's all right. Let's get a new one.
No! I want this one!
-Get out of my way!
-I'm sorry.
Who do you think you are?
Don't! We're managers!
-I'm sorry.
-You better be.
I'm sorry.
That was close.
Hello?
You were lying.
Judging from their moves,
they must be police.
They're not policemen.
I'm through negotiating.
Hold on! Wait!
Excuse me. Hello? Hold on a moment!
I'm sorry, but we're bodyguards.
We're not policemen.
That's an obvious lie.
Don't try to fool me.
I'm not lying.
If you're nearby, look around.
There's nobody besides us, right?
If we were the police,
there would be more of us.
Then prove it.
Run back down to the event area.
What?
I'm leaving for a moment. Hello?
Less than five minutes left.
I got through!
It's Kanon's secret account.
KANON (SUB-ACCOUNT)
Hello?
You don't see anyone that
looks like police anywhere, do you?
Okay, take off your jacket right there.
What?
If you're a cop,
you'll have a gun and a badge.
Raise your arms.
Good. Turn around to the right.
Hello? I don't have any weapons,
let alone a gun.
Or would you like me to strip naked?
I'll be waiting at Akirano Bridge
in one hour.
Wait! Let me talk to Kanon!
Mr. Bando says he won't give you the money
unless he knows Kanon is safe.
Hello?
-Hello.
-Hello?
This is Shimazaki. I'm a bodyguard.
Are you unharmed, Ms. Kanon?
Yes, but if you tell the police,
I'll really be killed.
Please. Do what he says.
If he has the money, I can return.
-What about Kanon?
-She's okay.
She spoke clearly, but...
But what?
Well...
Excuse me.
It has been 30 minutes.
I'm notifying the police, all right?
Hold on a minute.
This might be a fake kidnapping.
A fake kidnapping?
I just spoke to Kanon on the phone.
She said, "Please. Do what he says.
If he has the money, I can return."
Usually, wouldn't you say,
"If Mr. Bando pays"?
Also, would you just say "he"
when talking about the kidnapper?
Do you think she's working
with the kidnapper?
I can't be certain.
I found an odd post on her secret account.
A few hours before her kidnapping,
she told a friend that
she wouldn't do the movie.
Send a screenshot.
We'll send a screenshot
to Takanashi's phone.
Please check it.
SENDING EMAIL...
CONGRATS ON THE MOVIE!
YOU'LL BE A MOVIE STAR NEXT YEAR!
I DOUBT THAT.
DON'T BE SO HUMBLE. IT DOESN'T SUIT YOU.
"My real dream will come true."
It's that jerk.
Kanon used to date a hoodlum
from her hometown.
He's a lowlife.
Last year, she said she would marry him.
So I paid him off to get rid of him
and broke them up.
But she loves that cheap ring
that jerk gave her.
It always bothered me.
Do you know his name?
Nonomura.
Shoichi Nonomura,
a guy from her middle school.
I slept really well.
I'm thirsty.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Investigate Shoichi Nonomura.
Now it's a fake kidnapping?
I can't deal with this!
Man up, would you?
You want some lowlife to get her?
I'm going to the Investigation Department.
I won't let you have Kanon!
This is a good thing.
If it's a fake kidnapping,
we won't lose
our security company license.
No either way, we've failed
to inform them about illegal activity.
Excuse me.
Already?
What is it?
I've forgotten his name,
but where is the man
who failed to inform the police
the other day?
Oh, that would be Shimazaki.
He's out on a job.
I heard something I can't believe
from Minister Tachihara.
She asked Shimazaki to be her bodyguard,
and this Personal Security Division
supposedly accepted.
Excuse me?
I'm speaking for the SP.
A private company cannot protect
a cabinet minister.
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
I haven't heard anything
from Minister Tachihara or Shimazaki.
There's no reason to hide it.
I'm not so bold as to lie to the SP.
Maybe it's the Minister who's lying.
It's not easy to tell
when a woman is lying.
I found something out!
This guy is bad news!
INVESTIGATION REPORT
This is info about Shoichi Nonomura.
The used clothing store he ran in Machida
went bankrupt last October.
He has a mountain of debt.
Debt?
To a friend on a social networking site,
he said, "I won't 'jump' anymore."
They call it "jumping" when
you only pay the interest on a loan.
This means he plans to
pay off the whole loan.
I knew it. He's behind this.
Dang it!
I'm not paying!
I've been played like a fool.
I only want to take Kanon back!
I discovered her
when she was a total hoodlum,
polished her, and brought her this far.
She couldn't cry on cue.
She was criticized as a lousy actor.
I got on my knees and begged.
I spent all kinds of money.
I sold her with all my might.
Then she goes and kicks sand in my face!
Sir!
Don't stop me!
You're putting stress on your heart.
Calm down.
Darn it!
We did it!
With 100 million, you can pay off
your debt, and we can start a new life.
That's right. I'll always treat you well.
My dream is to live a normal life
with my precious Sho.
Kanon.
Hello?
Bando here.
Bring the money
to the middle of the bridge.
When will you return Kanon?
I'll return her when I receive the money.
I don't have the energy,
so I'll have the bodyguards bring it.
That's fine with me.
However, only one of them.
I don't care which of you does it.
Take this,
and bring back Kanon.
Bring her back with fake money?
That's one heck of a request.
You're a bodyguard, right?
Aren't you supposed to obey
the client's orders?
Certainly. I'll go.
I'm the BG.
The BG's duty is to protect
Mr. Bando and the 100 million yen.
Be careful.
I think the punk we ran into
at the mall...
is an accomplice.
We agree. How unusual.
I thought so too.
-Synchronized.
-Synchronized. Excuse me.
Chief, I looked up
the Hinode vehicle on the N System.
It drove toward Hachioji
early this morning.
-Hachioji?
-Is something bothering you?
No.
Give the local police the plate number
just in case.
-Tell them to be on the lookout.
-Yes, sir.
Just as we planned,
I'll be traded for the money and return.
I'll tell them I was blindfolded
so I didn't see the kidnapper's face,
and the shock was so big
that I can't work,
and I'll quit the agency.
Are you listening?
Put the 100 million away.
Don't you dare use it.
Of course.
That's the money that will make us happy.
Thank you.
How much longer will you keep up this act?
Who are you?
You don't have to quit.
You should keep earning money.
What are you talking about?
Sho!
You mean...
you used me to get the money?
You must be kidding!
You said you loved me!
Right?
Listen up!
Do you think I could love some woman
that shows off her flesh on stage?
You're so awful.
-Wait!
-Hey!
-Hold it!
-Let go of me!
Cut it out!
If you tell the cops...
I'll post this.
You'll never be an entertainer again.
I've brought what we promised!
Give Kanon back!
Excuse me!
I'm afraid of heights!
Hurry this up, please!
She's unharmed.
Put it down...
and step back.
I'm supposed to trade you in
for the money.
I'll return after I check it.
I'll go to you.
I can't do that.
Please.
Please! Do as I say!
We know everything.
If you come back now,
Mr. Bando will forgive you.
Come here.
I told you to step back!
What's wrong?
I think the fake just turned real.
Hey!
What did you say? Bring her back now!
Roger.
What do you plan to do?
What the heck is that guy doing?
Hurry up and do it!
All right.
I'll put it here.
I'm stepping back.
Holy cow!
I said I was afraid of heights!
If you're an actress,
don't you think you should learn
to act a little better?
I'll be fine.
Oh, no! The money!
We should go!
If he falls, we'll lose 100 million!
Let's go!
Hey!
You must be kidding!
-That hurts!
-I'll kill you if you fall!
If I fall, I'll be dead anyway!
That hurts!
I can't hold on!
My 100 million!
-Let's go!
-Wait right there!
I'll post...
these photos!
Let's go.
Help me.
I have a new assignment.
Run away.
Hey!
Wait!
Sir!
Is your heart all right?
My heart is fine!
I just wanted sympathy from the kidnapper.
Out of the way!
If they find me with all this money,
they'll find out about everything!
What do you think you're doing? Let go!
Let go!
I've had it. Tell us what happened.
Are you both going
to keep silent together?
METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
Quit fooling around!
You'll be in trouble if you keep silent.
You're nothing more than private security.
If someone got injured, what...
How dare you yawn!
If someone got injured,
what would you do to make up for it?
-Good question.
-Don't talk back like that!
You were exploited by a fake kidnapping?
I'm sorry.
I asked the bodyguards not to tell anyone.
It was to protect her image.
But you know, we arrested Nonomura,
and he says she was in on it.
She is a naive girl
and knows nothing of the world.
That's why she was duped by that man.
Isn't that right?
Yes. I'm sorry.
I thought it was a candid camera prank.
I didn't know that
I was being used for a crime.
Well, if that's the case,
it can't be helped, can it?
Kanon and Mr. Bando have been released.
I see.
They were given a severe warning.
Since the money is safe
and nobody was hurt,
the police won't publicize it.
And well, thank you for protecting Kanon!
Why are you thanking them?
Sorry.
Thank you very, very much.
I respect you. Goodbye.
-Here.
-Okay.
I'm so tired. Let's go.
METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
You like showing off, don't you?
-What?
-Have you always been like that?
If you have something to say, then say it.
If I did, you'd have to quit
the Personal Security Division.
I don't want that.
I see.
I want to be a first-rate bodyguard.
Do you think you got away with that?
Good evening.
This is my co-worker, Takanashi.
Why are you so hostile?
I don't have to answer that.
What's with you? We're both
in the business of protecting people.
That's an interesting remark.
What could possibly be similar
about what you and I do?
Don't forget that security companies
are under police jurisdiction.
You'll be dining with Kinoshita
from METI at 3:00 p.m.
-Okay.
-Don't forget.
AIKO TACHIHARA
HEALTH, LABOR, AND WELFARE MINISTER
Hello?
I'm replacing your appointed SP.
I didn't think you would allow
a replacement.
It was my decision.
It's to keep you
from hiring private security.
Avoid having any further contact
with Hinode Security Service.
You really do hate him, don't you?
No. We simply need to eliminate anyone
who takes security lightly.
Japan isn't as safe
as everyone thinks it is.
Thank you all for coming.
That was the director. Thank you, sir.
You're too old to be dozing all morning.
Let's hear from Kanon now.
Go ahead, Kanon.
I'm extremely grateful
for being given the leading role.
Becoming a great actress
is my way of repaying my fans
and the man who discovered me,
my agency's president.
I'll do my best to learn
how to be a great actress.
If you're going to be a bodyguard,
at least guard people like her.
That'll never happen.
Murata speaking.
Hello. I'd like you and Shimazaki
to come to my office now.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'll handle the trouble we had
with the Security Police.
That isn't what this is about.
We have an extremely important
top-secret request.
I'd like you to provide me security.
She will take three hours
to attend her meeting and return.
Why do you have to keep it secret
from the SP?
I'm sorry. The Minister has...
You know nothing about the Minister.
And you think you know her?
Minister, my mission is not yet complete.