It's all over!
It's my punishment for buying these shoes.
You're not going home barefoot.
This is a special report.
The decision regarding the 2011 murder
at the Akabane Nursing Home
will be coming down this Thursday.
Straighten up your shoes.
The entry hall isn't that big.
The former nurse, Yaeko Matsukawa,
is charged with the 2011 murder
of two nursing home residents...
-I can't wake up unless I watch Shiori.
-aged 82 and 89.
Until now...
Isn't she too old for you?
...the prosecution
has requested the death penalty
due to the cruel and brutal nature
of the crime,
and there's no possibility of reform.
Why are you cleaning up?
Are you leaving or something?
If you don't clean up, we'll get C.
-What?
-What's "C"?
Cockroaches.
At her first trial, the former nurse,
Yaeko Matsukawa,
received the death penalty.
At her appeal in the High Court,
new evidence from the defense was allowed,
so there is talk that the death penalty
and even the conviction itself
could be overturned.
-There's sure to be repercussions.
-Innocent? Wow.
If she is ruled innocent.
Yes. Considering the feelings
of the victims' families,
there's no escaping the fact that
the accused took two lives.
But this judge
is a defender of human rights.
In all his cases until now,
he has never sentenced...
-Stop it there.
-Yes, sir.
This is our client.
A judge?
TATSUO YUKINAGA
PRESIDING JUDGE
Before dawn today,
a fire was set in front of the house
of the judge for this case,
Tatsuo Yukinaga.
What's wrong?
At present, the police are
considering this a threat
regarding the decision
in the case this week.
They believe there could be
more threats or even attacks,
so the MPD has assigned the SP
to guard Judge Yukinaga.
However, his family won't be
under the protection of the SP.
Therefore, Mr. Yukinaga himself
requested personal security for his wife.
-The bicycle's burned to a crisp.
-We took the job?
The death penalty is involved.
This could be dangerous.
That's why he hired us, right?
We'll be working with the SP, won't we?
What a pain.
The risk for this is Level 3.
We're getting special pay.
I'll do it!
-Will you be BG, Suganuma--
-I'll do it!
As for backup...
can you do it, Shimazaki?
All right.
-Backup...
-Can you do it?
What?
This serious stuff is the kind of thing
Takanashi should do.
No way.
He's better at hauling money around.
Don't worry.
I have a lot of years under my belt.
That works against you.
What? I'll do it.
JUNYA, MVP THREE YEARS IN A ROW!
Why are you hiding this,
old man?
MASAYA TAKANASHI
CASH TRANSPORT SECURITY
YUKINAGA
We're from Hinode Security Service.
Visitors from Hinode Security Service.
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
I'm Suganuma.
I'm Shimazaki.
Come in.
YOSHIAKI OCHIAI
SECURITY BUREAU (SP), MPD
Hello.
These are your bodyguards.
I've asked them to protect you
24 hours a day.
I don't need it.
I'm Suganuma from Hinode Security Service.
I'll be your personal bodyguard.
Since we're both women,
please speak freely with me.
I'm Shimazaki. I'll be working backup.
I told him that bodyguards for me
are a waste.
I mean, it's you they're after.
Since your husband is a target,
it's quite possible that
you could be in danger as well.
You're blowing this out of proportion.
Excuse me, but was it only
your bicycle that was burned?
Yes.
Then it must be a threat
to influence the ruling in the case.
In court, I've received
many messages telling me
not to overturn the death penalty
and to pass a guilty sentence.
But nobody should know
where your home is, right?
Yes. Since we moved here three years ago,
this is the first time this has happened.
You're awfully zealous.
You're not police investigators.
You don't have the weapons
to subdue the perpetrator.
If anything happens,
please don't do anything stupid,
and contact the police.
What? Is that true?
You're bodyguards
but you don't carry guns?
Don't worry.
We've been trained to handle anything.
Hold on here.
That means you're just ordinary people.
But you're still charging
expensive bodyguard fees?
Actually, I think it's pretty reasonable.
It's not actually guns that
protect people.
What? Then what will you use
to protect me?
Don't try to tell me
that you'll use courage.
-Go ahead.
-Okay.
Okay, see you later.
See you. Take care.
You take care too, dear.
Please take care of my wife.
Never leave her side,
and stay with her wherever she goes.
Yes, sir.
We'll never leave her side,
and stay with her wherever she goes.
Keep your guard up.
-Roger.
Excuse me.
I'm going to close the curtains.
I'm going to hide the knives just in case.
The SP and bodyguards
are like chalk and cheese.
Which one is the cheese?
I mean, this is just crazy.
How come only my husband gets SP?
They look so tough and have guns.
But you're just...
In the US, the First Lady is always
guarded by the Secret Service.
In Japan, the Prime Minister's wife
doesn't always get SP.
He pays private companies like ours
to protect her.
Okay, could you please wash the dishes?
Excuse me?
I was too exhausted from the commotion
over the fire to do them.
You there.
Could you clean up the entrance?
Clean up?
After that fire,
it's dangerous to leave it as it is.
Certainly.
Are you kidding? What?
NEW CONDOMINIUM SHOWROOM OPEN!
YOKOTETSU REAL ESTATE
Since we moved here three years ago,
this is the first time this has happened.
I've finished cleaning the entrance.
Next, you clean the bath,
and you the toilet.
I'm going to do some shopping.
Shopping?
Your husband is about to make
his decision on the case.
That's exactly why.
Every time I turn on the TV,
it's all about
what my husband's decision will be.
If I don't do something to escape,
I'll suffocate.
Understood.
However, if you're going out,
we'll be coming with you.
Here.
Go ahead.
For this morning, there's a larceny case
and a molestation case.
I'll put one man in the gallery,
and one each at the front and back doors.
Good. Proceed.
I'll return home in the afternoon
to prepare the decision in question.
You seem to be very calm.
All cases are equal in the court.
No matter the criticism,
I must remain imperturbable.
Very admirable.
You're Judge Yukinaga, aren't you?
Excuse me...
Don't you dare exonerate that woman!
The new evidence is all lies!
Let go of me! Protecting a murderer
makes you a murderer too!
How dare you look so indifferent!
You don't know anything!
You don't have the right to pass judgment!
You look lovely, madam.
They suit you so well!
Dear me, really?
It's a total flattery.
Where is she going to wear those?
Women are satisfied by just owning them.
I'll take them.
I've had my eye on them for a while.
As always, thank you for coming.
"As always"?
JUDGE INQUIRY
TATSUO YUKINAGA
Yes?
Mr. Yukinaga was attacked
at the courthouse.
Was he hurt?
He had SP guarding him. He's uninjured.
The culprit was a woman.
The police are investigating her now.
Roger.
Let me know right away
if she's the arsonist.
She's still shopping now.
Shopping with the money
her husband makes in his tough job?
She's got a lot of nerve.
You're so young.
Oh, is your wife the same, sir?
What?
That's none of your business!
Keep your eye on the GPS!
Yes, sir.
Hurry up and find a replacement
for Mr. Takanashi.
We'll be shorthanded if he's not replaced.
Get in and lock up.
There's nobody there.
He must be imagining things.
Our job is to avoid a crisis
before it happens.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. I was mistaken.
It's like you're playing bodyguards.
Whatever. Take me to Seijo Higashi next.
What? You want to go somewhere else?
-We're late already. Hurry up.
-Certainly. Let's go.
Got it.
The woman from the attack earlier
is the daughter of one of the victims.
I see.
She was living in Taiwan for her job.
She hasn't been
at the courthouse until now.
When she heard that
the verdict could be innocent,
she couldn't wait and returned
on a flight this morning.
Which means she didn't start the fire
at your home.
It must be someone else.
It's part of a judge's job
to be the object of grudges.
The jury system was implemented
to include the views of ordinary people,
but some people still find it hard
to understand legal thinking.
It's time to begin.
I'll contact HQ.
Stay alert in the gallery.
Yes, sir.
INFORMATION
12:03 P.M. RECORDED MESSAGE FROM (1101)
Ochiai here. You called?
Can't you guard me?
How come a judge gets priority over me?
They're not usually put under guard.
It's an urgent request from
the Commissioner-General of the NPA.
I'm not your personal guard.
If you need something,
please ask your assigned SP, Kiyota.
I'm sorry, but that man is...
He's an excellent shot
and an expert in jukendo.
He's the perfect SP to protect you.
I understand that, but...
I think he still holds a grudge
against me.
He always looks so serious.
Out of the way!
You're imagining things.
An SP does not hold grudges
against the people they protect.
Even if it was your actions
that caused trouble,
the responsibility lies
entirely with the SP.
You're giving me lip service again?
All humans have emotions, right?
This is a serious SOS
I'm sending you, Mr. Ochiai.
Be careful about what you say.
Excuse me.
It's best to assume that someone
is always listening to your calls.
Oh, my! What would I do
if the FBI was listening in?
What could I say
that would make them happy?
I can't continue
this private conversation any longer.
It's my duty to my country to protect you.
Is that so?
Then maybe I'll open my own purse,
and hire a private bodyguard.
I know!
How about that man who got beaten up?
He was an interesting man.
The event can continue now.
You're an important person.
A private guard can't protect you.
Goodbye.
Okay,
let's give you a light touch
around your face...
Do you really need to visit
the beauty salon now?
I already had a reservation for a haircut.
-Take your time.
-Thank you.
What do you mean by saying,
"Take your time"?
What?
We'll get tired if we have to
hang out here for a long time.
We have to stand outside
in the cold, you know.
But Mr. Yukinaga told us to
never leave his wife's side
and stay with her wherever she goes.
I mean that we don't have to
let her order us around like this.
But those are our orders, you know.
Yes, that's true,
but do we have to obey all orders?
Use your head!
We have to protect that woman, you know!
If anything happens, I'm BG,
so it's my responsibility.
Then can I ask you a question, Ms. BG?
Do you think she really wanted
to get a haircut?
She's looking for her chance to be alone.
It makes me think that
she has another purpose
for going shopping
and to the beauty salon.
Another purpose?
CASH TRANSPORT DIVISION
What do you want?
Well...
we got a tough assignment today,
so I wanted to have
a drink with you later.
Tell me now.
What?
Men our age
don't go drinking together
without anything to talk about.
I thought it was a waste to
let you just quit like this.
Will you please come back?
I'll clear it with personnel.
I'm taking spot assignments
transporting money now.
At least tell me why you quit.
I mean, you requested to work in
the Personal Security Division.
Thank you.
What other purposes would she have?
Wasting money to relieve stress?
No.
She just wants to cause us trouble?
Then what is it?
I don't know.
Then quit talking about it.
She's an ordinary housewife,
not the kind that has secrets.
Oh, no! She's gone!
Here she is.
-Madam.
-What?
The car is this way.
You can't go off without saying anything
while we're guarding you.
I thought you were on a tea break.
We don't drink anything.
We'll have to use the restroom if we do.
Really? I guess it's tough
being a bodyguard.
But it doesn't compare to
the hardship of being a judge.
Your husband does admirable work.
I'm not so sure about that.
Being a judge is very confining.
"Confining"?
When there are no cases,
he does research all day long at home.
I wouldn't mind if he were handsome,
but it's confining having that
dull-faced old man at home all day.
Anyway...
Where to now?
Hey.
Can't you leave me alone for an hour?
I want to meet someone.
Could you tell us who that would be?
I'm not obligated to tell you, am I?
You may be my bodyguards,
but we just met today.
How can I trust you so soon?
You can't tell us anything
about this person?
There's nothing fishy about it.
It's a salesman for Yokotetsu Real Estate.
"Salesman" means it's a man, right?
What kind of question is that?
Is that him?
He's certainly young.
Quit imagining things!
I want to move to a condo in town,
so I'm consulting with him.
Mr. Mikami is a newlywed with a baby.
This was her purpose.
A typical younger man.
A typical handsome face.
How unoriginal.
She doesn't think of him
as just a salesman.
She thinks she has a chance with him.
How disgusting.
Hey, where did it go?
-What? The cheating wife is right there.
-No, there's something else missing.
The bag with the shoes is gone.
That's right.
She had it with her
when she went into the beauty salon.
She probably forgot it
at the beauty salon reception desk.
Forgot it?
Would she forget that?
What's going on? Did they break up?
Don't you think it's time to return home?
I still have shopping to do.
Is something wrong, madam?
What?
Aren't you feeling well?
I'm just fine.
We're your bodyguards, madam.
If you're having any problems,
please tell us.
I told you there's nothing wrong!
I don't mean to intrude,
but was there some trouble
between you and that real estate salesman?
If you think so, then keep quiet!
Hey.
Your husband has asked us
to protect you, madam.
Leave me alone, would you?
They're after my husband, not me.
It has nothing to do with me.
But in the fire at your house...
it was the bicycle that was burned.
That was yours, wasn't it, madam?
I've had enough of you! Leave me be!
I don't want to see you anymore!
You're fired!
I'd like to speak to Mr. Yukinaga.
He's working in his study.
-I have something to report.
-What is it? I'll tell him.
He's our client.
Allow me to speak to him directly.
I can't allow that.
For security reasons.
What's going on?
Do you have time, sir?
Excuse me.
I'm Sawaguchi. I'm replacing Shimazaki.
Hello.
You look much more trustworthy
than the last guy.
Like an SP.
Seriously? Thank you.
She's making fun of us. You're so vain.
I'm terribly sorry.
Your wife fired me.
She fired you? Why?
I put her in a bad mood.
Tell me in detail what happened.
Actually...
What's wrong?
You have an obligation to give
a detailed report to the client.
Yes, sir.
Basically, after my wife met
that real estate salesman,
she started acting strange?
That's right.
I see. I wonder why.
May I ask you a question?
Anything you like.
Is it possible
that it's not you they're after,
but your wife?
My wife? How could that be?
It was your wife's bicycle
that was set on fire.
That bothers me.
It was in front of my house. That's why.
She's a simple housewife.
She has few friends.
She doesn't know anyone
who would hold a grudge against her.
Do you have proof of your suspicions?
No, I don't have proof.
I'm sorry I was of no help.
The replacement bodyguard
will protect her well.
How old was the man?
He must have a family as well.
I noticed my wife was meeting a man
who I don't know.
Tell me exactly what happened.
I don't mind.
I apologize if I'm mistaken.
Does that mean
you hired bodyguards
because you wanted to know
if she was having an affair,
or what she was doing?
I don't need to tell you my reasons.
But you're deceiving your wife.
Sorry. That was out of line.
A judge must determine
whether people live or die.
Not only me but my family too
must live ethical and proper lives.
That's because nobody will trust
the decisions of a judge
whose private life is in shambles.
Do you understand?
As a judge,
I can't ask a detective agency
to investigate my wife.
Being a judge is very confining.
That's very confining.
It's not out of jealousy as a husband,
but out of duty as a judge
that you're investigating your wife.
If my mind is disturbed
because my wife is having an affair,
I can't pass judgment on people.
The man who met your wife was
a Mr. Mikami from Yokotetsu Real Estate.
He was probably in his early 30s.
I found this in the trash.
I was wondering why you had it
since you had such a new home.
YOKOTETSU REAL ESTATE
AGENT: YUSAKU MIKAMI
"Yusaku Mikami"?
What's the matter?
Well...
It seems like I've heard this name before.
Could it be that
he has something to do
with the nursing home murders?
I'll check into it myself.
If this man has anything to do
with tomorrow's case,
we'll need to act immediately.
Depending on what it is,
the decision might have to be postponed.
Considering the notifications
that have to be made,
the deadline is 7:00 p.m.
Bring back my wife by 7:00 p.m.
Understood.
However,
don't you dare tell the police about this.
Is that for the court too?
Of course. If the police act on it,
it'll cause an uproar.
Understood.
That's bad.
If this Mikami guy is related
to the nursing home murders,
then there will be trouble.
We need to inform the police
about this immediately.
I understand that this is a big problem,
but Mr. Yukinaga doesn't want us
to inform them.
But this isn't something
we can keep hidden from them.
But our client isn't the police.
It's Judge Yukinaga.
BEAUTY SALON ENTRANCE
If we tell them secretly,
we'll betray him.
ALTERNATE EXIT, ELEVATOR
I'll look into this first.
I appreciate it.
INVESTIGATION DEPARTMENT
This and this.
Don't you think it's about time
you went back home?
You need to get dinner ready, right?
-I guess so.
-Yes, that's right.
It hurts!
Are you okay, madam?
Don't touch me!
Help me!
What's wrong?
-She just started saying, "It hurts."
-Who are you?
We're not involved.
-I mean, we are.
-What's going on?
Hold on a second.
Here's our ID.
We're not doing anything suspicious.
It's all right.
What?
-Madam!
-Oh, no!
-Look for her!
-Okay!
Mrs. Yukinaga!
What's wrong?
AS FOR THE ERRONEOUS
DETERMINATION OF FACTS...
I'm working.
I'm sorry to bother you
while you're working.
Has something happened to your wife?
No.
Why did that bodyguard come here earlier?
He reported on her security.
There's no need to worry.
I'll ask you again.
Has something happened to your wife?
We at the SP are risking our lives
to protect you, Your Honor.
Do you trust a private company
working for money more than us?
Think it over carefully.
I have an important decision
to give tomorrow.
Please wait downstairs.
She won't answer her phone.
I'm sorry.
I let my guard down.
If anything happens...
I'll take responsibility.
You can't take responsibility. I will.
You can't take responsibility!
For us bodyguards,
once we've made a mistake...
we'll be forced out of the business.
There's an international blacklist.
You're kidding!
But we haven't failed yet.
That's right. We just need to
bring her back safely by 7:00 p.m.
BG...
give us orders.
We'll separate and search.
We'll find her and bring her back.
-Synchronized.
Synchronized.
REGALO SEIJO
FREEDOM TRUNK ROOM
Shimazaki here.
I just got details on Yusaku Mikami.
Go ahead.
First of all, he's lying about
being married and having a child.
Why would he lie about that?
Listen carefully, Shimazaki.
Mrs. Yukinaga,
this is the bodyguard Shimazaki.
I fired you!
Yes, but your husband asked me
to protect you.
Is that all you have to say?
That's my job.
How did you find me here?
The bag with the shoes you bought
disappeared while you were here.
Also, it sounded like you've been
to that store many times,
but there were no expensive shoes
at your home.
FROM: GORO MURATA
I FOUND HER SAFE AT REGALO SEIJO
She's okay!
IT'S SHIMAZAKI.
SHE'S SAFE. REGALO SEIJO
I secretly started renting this place
three months ago.
It's 18,000 yen a month.
It's only a two-mat room, but...
I keep the things I secretly buy here.
And sit alone quietly here.
This is the only place you have
that's not confining.
Your husband said...
that the family of a judge
must live a proper life.
That's right.
"It's all over if you commit a crime."
"Don't complain about the neighbors."
"Always talk pleasantly with them."
"Keep the TV and radio volume low."
"Don't order out."
"Don't be extravagant.
Don't wear flashy clothes."
I wouldn't even last a day.
But my husband...
doesn't complain at all
when he's criticized.
He doesn't get angry or whine.
I'm not a great person like my husband is.
I wanted a place to escape to.
So that's why you got this place?
Mr. Mikami told me about it.
His company runs it.
Thanks to him, I can spend time
not being a judge's wife.
Let's go.
Let's go home. Your husband is worried.
I can't go back.
BUILDING CLOSED
REGALO SEIJO
Why are you here, Takanashi?
I think I should tell you why I quit
the Personal Security Division.
Is there some trouble?
We should probably inform
the police, but...
we'll end up exposing
the client's secrets to them.
I'm thinking about what to do.
SHIMAZAKI: GUARD MRS. ASAMI YUKINAGA
Shimazaki told you
not to tell the police, didn't he?
-That was a good guess.
-It's something he would say.
-As a bodyguard, he's right.
-I think he's wrong.
If the client told us to
stand on our heads, would we?
Would we dance naked?
-That's not...
-It's the same thing!
Don't let that man control you, sir.
We keep on meeting.
I have important information
regarding Asami Yukinaga.
I'm terribly sorry
for losing sight of your wife.
We've found her,
so I promise we'll bring her back.
It's all right.
But why would my wife go there?
I just informed the proper authorities.
It was Yusaku Mikami who set the fire.
He met with your wife before.
He's a member of the victim's family
in a case you decided
a year ago, Your Honor.
A year ago?
A stalker case in Fuchu.
Do you remember it now?
Yes, I remember.
I will now read the verdict.
An ex-boyfriend found out
where the victim had moved to.
Based on a precedent,
I gave a suspended sentence.
I believe the victim was Kanako Otani.
She was engaged at the time.
She got married after the case,
but she was haunted by the fear
that the stalker would come back,
and she killed herself six months ago.
Apparently, she was pregnant.
And the woman was...
That's right.
She was married to Yusaku Mikami.
It wasn't a threat against
tomorrow's decision.
The opposite, in fact.
It was resentment against a past judgment.
It was Mr. Mikami who set the fire.
If your husband dies,
you'll be mine, Asami.
I'm the one who set your bicycle on fire.
I've always ridden an old bicycle
to go do my shopping.
When we were newlyweds,
my husband often took me
shopping in the car.
But he said a judge can't get into
an accident, so we sold the car.
My bicycle was
a symbol of my confined life.
I complained to Mr. Mikami about it.
So when I saw the bicycle burning,
I thought it might be him.
But there's nothing between us.
He was kind, and I liked
that he listened to me, but...
we only had tea together.
Then you can still go back home.
Wear this with pride,
and let's go back home.
What will I say to my husband?
Let's hurry.
It's too dangerous here.
-Dangerous?
-Mikami...
lied to you.
He doesn't have a wife or child.
They're dead.
What do you mean?
He is...
the husband of the victim
in a case your husband ruled on.
I'm sure he approached you
knowing exactly who you were.
Oh, wait!
Oh, dear.
Oh, my!
-Excuse me.
-Hey! What are you doing?
8F ELEVATOR HALL
There's a car waiting out front.
Get in.
The elevator isn't broken.
What?
I control where that elevator goes.
Nobody else...
can get inside this building.
I'm sorry, but you're going to die, Asami.
Are you crazy?
She has nothing to do with this!
Yes, she does.
My wife died!
Open these doors.
You'll become a criminal.
There's something I want to test.
Can a judge make a calm decision
when it's his own wife who has died?
EMERGENCY DESCENT
EMERGENCY INTERCOM
STAY CLEAR OF DOORS
What? That's odd. It's locked.
-Find another entrance.
-Okay.
It's all over!
It's my punishment for buying these shoes.
You're not going home barefoot.
EMERGENCY DESCENT
STAY CLEAR OF DOORS
EMERGENCY STOP
REGALO SEIJO
What the heck is going on?
He's not answering.
Get out of my way.
No, I won't. I'm her bodyguard.
Get out of the way.
Kanako died.
She's never coming back.
Run away.
Kanako...
EMERGENCY STOP
SECURITY OPERATION
Kanako!
Settle down!
He's...
He's a victim too.
-We'll be going.
-Thank you.
I'm sorry for causing you to worry.
It's okay.
Thank you for your work.
Thank goodness she's okay.
Madam,
your husband was worried about you.
Madam...
I don't know how to face him.
Face him just like that.
Don't be so flippant.
I was deceived and did stupid things.
That's right.
But you wanted to see your husband
do stupid things too.
You're really something.
I heard you took down an armed man
while you were empty-handed.
I can see why you're so confident
about being unarmed.
No, I was fighting pretty desperately.
I admire what you did.
You go shopping and
to a secret meeting with her,
almost get killed,
and even give marriage counseling.
Oh, I see. This is sarcasm.
Personal security is a service industry,
so doing what the client wants
is part of the job.
Would you die if the client told you to?
That's awfully extreme.
Isn't your job pretty confining?
If you blindly follow orders,
you'll find yourself in danger.
You need to consider that.
Listen to me for a second.
I'm not that audacious to say that
I'm confident in my unarmed ability...
All I said was
not having a weapon makes you stronger!
What?
-Mr. Shimazaki.
-Yes?
I was lying to myself.
My mind is not always in a calm state!
I was just concerned about my wife
like any other man...
Please, tell the rest to your wife.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I wonder if...
I'm fit to judge others.
You haven't done...
anything wrong.
I know that.
Look.
I bought these.
I'm not sure what to say, but...
they sure look cool.
You're terrible at giving compliments.
-Good night.
If you weren't a little more resourceful,
you'll always return home injured.
Hopefully, it'll always be just an injury.
Good night.
Takanashi will be returning.
Really?
He said he would carry
the Personal Security Division
on his shoulders.
Who does he think he is?
Who the heck is this?
Excuse me. What do you want?
Thank you for the other day,
for saving me.
No problem.
I have a favor to ask you.
Can you give me private security?
There's someone I have to meet
without the SP knowing.
Please go through the company
for any security requests.
Quit acting all protective.
You'll catch a cold.
Who cares?
Hey.
The reason I was cleaning up
this morning was...
I've started working as a bodyguard again.
I mean, I never know when I might die.
So I have to keep this place clean.
It's one of the basics.
I figured you did a long time ago.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
Good night.
Night.
This time, we'll be guarding
100 million yen.
She left without a word?
"If you bring me 100 million yen,
then I'll come back."
Has Kanon been kidnapped?
What's more important?
Her life or her value as an entertainer?
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.