Bring him here now!
In the corruption scandal
four years ago...
you pinned the blame on me
and then abandoned me!
The least you can do is apologize!
You should apologize!
Sir!
The only thing a shameless man
like you can do
is die a quick death!
Don't talk like that, sir!
I won't allow pointless deaths!
Apologize!
Are you all right?
The gunshot wound to his leg
damaged an artery
and may have fractured his femur.
I've informed your family.
Your son answered.
He said they'll be on their way soon.
TOKYO FIRE AND DISASTER MANAGEMENT AGENCY
-Shimazaki.
-Yes?
The time is 6:14 p.m.
and five seconds.
Synchronized.
What's going on?
-Cardiac arrest!
-Okay!
-I need to sit there.
-Okay.
-Get ready.
You must be kidding.
Boss!
-Give me that.
-Mr. Murata!
TOKYO FIRE AND DISASTER MANAGEMENT AGENCY
Mr. Murata!
The shooter is Yugo Ueno.
He's 48 years old and unemployed.
From 2001 to 2014,
he was the private secretary
for Secretary-General Igarashi.
Secretary-General Igarashi's
private secretary?
According to his statement,
the pistol used in the crime
was acquired for the purpose
of committing suicide.
Other elements of the case
are still under investigation.
That is all.
-What? That's it?
-It's over? Hey!
Mr. Hikawa!
-Mr. Hikawa.
-The SP were at the scene, correct?
They messed up, didn't they?
The SP's mission
is to protect important people.
They carried out that mission.
But a civilian has died!
Is protecting VIPs all they do?
I heard that the victim struggled
with the enraged shooter.
-Really?
-It's terribly regrettable.
You mean the victim provoked the shooter?
You saw the shots being fired,
didn't you, Minister?
What happened?
I was being protected by the SP,
so I didn't see
the moment of the shooting.
Minister, the victim
was a private bodyguard, right?
How did he provoke the shooter?
No matter the cause,
it doesn't change the fact that
a precious life has been lost.
I wish to express
my sincerest condolences.
Minister, we demand an explanation.
GORO MURATA
FUNERAL, MARCH 2ND, 10:00 A.M.
-Hey!
-Cut that out!
Stop that!
-Don't get violent!
-Hey! That hurts!
You don't have to get violent!
I knew it.
-Yoichi.
-Dad was a fool.
You're wrong.
He never provoked the shooter.
Your father worked
until the very end as a bodyguard
to protect the lives of everyone there.
Then...
why is this happening?
TRAGEDY OF A BODYGUARD'S
ACCIDENTAL SHOOTING AT RESTAURANT
BODYGUARD PRETENDING AS HERO
FAILS AT POLICE MAKE-BELIEVE
POLICE VERIFY VICTIM'S WORDS
PROVOKED RESTAURANT SHOOTER
It's like Dad was shot
because he meddled in the affair.
Madam...
Yoichi...
I won't let your father
be disgraced like this.
I'll work hard to clear this up.
Impossible.
The police and politicians are cooperating
to blame the bodyguard.
The dead cannot speak.
Bodyguards are nothing more than
underpaid slave labor!
-Don't say that about his work!
-Stop it!
Stop doing this.
Don't do this now.
Being a bodyguard
is sometimes a deadly job.
But we all cannot expect to die doing it!
The things that Personal Security Manager
Murata taught us...
Let us all properly remember them.
GORO MURATA
FUNERAL, MARCH 2ND, 10:00 A.M.
My dear,
thank you for all you've done.
If I may.
Time is 11:28 a.m.
Synchronized.
I wish us all success.
Thank you. Yes.
Certainly. We'll be waiting.
We just got a new security job.
The client will be arriving soon.
Sorry, but I'm not sure if I can work.
To be honest, the shock is just so huge.
I understand,
but due to the shooting,
we've lost several jobs.
We need to pull it together.
You're right.
That would make Mr. Murata happy.
I'm not in the mood for that.
More important than work is clearing
Mr. Murata's tarnished name.
But how?
By making the police admit fault!
If we could do that,
this never would have happened.
The police and Minister Tachihara
are in collusion
trying to cover up
the Secretary-General's provocation.
So we should just drop it?
How can Mr. Murata rest in peace?
You want him to be blamed
for his own death?
Of course not!
Who said we were going to drop this?
We still don't know
what the best thing to do is.
We can't act desperately!
Preparing perfectly before a mission
is the way that
we bodyguards work, isn't it?
Until we can see what to do,
we must keep this thing alive,
this Personal Security Division
that he started.
You sure are cold.
Do you really think it'll work out
if we just wait?
Hello, everyone!
Thank you for the other day.
Chairman Okubo, thank you as well.
You're the client, Chairman?
I'm very sorry to hear about
what happened.
Who would've thought
Mr. Murata would lose his life?
Thank you.
I wasn't sure if this was the right time,
but I thought hiring you
was the best way to pay my respects.
I'd like to hire you as security
for the announcement ceremony
of our new product.
Sunny-side-up egg flavor?
-Unusual, right?
-Yes.
-I'm confident it will succeed.
-Is that so?
However, I've come here
because the workers at a factory I closed
are threatening to start
a boycott of our products.
That sounds like trouble.
I'm not worried about myself.
I just don't want my precious
new product to suffer any damage.
This product took
over two years to develop.
Its taste is revolutionary.
Talk to him.
-Please have a seat.
-Thank you.
Can you boil some water for these?
Hey, wait! I said wait!
Wait, all right?
Listen up!
SP has received a lot of criticism
about the shooting the other day.
But we did nothing wrong.
Work with confidence. However...
don't let your guard down.
-Yes, sir!
Dismissed.
You're maintaining your stance on this?
I've thought this over very carefully.
Considering our current position,
we can't make an enemy
of the Secretary-General.
But Mr. Murata's reputation
will remain tarnished!
Hold on.
You were there too.
I'm protecting you as well.
You're only protecting yourself!
You're choking me.
Do you plan on killing me?
Ochiai!
We didn't kill him.
Murata was shot by the suspect.
That's undeniable.
We only changed one little detail.
It's time to take a firm stance.
The leadership
has great expectations of you.
I think we can cover this site
with three people.
I'll be the backup.
Can you be BG, Sawaguchi?
A commemorative first BG.
-Commemorative?
-Yes.
Earlier,
-I couldn't tell you this.
-Yes?
Is it okay if I resign?
I'm ashamed to admit it,
but my mom is pressuring me
to quit this dangerous job
as soon as possible.
What about you?
Do you want to quit, Sawaguchi?
I don't really know.
Working here every day
was really interesting.
But...
I think this isn't the kind of job
that I can do my whole life.
-Sorry for being so frank.
-No, it's okay.
It's better than making stuff up.
Are you going to be okay, Shimazaki?
Isn't Takanashi going to quit too?
I'll do this, even if I'm alone.
There's no other work I can do.
More importantly,
this your first and last BG job.
Do your best.
Yes, sir. I will.
I'll make this a good memory.
Memory...
Mr. Ochiai.
I want to talk to you.
I'm on my way to work.
Why won't you tell the truth?
Are the police being silenced?
I don't know what you mean.
Excuse me.
At first, I was angry at you
for looking down on private security.
But you're always very thorough.
I don't think you can be that way
unless you're extremely determined.
Mr. Ochiai,
save Mr. Murata.
Please!
I offer my deepest condolences
for Mr. Murata.
You're wasting your time.
He's an SP.
The police will never tell you the truth
if you confront them.
What else is there to do?
You really make me angry.
You're so heavy-handed.
But that's what I love about you.
That cleared your head, right? Let's go.
JYONAN UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
You did a good job putting out the fire.
It proves my belief in you
was well-founded.
I don't want to die just yet.
That's a pretty alarming thing to say.
When I was a newscaster,
I covered the Diet Member
who blew the whistle on illicit donations
from a major corporation
and then died in an accident.
That kind of thing isn't uncommon
in the political world.
You win only if you don't care
what means you use.
That's the world you live in.
TAKANASHI, SUGANUMA, SAWAGUCHI
OPERATION SCHEDULE:
MURATA, SHIMAZAKI
Everyone, we have our first job.
All I did was work as hard as I could.
Don't talk like that, sir!
I won't allow pointless deaths!
Minister Tachihara
wants to speak with you.
-May she?
-Do I have a choice?
-I'm sorry for--
-If you're going to apologize,
not to me.
Apologize to his family.
I didn't come here to apologize.
I decide only to make requests
when I know that
I'll get something in return.
Then why are you here?
Mr. Shimazaki,
you may think it's crazy for me
to say this to a bodyguard,
but be extra careful about your safety.
What?
Besides the police, the only people
who witnessed that whole incident...
were you and Mr. Murata.
I think you understand.
With Mr. Murata dead,
you're the only one left.
Are you telling me someone
might want to silence me?
Don't be stupid.
I'm merely a civilian
with zero interest in politics.
For ten years,
I've battled malicious gossip
about my newscaster past
while I embraced the political world,
so this is my warning to you.
Goodbye.
Good night.
HINODE BUILDING
-No! I told you no!
-Come on. Let me have it!
-Come on! Why not?
-I told you so.
I'm home.
So Shun,
did anything unusual happen?
Unusual? Like what?
Did anyone come by
or was anything delivered?
No.
You want this?
No, I don't.
Are you sure?
SUNNY-SIDE-UP EGG FLAVOR?
EGG-CHAN
I guess you do.
SUNNY-SIDE-UP EGG FLAVOR?
EGG-CHAN
Okay, let's eat.
Are you working?
Yes.
Pretty good, isn't it?
What flavor is this?
Sunny-side-up egg flavor.
That's unexpected.
Man, this is good.
Today is the announcement event
for Sasuke Foods' new product.
We need to pay special attention
to the tasting booth.
Suganuma and I will be the backup.
The BG will stick with Chairman Okubo.
Yes, sir.
Can you get my earphone?
What's your problem?
Thanks.
This is your first BG.
We're counting on you.
Roger.
The time is 8:31 a.m. and 15 seconds.
-Synchronized.
Synchronized. We're ready.
Let's do this.
Base team, we'll contact you
if we need support.
Okay.
Once this mission is complete,
we'll help you.
Waiting around is pointless.
Time is limited.
Thank you.
All right, let's go!
Okay!
Here it is!
Hello!
Congratulations on the new product!
There are samples, so please try some.
Have a taste of this miracle flavor!
Iguchi Cutter!
Thank you.
Okay.
Everyone, over here, please. This way.
-It looks delicious. I'll try some.
-Go ahead.
EGG-CHAN
BG, you look frightening.
Take a deep breath.
Roger.
-Chairman, congratulations.
-Congratulations.
Is this your new secretary?
No, he's my bodyguard.
-Bodyguard? Really?
-Quite handsome, isn't he?
-Yes, he is.
-What a handsome man!
Quit posing.
Sorry.
-Nice. Thank you.
-May I? Thank you.
-This is fascinating.
-It's egg flavor.
Egg flavor?
Everyone, this way, please.
-Is it good?
-Yes, it is.
It gets even better
if you add a little ketchup.
Suspicious individual
at the back near the entrance.
Checking it out.
How is the taste?
This is 03, on my way.
BG, remaining with the Chairman.
Excuse me.
Have you been invited?
BLACK COMPANY
WE WON'T FORGIVE YOU, SASUKE FOODS!
The only people allowed in
are those who have been invited.
Please leave.
What?
Leave us be!
We represent the people who Okubo fired.
How can he launch a new product
after closing a plant?
Today is a day of celebration.
The people who made it aren't to blame.
Shut up! This is none of your business.
-Hey, you!
-Come back!
Stop!
Out of the way!
That hurts!
-That hurts!
-Pardon me.
-Well done.
-Thank you.
The two men from the funeral are here.
What?
Right.
Is it possible
to take them to court over this?
I see.
Evidence?
Okay.
I see. Thank you.
Of course, there isn't any evidence.
JANUARY 21, CLIENT: SASUKE OKUBO
FEBRUARY 7, CLIENT: AIKO TACHIHARA
I first met Minister Tachihara
when we provided security
for the Civil Party.
I never thought
she'd request security herself.
Is this a personal security request?
I thought Cabinet members
were provided with SP.
He made recordings while on duty.
FEBRUARY 16, CLIENT: JUNYA KONO
Here you are, dear.
IN MEMORY OF GORO MURATA
Why put that there? He'll never eat it.
Aren't you going to prep school?
Don't answer it.
It's just a crazy reporter.
Your father
didn't do anything to be ashamed of.
Hello, this is the Murata household.
This is Takanashi from Hinode.
I'd like to ask you something.
Yes?
Did you get Mr. Murata's belongings
back from the police?
Yes. We got his clothes
and his wallet back.
So you still don't have
his mobile phone or any other items?
Right.
Why do you ask?
We might be able
to clear his tarnished reputation.
-Chairman.
-Yes?
A final word from you, please.
Okay.
Please.
Chairman!
Thank you for coming today.
We've labored very hard
on this new product, Egg-chan.
Being able to bring this product to you
pleases me very much!
Ever since I was a destitute child,
I have survived
because of the oath I swore to the moon.
I'll never give up
on my search for delicious food!
It was a full moon
much like Egg-chan here.
I would like to take this opportunity
to thank the moon.
Thank you so much for your work.
You're welcome, sir.
I'm glad that there were
no significant disturbances.
I've obtained the names
of the visitors from the plant.
I see.
I'll speak with them
so we can clear this up.
Thank you.
I hope the misunderstanding
about Mr. Murata gets cleared up too.
I've seen all the news stories,
but I don't believe any of them.
I believe Mr. Murata.
I mean,
look at this dependable bodyguard
that he has trained.
As bodyguards, we have to work together.
Okay! Let's get to work!
I really believe that
my work is much better now.
Coordinating a group of people
with so much individuality
is far more rewarding.
I'm glad to hear it.
I've always wanted
to be called dependable.
I like you so much,
I want you to be
my granddaughter's husband.
You do?
You gold digger.
Well, she's still only five years old.
Five years old?
It'll be a while then.
Excuse me.
But you're her age mentally.
Don't laugh at the mental age
of a five-year-old.
TAKANASHI: GO TO MURATA'S HOME IMMEDIATELY
AFTER YOU'RE DONE. IT'S IMPORTANT.
His belongings haven't been returned?
Right.
This is everything the police returned.
METROPOLITAN POLICE DEPARTMENT
His mobile phone
as well as his digital recorder
aren't here.
Digital recorder?
He recorded everything while on duty.
I'm sure he recorded that day as well.
Take responsibility
for this outrage by dying!
Don't talk like that, sir!
I won't allow pointless deaths!
He...
must have recorded everything
even before the incident.
Are you saying
the police took it?
-Those jerks!
-It's too soon to tell.
Then why isn't it here?
Calm down.
You father always stayed calm
and gave us encouragement.
Have a seat.
Let's go to the MPD tomorrow.
If a family member goes,
you can request the return
of his personal belongings.
All right.
I don't know if I can do it though.
I'll go.
I'll do it.
I'll make them give it back.
We can't let you go alone.
Why not?
I can go alone. I don't have a father
to go with me anyway!
If your father were here,
he would never let a minor like you
go by yourself.
IN MEMORY OF GORO MURATA
Please
take care of him.
Please protect my son.
We will.
Let's get it back,
no matter what it takes.
Don't rush this. It won't be easy.
But if there's a recording
of the incident,
we can prove that
he didn't recklessly provoke--
I said not to rush this!
Let's proceed carefully.
Sorry.
You seem to be fond of Yoichi.
That's not true.
I'm not criticizing you.
It's a compliment.
-You really are a pain.
-I know I'm a pain.
Anyway, have a drink.
It's only water though.
Oh, sorry.
I never told you
why I quit the JSDF, did I?
No. You didn't.
One time I was training
with a younger soldier,
there was an accident.
I was friends with him.
He was such a coward.
He was always afraid.
I told him to build some courage
and I took him on
a mountain training exercise.
But then, he had a fall
and was seriously injured.
He had to be released from the service.
For me alone to remain
made me feel guilty.
So I quit as well.
To be honest,
I probably should have stayed
and made up for what happened.
Then...
-that guy and Yoichi...
-Yes.
They're similar. A little.
Remember what you said?
What?
I'm afraid to work with someone
who's not afraid.
That was the one thing in this world
I never wanted to be told.
"In this world"?
Right.
But
I'm glad
that Mr. Murata convinced me
to return here.
That's exactly why I can't let
Mr. Murata's case remain unsettled.
Me either.
Hey, are you guys fighting again?
No, we're not.
Okay. I got dinner.
Where's Sawaguchi?
-Here!
-You're so slow.
That was heavy.
Actually, I've thought it over.
I'm giving up after all.
What?
To put it simply, after being BG...
Hold on!
You're giving up being a bodyguard?
No. I'm giving up on giving up.
What? You were going to quit?
-Maybe.
-You can't "maybe" quit!
-I agree.
-You said you wouldn't stop me.
-I did?
-What?
You're mean!
Here, Shimazaki.
This is yours, Takanashi.
-Mine?
-You think I like this?
What are you putting on yours, Shimazaki?
-I wouldn't have that.
-No, it's no good.
-No, I always have it that way.
-Are you kidding?
I haven't had the courage
to look at this lately.
I'm glad we took this.
Oh, dear.
I held these back at the funeral,
but I can't now.
Also...
I'll send you this photo later.
Who's there?
I know there's two of you there.
I'm a pro too. I know you're there.
If you have something to say,
then show your faces.
Be extra careful about your safety.
I embraced the political world,
so this is my warning to you.
Hurry up.
It's Sunday.
Why did you wake me up so early?
You're going back to your mom's.
-What?
-I called and told her.
Why are you doing this?
How old are you now?
How can you forget your son's age?
I'm 13.
How strong are you now?
Hurry up.
That's it?
That hurts!
Good enough.
Now...
I have some dangerous work to do.
You always do.
I wonder where that's going.
Shun.
I want you to go many places.
What's that all about?
Go somewhere incredibly far.
Or somewhere amazingly high.
Or somewhere unbelievably huge.
Or somewhere cold.
I hate the cold.
We've arrived.
Roger. We're on standby.
I'm going.
I'm the son of Goro Murata,
the victim of the shooting the other day.
I'd like you to return
my father's belongings.
I see. Let him wait for now.
Where's Ochiai?
He's part
of Minister Tachihara's detail today.
Do you know these guys?
Are they from Hinode?
I think they are.
Akira Shimazaki.
-Right?
-Yes.
I heard that was his name.
So you've come.
Thank you for waiting.
You're Mr. Murata, right?
Yes.
We forgot to return these by mistake.
Let's go.
Here's the digital recorder.
-We've overcome the first hurdle.
-I sure hope so.
Let's listen. I'll connect it.
-The recordings are still there.
-And the day of the incident?
FEBRUARY 26, CLIENT: HITOMI ODAGIRI
Is it on a memory card?
It's been deleted.
The recording on the day of the shooting
has been deleted.
That's why they returned it so easily.
I thought it was strange.
Yoichi...
It's over.
There must be some other way.
Don't try to console me.
Dad will be remembered
as an overzealous bodyguard!
All I did was work as hard as I could.
BODYGUARD PRETENDING AS HERO
FAILS AT POLICE MAKE-BELIEVE
POLICE VERIFY VICTIM'S WORDS
PROVOKED RESTAURANT SHOOTER
Shimazaki!
HINODE BUILDING
They were clearly targeting you.
Anyway, keep an eye on Yoichi.
All right.
I will be in charge of security
at the Civil Party Convention.
You will be guarded by four SPs, Minister.
Four is quite a burden.
I don't know if I'm deserving
of all this protection now.
When a person has lost
something precious to them,
all they think of is
holding on to their status.
Minister,
may I say something personal?
Certainly.
When Mr. Murata was in the SP,
he was my boss.
He took responsibility for my mistake,
quit the force,
and became a private bodyguard.
He told me
to change the system.
I often thought of doing so.
But I've never changed a thing.
The only thing I did was
I just stuck with the police.
Thank you
for opening up to me.
Sorry for speaking unnecessarily.
Shall we get going?
Stop!
-Stop!
-Excuse me!
Minister Tachihara,
can you make public
what happened that day?
You're the only one who can do that now.
Please, Minister.
Remove him.
Minister, I refuse to give up.
We don't have status, power, or weapons,
but the one thing we had
was stolen from us!
I swear, we'll never give up!
We'll never give up, no matter what!
Don't worry.
I swear we'll find a way.
Forget it.
I'm tired of this.
Stay here.
Sir, the fire hasn't been put out.
I'm sure that nobody can extinguish it.
The truth should be made public.
I was wrong.
And you were too, sir.
Do you have any idea what you're saying?
Yes, I do.
Mr. Ochiai,
I'll go home on my own.
You can't.
I'm resigning as a minister.
I won't need SP protection anymore.
I appreciate what you've done.
Thank you for everything.
Aiko Tachihara is resigning as a minister?
I hope she's not thinking
of doing anything stupid.
Don't let her near that Shimazaki
who was at the shooting.
Why don't we get rid of Akira Shimazaki
just like we did with those recordings?
It's not like you
to make a joke like that.
A joke?
You said it was time
to take a firm stance, right?
In order to protect
the 40,000 members of the MPD,
we have to do the unthinkable.
Isn't that what you mean by a firm stance?
Mr. Shimazaki.
I will reveal everything.
I'll make public the truth
about the shooting incident.
Thank you for doing this, Minister.
You're welcome.
Please fight with us.
The final episode.
I can't be sure of
what's right and what's wrong.
I can't be sure, however...
I want to protect these things.
These are the people we want to protect.
Stop, Ochiai!
FAREWELL, BODYGUARD