What? You left Kicks Guard,
and now, you want to join my office?
Yes. I've decided that I'll join you.
Hey, don't just make
that decision on your own!
But there's no place for me
in Kicks Guard anymore.
What?
Oh, was it because you helped me
with that last assignment?
I'll call the chief
and tell them that
I was the one who forced you to help,
so just go along and bow your head down.
Don't just act on impulse!
Didn't you fight with the president
and resign on impulse too?
-We didn't exactly fight.
-So what happened?
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
If you tell me the reason,
I won't mind bowing my head down to them.
It wasn't even anything serious… What?
Isn't that strange?
"I won't mind"?
This concerns you, you know?
MAYU SUGANUMA
BODYGUARD, KICKS GUARD
SEITARO SAWAGUCHI
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you a new employee
of Shimazaki Security?
No.
Anyway, don't underestimate
the rent in this building--
-I'm not.
-You're not?
This place is old,
but it's still quite expensive.
You should promote your business more.
-Thanks for your kind advice.
-By the way…
I major in Computer Science
at my university.
Just let me know if you want
to set up a company website.
I'll help you set one up
for a cheap consultation fee.
Hey, could you read the room?
I'm not in a position
to employ anyone at the moment.
Particularly someone who is
entirely brawny and tactless like you
will be of no help
to a small company like mine.
-Do you get me?
-Are you sure you can do it alone?
I just have no choice but to make do
with small assignments
that don't require much manpower.
Shun was worried.
He doesn't know
what is going to happen to him.
I'll make sure he has
nothing to worry about… What?
Just what did you talk about with Shun?
Ema.
You didn't put your heart into the music.
I'm glad that wasn't
the actual performance.
The car is this way.
Please take one step down.
It was a wonderful performance.
I'm sure you'll win
the international piano competition.
Please.
-Ema!
-It's dangerous!
Mr. Takanashi?
We talked a lot.
He brought me some adzuki bean jelly too.
I see… It wasn't meat buns.
He's interesting.
That Takanashi actually said
something interesting?
No, he didn't.
That's why he's interesting.
My homeroom teacher tries so hard
to be funny that it's painful to watch.
-You're quite harsh on people.
-Not really.
Hey.
Everything will be fine, Shun.
You told Takanashi, right?
You were worried about
what is going to happen from now on.
Well, we'll survive somehow.
But I guess saying "somehow"
sounds very irresponsible.
I'll do something about it.
I mean, I do have 25 years of experience
being a bodyguard, after all.
So…
I'm finally independent after establishing
-a management outlook in my office--
-How discouraging.
A blind person
is aiming to be the world's best.
I wonder what I'm even doing here.
Wait.
-You still have a long road ahead of you.
-No way.
My parent is a divorcee,
and he just resigned from his job.
Her music has surpassed
500,000 downloads online.
I know my place in the world.
-Thanks for the food.
-She will be leaving for Poland next week.
Will she be able to
overcome her visual handicap
and realize her dream of being
the world's best pianist?
APRIL 15
OPEN FOR BUSINESS
What?
-It's been a while.
-Yes.
I was so surprised
since you left without saying anything.
So this is your office.
It's not exactly retro,
but your office does have
a certain atmosphere to it.
-It has been a while.
-Yes.
I asked Takanashi for your address.
I see.
So, did he go back to Kicks Guard?
Yes, he did.
But the chief was angry at him.
What am I supposed to think about
you helping someone who left our company?
Is he talking about Shimazaki?
Takanashi.
You're an employee of Kicks Guard, right?
So…
are you here to spy on me today?
It's not that!
I'm here to give you some work.
You? Giving me work?
Are you sure you want
to talk to me like that?
Here. She's a VIP.
VIP? Who?
Ema Morio.
-Oh, that pianist?
-Yes.
The blind pianist they dubbed as
"the Cinderella of the classical world."
Well, I'm grateful, but…
it's impossible for me
since I'm working alone.
Actually,
she was originally under our protection
in Kicks Guard.
But well, we decided to drop her.
No one is willing to take over from us,
so the chief suggested
that we pass it over to you.
Wait.
So Kicks Guard dropped her?
-But no one wants to take over?
-Yes.
Why? Isn't she a famous pianist?
That's… something I can't reveal.
Please ask the client directly.
INVESTIGATION REPORT
The International Piano Competition
is drawing near.
Everyone expects you to
win the competition.
Are you confident?
I'm not confident at all.
Oh, you're really humble!
I'm Shimazaki.
I came here
for Ema Morio's bodyguard request.
Please give me a moment.
-Sure.
-I'm Takanashi, here on the same request.
Our representative will meet you.
This way.
-Yes.
Leave.
They canceled my contract
before I could bow down my head to them.
I don't regret anything.
That company only knows
how to fawn over women.
Don't worry.
I know how to smile, at least.
Just get on the elevator quickly.
I'm Shimazaki.
Thank you for the name card.
-You're Mr. Shimazaki, and you're…
-I'm Takanashi.
Mr. Takanashi.
I'm Miwa Moria, Ema's older sister.
I'm the company president, and I oversee
Ema's management as an artist.
-Please have a seat.
-Thank you.
I heard you've left Kicks Guard
to set up your own office.
I'm sorry, but will it really be possible
with just the two of you?
Oh, I understand
what you're worried about.
But we don't have strict rules
unlike the big companies,
so we'll be able to deal with
all types of situations accordingly.
I see.
Ema will leave on the 22nd
for the International Piano Competition.
Can I trust you to protect her
until she returns from Poland?
We'll pay you the same amount
as we offered to the big companies.
Before we accept this assignment,
can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
I heard that Kicks Guard terminated
the bodyguard request.
And if I recall, even Guard Tech
rejected the request as well.
Will you accept the request,
no matter what I tell you?
It's just a joke. I'm sorry.
But since you requested
for bodyguard services,
then you must perceive that
she is in some sort of danger.
-Yes.
-Is she being targeted by someone?
Do you know who it could be?
Yes.
Who is it?
Have you contacted the police?
-No.
-Who is it?
If you don't tell us, we won't know
how to deal with the situation.
It's…
Ema herself.
There are cases where visually-impaired
pianists have won in competitions,
but not in the case of
international competitions.
If you win, you will be writing
a new page in history.
How do you feel about that?
There is no way I would answer
a ridiculous question like that.
What's the matter, Ema?
You're in the middle of an interview…
Watch out!
You can't injure your fingers!
Get away from me.
It's as you've seen.
She would leave without her guiding stick
and has even tried to
kill herself multiple times.
Kicks Guard told us that
they cannot protect someone who
constantly tries to put herself in danger.
Is there any reason why
she has been trying to kill herself?
It's probably because of
the overwhelming pressure that
she deals with due to her fame.
But it has been her dream to participate
in the International Piano Competition.
If she doesn't overcome this,
she won't be able to survive as a pianist.
Could you please
take her to Poland safely?
I understand. We will accept your request.
Are you crazy?
Bodyguards protect their clients
from external threats.
I've never heard of a case where
the clients themselves are the threat.
It doesn't change the fact that
we need to protect them.
We're bodyguards.
If you don't like this, then leave!
With skills like yours,
any company would gladly welcome you.
Ms. Ema!
Who are you?
I received your bodyguard request
from your sister.
I'm your bodyguard, Shimazaki.
I'm Takanashi.
I said I don't need a bodyguard.
It's just exhausting to have
someone unrelated following me around.
But…
it's important to keep you safe
before the competition.
Say something.
You know…
Let's realize your dreams in Poland.
Don't say things you don't mean!
It's easy to tell what you think
from your tone.
You…
You think that it's a pain trying
to protect a selfish girl like me.
And as for you,
you're confident that you'll be able to
tame anyone, no matter who it is.
Do you guys think that
blind people can't see for real?
It's the opposite.
We can see exactly because we're blind.
Everything, in fact.
About Ema Morio,
Shimazaki and Takanashi have
accepted her bodyguard request.
I see.
In the end,
the two of them are working together.
Isn't it wonderful?
You helped your seniors.
Yes.
I wanted to be with her
until she left for Poland.
But the client tried to kill herself
right before your eyes.
I protected her
and averted the crisis immediately.
I had the confidence to protect her
-until our contract was up.
-Hey.
Don't get ahead of yourself just because
you're appointed as the new leader.
President Ryu terminated her contract
for your sake.
For our sake?
If something happened
to a famous pianist like her,
not only will the company's reputation
be tarnished,
the bodyguards themselves
will be under fire too.
Protecting your future
is my responsibility
as the CEO of the company.
Shouldn't protecting the client be
our top priority instead?
COMMERCIAL LAW CASE STUDIES
It doesn't matter if
it's Shimazaki or Takanashi…
you bodyguards from Hinode Security
are really interesting.
I'm truly sorry.
They are capable,
but they lack manners.
-I will educate them accordingly.
-No, it's fine.
I love energetic employees.
I'll make an exception
and tell you my thoughts.
In business,
it's important to avoid risks.
It's no exception
in the security industry.
If there are potential risks
in an assignment,
just throw it to a subcontractor.
A subcontractor…
We have our meals over here.
I usually make breakfast,
and the part-time housekeeper
makes lunch and dinner.
As for the location of objects,
please relay it to her
in terms of clock position.
For example, "Your scores are
at your 12 o'clock position."
I understand.
These drawers…
Is this for suicide prevention?
No. I can't allow her hands
to get injured,
so we usually lock up any drawers
that could potentially cause injury.
If I recall, your mother passed away
three years ago?
Yes.
Ema got into an accident
when she was five years old.
Our father passed away from the accident,
and she lost her vision.
Putting her own life on the line,
our mother spent her entire life
bringing Ema up to be a skillful pianist
despite her visual impairment.
-Do you play the piano as well, Ms. Miwa?
-Yes.
I attended piano lessons at the church
up until middle school.
The piano sounds Ema heard
during my practice
was the reason why
she became interested in playing it.
Good morning, Ms. Ema.
Today, you'll be having your final lesson
at the conservatory,
and then your send-off party
will be held later tonight.
We'll be with you.
Please rest assured.
I don't need the stick
in places I'm familiar with.
I'm sorry. Please show us the way then.
-We've arrived at the conservatory.
-I know.
The piano faculty is over this way.
It's dangerous, so please
hold the stick while you're outdoors.
Isn't it your job
to protect me from danger?
There's an elevated step
in your 12 o'clock position.
There's a group of people
in your 11 o'clock position.
You're doing quite well for someone
who did last-minute cramming.
Bodyguards often use the clock position
when protecting our clients.
The clock is
a universal concept, after all.
Hey, Ema Morio is here.
-Hey, don't you think she can see?
-She must've been lying!
Ema!
Who is this man?
Everyone is waiting for you.
You're her bodyguards, right?
I heard from Ms. Miwa.
I'm Sakurai. I used to teach Ema.
This way, please.
Please.
Oh, Ema!
The day is finally here, Ema.
The International Piano Competition
values expressive artists.
Please forget about your handicap
and play to your heart's content.
What's the matter, Ema?
Your professor
is offering kind words of advice to you.
I'll take your bag.
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE ANY TALENT!
Now, please play
as if you're at the actual event.
What was that paper?
It was a message of encouragement.
Please read it, Mr. Sakurai.
What?
Please perform to
the best of your abilities!
We're cheering you on.
You're lying.
It probably says that
I'm given special treatment
because of my handicap, right?
It's what you and all the students
think of me.
Are you all right?
Don't pity me.
That was my fault.
So why would you ask if I'm all right?
That's a strange thing to say.
I'm sorry.
You're right. I said that out of habit.
Please forgive me.
There's a place I want to go to.
-Where is it?
-Shibuya.
Why?
You have a send-off party tonight.
No particular reason.
I like the smell of the streets there.
I'm sorry.
I…
I outsourced a dangerous job
to Shimazaki and Takanashi.
Why are you apologizing to me?
I have nothing to do with them anymore.
But somehow,
don't you think it's strange?
That when the president
talked about Shimazaki and Takanashi…
he sounded very cold.
The security industry
is already lacking manpower,
yet he doesn't even make them stay,
even though they're so capable.
-It's really strange.
-I'm surprised.
So you aren't just
goody two-shoes after all.
There's no need to say
that you're surprised.
This is 03. The client is leaving. Over.
-This is 01. Understood.
-This is 02. Understood.
-That was amazing, sir.
-I'm glad to hear that.
-It was wonderful.
-Thank you.
-I hope I can create another masterpiece.
-Yes.
There's an elevated step.
How much is this?
It's 10,800 yen.
Does it look good on me?
Yes, it does.
Don't just answer without thinking.
You guys can see.
I believe that looks good as well,
but for you, Ms. Ema…
I believe this would suit you better.
You can feel the fabric for yourself.
Is this an objective opinion?
Or your subjective opinion?
I'm sorry. That was my own preference.
Then I can trust what you say.
Excuse me. I'll have this.
Yes.
It's almost time.
Let's head to the send-off party
after making the payment.
I'm hungry. I want to have a steak.
I understand. This way, please.
It might be a little late,
but don't you think Professor Ivanov's
teaching methods aren't suited for Ema?
Mr. Ivanov has connections
with the judging panel.
We need him in order to claim first place
in the competition.
There are things that are
more important than lobbying!
Could you please let me tutor Ema again?
As someone
who has known her for a long time,
it would help to stabilize
Ema's emotions as well.
She's aiming for international fame,
so it's normal to feel tormented.
I'll be honest with you.
I won't allow you to teach Ema anymore.
Don't get the wrong idea.
It wasn't because we broke up.
It's all for the sake of Ema's talent.
I'm Takanashi, Ms. Ema's bodyguard.
At Ms. Ema's request,
we're currently in a restaurant named
Bonne Femme located in Omotesando.
Bonne Femme?
Yes.
The send-off party starts at 6:30 p.m.
The conservatory's president
will be there,
as well as the vice-minister of
the Agency for Cultural Affairs,
-so make sure you bring her there on time.
-We'll take her there after her meal.
Hello.
That place you're at,
I heard that Ms. Ema and Ms. Miwa
used to frequent that restaurant
together with their mother
before she passed away.
Did you come here
when she was under your watch?
No. Ms. Ema made a promise
that she will not go to that restaurant
until she wins the competition.
What?
Doesn't that mean she already
gave up on the competition,
and that she doesn't want to
go to Poland anymore?
If she really killed herself,
you guys would gain a bad reputation
for failing to protect your client.
I'm hanging up
if you're just here to ridicule me.
Do you know why
she's running away from the piano?
The problem lies with her sister,
who is managing her.
She only tries to put herself in danger
in front of her sister.
I can understand her
since I have a sister.
Some sisters share a strange relationship.
Stop beating around the bush.
Just make yourself clear.
Human relationships cannot be
made clear with words alone,
not between siblings,
and not between a man and a woman!
Please excuse me.
I told your sister that we'll bring you
to the party after your meal.
You didn't tell my sister,
but the president, did you?
Do you always call her that?
I feel at ease
when I don't see her as my sibling,
but rather as a president
managing her artist.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Can I have a glass of red wine?
Understood.
Isn't it better to just have it
as an aperitif?
I heard that you're not allowed to have
alcohol until the competition is over.
This much is fine.
SUGANUMA THINKS IT'S A RELATIONSHIP ISSUE
BETWEEN THE SISTERS.
What are you reading?
When someone keeps quiet in front of me,
it's when they're reading something
that they don't want me to know.
We were having a discussion,
and we believe that
you don't have a good relationship
with your sister.
I'm sorry that I lied to you
back at the conservatory.
I believe it's for the best
if I tell you everything from now on.
You made the right decision.
I'll answer you.
I don't trust the president.
But she set up a company for you, Ms. Ema,
and she wishes for your success
more than anyone else.
Do you know this song?
Is this Schumann?
So you know your stuff.
I played the piano when I was young.
Is there anything weird about that?
No.
This piece…
I made a mistake
when I performed it at my last recital.
The president reprimanded me
and said I wasn't giving it my all.
In that person's eyes,
I'm just an asset in her work.
But…
Ms. Miwa said that
she wants to realize your dream of winning
the International Piano Competition.
If I win the competition,
do you know what people will say?
"Ema Moria, the visually-impaired artist,
wins first place."
"It's a remarkable achievement
as the first blind pianist to win
the International Piano Competition."
That's not my dream,
yet during my interviews and promotion,
the president kept emphasizing
my visual impairment.
My visual impairment is not the reason
why I can play the piano.
Being blind is nothing special.
I don't want to use it to my advantage.
I understand.
Please excuse me.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is the wagyu steak you ordered.
Please excuse me.
Smells good.
Aren't you two eating?
We're not allowed to eat on duty.
We sure are some troublesome customers.
I've apologized to the restaurant.
I'll cut the steak for you.
Don't!
You know,
steak tastes better
when you cut it yourself.
There's a long flight of stairs ahead,
-so please hold on to me.
-Don't touch me.
I don't want anyone's help
just to get down a flight of stairs.
-Excuse me.
-What is going on?
Can you see the perpetrator
from there, Takanashi?
I think they're using a slingshot.
It's a guy, probably around 180cm tall.
-Back me up.
-Understood!
Don't worry. When the time comes…
When the time comes,
I'll cover you and we'll run
toward your two o'clock.
Let's move!
Ms. Ema…
Can you stand up?
Please get in.
Mr. Sakurai?
Let me go…
It doesn't seem like there is any
physical or nerve injury in her fingers.
Are you feeling any pain?
No.
I'm glad.
You're Japan's treasure, after all.
Let's take an echocardiogram,
just in case.
Okay.
I'll leave it to you, Kobayashi.
Sorry that I had to ask for your help
while you're off-duty, Dr. Kasamatsu.
It's all right.
I stayed back to do
some administrative work anyway.
-What about you, Mr. Shimazaki?
-What?
Your back.
Those bruises must be quite a pain.
I can tell just by looking at you.
I'll visit you after I'm done with
this assignment. It's rather painful.
You should ask your company
for some hazard pay.
Oh, I'm sorry to inform you so late,
but I already resigned from my company.
Oh, I see.
What?
I followed your advice
and gave my superior a good kick.
-No way…
-Now, I've gone independent
and set my up own office.
Then this is quite
a big assignment for you.
You know,
humans instinctively stretch out
their hands when they fall over.
Even more so for those
who are visually impaired. But she…
She covered her hands as she fell.
This means that you've done a good job
protecting her hands,
the part of her body that
she valued the most, Mr. Shimazaki.
Let's go, Ms. Ema.
The send-off party is starting soon.
I…
won't participate in the competition.
Everyone will be unhappy if I go.
Mr. Sakurai…
He used to be a good person.
He taught me passionately.
But ever since he stopped teaching me,
he didn't like the idea of me
growing as an artist.
-That's why he did that.
-Not only that.
I think the reason why
he didn't marry the president
-was because of me too.
-He was together with your sister?
The president…
rejected Mr. Sakurai's proposal.
She said that
in order to realize my dream,
she cannot afford to get married.
I didn't want this.
One should only play the piano
to make people happy.
The one who taught me
the joy of playing the piano…
was that person.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid of dying now?
No!
-Let's go.
-I don't want to go back!
We won't go back.
What?
Where are we going?
The time is 6:47 p.m.
We've arrested the suspect on grounds
of assault and property damage.
-The weapon is a hunting slingshot, and…
-Will you be filing a police report?
We'll contact you again
after consulting with the victim.
As if you'll file one.
It's going to be a huge scandal!
Hey!
POLICE
Please leave your message after the tone.
Hello? I'm done handing the guy
over to the police.
Where are you?
You don't know where Ema is?
-Are you joking?
-I'm really sorry.
I know that she went to the hospital
with Shimazaki, but after that…
I'm unable to reach them by phone.
Unbelievable.
How can a bodyguard take their client out
without permission?
I'm truly sorry.
I was surprised by
what Mr. Sakurai had done.
I'm sure Ema must be
even more shocked by that.
-I'm calling the police!
-Please wait.
I believe there must be a reason.
What reason would it be?
-This is an abduction!
-I'm angry too.
However, Shimazaki always
takes any action as a bodyguard.
He is not someone
who just abandons his duties.
This place…
So you know.
That's because I can hear
the weather vane.
So it was never fixed.
Please come out.
-Please excuse me.
-What?
Hey, wait!
I never expected you to visit us again.
It's an honor.
You're leaving for Poland soon, right?
Along with the children,
I'm looking forward to your performance.
Why did you bring me here?
I wanted to bring you here, to the place
where you first started playing the piano.
This isn't part of a bodyguard's job.
Your sister told me
to protect you so that you can perform
at your best during the competition.
So what?
You think my feelings will change
from such a cheap tactic?
I'm not that simple-minded.
You said you didn't want to use
your blindness to your advantage, right?
But you walk around
without a guiding stick
and jump in front of cars,
worrying your sister and those around you.
-Shut up.
-Aren't you using it to your advantage?
If Ema is unable to join the competition,
do you know how much trouble
it will cause other people?
How much trouble?
What?
Please give me a detailed explanation.
The music association,
our sponsors, publishers,
and record companies…
Those supporting her would incur losses,
and we would betray their expectations.
What about you, Ms. Miwa?
What do you think?
Please excuse me.
Hello. What are you doing?
Ms. Miwa said that
she's going to call the police!
I thought so.
What?
We'll return Ms. Ema to her
once she agrees to our condition.
Please relay that message to her.
Stop joking around!
The location is Setagaya Malfa Church.
The current time is 7:46 p.m.
-Synchronized.
SETAGAYA MALFA CHURCH
What are you doing?
Let's go back, Ema!
The VIPs are waiting for you.
-We have to greet them!
-Can I state my condition?
I don't really want to hear
what you have to say,
but what is it?
Ms. Ema wants you
to resign from your position
as the president of the company.
If you agree to that,
then she will do her best
in the competition.
I don't understand what you're getting at.
Ms. Ema.
Please stop working for my sake.
What are you saying?
You can't do anything without me!
-You're not normal!
-I am normal!
I know everything.
You injured your own hands deliberately.
You told Mom that you quit the piano
because I asked you to?
I never asked that of you!
I was so torn.
I had no choice but to listen to you.
But not anymore.
It doesn't make me happy to win
a competition by sacrificing others!
Marry someone you like,
and get a job you love!
I want to do this alone!
I hate you, Miwa!
Ema…
When I heard you playing the piano,
I…
realized that I had no talent.
That's why I ran from it.
I was miserable.
I wanted to die.
But now,
I really want
to help you realize your dream, Ema.
And I would do anything
to achieve that.
If you can't even tell what I feel,
how would you be able to play anything
that moves people's hearts?
Ms. Ema.
If you truly think that
being blind is nothing special,
then isn't it fine to be brazen
and ask someone for help
to realize your dream?
Ms. Ema, I believe
you don't need to use anything
to your advantage.
Will you really be fine alone?
You're persistent.
I knew you would say that.
Wishing you all the best.
Thank you, Mr. Shimazaki.
You…
Yes?
Nothing.
See you.
I am indebted to you.
As I was talking to Mr. Takanashi,
I remembered some things
that I had forgotten.
Oh, right.
In fact, I forgot something too.
-This is the invoice. If you may.
-You shouldn't give it to her now.
SECURITY SERVICES FOR MS. EMA MORIO
TOTAL AMOUNT: 368,000 YEN
Didn't Mr. Shimazaki get hurt?
-What about his medical fees?
-It's fine. It's nothing serious.
-You two make a good combination.
-Really?
I guess.
You two bicker
and don't seem to get along,
but you both know
what each other is thinking.
I understand what Ema is thinking too.
Just now…
I think Ema wanted to tell you this,
Mr. Shimazaki.
"Thank you for protecting my dream."
Well then, we'll be taking our leave.
-How are you feeling now?
-So she left safely.
-I feel quite relaxed.
-I'm glad.
As expected of Zaki and Nashi.
Maybe I should join
Shimazaki Security too.
You're going to get it from me
the next time I hear that.
-Oh, you're leaving early today?
-Good work.
Good work.
I'M DOING OVERTIME TODAY.
I'LL BE 30 MINUTES LATE…
THAT'S OKAY. THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO CHECK ON ANYWAY.
SEE YOU LATER THEN!
SURE
KOUMEI RYU
This spells trouble.
-I only have plain water. Is that fine?
-Yes.
Good work.
That client was extremely exhausting.
I never expected you to learn the piano.
I only learned for two years, though.
-Do you really plan to work with me?
-Don't make me repeat myself.
But you know,
we won't just be receiving normal clients
as we did back in Kicks Guard,
and there might be
more dangerous assignments.
I'll be fine as long as you keep me fed.
Then I guess I should let you know
the real reason why I left Kicks Guard.
Do not reveal it to anymore.
Can you promise me that?
If necessary, yes.
Well, it also involves
Suganuma and Sawaguchi,
who are still in Kicks Guard.
It's also to protect the position
of bodyguards like us in society.
In order to garner
sympathy votes for Mr. Kuwata
and to promote your own company,
did you two come up
with that ridiculous plan?
And you decided not to target Mr. Kuwata,
but Sawaguchi, the most inexperienced
in our division?
But if you don't agree with my methods,
you are free to leave.
Please promise that
you will never do anything to mess with
the bodyguards working on-site ever again.
Otherwise…
I will expose everything that
you and Mr. Kuwata have done.
The man that supposedly
attacked the assemblyman
came to the restaurant yesterday.
He might be targeting you.
Are you fine with that?
Yes.
The two of them
are remarkable, aren't they?
I'm glad that we handed over
the assignment to them.
Wasn't it different
from what you intended?
You guys really are interesting.
Today,
I have something important
to tell you, Suganuma.
I believe that it is my duty
to change the uncouth image
that people have of the security industry.
To achieve that,
I require the power of a woman like you.
Yes.
How about this?
Would you like to join me
in managing the company?
What? Management?
I would like to prepare you
to become an executive member
of our company.
I want to help you.
In private matters too, if possible.
I've already investigated
your relationship with Takanashi.
It doesn't seem like you're in
a constructive relationship right now.
I always do a thorough investigation
of what I want.
That is how I do things.
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
I see that she won second place.
It was all worth it that you pulled off
a Shinsengumi on her, Mr. Shimazaki.
A "Shinsengumi"?
The Ikedaya stair-tumbling act.
I see.
For the record, I don't think
it's a commendable act as a doctor.
I'm sorry.
I knew this would happen,
but I just couldn't help it and…
And what?
Nothing. When it comes to my work…
That hurts… I just tend to go all out.
You really are a bodyguard,
through and through.
-Okay, all done.
-Thank you.
Yes?
You left Kicks Guard, right?
Yes.
-And you're working as a freelancer?
-Yes.
Actually,
I know someone
who is looking for a bodyguard.
Are you interested
in learning more about it?
What?
I think you should be able to receive
a huge sum as a reward.
However, it's quite dangerous
in various ways.
I mean, this is
a high-risk occupation after all--
It's very dangerous.
I wasn't able to contact her,
and she wasn't in her room too.
Assist me!
He has guts. Do your best to protect me.
You think I asked him to follow you?
That man is treading on a dangerous path.
Stop playing around
with the lives of bodyguards!
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu