Just look at this!
We've just spotted him
among this huge crowd of fans.
The ace of Japan's
national soccer team, Junya Kono,
has made a dashing entrance.
The scoring champion
three years running for Kamakura Regulus,
Junya has transferred to
the famous Italian club, Piedmont FC.
-Thank you.
-He's just returned to Japan.
Junya!
You traitor!
You left Japan just for the money!
You can have this back.
Stand back.
-Hey!
-Hey, Junya!
Let's go.
Okay, go ahead.
Sorry. Please take a detour.
There's construction going on.
Sorry.
Thanks. Sorry.
CLOSED TO TRAFFIC
-Dang, it's cold.
-It's rough tonight.
Here, have one.
I brought extras.
-You sure?
-Yes.
You sure are used to this.
Have you been doing guard work for long?
Well, about six years.
Really?
For a guy like me on a pension,
it's a good way to make some extra money.
But it must be boring for a young guy.
I'm not young.
You're younger than me.
I didn't notice.
Excuse me!
Hold on! Excuse me!
There's construction going on.
Please take a detour.
We're in a hurry. Let us through.
Sorry, but nobody's allowed through.
Can you please help us?
Well, I can't let an accident happen here.
Sorry.
There's construction going on. Sorry!
-Sorry!
-Hey!
What about that car just now?
It went without permission.
Are you kidding?
Aren't you supposed to keep people out?
-Do your job!
-Calm down!
Arguing with the guard
won't change anything. Right?
-Sorry!
She got away, darn it!
Can you believe this?
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI, TRAFFIC GUARD DIVISION,
HINODE SECURITY SERVICE
WILL THE GAFFE MINISTER,
AIKO TACHIHARA, STEP DOWN?
I heard.
You let a car through an off-limits area.
I'm very sorry.
That was a big help.
You kept it from becoming an issue.
That client is very sensitive.
Thank you.
Actually, I called you here
about something else.
We'll be starting
a Personal Security Division.
We'll be needing bodyguards.
PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
When we think of bodyguards in Japan,
we think they're used by
celebrities and rich people.
But these days,
anyone could get caught up in a crime.
People are beginning to believe
that security comes only at a price.
Experience is crucial
for private security companies.
It would be very reassuring
if you joined the division.
Well...
I really appreciate that you
helped me get back on my feet.
But Mr. President, I'm sure you must know,
in the bodyguard profession,
anyone who has failed at his job
cannot return to it.
There's no reason for anyone to know.
I have no intention of telling anyone
about what happened six years ago.
You'll be like everyone else on the team.
You'll be assigned to
the Personal Security Division
as a novice bodyguard.
Novice?
But a long period of inactivity
can be fatal to a bodyguard.
I've aged a lot too.
I'm sure my senses have dulled.
Is this really what you want?
Shimazaki...
I want you to make
a magnificent comeback for me.
I'm sure you can do that.
It hurts!
I want you to start training.
Personal security can't be done alone.
It requires teamwork.
SEITARO SAWAGUCHI
CRISIS MANAGEMENT
I found it.
I've already gotten people
from other departments.
MASAYA TAKANASHI
CASH TRANSPORT SECURITY
MAYU SUGANUMA
STORE SECURITY DIVISION
I'm expecting that it'll be a great team.
GORO MURATA
BUILDING SECURITY DIVISION
Stand back! You want to die?
-You left yourself wide open.
-That hurt.
He has a knife. I'm unarmed.
You learned what to do.
Unlike the Security Police,
private bodyguards aren't allowed
to carry guns since they're too deadly.
But does the practice have to be
so realistic?
This is our final training.
That's why I want you
to go at it for real.
Watch it! I'll kill this woman!
That hurts! Help me!
Go ahead.
Well done.
Sorry.
What? Was that just luck?
How did that happen?
Let's do it again.
I'm impressed by how
you're always training.
What do you want?
OSAMU HIKAWA
CHIEF OF SECURITY, MPD
Minister Aiko has received a package.
YOSHIAKI OCHIAI
SECURITY BUREAU (SP), MPD
MPD to bomb disposal captain.
Describe the object.
The object is a brown paper bag.
It's addressed to
the Minister of Health, Labor and Welfare,
Aiko Tachihara.
Sender unknown.
We'll be doing an x-ray next.
When did the package arrive?
Around 3:00 p.m.
It was mixed in with other packages.
I wonder if it isn't really
a present from a fan.
When I was a news anchor,
I got fan mail every day.
It must be about my gaffes.
There are old batteries inside.
Batteries?
X-ray inspection complete.
The object is not a bomb.
We'll open and examine the contents now.
Here it is.
"Pride is man's biggest enemy."
"Resign, or the starting gun
will signal your death."
"From your ex-fan."
This is awfully malicious for a prank.
I've received lots of requests
for my resignation,
but this is the first threat.
What do they mean by "starting gun"?
Do you have any idea what it means?
No.
Could they be referring to
the Sumida River Marathon?
It's a marathon that takes place
in her electoral district.
The Minister will be acting as
the starter for the race.
This could be a warning
that if the Minister doesn't resign,
they'll go after her there.
Please don't attend.
Okay. I'll notify them
that she can't attend.
Wait.
I don't want to give in to this threat.
I'll have SP guarding you
around the clock.
-Have this examined.
-Yes, sir.
-Increase the guards.
Kiyota, report to Section 4
and inform Nakamura and Tanaka.
Yes, sir.
I'm at the Diet Members'
Office Building in Nagatacho.
Yesterday, at around 3:00 p.m.,
the police were called to report
that Minister Aiko Tachihara
had received a mysterious package.
After receiving the call,
the riot police squad...
Hurry up and eat or you'll be late.
I know.
As you can see, the police line
has been removed...
What about your school?
If you're not going back home,
then transfer to a closer school.
Do you want me to go back to Mom?
That's not what I mean.
If you want to live here, Shun,
then that's fine.
I'm not here
because I want to be with you.
Mom just got married.
I don't want to get in her way.
I want her to be happy this time.
I see.
How considerate.
This morning at 7:30 a.m.,
Minister Tachihara appeared
at the Diet Members' Office Building,
but quickly entered
without speaking to the press.
That's...
She's your type, isn't she?
Okay, that's enough.
Lock up when you leave.
Government sources say the incident
was only to be expected,
and that there will be more calls
for her to step down.
That's all. Back to you.
Be careful on your way to school.
You're so handsome!
You're all bodyguards, right?
You look just like that Eastwood guy.
And you're like...
that Kevin-something guy.
You're like Nicholas.
Oh, and you're like Whitney.
She was being guarded.
That was before my time.
Excuse me. Who are you?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm here because you need insurance.
This is a dangerous job,
so you need to be prepared.
The company has insurance.
I don't have money to spend on this.
Just between us,
your president is a cheapskate.
He makes sure the client is well-insured,
but not the employees.
Here, Kevin.
You must have three children, right?
You need to leave your lovely wife
with 500,000...
No, I don't need that.
You're not even close anyway.
You could get shot, you know?
Don't jinx us by talking like that.
Oh, it's the manager!
I've prepared a special plan for you.
I'll look it over carefully later.
We just have an urgent job.
Hey! Wait! Making exits is my specialty.
Wait! I...
Goodbye.
Hey, wait!
Okay.
PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
That was no lie.
Congratulations on completing
your difficult training.
We have our first job.
First, have a look at this.
FIRST TIME ASSUMING OFFICE
HEALTH, LABOR, AND WELFARE MINISTRY
Yesterday at 3:00 p.m.,
a package from a former fan arrived
at the office of the Health, Labor,
and Welfare Minister, Aiko Tachihara.
Though it only contained old batteries,
and nobody was injured,
it included a threatening letter.
It's believed to be a reaction
to the gaffe she made the other day.
Employment is definitely on the rise.
To be perfectly clear,
jobs aren't just handed out.
The unemployed must take
some of the responsibility.
Take responsibility?
What do you mean by that?
What do you mean by "take responsibility"?
-Any comment for the perpetrator?
-Is your gaffe the cause?
Minister Tachihara!
People want to hear from you!
I've known this reporter for a long time.
I'll give you a three-minute interview.
What? No way!
Hey! Minister!
Thank you.
-What's going on?
-Why the special treatment?
-Hey!
-Stand back!
WEEKLY OPINION
Thank you, Minister.
I'm glad you're giving me
an exclusive interview.
Mr. Inukai, you're not like
those gossip reporters.
You're a journalist.
Let's begin.
Do you think your gaffe
is the cause of this threat?
Yes.
However, I don't believe
what I said was a gaffe.
Everyone is interpreting my use
of "responsibility" in a bad way.
It also means having self-respect,
and not taking handouts.
So you have no intention of stepping down.
Of course not.
I will also attend
the Sumida River Marathon as planned.
I won't run away.
The client is the chairman
of Sasuke Foods, Sasuke Okubo, age 71.
They sponsor the Sumida River Marathon.
He's an old acquaintance of our president.
He has asked us to guard him
during the awards ceremony.
So we're not protecting
Minister Tachihara?
What a disappointment. If it were
a politician, we'd get better pay.
The MPD's Security Police
guard politicians just fine.
They would never ask for private help.
What a jerk.
Chairman Okubo is worried that
he'll end up as collateral damage
if Minister Tachihara gets attacked.
That was just a prank, right?
If you're not serious, you'll get hurt.
They were only batteries.
The BG for this assignment is...
Allow me to do it.
BG isn't just an abbreviation
for bodyguard.
It's the person who sticks
closest to the client,
and who gives orders to the team.
Any mistake could be fatal.
-Oh, such a strong sense of duty.
-Yours is too weak!
-Who asked you?
-Now, now.
-All right. You're in charge, Takanashi.
-Yes, sir.
Shimazaki, you assist Takanashi,
and deal with the MPD.
Yes, sir.
Suganuma and Sawaguchi,
check out the venue and schedule.
-Yes, sir.
I'm Takanashi from Personal Security
at Hinode Security Service.
I'll be handling your security.
Likewise, I'm Shimazaki.
I'm counting on you.
I'll pay you whatever it takes.
I'm not letting myself
get incidentally killed!
Please, sit down.
-Thank you.
Do you know the seating arrangement?
Please.
-This is it.
-Thank you.
18TH SUMIDA RIVER MARATHON VIP SEATING
CONFIDENTIAL
You're sitting far from the Minister, sir.
Just because I'm far away,
doesn't mean I'm safe!
If she's attacked by
a machine gun or a bomb,
I could become collateral damage.
The MPD will also be at the event.
All attendees will be carefully checked.
Just between us,
I secretly received
the contents of the threatening letter
from Aiko Tachihara's secretary.
I really doubt this was simply a prank.
Even so, the police didn't take
my request seriously.
But they'll use dozens of people
to protect a politician.
Just how much in taxes do they think
this company pays to the country?
Don't worry.
Even if the worst happens,
I'll shield you.
I don't want to die!
You'll sacrifice yourself for me, right?
That's right.
Mr. Chairman,
I hate to be rude,
but have you thought about
not even going to the venue?
-What?
-You said you don't want to die.
If you don't go, there's no chance
you'll get killed by accident.
I must go!
The Sumida River Marathon commemorates
the success of our new ramen,
and was the first event we sponsored.
I sponsored it
because I wanted our success
to last long like a marathon.
It has been nearly 20 years.
I've sponsored it during
both good times and bad.
For me and my employees,
the Sumida River Marathon is
a source of moral support.
I understand.
We'll do everything to protect you.
Are you afraid?
What?
Yes, I guess so.
If even this scares you,
then you're unfit to be a bodyguard.
-You think so?
-If you're not ready to die,
then you can't shield the client.
But if the shield dies,
that's not good either.
Don't get smart.
You could get injured if you try too hard.
That's the kind of job this is.
I'm not trying to be smart.
If we bodyguards get hurt,
the client is unprotected.
Isn't that...
the same as running away from a job?
I mean, if we're going to protect
the client, we can't get hurt--
I won't get hurt.
Wow, you have such confidence.
That's dangerous.
You're just trying to justify
your cowardice.
No, attackers have a huge advantage
over the protectors.
If a guy points a gun at us,
we're unarmed and totally useless.
Isn't that scary?
What's so funny?
You look good in that pose.
Then be afraid. What do I care?
I'll handle everything.
I can protect him all by myself. Bye.
You're the one who's unfit for this job.
If I'm afraid, therefore,
I'll work out strategies
to avoid any danger.
If you're not afraid,
you could do something desperate.
You see...
I'm afraid to work with someone
who's not afraid.
Hey!
Six of us SP officers
will guard Minister Tachihara.
Venue security will be handled
by the local security bureau,
and 180 Riot Police officers.
This isn't an official function
for the Minister.
Dispatching 180 men
because of a prank? What a joke!
However, no fingerprints were found
on the threatening letter.
It's dangerous to brush this off
as a simple prank.
Let's just go with it.
If the Civil Party owes us a favor,
then it'll make our bosses happy.
Isn't that right, Ochiai?
But if something goes wrong,
we'll all be ruined.
So I'll do my best.
Situation normal.
This has become a real problem.
There's been criticism of
the party leaders as well.
They want us to make you step down
as soon as possible.
Can you go on standby for a while?
We'll be waiting outside.
I'm terribly sorry. I'll settle this soon.
Make sure it's handled
before the next Diet session.
You were a monotone newscaster,
but I backed your political career!
You've put my position in jeopardy!
I understand that this is my last chance.
I've set things in motion.
This is your own responsibility, you know.
I'm Shimazaki
from Hinode Security Service.
This is our security plan
for the Sumida River Marathon.
Let me have a look.
We're guarding the chairman
of the sponsor, Sasuke Foods.
I see.
I'm Ochiai. I'll be in charge of security.
-Let me have a look.
-Yes, sir.
Oh, you're Minister Tachihara's bodyguard.
Have we met before?
Pardon me. I've seen you before.
This isn't your final plan, is it?
No, it is.
Sorry, but could you tell me
what's wrong with it?
Figure it out yourself.
To avoid leaks,
I can't cooperate with private security.
I will say this though.
You do realize you'll be unarmed, right?
Pardon the expression,
but private security is
no better than yojimbo thugs.
SUMIDA SPORTS STADIUM
GATE CLOSED
SECURITY ROOM
There's nobody here.
Afternoon.
You left it open.
MINISTER'S SEAT
The client's position.
CLIENT POSITION
The meet-up point.
MEET-UP POINT
Gunshots.
If she's attacked by
a machine gun or a bomb,
I could become collateral damage.
GUNMAN
60-DEGREE ANGLE
6.6 METERS
11.8 METERS
Less than 12 meters.
In a bombing scenario...
the elevator probably wouldn't work.
BOMB, SERIOUS INJURY, MINOR INJURY
6.6 METERS
A maximum of 20,000 spectators.
8.2 METERS, EXIT
Secure an escape route...
Intruder!
No, I'm not!
I'm not. Really!
You must realize it's illegal entry
if you don't get permission.
We're in the same business.
But we did mess up
our security procedures as well.
Sorry. I wanted to scout for security.
Just in case, let's see your ID.
I'm really sorry.
-Hurry up.
-Okay. That hurts.
Sorry.
Hey!
Why is this broken?
You poor thing.
It's not funny.
It wasn't easy to scout that place out.
I know. Good work.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
I'll share this with Takanashi.
Actually...
Takanashi said he wanted to quit.
Quit?
Just this BG assignment, right?
No, the Personal Security Division.
He wants to return
to the Cash Transport Division.
That was sudden.
I tried to persuade him not to.
Not sure if it helped though.
Can you be the leader
for this one, Shimazaki?
Okay.
Even after passing that tough training,
he sure...
gave up easily.
He used to be a member
of the Self-Defense Forces.
He had the knowledge and talent.
He was fired up about leading everyone,
but I guess it wasn't what he expected.
Bodyguards seem flashy and cool.
But it's actually quite dull.
There are lots of odd clients too.
Well, I wouldn't worry about it.
This is what he wants.
So what did you used to do, Shimazaki?
What?
Everyone in our company
used to work elsewhere.
Oh, I should tell you about myself first.
It's okay.
I used to be a police officer.
Are you sure it's okay to tell me?
I was a terrible officer.
I was always a burden,
so it became hard to stick around.
My skills were worthless elsewhere,
so I ended up at a security company.
Now, I'm the boss of
the Personal Security Division.
When it comes right down to it,
I guess I enjoy protecting people.
-Here.
-Thanks.
I...
used to be a guard
at a different security company.
You seem unusually composed,
so I wondered what you did.
I can tell you used to be a cop.
I feel like I'm being questioned.
I told you,
I was a terrible police officer.
NEW EMAIL FROM SATORU INUKAI
WEEKLY OPINION REPORTER
Thank you. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Here you go.
I'll be waiting outside.
MINISTER AIKO TACHIHARA WILL FIGHT!
(I WON'T RUN AWAY)
I RESPECT AIKO. WELL SAID.
DON'T GIVE IN TO THREATS!
WHO DOES SHE THINK SHE IS?
WHAT A JOKE.
Yes.
IS THE THREAT
REALLY DUE TO THE GAFFE?
However, I don't believe
what I said was a gaffe.
Everyone is interpreting my use
of "responsibility" in a bad way.
Hello?
That's quite an impartial article.
I'm glad I trusted you.
But I hope you're all right.
If this provokes the perpetrator
and he attacks you,
then we're partly responsible.
Don't be silly.
That was only a prank.
Can you be so certain?
Yes.
The fact that they used a quote
from Shakespeare
means that they're not serious.
Shakespeare?
You mean the threatening letter?
Since you've been so impartial,
I'll tell you, Mr. Inukai.
It said, "Pride is man's biggest enemy."
What rubbish.
EVENT DAY
JANUARY 21, SUNDAY
Here are the radio codes.
The starting point,
the staff entrance, is P1.
Corridor is P2, backyard is P3.
Memorize the rest.
Shimazaki, the BG, is 01. I'll be 02.
-Okay, I'm 03.
-I'm 04.
Well then...
the estimated attendance
for today's event,
including event coordinators,
is 16,000 people.
Focus on your duty,
and put the client first!
Are you nervous?
-Extremely.
-You're kidding.
That was only a threat.
They'll never attack.
The client is just a rich coward.
Sawaguchi!
What did you learn about what happens
when you assume you're safe in a crisis?
-Normalcy bias.
-That's right!
You could misjudge the danger you face.
-Remember that.
-Okay.
A little nervousness is just right,
within bounds.
Yes, sir.
-Synchronized.
-Do your best out there.
I'm at the Sumida Sports Park Track.
Minister Tachihara has received threats
regarding her gaffe,
but she's opening the race here today.
The event operators announced
that security would be
greater than at past events.
As you can see, strict checks
of all bags are being conducted.
We all hope that the event ends
without incident.
1. HANDBAG SEARCH
2. METAL DETECTORS
-I have an armband.
-Thank you.
I'll do it myself.
Thank you.
Point 6, situation normal.
After the Minister arrives,
we'll let the media in.
Isn't that her?
Here she comes!
You're right!
That's not her.
What a letdown.
You already checked before. Hurry up!
Ishida, there's no point
in arguing with the security.
Please.
Is it all right?
Yes.
The chairman has arrived at P1.
Entering Area 2.
This is 02, copy.
This is 03, copy.
I'm counting on you.
-You're sure it's all right?
-Yes.
Are you sure?
We're professionals after all.
Please trust us.
Then you'll block any bullets
from hitting me?
Block bullets?
Being a shield is
a bodyguard's duty, right?
I'm paying you enough!
Mr. Chairman, he's pretty slim,
so the bullets might go through.
Why don't you trust me?
Now that's guts.
No matter what happens, protect me.
We'll keep you alive, Mr. Chairman.
This way.
You lead.
The doors are closing.
We've arrived.
-Is that the Minister?
-It's the Minister!
Why is she waving?
She has no idea what people think of her.
Look at that flashy outfit.
Good morning, Mr. Chairman.
No need to bother.
Even with all the uproar,
I appreciate being given
this special task.
Oh, my!
You do this kind of security too?
Do you remember me?
Yes, I remember.
-Thank you for the other day.
-Minister.
We're from Hinode Security Service.
Good to work with you.
Mura.
It's been a while.
Let's work together, even though
you're police and I'm private security.
Work together?
I have no intention of
reliving old times here.
Murata used to be an SP.
Only the most talented can become SPs.
What's wrong?
Hello?
It's me, Takanashi.
I'm on guard duty now!
If you're going to make excuses
for dropping out, forget it.
I don't intend to apologize to you.
I've found a disturbing comment
regarding Minister Tachihara.
A comment?
"Aiko Tachihara is a liar."
"I'll prove to you that
pride is man's biggest enemy."
What do they mean by "liar"?
I don't know.
The police didn't release
the contents of the threatening letter.
Including us, only a few people know
what the letter said.
That's all.
The race will be starting soon.
The stadium is alive
with enthusiasm and anticipation.
Thank you for your patience, everyone.
The race will be starting soon.
"Liar"?
Minister Tachihara will be
entering the field. Stay alert!
Please come to the main gate,
Ms. Tachihara.
It is said that
the first marathon was run by
an ancient Greek soldier
to announce victory in battle.
After running more than 40 kilometers
and arriving at the gates of Athens,
he died.
Yes, a marathon is a strenuous race.
Just like you're taking on
this difficult race,
I have come here with
the same intention of taking on
a difficult challenge.
I take this opportunity to apologize
for the statement that has
caused so much misunderstanding.
I also promise to do my utmost
to help Japan.
18TH SUMIDA RIVER METROPOLITAN MARATHON
Now, it's time to begin
the 18th Sumida River
Metropolitan Marathon.
18TH SUMIDA RIVER METROPOLITAN MARATHON
The Minister was very brave.
This will improve her approval rating.
She's quite a woman.
Kiyota, the Chief is calling.
Take over here.
Yes, sir.
Attention...
Why no report?
Nothing has happened.
Increasing your duties
and running a big-shot site.
It must feel so good, doesn't it?
I should have invited you.
Sorry for being so rude.
Minister.
What's that smoke?
Hey!
Stay right here. I'm checking on it.
Hey! Wasn't that a bomb?
It's a bomb!
I'm not staying here!
It's dangerous here!
Run away!
Let's go.
You can't be serious.
Move the Minister from Point 3 to Point 1.
Hurry! Run away!
-Take the Chairman outside!
-This is bad. Everyone's pushing!
How will you protect me?
Mr. Chairman, there's a route out
through the parking garage.
Hey! Aren't you a professional?
You don't need to tell me!
Minister, this way!
Minister! Hurry!
Hey! Out of the way!
Out of the way! Minister!
I've lost the Minister!
Mr. Chairman,
you said this marathon was always
a source of moral support.
Yes, I did!
But this is the end of that.
I'll check that there are no more bombs.
Shimazaki!
Use Exit F, then R4 to the first floor,
north side storage.
It's narrow, but Emergency Exit 8
is 25 meters below it.
Yes, sir.
-Okay, Mr. Chairman.
-This way.
Please make way!
Please get out of the way!
Be careful!
What are you doing here?
The SPs are desperately searching for you.
This has nothing to do with you.
I'm sorry if I'm wrong,
but you know something, don't you?
Those clothes.
They're not the clothes someone
being threatened and targeted wears.
You make a great target.
Is it possible
that the threatening letter was a fake?
I knew it.
You knew what?
Your backpack.
Where did you put it?
You had one when you came in here.
It's a smoke bomb.
Black backpack, 70 centimeters.
A black backpack?
Did anyone see who brought it in?
My own client is here at this event.
If there's another bomb,
then I can't ignore it.
I only asked to interview the Minister.
She came to give me that interview, right?
"You know who wrote
the threatening letter, don't you?"
"I'll be waiting for you
in the training room."
YOU KNOW WHO WROTE
THE THREATENING LETTER, DON'T YOU?
Hey! Where are we going?
I don't want to die!
Then follow us!
Car to P9.
This is 03, the car has arrived.
Minister Tachihara,
you used this event as a platform
to restore your popularity, didn't you?
Cut it out.
Get out of my way.
Don't interfere!
Answer my question, Minister.
Get out of here!
-Cut it out!
-Leave me alone!
Don't interfere!
Cut it out!
DANGER, DO NOT SIT ON!
Let's cut this out, all right?
Go!
I've had it with you!
Let go!
Copy, 01, the chairman arrived safely
in the car. Standing by.
Do you copy, 01?
We're standing by!
Inukai!
Hands up and step forward!
You should be arresting
the Minister first.
The threatening letter
was written and sent by her.
Don't make things up!
You told me yesterday.
It said, "Pride is man's biggest enemy."
What rubbish.
Don't you remember those words?
It's what I wrote to you
when you became a minister.
In the words of Shakespeare.
"To obtain the trust of the people,
you must not have pride."
"Do your best."
"Inukai."
You must have forgotten.
That's why you used them
in your threatening letter, Minister.
Enough!
Do you know why she did that?
She wanted to make a big deal of being
the woman who stands up to threats.
I merely turned her lie into the truth.
I'm not interested in your conjectures.
Come on.
Release the Minister.
Minister...
It was me who made her a minister.
She gained popularity
thanks to the articles that I wrote.
It was all thanks to me!
Can't you say at least
one word of appreciation?
You traitor!
You really must love her.
What?
What you're saying makes no sense at all.
But you feel betrayed...
because you expected a lot from her.
You trusted her.
Shut up.
If you never trusted her...
you never would have been betrayed.
Sad, isn't it?
-Let go!
-Get back!
Let go! I have the duty
to report this as a journalist!
What a crazy fabrication!
You're no journalist.
You're just too full of yourself!
Here.
Why were you here?
Sorry. I got lost.
The event can continue now.
Excuse me.
Did that bodyguard do that on purpose?
Do what on purpose?
Nothing.
If there's anything you want to ask,
I'll answer all your questions.
There were no other bombs.
I'm returning now.
Hold it right there.
This is a request from
the MPD Security Police.
What you just overheard
regarding Minister Tachihara
must be kept secret
to protect her privacy.
Yes, I understand.
Also...
I'm against private personal security.
Money won't protect people.
This is no place for yojimbo thugs.
Do you know what "yojimbo" means?
Originally,
it didn't mean a tough guy
the mafia or samurai hired
to kill their enemies.
A pole that's used to
protect yourself from enemies...
is called a yojimbo.
-So what?
-If you hadn't drawn your guns,
I doubt he would have pulled a knife.
Even though I'm an unarmed bodyguard...
No, the fact that I'm an unarmed bodyguard
means I can offer proper protection.
It must be nice.
You private guards can say
whatever you like.
Sorry. That was pompous of me.
Excuse me.
Today at the Sumida River Marathon,
the weekly magazine reporter,
Satoru Inukai, 34 years old,
was arrested on suspicion of
-attempting to attack Minister Tachihara.
-Mr. Chairman.
For a moment,
I wasn't sure it would be okay.
But all's well that ends well.
Thank you.
I heard the newbie played
an important role.
Not at all.
Imazeki, he's still got room
to improve as a bodyguard.
He ran off looking for a bomb,
but ends up tripping and getting hurt.
I'm very sorry.
But I was reminded of...
when I first decided
to sponsor the marathon.
I was running around desperately then
just as much as you were.
I had no regrets. I was prepared to die.
DELICIOUSLY BIG
SASUKE FOODS CORPORATION
HYAKUMENSO
ASSORTED
Chicken Yuzu Soy Sauce.
I'm not about to retire yet!
If I need your help again,
I'll come to you.
Guarding you is very tough,
so allow us to negotiate the fees.
-Well, well!
-Excuse me.
She's a sharp one!
Sorry.
No problem. Not at all.
I just wanted to tell you something.
What?
I appreciate you telling me
about the "liar" comment.
-That's all.
-I have something to tell you too.
I quit because I didn't want
to be partnered with you.
Not with a liar like you.
Today, Minister of Health,
Labor, and Welfare, Aiko Tachihara,
was the starter at the 18th
Sumida River Metropolitan marathon.
There was a bomb scare at the event,
which caused an uproar.
The suspected bomb...
MESSAGE FROM AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
Bringing home ramen.
Let's pile on Welsh onions and enjoy.
I had some pizza.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
A present? I guess you're moving up.
-Thanks for this!
-No problem.
There.
How is it, being a bodyguard?
Well...
It's cooler than waving a traffic wand.
I'm not so sure...
I'm sore all over.
Really?
It's better with Welsh onions.
-Welsh onions? Nice!
-Plenty of them.
This is good!
Delicious.
Yummy.
That hurts!
Your noodles will get soggy.
Actually, I fell and got hurt.
A threat to influence the ruling
in the case.
They're after my husband.
Can't you leave me alone?
I want to meet someone.
Bring my wife back by 7:00 p.m.
You don't have the weapons
to subdue the perpetrator.
Run away. It's too dangerous here.
Madam!