THE WORLD CHANGES DRASTICALLY OVERNIGHT.
THOSE WHO CAN STAND UP TO IT
ARE PROFESSIONALS WITH THE RIGHT SKILLS.
THE NEED FOR PROTECTORS HAS ARRIVED…
CHIYODA WARD, TOKYO
JANUARY 29, WEDNESDAY
IN CELEBRATION OF ASSEMBLYMAN
TAKASHI KUWATA'S 20TH ANNIVERSARY
IN POLITICS AND THE ELECTORAL COMMITTEE
Mr. Kuwata, thank you very much.
Congratulations, Mr. Kuwata.
-Thank you.
-That is the perfect chance.
And that is why we have to go for it.
SEITARO SAWAGUCHI
BODYGUARD, KICKS GUARD
This is 01.
The performance ends in 45 seconds.
The number of guests has increased.
Everyone should exercise caution.
-Would you like something to drink?
-No, thank you.
This is 02. Understood.
Attention to all, our mission this time
is just to protect Mr. Kuwata.
Nothing more, nothing less.
-This is 03. Roger that.
-This is 04. Understood.
This is 01, to 02.
I'm the one issuing orders.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations, Mr. Kuwata.
Hello, Mr. Ryu.
Celebrating your 20th anniversary
as a politician in 2020…
That's a good omen.
I've made a lot of enemies in my work,
but I will continue on
for the sake of the people!
This is 02, to 04.
Please check out the waiter at Table B.
This is 04.
Target is holding a corkscrew
under the napkin in his right hand.
A corkscrew?
All the wines here
should have been uncorked beforehand.
That waiter is not on the employee list.
-This is 02, dealing with the situation.
-This is 03, assisting 02.
I would like a glass of champagne, please.
Please excuse us.
This is 01.
We're changing formations.
Squad B is to keep an eye
on Assemblyman Kuwata.
-This is B1. Understood.
-This is B2. Understood.
Sorry to interrupt your conversation.
We've found someone suspicious
and have removed them.
Let's head over there.
What gives you the right to do this?
You guys aren't even cops!
You're just mere bodyguards.
Don't get ahead of yourselves!
-Hey!
-Takanashi!
This is as far as our work goes.
Hopefully, he won't try anything else…
I'm sorry, Shimazaki.
What are you doing, 01?
Hey… are you all right?
What's wrong?
Do you think some good wine
will come out if I pull it out?
Personal Security Division reporting.
Team A, Sawaguchi, Takanashi, Suganuma,
and Team B, Shirai, Kawazu, Ito, Hagiwara,
have successfully completed the mission
of protecting Mr. Takashi Kuwata.
Shimazaki is currently being questioned
at the prefectural police station.
That is all.
Good work.
Mr. Kuwata and President Ryu
are pleased with your work.
It was a good advertisement for us too.
-Dismissed.
-Yes, sir.
A news article has been released.
It says that bodyguards
took down the intruder!
Those against the Political Funds Control
Law revision apparently planned this.
-There's even a video.
-What do you have to say about that?
-Oh, my.
-No matter who is behind this…
I'm glad that
it worked in our favor eventually.
Isn't it great?
Your first assignment as 01
is the talk of the town.
But Shimazaki got hurt
because that guy went after me.
He wasn't after you.
Don't be so self-conscious.
-Really?
-I will never succumb to violence.
That is all.
-Good work.
-Are you all right, Shimazaki?
-Yes, I'm fine.
I only covered for you
because I thought that
the girlfriend you finally have
might get sad if you got hurt.
How did you know
I got myself a girlfriend?
-What?
-You wouldn't shut up about it.
-She's the cutest so far, right?
-Yes.
I'm back from my questioning.
It must have been hard on you.
Not at all.
-Can we have a talk?
-Yes, sir.
What is it?
Did you do as I instructed?
Yes, I didn't file a police report.
Good job.
I'll reimburse your medical fees
under a different name.
If the media gets wind of the fact
that blood was shed there,
it could put a blemish on Mr. Kuwata's
20th-anniversary celebration.
But…
was it really okay
not to chase the criminal?
The duty of a bodyguard
is not to capture criminals.
You should draw a line
between duty and morals.
The security industry is prone
to workplace reforms,
-you should know that…
-Yes, I understand.
Shimazaki!
-Shimazaki!
-Yes?
What's wrong with your hand?
Oh, it's nothing.
This is a letter addressed to
your previous company.
-Thank you.
-Please excuse me. Good work today!
TO AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
HINODE SECURITY SERVICE
FROM SHINSUKE MATSUNO
CHIBA CITY, CHIBA PREFECTURE
What's that, a love letter?
No.
Wait, this address…
ACQUAINTANCE
I knew it.
It's from Chiba Chuo Detention Center.
Is your friend in prison or something?
No…
It might be a bodyguard request.
-"Good day. I'm sorry…
-Hey.
for suddenly contacting you."
"I am Shinsuke Matsuno,
currently serving my sentence
in Chiba Chuo Detention Center."
"I am about to finish serving my sentence,
and I would like to
request Akira Shimazaki's service
to protect me upon my release."
Who is Shinsuke Matsuno again?
I think he's the one involved in
the Kanto University of Technology case.
-That's right…
-Right, the sealed room mystery!
KANTO UNIVERSITY FEMALE RESEARCHER
FATALLY SUFFOCATES IN LABORATORY COLD ROOM
This was on the news
every single day then.
COULD THIS BE A CASE OF MURDER BY
A STALKER DISGUISED AS AN ACCIDENT?
The court ruled the incident an oversight,
but the media called it
a well-planned murder, didn't they?
But why would Shinsuke Matsuno
ask Shimazaki for help?
Since he sent it to me,
I should give him a reply…
That is unnecessary.
There's no way
we would protect a criminal.
But he made the effort
to write us a letter.
-I think--
-That is not necessary.
We only serve VIPs here in Kicks Guard.
That is President Ryu's company vision.
There will be no exceptions.
I've read the letter you sent me.
I'm Shimazaki.
I'm Matsuno.
I'm sorry that
I sent you a letter so suddenly.
No, that's fine.
Excuse me, but how did you know me?
I was in the same workshop as Junya Kono,
the former soccer athlete.
I made him reveal your name.
I heard that a bodyguard protected him
with his life on the line, like a fool.
See you later, Zaki.
A "fool"…
I'm honored.
Well, I intend to visit the laboratory
after I'm released.
Wait, do you mean
where the incident occurred?
Yes.
I would like to pay my respects
to the late Ayako Itami,
and I would like to apologize
to Professor Sakagami
for causing him trouble.
I know.
Everyone says that it wasn't an accident
and that I was the one who killed her.
The press probably won't let me be,
once I'm out of prison.
But…
I really want to go to the laboratory,
no matter what.
I have to go there.
Will you protect me until I'm able to
offer my apologies to him?
I'm really sorry.
Due to our company's policy,
I am unable to accept your request.
Is that because… I'm a criminal?
I guess so.
There's no way
you would protect a murderer.
Thank you, Mr. Shimazaki.
You came all the way here
just to refuse my request.
I'm really grateful for
your consideration.
It has been a long time since
I was treated as a proper human being.
I'm glad that I sent you that request.
About Matsuno's bodyguard request,
it would've been accepted
if we were back in Hinode.
It can't be helped.
Kicks Corp. bought in Hinode.
That was tough.
Hey, how about changing your perspective?
Our salary increased,
and we only have VIPs as customers.
There's nothing to complain about
as a bodyguard.
You're really simple-minded.
Then what are you so unhappy about?
I don't know.
The security industry is growing rapidly,
for better or worse.
We have no choice but to follow suit.
I won't grow with it.
You're really childish.
Even I have my fair share of memories
back in Hinode too.
I didn't forget all of that.
But doesn't it feel much better
if you just focus on your current job?
Hey, are you listening?
Are you trying to kill me?
Fool.
SHIROYAMA GENERAL HOSPITAL
It hurts!
-That hurts!
-It's going to be done in an instant.
It wouldn't have been so painful if you
had it treated right after you got hurt.
I thought it wasn't a big deal.
Some professional you are.
Your body is an important part of
your work.
That hurts!
Come on, put it straight!
-Bite down on your teeth.
-Are you serious?
You're a demon.
Japan is getting really dangerous.
Who would've thought that
someone would launch
an assault at a party?
But my superior was happy and said that
it was a good advertisement for the firm.
Advertisement?
You should give guys like that
a good kick.
Hey, I'm working in a company.
Why are you acting all cool?
Being a bodyguard is about
protecting others,
but the company may not necessarily
protect the bodyguards themselves.
You'll die if you push yourself.
Just joking.
As a doctor,
I'm not in a position to lecture others.
Well, you're putting
your life on the line.
Make sure you don't have any regrets.
All right, all done!
I'll prescribe you
some anti-inflammatory drugs.
I'm sure you know, but please refrain
from consuming alcohol tonight.
-Yes.
-Good.
"No regrets", right…
Hinode has merged with Kicks Corp.
at the start of this year.
I'm also glad that we were given
an opportunity at this time
to provide security services
for Assemblyman Kuwata.
Why is Kicks Corp., a top IT corporation,
interested in security services?
As I traveled around the world,
I learned that the level of security
defines a nation's international standing.
With Kicks' participation
in the security industry,
we will be able to develop
new security technologies
that incorporate communication.
I hope to improve international trust
in Japan in the future.
That is my new ambition.
How is your injury, Shimazaki?
It's fine.
But I suppose injury is part and parcel
of this occupation.
Be careful.
You're the ace
that will lead our security division.
Yes, sir.
President, I came here today
to consult about something.
Please take a look at this.
Oh, this?
The request was to protect him until
he offered his apology to the victim.
What's the matter, Shimazaki?
Our target clientele is VIPs.
I'm sure you know about that.
Yes, sir.
But I would like to meet him in person.
And if possible, I would like to
help him somehow…
Is that sympathy you're feeling?
Doesn't that contradict your duty
as a bodyguard?
You know,
I want to improve the societal status
of bodyguards in Japan.
I'm sure you understand.
Oh, it's time for my dinner meeting.
Thanks for coming.
I'm always open to direct negotiation.
FROM SHINSUKE MATSUNO
You're just mere bodyguards.
Did he go to the basement?
SUBWAY
Isn't he Mr. Kuwata's…
Japan is getting really dangerous.
Who would've thought that
someone would launch
an assault at a party?
Why did you meet
with Mr. Kuwata's secretary?
You received something just now,
didn't you?
-That hurts…
-Answer me!
I said it hurts!
Hey!
What did you receive?
Were you instructed to do that
under Mr. Kuwata's instructions?
What the hell are you doing?
Did you really want all that dirty money?
Don't talk all big, you bastard.
It was your president
who came up with that plan!
If you didn't get in the way,
the incident would have just ended with
your colleague getting a small scratch!
My supporters have rapidly increased,
thanks to you.
It was right of me to say that
I will never succumb to violence.
We have also received
a lot more inquiries.
Excuse me.
There is a message for you.
Please excuse me.
-Please excuse me for a moment.
-Sure.
I'll treat you to this.
Leave after you're done drinking it.
Were you having your dinner meeting
with Mr. Kuwata?
Just now, I met with the man
who attacked Mr. Kuwata.
That man received an envelope of cash
from Mr. Kuwata's secretary.
This is a portion of it.
Please return it to Mr. Kuwata.
What are you talking about?
In order to garner
sympathy votes for Mr. Kuwata
and to promote your own company,
did you two come up
with that ridiculous plan?
And you decided not to target Mr. Kuwata,
but Sawaguchi, the most inexperienced
in our division?
Let's calm down, shall we?
President.
We bodyguards are putting our lives
on the line in our work.
Shimazaki.
The thing about business is that
it's not about working your muscles,
but working your brains.
President, your method
may help you protect money,
but it will never help you protect lives.
Is that so?
I see.
What a shame. I bought you with my money.
But if you don't agree with my methods,
you are free to leave.
Of course, I'll give you
your severance payment accordingly.
But if you do that,
I'm afraid that it'll be hard for you
to get a job in the security industry.
"I don't want to do something
that will ruin my entire career."
Aren't you thinking of that right now?
Are you going to hit me?
In the end, bodyguards only think about
resolving issues with violence.
That's why people always say that
bodyguards are no better than bouncers.
I understand.
There is no way I'm staying in Kicks Guard
after knowing something like this.
I'm resigning.
In exchange,
please promise that
you will never do anything to mess with
the bodyguards working on-site ever again.
Otherwise…
I will expose everything that
you and Mr. Kuwata have done.
Please.
Hey.
Breakfast is ready.
SHUN SHIMAZAKI
AKIRA'S SON
-Fully toasted or lightly browned?
-Fully toasted.
Two eggs. This is bad.
What about it?
Is your work dangerous today?
Will your life be in danger?
How long do you think
we've been living together?
Let's see, you came over
from your mom's place
in December during
your first year in middle school…
So it's around a year and four months?
You didn't have to calculate it.
I was using it as an analogy.
Then tell me that sooner.
You know, you usually prepare
a filling breakfast
on days when you've resolved yourself…
Hey, why are you…
…that it might be your last meal.
I don't really mind, you know.
That's the life of a bodyguard after all.
I'm glad to hear that as a man.
But make sure you've done
all the necessary procedures.
Your severance pay, condolence money,
and life insurance policies…
Make sure
I'm the beneficiary of all these.
About that…
Man, that's hot.
You know…
I resigned from my company.
-What? I didn't hear anything about this!
-That's why I'm telling you now.
Don't tell me you got retrenched?
It's not exactly that.
-Then did you sexually harass--
-There's no way I did that!
To put it simply,
I was fired.
Then what are you going to do from now on?
-In fact, what about me--
-Don't worry.
No matter what, I'll make sure
you'll be able to attend university.
"No matter what"?
Oh, right.
This…
I decided that
I'm giving this to you first.
I'm counting on you from now on.
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
BODYGUARD
I wonder what happened to Mr. Shimazaki.
He just suddenly resigned
and gave up on everything.
That is so unlike him.
I'm sure he must've had some reason.
What kind of reason?
Maybe he suddenly felt like retiring?
You think that geezer would retire?
I mean, he injured himself
before his resignation.
There are times
when humans get scared all of a sudden.
And his son is growing up too.
Maybe he felt like
having a more secure job now.
Can he really find work
other than being a bodyguard?
Chairman Sudou will arrive at 11:00 a.m.
Is everyone ready?
-Yes, sir.
Right.
I'll announce this since everyone is here.
With Shimazaki's departure,
the one to fill up the empty position
of Squad A's leader…
is you, Suganuma.
What?
President Ryu said that he would like
to make use of your image as a woman.
I hope you meet with his expectations.
Yes, sir!
He has arrived.
Pleased to meet you.
CHIBA CHUO DETENTION CENTER
Mr. Shimazaki!
You've worked hard.
I'm Shimazaki, here on
Mr. Matsuno's request for a bodyguard.
I'm Haneyama, Matsuno's attorney.
Thank you.
I've heard about what happened.
Will it really be all right for him
to go to the laboratory?
I've already obtained permission
from the professors there.
We'll reach Kamakura today, then head to
Kanto University of Technology tomorrow.
His release from prison
is still kept a secret,
but why didn't you come in a car?
Everyone would be able to see Matsuno!
I asked him to do this, Mr. Haneyama.
I can't hide from everyone forever.
I should get used to it.
I will take extra caution.
I'm counting on you.
You grew out your hair a little.
Oh, yes.
Right, here you go.
The phone you requested for.
I applied for a temporary contract
that lasts for a month.
Thank you very much.
I don't mean to be rude, but it's better
if you don't stand out from the crowd.
Please take this too.
Thank you for all these.
Actually, we've received
an anonymous call in our office
asking if it's right to let a murderer
like Matsuno roam around society freely.
I'm his attorney, so I believe in him…
but the majority of society believes that
Matsuno killed that woman.
KANTO UNIVERSITY FEMALE RESEARCHER
FATALLY SUFFOCATES IN LABORATORY COLD ROOM
THE ACCUSED, SHINSUKE MATSUNO,
AVOIDS THE DEATH PENALTY
Please don't forget that.
Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Thank you.
This is just something from me
to celebrate your release. Please.
Thank you.
Aren't you going to eat, Mr. Shimazaki?
I try my best not to eat when I'm on duty.
-All right, thank you.
-Please do.
Delicious.
I've tried the food
they served here before.
This place serves better ebi tempura than
the soba restaurant at the train station.
Please listen to me while you eat.
Usually, bodyguards work in pairs
to ensure that
we can carry out our duties perfectly.
However, I resigned from Kicks Guard,
so I will be the only one protecting you.
I understand.
Unlike police, private bodyguards are
not allowed to carry any firearms.
I've just become a freelancer,
so I can't even use a police baton.
In other words, I'm completely unarmed.
Do you understand what I'm trying to say?
Yes.
I'm sorry that I have to use
some of the pay I saved from my workshop.
-I'll pay for your service in advance--
-No, it's fine.
You can pay me after it's done.
-But I would like to--
-No.
I will gladly accept it after my work
is successfully completed.
You're scary.
Excuse me, but you didn't resign from
your company because of me, did you?
No, but I've been thinking for a while.
I felt quite restricted working
for a company,
and I thought that I might feel
more at ease if I work as a freelancer.
-I see. Even so…
-Yes.
In my case, I couldn't return
to the organization anymore,
and I can't continue my research either.
It feels rather lonely.
I told myself that
I should never forget what I did.
Oh, so this is Ayako Itami…
And the one in the middle
is Professor Sakagami.
He's the top researcher in the laboratory.
He's a wonderful researcher
who poured his entire life into his work.
But that incident happened,
and I hurt the professor
I respected the most.
But he said he's waiting for you.
If Matsuno really said that,
then I'll meet with him.
Thank you very much.
We would like to keep
the media in the dark,
so could you keep his release a secret?
Of course.
Professor Sakagami…
I'm so grateful.
Let's go, Mr. Matsuno.
Please stop taking photos
with your phones.
-We'll leave through the kitchen.
-Okay.
Sorry, thanks for the food!
-Take care.
-We'll come again.
This is 01.
I'm entering the audience's seats.
This is 03.
A man with long hair in his twenties
is approaching the target
while checking the audience's seats.
This is 01. Understood. Please confirm.
This is 02. I'm on it.
Switching places with 05.
This is 05. Understood.
Excuse me, but could you please
present your staff pass?
Why would I need one?
What is with you?
Oh, you're here, Tamotsu!
He's my second son.
Why did you stop him?
I was instructed that anyone passing by
should present their staff pass.
-Do not talk back--
-I am really sorry!
You're really rude!
You're just a bodyguard.
Who do you think you are?
Don't show what you're thinking
on your face.
You must always obey the client.
Even if the clients themselves
do not observe the rules?
That's a given.
Bodyguards are
part of the service industry.
Fawning over clients will not allow us
to get rid of threats.
Don't be so conceited.
Do you think you're special
just because you're from the JSDF?
It's no wonder why
you've been overtaken by a woman.
Takanashi.
It's just a joke.
Let's be careful with
our words and actions.
If you don't want
to end up like Shimazaki, that is.
What?
Didn't Shimazaki resign on his own accord?
Resume your duties.
Here's your ticket.
This way.
The departure time is 12:10 p.m.
We'll reach Kamakura after 3:00 p.m.
I've made reservations at a cheap hotel
near the university.
Thank you very much.
Hey. Isn't that Matsuno?
Please excuse me.
It seems like there are
news reporters and cameramen.
What? Was my release leaked to the press?
Don't look back!
-Mr. Matsuno?
-You're Mr. Matsuno, right?
Please excuse us.
Could you have a talk with us?
You're in the way!
-Mr. Matsuno?
-Please say something!
-That's Mr. Matsuno, right?
Please hand over
all the photos you've taken.
What are you saying? Where is Matsuno?
Are you allowed to cover news here?
Do you have a permit?
What about your armbands?
Who are you?
You're not with the police, right?
Just let us interview Matsuno.
I'm sure he wants to say something!
Why aren't you addressing him politely?
He has atoned for his sins
and has a future ahead of him.
He's not someone you can talk down on.
Please hand over the photos.
You're going against the regulations here!
-Give it to him.
-Are you serious?
Just give it to him!
Damn it.
-I can't accept it!
-Just forget it!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go.
You're Shun Shimazaki, right?
Yes.
I'm Takanashi, a colleague of your father
at his workplace.
Ex-colleague, you mean?
I see. So you know
that he resigned from his work.
Where is your father right now?
SHIMAZAKI SECURITY
Please.
It appears that
our movement is being leaked,
so we'll have to stay here tonight.
Even so,
I've only just rented this place,
so there's nothing.
It's all right.
Compared to prison,
this place feels like heaven.
Oh, you should have a shower
if you would like to.
I'll turn on the hot water supply.
Let me take out a towel.
If you don't mind,
you can change into these.
Oh, thank you very much.
-Hello?
-Hello.
I'm working now,
so I'll just get to the point.
I'm staying out for the night.
There's gratin in the fridge,
so eat that, and make sure
the doors are all closed before you sleep.
Are you listening?
Make sure you're not late
for school tomorrow.
Also, don't call me
if there's nothing important.
Bye.
He said he's not coming home tonight
because of work.
Work…
He's always messing around.
He gave me this right after he resigned.
I see.
You're right, he's messing around.
Isn't it impossible to survive
as a freelance bodyguard?
He should think about his age!
You're right, he should.
Can't you tell him off, Mr. Takanashi?
Tell him to quit being a bodyguard
and get a proper job instead.
Are you really fine
with him quitting as a bodyguard?
I'm all for it, in fact.
I mean, it's a dangerous job.
There are times
when our work makes someone happy.
But you guys earn too little
to justify that.
But food tastes so much better
when you finish your work.
Then are you telling him
to continue his work?
I'm not saying that…
Make yourself clear!
You talk too much.
There are things in life
that can't be made clear.
You don't act like an adult,
Mr. Takanashi.
I don't want a kid like you
to tell me that!
What's so funny?
I think I like you, Mr. Takanashi.
Thanks.
I'm done.
Oh, thanks.
Please go ahead.
Oh, I'm all right.
I won't be able to protect you
if I'm naked.
That phone call just now…
Did you call your child?
Oh, sorry. It was a personal call.
I'm divorced,
so I'm living with my son.
I'm envious.
I might've had a family of my own
if this incident hadn't happened.
I'm from Café Junction!
It's okay. I asked the shop downstairs
to deliver some food.
I'm coming!
-I've brought what you requested!
-You don't have to come in.
-Give me that.
-I'm glad you got your first assignment!
I never thought that someone would
actually need a bodyguard.
It wouldn't be a job in the first place
if no one needed it.
-Here's 3,800 yen.
-Okay.
If you have any additional purchases,
you can pay altogether.
Additional purchases?
There's a man outside the building
who keeps looking up over here.
No additional purchases.
-Oh, all right.
-Thank you.
-Thank you--
-Thanks!
Did the media find out about this?
Don't worry.
I won't let them in here.
Please have a seat.
Mr. Matsuno.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Was it really just an accident?
No, I'm not doubting you.
But if I don't know the truth,
I won't know the best way to protect you.
I promise not to tell anyone,
so could you please tell me?
My duty
is to prevent any potential problems
from happening.
I believe this is one
of the potential problems.
It was an accident.
Yes.
It was before Professor Sakagami
made his research presentation.
My days were just full of
nothing but lab experiments,
and I was really exhausted
from pulling consecutive all-nighters.
We were doing research
on bacteria found within an ice pillar
that we brought back from the South Pole.
We spent a huge amount of money
in order to obtain that ice pillar.
However, the cold room
in the laboratory malfunctioned…
And the ice pillar began to melt.
-Itami.
-Yes?
Gather all the liquid nitrogen we have.
Yes, I understand!
In a panic to cool down
the room immediately,
I asked Itami to release
liquid nitrogen into the cold room.
-I'll call Professor Sakagami!
-Please do!
Because of that,
the oxygen in the cold room depleted.
As I was on my way
to notify Professor Sakagami,
I didn't notice that she was in danger.
Because of that accident,
Professor Sakagami's research
was frowned upon by society.
That's why I have to meet him,
no matter what.
Thank you very much.
I will put my faith in you, Mr. Matsuno.
Please.
Sorry.
We might have been followed
from the bus terminal.
Could you please check
if it's an acquaintance of yours?
What are you doing?
Stay back.
I must talk to Matsuno!
-Who is this?
-Ms. Itami's younger brother.
You can talk to me instead.
Matsuno, you lucky bastard.
You actually got a bodyguard and all?
Mr. Matsuno has
atoned for his sins properly!
How could he have atoned
when all he did was lie?
It's not too late, Matsuno.
Tell me the truth!
I received a call from my sister
before the incident!
There's a problem at the lab,
so I'll be home late.
Please let Mom know
so that she won't get worried.
What problem are you talking about?
It's all right.
I'm going to sue him.
It wasn't brought up during the trial,
but she was referring to you!
That photo was the evidence!
That was definitely no accident!
You killed her!
Tell us the truth!
Please stop.
Move aside!
Let go! I'm dead serious!
I'll never forgive you!
It's the signal…
Open the door as hard as you can!
What a run-down office.
He's an ex-colleague of mine.
He won't report it to the police.
Oh, no. You can call the police.
I'm the one at fault after all.
Why are you guys protecting
a murderer like him?
Do you protect anyone
as long as they give you money…
Damn it!
Why did you open the door?
I thought that if it was a reporter,
I would tell them to stop following us.
So I just opened it without thinking.
I'm sorry.
I'm closing the door.
CHUO WARD, TOKYO
APRIL 16, THURSDAY
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
The company's going to be mad at you
if they find out you're helping me!
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping the client.
Let's hurry up.
The client's safety
is our responsibility, right?
Estimated time to reach
Sasano Town, Kamakura City is 1:00 p.m.
The time now is 11:35 a.m.
-Synchronized.
KANTO UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY
-We've arrived, Mr. Matsuno.
-Okay.
We're news reporters,
and we would like to know
-about the incident in the cold room…
-So they came here, anyway…
I'll go fill up the visitor's form.
I heard that Shinsuke Matsuno
has been released from prison.
Is that so?
We can't stay here any longer.
Let's go through the back of the building.
Understood.
Please lower your head, Mr. Matsuno.
Let's do this.
Change places, Takanashi.
Sorry, but we'll climb all the way
to the seventh floor.
Professor Sakagami's research lab
is up ahead.
If we enter now,
students and staff members will notice us.
We have no choice.
What?
Mr. Matsuno wants that exactly.
Am I wrong?
I've been thinking about how the media
got info about your release so soon.
Didn't you leak the information
using your phone?
You turned your face toward the reporters
at the bus terminal, didn't you?
And you opened the door without asking
back in my office.
Even just now,
you deliberately lifted your head
so that others would notice you, right?
Your actions don't seem like
you're afraid of the press.
In fact, you were waiting for them.
What exactly do you want?
There's no way I would tell everything
to mere bodyguards!
I guess you're right.
In fact, there's something that
I've been hiding from you as well.
I said I resigned from my company
because I wanted more freedom,
but that was a lie.
The truth is…
I was fired
because I talked back to my boss.
"Whether it's an ex-convict or not,
we should help those in need."
That's what I told him.
However…
I don't regret my decision now.
I…
I don't belong to any organization.
As long as you tell me the truth,
I intend to protect you to the very end,
even if it means breaking the law.
-Mr. Matsuno!
-I'll deal with the guard.
It's been a while, Professor Sakagami.
I'm Shimazaki, his bodyguard.
Please allow me to stay here.
Please leave. I have something important
to tell Professor Sakagami.
Please move aside.
Move!
You want to know the truth, right?
He was the one who let Ms. Itami die!
It's over…
There goes your dream as a researcher too…
Professor Sakagami ordered Itami
to release the liquid nitrogen!
I took the blame to protect his research!
But when those photos appeared on my desk,
I realized the truth.
Professor Sakagami was the one
who took the photos.
Wasn't it?
The dirt on your camera lens appeared
on the photos!
You were the one who tried to
approach Ms. Itami,
weren't you, Professor Sakagami?
That was no accident!
She said she was going to sue you!
You were the one who killed her!
Professor Sakagami…
The media is waiting
right at the front gate.
Reveal the truth in front of the cameras,
and apologize for the fact
that you robbed her of her future!
So you want revenge?
Yes.
If you don't reveal the truth,
then I'll kill you.
-You…
-Is this what you were planning?
Yes!
I gathered the press because
I wanted Professor Sakagami to confess!
I hired you because
I wanted you to protect me
in case someone gets in the way!
Are you running away, Professor Sakagami?
Get off me!
Hey!
Why are you running away?
Professor Sakagami!
I've adjusted the settings
for the door lock,
so it won't open from the inside.
I also told staff members
not to come to the lab today.
If I have to tarnish my own reputation,
I would rather choose to die.
Ever since I heard you were coming,
I had planned to do this.
Wait a minute.
You're planning to die with Mr. Matsuno
just to silence him?
I have the responsibility
of protecting this lab.
Don't worry.
You'll start to feel sleepy
after 30 minutes.
You won't feel any pain.
RAPID COOLING IN PROGRESS
No way…
Takanashi.
-Takanashi.
-You won't reach him!
You won't be able to hear anything
from outside either.
We spent millions on this security system
to protect the valuable ice pillar!
I'm in front of the laboratory.
Where are you?
Can you hear me?
COLD ROOM IN OPERATION
"Responsibility"? What is this bullshit?
You're just sacrificing the lives of
others for your own reputation!
You know, Matsuno…
researchers are all egoists.
Sakagami!
Can you hear me, Shimazaki?
Shimazaki?
Where the hell are you, Akira Shimazaki?
I came here with the determination
to kill him, so let me do it!
My duty is to protect you.
I'm going to die anyway!
You too!
Please excuse me.
I'm not going to give up.
I still haven't received my pay from you.
Shimazaki?
Shimazaki!
RAPID COOLING IN PROGRESS
SYSTEM LOG
FORCE RAPID COOLING SETTINGS
FORCE CANCEL
COLD ROOM IN OPERATION
Mr. Matsuno…
Mr. Matsuno!
It's frozen tight.
That's…
Professor Sakagami…
Could you please turn yourself in?
Mr. Matsuno did not come here
to exact revenge.
As someone he once respected,
I believe he came here
because he wanted to
place his trust in you again.
-What is that?
-What's going on?
-He's handcuffed?
-Let's go!
KANAGAWA POLICE
-Take pictures!
-Hey!
Well, how much is the payment?
You're asking that now?
It's for 30 hours,
so it'll be 150,000 yen.
You don't have to pay any taxes.
Here's the receipt.
The amount is correct.
Mr. Shimazaki.
You really are a fool.
You realized what I planned to do,
yet you followed me to the very end.
I'm your bodyguard after all.
You protected my future.
Thank you for stopping me.
We would like to invite you
for a questioning.
Really? I never expected that to happen.
Yes.
I never thought that Shimazaki
and even Takanashi would be there.
They went against your expectations.
-I'm truly sorry.
-It's fine.
This would probably be
their last assignment as bodyguards.
I'll overlook it.
NORTH KAMAKURA STATION,
KANAGAWA POLICE
That hurts…
I sprained my waist.
Of course, you did, you old geezer.
You're almost an old geezer too.
-When did you realize Mr. Matsuno's plan?
-What?
Don't tell me you knew everything
from the start?
Well, I thought that it'll be dangerous,
-so…
-Unbelievable.
You were about to sacrifice your own life
for a single client!
There was no choice!
I'm a bodyguard.
I heard you went against the president.
Tell me about it.
Is it just me,
or have you been talking down on me?
You're not my superior now.
As expected of an ex-SDF officer.
You're so strict with hierarchy.
Stop joking and tell me.
What happened
between you and the president?
Thanks for today.
In fact,
I should say you saved me.
Hello.
You might get yourself fired
for violating service regulations!
Why did you keep this from me?
I wanted to know.
About what?
I can't be in a relationship with you
like this.
Let's end it.
-I understand.
-What?
You don't have to look after
a child like me anymore.
He's joking, right?
I'll never forgive him!
Takanashi has finally done it…
Good work today!
That was dangerous.
What now?
What's up?
Hey!
I'm not a taxi driver, you know…
She's a blind pianist.
You think that it's a pain trying
to protect a selfish girl like me.
-Do you really plan to work with me?
-Don't make me repeat myself.
The two of them are working together.
Being blind is nothing special.
I don't want to use it to my advantage.
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
Watch out!
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu