I'm currently in front of
Akaruzaka Police Station.
Mr. Saburo Michioka, who was arrested
on suspected investment fraud,
has been released due to
insufficient evidence for an indictment.
-Mr. Michioka!
-Please say something, Mr. Michioka!
Please comment, Mr. Michoka!
Anything will do!
That wasn't the truth, right?
What actually happened?
No one's following us, President.
Michioka! Are you going to run away?
Michioka!
-Michioka…
-Listen up.
There are risks involved in investing.
Didn't I tell you that?
And you still insisted on joining in.
Even if the law lets you run free,
I will never forgive you!
Oh, is that so?
Kill me if you dare.
Damn you!
You bastard…
President!
Mr. Saburou Michioka is suspected of
using the money he swindled from victims
to provide benefits to
Lower House assemblymen.
There is increasing dissent over
his non-indictment.
Saburo Michioka.
He has been admitted to our hospital
in the utmost secrecy.
He ruptured his Achilles tendon
and I was supposed to be
the surgeon in charge of his operation,
but now, the higher-ups are hesitating.
So they don't want to treat people
who are public enemies?
If he is attacked again
during his stay there,
they're worried that
it'll affect their reputation.
So the higher-ups now state his security
as part of the requirements
for his admission.
I just need you to protect him
during his two-week stay.
Could you please accept
his bodyguard request?
I would be more than happy to,
but why did you come to us?
I mean, with someone of his background,
he could have requested a bigger company…
Mr. Michioka…
Even though his secretary tried
to restrain him,
he broke free and provoked the attacker.
He told the guy, "Kill me if you dare."
"Kill me if you dare"?
All the big companies got scared
when they heard that.
Even Kicks Guard,
the company you two were in.
Who is it?
Oh, I'll get it.
Excuse me. Yes?
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Thank you. Just put it on the table.
Is the consultation going well?
You might be worried
that there's only two of them,
but because of this,
they can focus on a single task.
I do think this is cost-effective.
Please don't go prattling unnecessarily.
-What?
-Thanks. You don't have to promote us.
-Thanks for your patronage.
-Sure.
He seems to be really worried about you.
You can expect
to earn a huge sum from this.
-Yes.
-Please let us consider the assignment.
We can't protect the client
if they actively provoke people.
But if we reject him,
no one else will accept his request.
People are going to point at you
and say that you're protecting a villain
-just for the money…
-Villain?
You haven't even met the guy,
and you already know him? Impressive.
That's huge!
Another dangerous assignment?
I guess.
How difficult is it this time?
As difficult as getting
into an elite school, sorry.
I don't really mind,
but don't you have safer tasks?
Safer ones? That's hard to come across.
If it's safe, they wouldn't even hire
a bodyguard in the first place.
I see.
I guess so.
That's hot.
My friend from the soccer club said that
he's aiming for medical school
since his parents are doctors.
But I can never be a bodyguard.
Why not?
I guess I just want a job that I enjoy
while allowing me to have
ample time for myself
without any danger involved.
You can go for any job you want,
but are there really any jobs
that have no risks involved?
Normal jobs aren't dangerous.
I'm digging in.
-Do you want some ketchup?
-I'm not a kid.
I'll have it,
even though I'm 47 years old.
Mr. Saburo Michioka, an investor
arrested on suspicion of fraud,
has been released
from Akaruzaka Police Station.
Mr. Michioka then left the police station
in a private vehicle,
but a scam victim ambushed him
near the police station
-and assaulted the investor.
-Mr. Saburo Michioka's bodyguard request
has been accepted by Shimazaki Security.
Will they be fine?
There's only the two of them.
-I mean, Michioka is--
-It's them, they'll be fine.
Even President Ryu was glad
and said that it's a good thing for them
to be proactive in assignments like these.
Does he really feel that way?
If they keep
accepting jobs that we reject,
I can't help but
get a bad feeling from that.
Maybe the president
just doesn't view them as a threat.
You know, I…
I wonder if Shimazaki quit because
he had some conflict with the president.
Why the president?
I mean, it must be really serious
since Takanashi left as well.
Hey.
If you have time to poke your nose
into where it doesn't belong,
go have your medical checkup instead.
I'm leaving for the inspection.
Have a safe trip!
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
What are you doing?
I'll get in the car first.
What do you want from me?
There's no need for us to meet
unless we have business
with each other, is there?
So what is it?
You should reject
Saburo Michioka's bodyguard request.
Tell that to Shimazaki.
He requested our services
in Kicks Guard too,
but we rejected his request,
since his threat level
was the maximum, Level 5.
He is not just targeted by his victims.
That man is treading on a dangerous path.
It won't be surprising
if you get caught in his affairs
-and get silenced--
-We already accepted it.
Hey. Don't tell me
you plan to go against
your former employer?
I still don't know the real reason
why you and Shimazaki left.
Why would I bother with everything
that Kicks Guard does?
What's with that attitude?
I was just worried about you!
I can't be bothered to listen
to what an old flame tells me.
"An old flame"?
Fine!
There's still time, go chase after her.
She's not the kind to apologize first.
-Your relationship's really going to end.
-I don't want to hear this from you.
I'm your senior
when it comes to romantic relationships.
-That's coming from a divorcee?
-That's exactly why I know!
Just go already!
Oh, my!
-You really know your stuff, sir.
-And you acted too late, my boy!
I'm Shimazaki. Pleased to meet you.
I'm Kogure, Mr. Michioka's secretary.
Pleased to meet you.
-Thank you for the business card.
-Likewise, I'm Takanashi.
I'm Kogure. Pleased to meet you.
So you were from Kicks Guard?
Yes. We left the company.
I see.
Will I be safe with you guys?
I can't help but think
that you must've gotten into trouble
if you resigned from a good company.
Please don't worry.
I left because my contract ended.
You can't fool me.
I've seen all kinds of hell after all.
My name has been blacklisted
by security companies,
so I can't afford to be choosy.
But you're a little old to be a bodyguard.
And you over there, you're not suited
for the service industry.
On top of that, you guys have
no sense of teamwork, right?
Thank you for your criticisms.
We will work on these flaws and
cater to your security needs accordingly.
Oh, and also…
Don't expect to get paid a lot.
I only engaged you
because of the hospital's request.
I'll only pay the lowest rate possible.
They're not particular about money.
Right?
I've incurred the wrath of many people.
I don't know when I'll be killed.
But I won't hide.
"Kill me if you dare."
That's what I always say.
-Prepare yourselves.
-Yes, sir!
However, the duty of a bodyguard
doesn't include locking up their client.
We'll be with you,
be it in heaven or in hell.
He has guts.
Well, I guess…
Do your best to protect me.
Yes.
I understand. Thank you.
The special ward is only on the 9th floor,
so there's probably a low chance
of it being attacked from the outside.
If we were to consider
any possible ambushes…
There would only be two routes,
via the elevator or the emergency stairs.
We'll be able to prevent it completely
if we're on standby outside the door.
But if we stand outside the ward door,
the fact that Mr. Michioka
has been hospitalized will be revealed.
It would be dangerous instead.
Good morning!
Good morning.
I've heard rumors about you two.
You're bodyguards for the patient
in the special ward, right?
Yes.
How cool!
It's my first time meeting bodyguards!
Here you go, a free sample!
-No, thank you.
-We're on duty, so…
It's all right!
Anyway, tell me
who was admitted to the ward!
I won't tell anyone!
Is it a celebrity? A politician?
-There's no way we'll tell you!
-Sorry.
We're not allowed
to consume food while on duty.
Please excuse us.
I'm always here during the weekdays,
-so feel free to talk to me!
-Please excuse us.
MICHIOKA SECRETLY ADMITTED TO A HOSPITAL?
A VILLAIN'S DISAPPEARING ACT
BRIBES OFFERED TO ASSEMBLYMAN WAKINAGA
SHROUDED IN MYSTERY
"It wouldn't be strange
to receive the death penalty," they say.
This is awesome.
Dissent has been increasing
ever since your non-indictment.
I think it's best
not to read the comments.
Why would I care about
what people say on the Internet?
Don't put me on the same level as you,
you good-for-nothing!
Please excuse us.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt you.
It's fine. I was just giving pointers
to my employee.
While we're on duty,
we'll be on standby here.
So we'll immediately know
if someone approaches you.
-Please rest assured.
-What? Wait!
You guys will be there all the time?
That feels so gloomy!
Please excuse me.
Please stop complaining, Mr. Michioka.
Oh, Dr. Takako.
The hospital as well as Mr. Shimazaki
are doing their best to protect you.
I got it already.
Anyway, Dr. Takako…
you resemble a teacher I had a crush on
back in elementary school.
The operation will be
at 3:00 p.m tomorrow.
You will start your rehabilitation
the day after.
I'm in charge of your rehabilitation.
My name is Yukawa. Pleased to meet you.
A young lad, aren't you…
Don't you have more experienced ones?
Yukawa is a passionate physiotherapist.
He offered to help you this time.
I may not meet your expectations,
but I'll do my best for you.
Let's do this together!
"Let's do this together!"
Do you think I'll actually say that?
That's your job, isn't it?
Yes.
The doctor operates.
The physiotherapist is
in charge of the rehabilitation.
And the bodyguards place
their lives on the line.
And my job
is to earn money
and be hated by everyone else.
Isn't it?
Excuse me.
Hello?
What?
Actually, we received this.
I WON'T FORGIVE
THE DOCTOR TREATING MICHIOKA.
THEY WILL BE EXECUTED.
A death threat.
It seems that Mr. Michioka's admission
has been leaked.
Perhaps we should
reconsider his treatment here.
It may not just be an empty threat.
But didn't we engage excellent bodyguards
for that very purpose?
We're not a public hospital.
This might sound ugly,
but we're not obligated
to help someone like him.
I don't like him either.
But no matter who they are, we help those
in need to the best of our ability…
Isn't that what professional doctors do?
That is indeed a wonderful mindset,
but aren't you the deputy chief
of the orthopedic department?
You have to think about
the business aspect of our hospital too.
Excuse me.
If news of Mr. Michioka's admission
was leaked,
then news of the hospital rejecting
his treatment would also be leaked, right?
I mean, it would sound really bad
for a hospital
if people knew they rejected patients.
I'm sorry.
Who is it?
My name is Suzuki.
May I know your full name?
He'll know once you tell him my surname.
I'm surprised you actually found me.
As expected from Assemblyman Wakinaga.
Could the two of you please leave?
I am obliged to protect
my client's confidentiality.
It's related to a complicated issue.
Hey.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Wakinaga says…
he bears no relation to you at all.
I seek your understanding.
That's so cold all of a sudden.
All this time, I've given so much
assistance to Mr. Wakinaga.
Even this book sold well, didn't it?
I hope your injuries heal soon.
What are you doing?
Hey, be careful.
He's Assemblyman Wakinaga's rabid lap dog.
This is quite a lively visit.
Please step back.
A bodyguard is not allowed
to attack people!
It was awesome, Dr. Takako!
I felt like I was watching
a kickboxing competition
in the middle of the ring itself.
That's very rude of you, Mr. Michioka.
You should be thankful that you're safe.
That hurt…
Sorry about that.
But it wasn't that bad.
As if. You were serious.
If I was serious,
your shoulder would've been dislocated.
Maybe it really got dislocated.
We're in the middle of our duty now!
I was kidding.
He really must be a bad person.
I don't know if we should continue
our bodyguard assignment.
You're right, he might be an evil person.
But I don't want to
choose clients based on that.
We would be the same as Kicks Guard,
which only chooses VIPs as clients.
What?
So it's just your obstinacy talking here?
If all you want is to accept jobs
that President Ryu rejected,
I won't be able to stay with you.
Oh, my, are you two fighting?
No, we're just having a briefing.
You have to get along!
You never know
what's going to happen in life!
Oh, would you like a drink of this?
-Oh, no…
-This is a present from my son.
He bought it for me
using his first paycheck.
Sorry, but we're not allowed to drink
while we're on duty.
Hey!
Could you tell me who is the patient
-in the special ward?
-I'm sorry.
-Just tell me if it's a man or a woman!
Or just their initials will do!
I see.
So this is the Personal Security Division,
where the bodyguards are.
The departure of Shimazaki and Takanashi,
two of our veteran bodyguards,
pains my heart, but…
this could be a chance for us to change
the old-fashioned ways
of the security industry.
Let's reform our organization,
and aim to expand our business further.
-Yes, sir!
In order to achieve that…
I especially require the power of women.
Yes, sir.
Suganuma,
I'll be waiting for your reply
to that request.
COLD
I'll take over.
I can still go on.
You should get some rest for tomorrow.
As for my reply to what you said earlier…
I wasn't trying to be stubborn.
Really.
You fall asleep quicker than Nobita.
Once I've decided to protect someone,
I don't want to go back on my word.
Since I'm a bodyguard.
-Hey.
-Yes.
What is it?
Could you open the curtains?
I want to see the sky.
Yes.
It's a full moon.
So tomorrow is the operation,
I'm scared.
I don't really care if people hate me,
but I'm scared of injections.
You have to do it
if you want to walk again.
But I've already traveled
all over the world.
The only place I haven't been to is hell.
Come in.
The operation room is ready.
I'll be there to observe.
-Got it. I'm counting on you.
-Likewise.
Please be careful.
I'll be covering you with a cloth.
Please excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It seems that Dr. Kasamatsu
is taking some time to get prepared,
so could you please wait a moment?
-What?
-I'm sorry.
Hey, wait a minute…
Hey!
Excuse me!
Did something happen to Dr. Kasamatsu?
Well…
I wasn't able to contact her,
and she wasn't in her room too.
Understood. Thank you.
Actually, we received this.
I WON'T FORGIVE
THE DOCTOR TREATING MICHIOKA.
The route to the operating room is…
ORTHOPEDICS DEPUTY CHIEF
TAKAKO KASAMATSU
Hey!
Dr. Kasamatsu. Are you all right?
-Mr. Shimazaki…
-Are you injured?
They suddenly charged at me.
I really thought
I was going to be executed.
Did you see their face?
They were wearing a mask, so…
Oh, you're right. I'm sorry.
I'm fine already, so you can go.
You don't have to worry anymore.
What…
Stop that.
I won't be scared
over something like this.
I'm fine, I see blood every day.
You're my client's important doctor.
I have to protect you.
Here.
All right!
Let's go.
We will now begin
the Achilles tendon repair surgery.
-Scapel.
-Yes.
-Gauze.
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
They couldn't find anyone from
the security room's surveillance cameras.
They couldn't find anyone?
Really?
So was it done by someone
who knows the location of the cameras?
Could it be that guy?
That would be too reckless.
He's a politician's underling.
Would he even try something like that?
Then who could it be?
What?
Hello?
Hello, it's Sawaguchi.
Are you on duty at the moment?
No, I guess I'm taking
a short break right now.
What's up?
I want to know the reason
why you left Kicks Guard, Shimazaki.
-What's up with that so suddenly?
-Well…
I'm sorry.
It's been on my mind for a while.
Well, there was an assault here
in the hospital,
so I'm a little busy at the moment.
Did someone attack Michioka?
-No, they went after his doctor.
-That is really bad.
I understand. I'll investigate that too.
We received some information
when he came to us, so…
Don't forget that
confidentiality is part of our job.
Yes, sir.
What?
Did he hang up the phone?
-Skin stapler.
-Yes.
We're done.
-Good work.
Mr. Michioka? How are you feeling?
I feel like crap.
What's left is your rehabilitation.
Please do your best.
-I'm leaving it to you.
-Yes.
Let's try to move your body,
starting tomorrow.
Try to do light exercises now,
so that the muscles around your tendon
won't harden up.
I just woke up, for god's sake.
Let's do this later.
President.
It's important to do it immediately.
What is with you?
I told you not to come over.
I'm sorry.
I was very worried about the operation.
My injury won't heal
if I look at your unlucky face.
Just go back when I tell you to!
I'm sorry.
SPECIAL WARD
Is it possible that Mr. Kogure,
Mr. Michioka's secretary,
attacked Dr. Kasamatsu?
It's not surprising
that he would hold a grudge
after being mistreated like that.
In a sense, he's the first victim
of Michioka's actions.
MICHIOKA ASSAULTED AFTER RELEASE,
HOSPITALIZED DUE TO SERIOUS INJURIES
What are you doing in secret?
I was just doing some revision
for tomorrow's assignment.
For two shady men?
I'll help.
But it'll be the first and last time.
Thank you.
PLEASE GO TO THE EMERGENCY DESK
TO VISIT PATIENTS DURING HOLIDAYS
Next, let's try to walk
using the parallel bars.
I feel so sluggish.
I'm not doing this.
President, you have to do it.
Why are you here?
I told you not to come,
you piece of trash!
You have to get better soon
and resume work quickly.
So you want me to do more bad deeds?
No.
Not everything you do is bad.
Stop getting ahead of yourself!
I don't need a secretary
who speaks out of his place.
Quit, you piece of trash.
I won't resign.
Oh, is that so?
If that's the case,
bring over the thing that I want the most.
And what is that?
I won't tell you.
If you're my secretary,
then you should know!
You don't want to quit, right?
Can you do this alone?
I won't let anyone pass.
I'll be back
right after I'm done talking to him.
The current time is 2:56 p.m.
-Synchronized.
Mr. Kogure!
Do you know what
Mr. Michioka was referring to?
No. I'll head back to the company
and think about it.
Well, when did you start working
for Mr. Michioka?
It was 11 years ago.
I had some personal issues
with my previous company,
and I met Mr. Michioka
at one of his seminars.
When I heard him speak,
I felt like even I had some potential.
So I begged him to take me in.
So your life changed
after meeting Mr. Michioka.
What are you trying to say?
Oh, please pardon me.
It's just that there are times
when I can't help but feel that
I've changed the lives of those who are
with me after I set up my own office.
Mr. Shimazaki.
I don't regret my decision.
Mr. Shimazaki!
Why are you here, Sawaguchi?
Please take a look at this.
This…
Are you in the rehab room, Takanashi?
No.
Mr. Yukawa wanted the rehab session
to be conducted on the rooftop,
so we're currently here.
He's the one we should be careful of.
Yukawa's sister
was a victim of Michioka's scam…
SUICIDE
…and killed herself!
-Sorry!
-Good afternoon!
-Have you two made up--
-I'm in a rush now, so…
Thank you for working hard
even on a Sunday.
Sunday?
I'll separate the client from the threat.
Don't try anything too rough.
He might have a knife with him.
Understood.
The weather got a little cold,
so shall we return to the ward?
I'm helping him manage
his body temperature.
-You can return first if you like.
-I can't do that.
It looks like Mr. Michioka
doesn't look very well, so…
I'm fine.
The wind feels good.
We're taking too much time here.
What's wrong?
You're making such a scary face.
Excuse me!
Sorry, he's not very good
at expressing himself.
How are you feeling?
Well, it hurts,
but I was able to walk a little.
That's incredible!
Yes.
I have to escape from those
who hold a grudge against me.
Let him go.
That's impossible.
I mean, he became my therapist
just to kill me.
You knew?
Your sister killed herself
because I swindled her, right?
I saw her at the victims' association.
Just do it.
I said no fighting, right?
Please stay back.
No one is allowed to come here
-except for related personnel--
-No. She's related, right?
She's the mother of Kazuya Yoshimura,
who died because of your actions!
So the bereaved families
teamed up to kill me?
How much should I pay
to earn your forgiveness?
I don't need a single cent from you!
Atone for your sins!
Turn yourself in to the police
along with the evidence!
Reveal the entire truth!
Listen up.
If you have time to blame me,
why not blame your sister
or your stupid son?
My father…
He had to pay his friend's loans
and was fired by his company.
As a child, I learned to lie
in order to survive,
and that's how I became rich today!
It's a given that there are risks
either in investment or in our lives!
Those that end their own lives
just because they were deceived
are nothing but losers!
Shut the hell up!
Let go of me!
I'll kill him!
Don't use your son's gift
for something like this!
Mr. Michioka.
Do you really want to die that badly?
Even the fight you had
near the police station…
Kill me if you dare.
…was the same as now.
You came out front on your own accord.
You would rather be killed.
Is that what you really want?
I believe the President
wanted someone to stop him.
Don't talk as if you know me!
I've brought it over.
This is the thing
you want the most, President.
The evidence related to your scam.
You even wrote down
Assemblyman Wakinaga's involvement
in the case!
Mr. Michioka.
No one's going to stop you anymore.
Didn't you say it yourself?
I don't know when I'll be killed.
But I won't hide.
I was involved
in Mr. Michioka's scam as well.
I'm very sorry!
This is your last task.
Take me to the police station.
Understood.
OUTPATIENT RELEASING
You've been a great help, Dr. Takako.
You'll be resuming your rehabilitation
in the detention center, Mr. Michioka.
Please don't skip them.
Sounds nice. That's what I like about you.
I'm closing the door.
We're leaving.
Mr. Shimazaki.
I…
Good work. I'm leaving my patient to you.
Yes.
Are you all right, Dr. Kasamatsu?
Please keep that a secret.
I'll keep that in mind.
Oh, the injury on your hand.
I'll wait for you.
I'm counting on you.
Right. I haven't paid
for your services yet.
Well, it was for 52 hours,
so it'll be 520,000 yen in total.
That's cheap.
It's the lowest rate.
But my entire fortune was given
to the victims to pay back their loans.
Can I pay it back
after leaving the detention center?
Sure.
I'll pay you, I promise.
And to do that, I'll work my way up again.
Yes.
Thank you.
You protected my ambition.
Let's go.
Mr. Saburo Michioka,
who was previously released
due to insufficient evidence
on suspicion of investment fraud,
has turned himself in once again
at Akaruzaka Police Station.
The police commented that…
That's great, isn't it?
Although the chief doesn't look
very happy right now.
Regarding what you discussed
with me before,
I'll accept your offer.
You're indeed wise.
I knew you would say that.
To commemorate this day,
why don't I talk about myself?
Yourself?
The real reason why I started focusing
on the security industry.
Of course, no one else
in the company knows about this.
Please excuse me.
President.
Do you feel like returning now?
I've never considered that.
What a shame.
I would've welcomed you with open arms.
That man has been following me.
I'm not mistaken
since it's part of my work.
"That man"?
The waiter that I stopped
when you engaged him to injure Sawaguchi!
Don't tell me…
You think I asked him to follow you?
I'm not that free.
You must have incurred
someone else's wrath.
That's part of the risk
when working as a bodyguard.
If you don't know anything
about him, that's fine.
However,
I'm sure I told you.
I'll overlook what you have done.
In return, stop playing around
with the lives of bodyguards!
Please don't ever forget that.
Shimazaki.
Your beloved occupation as a bodyguard…
I sure hope you can continue it forever.
I heard he's an unemployed
middle-aged man.
You'll put your lives on the line, right?
I'm being targeted.
I'm worried.
Just go to the class reunion
with your head held high!
You have no right to talk to me like that!
You shouldn't judge me
using normal standards.
Let's refuse this request.
I trust my client.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu