In the corruption scandal four years ago,
you pinned the blame on me
and then abandoned me!
The least you can do is apologize!
You should apologize!
Sir!
The only thing a shameless man
like you can do
is die a quick death!
Don't talk like that, sir!
I won't allow pointless deaths!
Dad was a fool.
Bodyguards are nothing more than
underpaid slave labor!
-Don't say that about his work!
-Stop it!
Your father worked until the very end
as a bodyguard to protect everyone there.
-Synchronized.
Besides the police, the only person left
who witnessed that incident
is you now.
Are you telling me someone might
want to silence me?
We might be able to clear
his tarnished reputation.
He recorded everything while on duty.
I'm sure he recorded that day as well.
Are you saying the police took it?
I'll make them give it back.
So you've come.
The day of the shooting has been deleted.
Dad will be remembered
as an overzealous bodyguard!
Can you make public
what happened that day?
-Remove him.
-Minister, I refuse to give up.
We don't have status, power, or weapons,
but the one thing we had
was stolen from us!
Don't let her near that Shimazaki
who was at the shooting.
Why don't we get rid of Akira Shimazaki
just like with those recordings?
I'll make public the truth
about the shooting incident.
Please fight with us.
Will you really reveal the truth?
Thank you. I'm deeply impressed.
I'm friends with one of the producers
on my old program,
News Level 5.
He promised to let me
secretly appear on it live tomorrow.
On TV?
This isn't something
that can be posted on social media.
I need to show my face
and talk about what happened that day.
But you'll be making enemies
not just of the police,
but also of Mr. Igarashi
and the Civil Party.
I've already made him my enemy.
What?
Earlier, I was advised to step down
from my post as a minister.
Aiko Tachihara tried to sidestep
her comment belittling the unemployed
and is overshadowed by the scandal of
sending the threatening letter to herself,
so she is stepping down
to take responsibility.
They'll be announcing it that way soon.
No way.
-No way!
-Don't worry.
I'll make the best of it.
Revealing the truth will lead
to the denunciation of
Secretary-General Igarashi's misconduct.
Hold on.
People who commit a cover-up
must fight against cover-ups.
Is that wishful thinking?
Back when that happened,
you all saved my life.
When I met my daughter,
you all kept my secret.
Now,
it's my turn to protect
Mr. Murata's honor.
But you'll be putting yourself in danger.
There have been
many cases of whistle-blowers' lives
being threatened.
It's okay.
I'll have a capable bodyguard
to protect me.
After stepping down as a minister,
I won't have SP protection anymore.
They'll do anything to stop me,
so I want to request your protection
until I can reveal the truth
about the shooting.
-Yes, ma'am.
The SP Ochiai?
He said that he would
settle this incident himself.
He sounds like a good man.
I'm also taking discreet steps.
I wonder how magnificently
he will handle this.
I'd like to see it.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid?
No. Thanks to being part of
your protection detail,
I achieved my position.
Okay, I wonder how
that ungrateful woman is being dealt with.
It's time to check.
Sorry to interrupt the program,
but we have breaking news.
Aiko Tachihara, a Civil Party member
of the Lower House,
has announced she is stepping down
as Health, Labor, and Welfare Minister.
I repeat.
Aiko Tachihara, a Civil Party member
of the Lower House,
has announced she is stepping down
as Health, Labor, and Welfare Minister.
She tried to sidestep her comment
belittling the unemployed
and was scandalized by sending
a threatening letter to herself.
She is taking responsibility
for those things.
Diet Member Aiko Tachihara is
leaving the Civil Party as of today
and will announce later
what her future political plans will be.
Returning to the previous topic...
We'll pick you up at 9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Please wait for me here.
I'll contact you once I'm prepared.
Yes, ma'am.
Minister.
Thank you very much.
Not at all. I owe you.
When you said I was
the only one who could do this,
I realized what I must do.
Can you make public
what happened that day?
You're the only one who can do that now.
-Mr. Shimazaki.
-Yes?
When everything is over,
will you join me for the dinner
that we both know we've been anticipating?
What's your answer?
This is your client's order.
Understood.
I would be glad to.
I'll see you to your room.
Wait for me to open your door.
Go ahead.
Wait a moment, please.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
MURATA
Thank you.
This will make my husband happy.
My dear.
Really?
But she always lied that
she didn't see anything at the shooting.
She's just working for Igarashi.
She regrets doing that now
and will speak the truth on TV.
I can't trust anyone.
Including the people
who worked for your father?
Fine. If you can't, then don't.
However,
if Minister Tachihara
really does speak the truth,
I want you to trust her.
Also,
promise to go to prep school.
Because Dad would be sad if I didn't?
-He can't be sad if he's dead.
-Wrong.
That's what I want you to do.
You're awfully intense.
Fine, I will.
Hello?
What? You're still alive?
Gee, I'm sorry.
I forgot my ball.
I'm coming to get it now.
Okay.
How are you?
Not bad. I'm going to see
the Japan National Team play this Sunday
with Mr. Odagiri.
Really?
That Mr. Odagiri is quite something.
He wants me to live here.
He says not to worry about a thing.
That's good.
Yes.
Right.
Okay, I have to go to work.
Don't forget
to clean up the place
so you can die anytime.
That's one of the basics.
What are you talking about?
That's what I told you.
Don't add "so you can die anytime."
I'm not going to die.
Don't go and change it.
TO SHUN,
JUNYA, KAMAKURA REGULUS
He should try kicking the ball
with his eyes closed.
When you realize how helpless you are,
you won't be so tense.
This is 01, we're here.
The client will be arriving soon.
Going on standby.
-Good morning.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
This is 02, roger.
All clear at Point 1.
Points 2 and 3, no police.
Minister Tachihara is late.
-Hello?
-What's wrong?
It's been 15 minutes.
NEWS LEVEL 5
It's been 45 minutes.
Contact the client.
The number you have dialed
is either outside the service range...
The program before it is almost over.
Even if you get here in ten minutes...
she still has to prep.
She won't make it.
She's not coming, is she?
Let's wait.
It's been over an hour.
You can't even contact her.
She broke her promise.
It was you, wasn't it, Mr. Yamane?
Yes. It was an honor to be asked
to MC this amazing annual event.
Weren't you nervous about being MC
for such a renowned event?
Everyone wanted to have fun,
so I was able to have fun too.
It's a sporting event, but...
It's just a little more. Hang in there.
-I'm not sure I can.
-Oh, dear.
Next year, I will...
What will you do,
Zaki?
See you tomorrow.
HOW FAR WILL
INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY TAKE YOU?
She left us high and dry!
She played us for fools!
She didn't even leave a word.
We trusted her.
When we arrived at the hotel,
she had already checked out of her room.
It means something might have happened
to Minister Tachihara.
Even so, she could at least call us.
Dang. I may never trust women again.
Let's forget this.
All politicians are
nothing more than liars.
-We never should've trusted her.
-President!
Why are you all looking so gloomy?
Of course, we are.
I haven't been tricked like this in ages.
You've been tricked before?
A guy betrayed me once and fleeced me.
I couldn't trust anyone for a while.
What?
I'm better now.
This just arrived.
It's from a company called AI Inc.
What? Could that be Minister Tachihara?
She sent it to me just in case.
I'm sorry for not keeping
my promise this morning.
A moment ago,
Sanko TV refused to allow me on the show.
I think the party had
something to do with it.
I was worried about leaks,
so I didn't contact you.
As you said, Mr. Shimazaki,
whistle-blowers' lives
really are threatened.
But I haven't given up.
In fact, I'm more convinced than ever
that I must do this.
Give me another chance.
This time, I swear I'll keep my promise.
At the Civil Party Conference on the 18th,
she says she'll set the record straight
about Mr. Igarashi.
Even the Prime Minister will be there.
When the Secretary-General is pressured
in front of the PM and party leaders,
he can't escape.
However, since Minister Tachihara
left the party, she can't get in.
Nobody without an invitation can enter.
-You mean...
-That's right.
She has asked for you to provide her
protection past the strict security,
and into the meeting room.
What if she leaves us high and dry again?
She'll come for sure.
-Is that wishful thinking?
-No.
Remember what she said?
Now,
it's my turn to protect
Mr. Murata's honor.
She used the word "protect."
There was truth in her words.
Let's trust her.
-Shimazaki.
-Yes, sir.
Don't do this if you can't.
This has been on my mind
since Murata died.
Protecting the client is important,
but you must protect yourselves as well.
I'm sure that's what he taught you.
That's right.
Shimazaki! Yoichi...
He posted on social media.
It's on news websites.
ARE THE TEARFUL ACCUSATIONS
OF THE VICTIM'S SON TRUE?
SON OF SHOOTING VICTIM SPEAKS OUT
Do you know about what Murata's son did?
Shimazaki is probably trying
to start something.
Are you really going to do this?
Are you going to stop me?
Don't you want to protect the system?
Unless you plug the hole,
the levee will break.
Party leader squad chiefs,
Nemoto, Sakai, Kiyota.
Continue as-is with your protection.
Review your security plans. Don't mess up.
-Yes, sir!
We know you're in there, Yoichi Murata.
-Let us talk to you.
-Excuse me.
-Let us through.
There's more and more of them.
Why couldn't you wait?
Tachihara is a liar.
That's why I decided
to do something myself.
What you did was very dangerous.
I only told the truth.
If you leave now, they'll just mob you.
I'm not afraid of that!
Saying you're not afraid...
doesn't impress anyone.
You posted that out of frustration,
but you've hurt your dad more.
Can't you understand even that?
I apologize for what Yoichi did.
The press will be after you for a while.
Is there anywhere else that you can stay?
-My sister's place.
-We'll take you there.
Then we'll think about what to do next.
Thank you so much.
Yoichi!
-How will we get through?
-There's a ton of them out there.
You got it!
They're coming out!
Yoichi Murata?
You wrote that you had proof, right?
-Step back!
-Get back!
Why are you making enemies of the police?
-Do you have anything to say?
-Stand back!
-Get back!
-Don't you have anything to say?
Stay back!
-Stay back!
-Lay off!
If you don't speak, the truth won't...
Get back!
-This way.
-Okay.
I hope that fooled them.
Nice job.
-I'm going back to the office.
-Let's go.
When everyone out front leaves,
we'll go join your mother.
You know,
I'm sorry...
You did it for your father, right?
But I didn't think this would happen.
An apology...
should only be made when your heart
tells you that you really must.
Your father was that way.
He was a very gentle person.
But more than that...
he had a strength that wouldn't
let him bend his beliefs.
Really?
Before your father died...
he talked about you, Yoichi.
Even my son is still rebellious at age 19.
You said he was being rebellious.
He was actually very proper.
He even thanked me.
Really?
Is that so?
Is that all?
As your father, I think he felt relieved.
I didn't like my father.
I could never understand
why he did such an ungrateful job
like being a bodyguard.
It made me so angry.
Don't go anywhere.
Take your shoes off when you come in!
Time to die, pal!
Are you okay?
-What about you?
-I'm fine.
That's good.
What about you, Mr. Shimazaki?
No, I'm okay.
I'll be fine once I get to the hospital.
Are you okay?
-Yes. Just a little dislocation.
-What?
-Can I have some water, Sawaguchi?
-Okay.
So who were those two guys
who attacked you?
They were hired by people
who don't want the truth to come out.
The Secretary-General? The police?
Either way, that's plain nasty!
Powerful people have no scruples.
It makes me so angry!
-Oh, I'm sorry!
-It's okay.
I doubt they'll show up again.
I took photos of them.
You remember these guys, right?
I've just checked on Yoichi's family.
They're fine.
I told them to stay inside for a while.
Takanashi, what's that?
Is that a get-well gift for Shimazaki
since he was injured?
They're leftovers from the food
I brought to Yoichi.
You know, I could get used to this.
Your choice is very feminine.
I wish you were my wife.
Thank you.
The Civil Party Conference is in six days.
Will you be better by then?
Well, as for that...
Could I ask you to take over as BG?
When I was young,
I'd still do it even if I was injured.
But I don't want to cause us any trouble.
I'm the only one who can do it.
Don't be so humble.
Can you trust our client?
It's hard for me to do that.
I know our only choice is to rely on her
to restore Mr. Murata's honor.
Will she really do something that
would knock her out of her seat
in the Diet?
I see.
Of course, a bodyguard
has to be trustworthy.
But it's even more important
to trust your client.
You see...
how can you trust someone
who doesn't trust you?
I've decided to trust her.
I couldn't prepare if I didn't.
Nice.
Actually, I'm the type
who trusts just about anyone.
SCHEDULE OF CLIENT ACTIVITY
-You've really matured.
-Thanks.
May I come in?
You're already inside, as always.
Were you injured?
You sure timed your visit just right.
What did Minister Tachihara
speak to you about?
I know she came here
after announcing her departure.
Nothing.
I see. So it was something
that you have to hide.
-Hey, that's...
-Stop that!
Sorry.
Please leave.
Mr. Ochiai,
can the police do what they like
to private citizens?
I think that future SP operations
should be done
in cooperation with private companies.
What are you saying?
We'll be getting more visitors from abroad
as 2020 approaches.
There will be even greater demand
for protection services.
But there aren't any private firms
fit to cooperate with the police.
That's only my personal opinion.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
HINODE BUILDING
What do you want?
Sorry if I'm wrong, but...
is my existence
an inconvenience to the police?
I was at the scene of that shooting.
Take responsibility
for this outrage by dying!
Apologize!
For those who don't want
the truth to be known,
I'm a thorn in their side.
I don't know if this
will answer your question.
I will never give useless warnings.
Regarding that shooting incident,
I'll bear responsibility for settling it.
"Settling it"?
What do you mean by "settling it"?
Goodbye.
We'll scout out
the party conference location
and map out Minister Tachihara's route.
We may have to use brute force.
I'll try to get inside
so I can report on the proceedings.
I was a shoplifting spotter,
so I know how to watch people.
I'd like a job here.
I'll prepare the equipment.
We're doomed if we lose contact.
I'll check the radio output
and transmission relays.
SPARE BATTERIES
We're doing this
to restore Mr. Murata's honor.
It's our duty
as the Personal Security Division.
I'm from Hinode Security.
We must succeed.
We'll go in unarmed.
We'll drive the car past the SP once,
stop here, and let the client in.
We'll pass through the kitchen and pantry
behind the refrigerator here.
There's sure to be SP stationed here.
Sawaguchi and I will go as far as we can,
but if there's trouble,
we'll need you to take over.
Roger.
We'll meet Minister Tachihara
in front of the hotel
she's hiding in at 11:30 a.m.
We'll enter at venue P1.
As 01, I'll keep you updated
on the situation at the conference.
As 02, I'll check the area.
As 03, I'll provide backup for BG.
Okay.
We must get her onto the stage
before the conference ends at 2:00 p.m.
The time is 8:50. Synchronized.
-Synchronized.
Synchronized. I wish us...
Synchronized. I wish us all success.
Okay. Let's go.
This is 03. On standby.
This is 02.
Five security guards
at the reception in the foyer.
CIVIL PARTY
CIVIL PARTY REGULAR CONFERENCE
RECEPTION
Would you like something to drink?
This is 01,
a third of the guests have arrived.
-One minute 50 seconds left.
-Hey!
-One minute...
-Quit counting down.
What?
Don't you trust the client?
I trust her.
One minute 30 seconds left.
I'm certain Minister Tachihara will come.
Okay, in the minute and 20 seconds left,
I have something to tell you.
One minute 15 seconds. What?
Just for your information...
I trust you.
That's why I asked you to be the BG.
Fifty-five seconds.
Fifty seconds.
I do too.
Forty-five seconds.
She's here.
I'll take that.
Thank you for waiting.
I've come this far, so no matter
how hard they try to stop me,
I'll reveal the truth about the shooting.
Please protect my wishes.
Understood. Leave it to us.
We'll protect you to the very end.
This is 01, Secretary-General has arrived.
All clear.
Aiko Tachihara will likely come
with Hinode guards.
If you see her,
inform me and don't let them through.
This is 02, many ordinary guests
outside the restaurant near the east exit
and no sight of the police.
Thank you very much for coming, everyone.
The speech by Prime Minister and
Civil Party President, Hiroshi Shinoyama
will commence shortly.
Last year was a trying year
for the Civil Party.
But you entrusted the government
to a greenhorn like me.
This has inspired me.
Also, we heard earlier
from the distinguished...
This is 01,
Prime Minister's speech has begun.
Conference scheduled to end at 2:00 p.m.
Hurry, please.
Passing through the pantry.
Heading to the foyer.
Where are you going?
You can't go in there.
They're coming.
Suspicious persons detected.
Excuse me.
Is that Minister Aiko Tachihara?
Me?
We've been identified. Can you take over?
Roger.
Head from P3 to P6. I'll meet you there.
Go on ahead. I'll distract them.
It hurts!
Excuse me,
is there a restroom around here?
-Let's go.
-It hurts!
-My stomach hurts!
-Out of the way!
No! Don't shake me so much!
I'd like to wipe away
the negative image we have
and start fresh as a clean Civil Party.
Roger.
Don't make contact
with Aiko Tachihara yet.
This is 01, SP Ochiai has left the room.
I don't know his destination. Be careful.
This is 03, roger.
This is 03, arrived at the meet-up point.
This way.
Pardon me.
Stop!
-He's going down!
-Okay.
Hey! Stop!
Darn, who is this guy?
I'll be at Stairwell 9 soon.
Roger.
It's swarming with SP in there.
This way.
Are you certain about this,
Minister Tachihara?
Past that door and down the hall
is the banquet hall.
If you're even slightly unsure,
I won't force you to do this.
Don't underestimate me.
I don't hesitate
once I've made up my mind.
For all of you, and for me,
this must happen today.
It's been a while, Minister Tachihara.
How are you feeling?
Mr. Ochiai, please let us through.
You cannot enter without an invitation.
Please.
We have to go past there.
If you must,
then it'll be over my dead body.
Mr. Ochiai!
What you all are trying to do
is outrageous.
If you reveal the truth,
it will affect the government.
Will disrupting the system
and public order...
bring Mr. Murata back to life?
No, it won't.
Am I wrong, Mr. Shimazaki?
I don't know.
I can't be sure of what's right
and what's wrong.
I can't be sure, however...
I want to protect these things.
Mr. Murata.
The wishes of Minister Tachihara.
These are...
the people we want to protect.
You're not going after my injured arm?
The police are helpless
if they don't have evidence.
I recorded the shooting too.
I've done it ever since
Mr. Murata taught me to.
If I took the blame,
it would throw politics
and the people into confusion.
It's the secretary's job to prevent that.
As a police officer at the scene,
I will reveal the truth.
No, I will.
There are other things
you should be doing.
You're not under my protection anymore.
Let them keep you safe.
Mr. Ochiai.
Remember what I said?
I will bear responsibility
for settling that shooting incident.
Mr. Murata rescued me
when I was in a jam before.
Also, you, the people working for him,
helped me overcome
my remaining misgivings.
I'll accompany you from here.
Thank you.
Sir, are you serious?
Yes.
Chief, Ochiai has abandoned his...
Stop it!
Mr. Ochiai!
-Take her somewhere safe.
-Right. This way, Minister.
Hurry up!
What are you doing?
Stop Ochiai! That's an order!
Stop!
-That's not part of our orders!
-Don't, Nemoto!
You... Did you deceive me?
You call this settling it?
You were planning
to go public right from the start!
We'll be ruined if police misconduct
is revealed from outside.
I'm a police officer.
Go on ahead.
What the heck are you doing?
Hold on to me.
I won't rely on unarmed private security.
This is a public-private partnership.
Stop, Ochiai!
Today has been a peaceful day.
I got caught up
in an unfortunate incident,
but I'm thoroughly refreshed now
and will press on
for the citizens of this country!
Okay.
Let us applaud together.
Ready!
-Excuse me.
-Excuse us. Let us through.
-Let us through.
-Excuse me.
Let us through.
-Sorry. Excuse me.
Mr. Igarashi.
You're finished.
If I took the blame,
it would throw politics
and the people into confusion.
It's the secretary's job to prevent that.
You did a good job!
You lie!
You pinned the blame on me
and then abandoned me!
The least you can do is apologize!
You should apologize!
Take responsibility for this outrage
by dying!
Sir!
What's wrong?
Isn't that why you came here?
The only thing a shameless man
like you can do
is die a quick death!
Don't talk like that, sir!
I won't allow pointless deaths!
SHOCKING REVELATION OF SHOOTING FACTS
SECRETARY-GENERAL IGARASHI
REBUKED FORMER SECRETARY
The police have made a new announcement
about the shooting that occurred
in Meguro the other day.
The shooter, Ueno,
was provoked by the inhumane remarks
made by Secretary-General Igarashi.
Another look is being taken
at the testimony
of Igarashi's former secretary
that Igarashi directed him
to accept 70,000,000 yen in bribes
four years ago.
Diet Member Igarashi...
Murata, the people who work for you
protected you while being unarmed.
There are already moves to replace him.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for this.
So you know how to speak politely.
I always could.
Are you going to prep school?
-A little.
-You better go all the time.
He can go at his own pace, right?
But...
I'll...
take care of my mom.
Good.
Here.
This was returned by the police.
It's the final recordings.
Take care of it.
Can I listen to it with you here?
Of course.
You said he was being rebellious.
He was actually very proper.
He even thanked me.
Really?
Is that so?
Shimazaki.
Yes?
Is your watch
all right?
Yes. It's working perfectly.
-I'm glad to hear it.
-Thank you.
The time is 6:14 p.m...
and five seconds.
Synchronized.
What?
-There's no food.
-What are you doing?
-Oh, I'm home.
-Welcome home.
Wait, I didn't tell you to come back.
-I decided to.
-What?
Mom tried to stop me
but ultimately said to do as I like.
So she told me to say "hi" to you.
I see.
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm just going to meet someone.
-Who?
-Why should I tell you?
So it's a date?
No, it's not that kind of thing.
Women are pretty selfish, aren't they?
What?
They're totally different
depending on the day.
It makes me so mad
how they keep changing their minds.
You have so much to learn.
It's a man's job to have his life
turned upside-down by women.
But you got divorced.
You're right.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, I just got here.
-I'm sorry.
Please don't laugh.
Okay, I won't laugh.
I'm going to try
to become the prime minister.
I intended to give it all up that day.
When I remember that,
I realized I can change things.
I...
will continue working to protect people.
Just like I have been.
Let's have a date again sometime.
I appreciate your honest vote.
You know that's against voting laws.
Is your injury healed?
Yes, it is. Thank you.
I called to tell you that I've been put
in charge of embassy protection.
Well, that sounds like a promotion.
Congratulations.
They're trying to keep me quiet.
That's why they've put me here.
I see.
By the way, would you like to join us?
The Foreign Office has a system
for "ascending" private citizens
to temporarily work
as security specialists.
"Ascending"?
I'll give you a recommendation.
I doubt you can give
your answer immediately.
I'll give you a week.
Oh, I already have an answer.
That was fast.
In that job, you only protect
certain VIPs, don't you?
I believe that
there should be no limit
to the kind of people that we protect.
I thought you'd say that.
-Bye.
-But actually, I...
He really doesn't listen to anyone.
AIKO TACHIHARA
Go ahead.
Hey, is that you, Mr. Sato?
-Sir!
-Don't call me that.
Have you gotten used to
being a bodyguard yet?
No, not yet.
What? What's wrong with you?
Get your act together.
Sorry. I will.
-Here, why don't you have this?
-What is it?
-Meat buns.
-Meat buns?
But...
Okay, sure.
-Bye.
-Okay.
-Good night.
-Thank you.
Go ahead.
Prep for Kazuki Koda is done.
Final route check complete.
-You're late, newbie!
-Yes, sir!
You get ready too, Acting Chief.
We need to be punctual.
-Shingawa.
-Yes, sir. What is it?
The time is 8:55 a.m.
-Synchronized.
Synchronized. I wish us all success.
-Come on.
-Yes, sir.
Please continue walking.
This way.
Hey.
Don't lose sight of the subject.
Yes, ma'am.
SEITARO SAWAGUCHI: DUTY STARTED
MAYU SUGANUMA: DUTY STARTED
This is 01. Arriving soon.
Roger.
Thanks again for today.
Our pleasure.
Passing Point 3 soon.
Roger.
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.