DANGER!
DON'T RUN INSIDE THE HOSPITAL!
You don't need to rush.
Your legs are just scraped.
The bone on your right wrist is fine too.
I think they should heal in two weeks.
I see…
Thank you very much.
-I'm glad.
-Thank you.
TAKAKO KASAMATSU
SURGEON, SHIROYAMA GENERAL HOSPITAL
Your girlfriend, Sawaguchi?
What? I…
Yes.
Well, Nagiko is the ace
of the Kicks Corp secretarial team.
It'll be our sixth month together soon.
I can hear you from the corridor.
-You should be embarrassed.
-You're here.
It's been a while since I came here.
Thank you.
I'm glad that
you're close to Dr. Kasamatsu.
"Close"? You're being rude.
She just took care of my injuries,
that's all.
What?
So was it a purse snatcher?
-Yes.
-You must've been scared. Are you fine?
Have you called the police?
I called them over to the crime scene.
Also, Nagiko's cell phone was stolen,
so I reported that as well.
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you apologizing?
Of course, I should do that.
-Hey.
-What?
-Shouldn't you two get going now?
-Oh, sorry!
Let's go.
Please excuse us. Thank you very much.
-I'll call you later.
-Got it.
Sorry to bother you at this time.
You really call me a lot
for someone
who's just taking care of your injuries.
No, I…
I think you really need
to treat me this time.
Oh, okay. Sure.
-All jokes aside…
-Joke?
she said she was chased
by a purse snatcher.
-But I don't think it was the first time.
-What?
She had three buzzers with her.
Three?
There was a time when I had four of them.
If you're a bodyguard,
the reason why a woman
would have so many buzzers with her…
is so easy to tell, right?
How was it?
Well, I was touched. It was impressive.
Hello?
Oh, it's you.
KOUMEI RYU
PRESIDENT, KICKS CORP.
What you said just sobered me up.
Three months ago?
Yes.
Actually, I had been targeted
by a stalker since then.
So who is that stalker?
That's…
I don't know who they are.
They followed me
and even waited in front of my apartment,
but I was so scared,
I couldn't take close look on their face.
Do you have any idea who it could be?
Not at all.
But this means that
her address has been discovered, right?
-Man, I'm so thirsty.
-So you came, Takanashi?
What? Actually, I didn't intend
to come here anymore.
I knew it.
-Don't tell me you two had a fight?
-What?
No way. We're adults. Right?
Do you use social media?
Oh, yes.
Log in to your account.
NAGIKO TSUNODA
There are many instances
wherein a victim's address was tracked
via their photos' background
or the reflections on their irises.
It might be better
to deactivate your account for now.
So that's how it is.
So Shimazaki, Takanashi,
could I ask you both to protect Nagiko?
What?
Shimazaki and I?
Yes.
I'll be on duty tomorrow,
so I have to work at night.
I won't be able to
accompany her back home.
I mean…
you two should have more time, right?
-Are you saying that we have no jobs?
-No!
I don't mean that. What I'm saying is,
I believe that you two are capable
of stopping and handing the culprit
over to the police.
I mean…
please help Nagiko so that she could
live her life with peace of mind.
You don't have to do so much for me!
I just tripped over myself this time.
They didn't hit me!
What are you saying?
You might be assaulted next time!
What will I do
if something happens to you?
Please. I beg you…
I plan to marry her.
Sei?
Hey, don't propose to her
in a place like this.
I mean it! Nagiko…
She's pure, she's serious with her work,
and she's different from
all the flashy women I've been with!
Would you normally say things like that
in front of your girlfriend?
Anyway,
please…
I'll pay for the fees with my savings.
Do you really have savings, Sawaguchi?
Not your parents' savings, you hear?
My salary increased
after I went to Kicks Guard!
-Your salary increased?
-Yes.
-We've had risk allowances since April.
-Risk allowances?
Don't expect that from me.
Big corporations can afford that.
Sei…
It's fine. I don't care
what they say about me.
-All right?
-For now…
we're a weak and small company, so…
-No, I don't mean that!
-No…
I don't mean that. You're close to us,
so it'll be dangerous if you let
your guard down because of that.
Even so, would you still…
leave her protection with us
as an official job request?
Of course.
He's saying that he won't be giving you
any discounts, not even a single yen.
Not even a single yen?
For personal protection services,
there are two major types
you can choose from.
The first is to show the perpetrator
that you have bodyguards
to discourage them from attacking you.
The second is to let the bodyguards
protect you from the shadows.
Instead of suits, we'll wear
casual clothing to catch them off-guard
and effectively capture them.
If you want to catch the stalker,
I believe the latter is better.
Would that be fine?
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
It's a new pattern.
It's good to have rice
for breakfast, isn't it?
At Mom's place, she makes miso soup,
grilled fish, and preserved pickles.
Hey, you feel like going back there now?
Not at all.
SHUN SHIMAZAKI
AKIRA'S SON
There's nothing more irritating
than seeing your mom getting
all chummy with her new husband.
I see. So they're all chummy.
Don't tell me you're hurt now?
Well then, shall we have some seaweed?
I mean, things are going well
between you and Dr. Kasamatsu, right?
-Hey, she's a doctor, you know?
-Occupation has nothing to do with it.
Where was it again?
Somewhere on the top rack on the right.
What? I can't open it.
Hey. Let me say this.
You know, I…
I don't plan on deepening
my relationship with any woman.
My work has a lot
of unknown factors after all.
-That won't make you popular.
-What?
You know, women like men
with the courage to jump over high walls.
You sure talk a lot.
-Oh, it opened.
-It sure did.
President Ryu will be
in the company today.
Tonight, he'll be having an interview
at the Freundschaft Hotel.
I'll be with him.
Ms. Yamashita,
can you call the hotel to let them know
we'll be arriving tonight?
Yes, sir.
Well then, I'm counting on everyone.
-Yes.
-Yes, sir.
-Excuse me, Iwata.
-Yes?
As for the previous security plan,
the president has placed me in charge.
Understood. I will be counting on you.
We'll finish it as quickly as possible.
Rest assured.
What's this?
Are you injured?
Oh, I just tripped.
As expected of
the Security Division Chief!
I'm sorry that I didn't notice it,
Ms. Tsunoda.
Please let me know
if there are any inconveniences.
Thank you very much.
Please allow me to explain.
Assemblyman Kuwata has been appointed
as Special Aide to the Prime Minister
as of June 1st.
Apparently, he leaked rumors
that his predecessor,
Assemblyman Otonari,
conducted acts of dishonesty,
and is now being hounded
by the mass media.
But if we are able to
protect him perfectly,
it could be a chance to strengthen
Kicks Guard's reputation.
Please exercise extreme caution.
-Yes, ma'am.
I will be the BG.
Backups will be Shirai, Kawazu,
-and Sawaguchi.
-Yes, ma'am.
The corresponding B Team will also…
She's like the president.
Keep quiet.
-Yes, ma'am!
-Well then, I'm counting on everyone.
-Yes, ma'am.
This is 02.
No suspicious person detected
en route to the train station.
This is 01. Understood.
You can go back if you don't like this.
Who's the kid now?
You can't protect her alone.
It's not impossible.
Hello? This is Tsunoda.
This is Shimazaki.
Can we call you on this cell phone?
Yes.
I've contacted the police,
but my cell phone wasn't returned to them.
I see.
Just forget that we're around
and proceed with your daily activities.
We've checked the route back to your home.
Takanashi and I will take turns
to protect you
while trying not to attract any attention,
so we're counting on you.
I understand.
300M TO TRAIN STATION (4 MINUTES)
LEFT TURN IN 37M
WALK STRAIGHT FOR 120M
120M FROM TRAIN STATION
TO GREEN BELT (3 MINUTES)
BACKUP ALWAYS CHECKS THE REAR
She's leaving.
It's strange.
You think so too?
She wasn't scared when she heard
those footsteps behind her just now.
What do you think is the reason?
She feels safe that we're protecting her.
At least that's what I want to believe.
I don't think so.
In the case of stalker victims,
they're usually in fear around the clock
as long as the stalker hasn't been caught.
Maybe she knows.
She knows?
That the stalker won't come?
She knows who the stalker is.
Are you all right?
A suspicious person wearing
work clothes is headed to you.
Understood.
I'm tracking him.
GOURYOU SHRINE
Have a seat.
It's rather cramped here.
Can you really protect someone
in a place like this?
Thank you for your concern.
We're a small company,
so it works in our favor.
Don't you have coffee?
I'm fine with black.
Ms. Tsunoda is
being targeted by a stalker.
Judging from the situation,
the stalker would be you, Mr. Omata.
No way.
I'm not that shameless.
I don't think your actions
are befitting of someone
who used to work as the chief of
the SP division of police HQ.
You deliberately disguised yourself
and loitered around her apartment.
It's not a coincidence, right?
Mayu Suganuma became
an executive officer before you,
so you're tailing female employees
out of spite now?
I'm not such a petty person.
To me,
now you're just a middle-aged man
under suspicion of stalking activities.
Wow, you're so sneaky, Takanashi!
You brought a pretty lady here.
I'm working.
Stop spouting nonsense
and just go already.
It may be business,
but it's etiquette to praise a lady!
I'm sorry that he's so insensitive.
You're annoying. Just go already.
Sawaguchi will be here soon.
Could you please let Chief Omata go?
Don't tell Sei either.
Why?
He was waiting in ambush for you.
But he didn't do anything to me.
Why do you want to cover for him?
Do you have a reason for that?
There's nothing like that.
He is Sawaguchi's superior,
so I don't think it's good to act rashly.
Welcome.
If you're my bodyguard,
then please listen to my orders.
Are you all right?
Thank you, Takanashi.
Is it true that
there was someone suspicious?
Yes.
But we didn't have any proof,
so we couldn't do anything.
What?
Why couldn't you detain him?
You could've just handed him over
to the police.
I'm fine.
You know, I don't think
I really need bodyguards.
-Let's end the contract.
-Wait a minute!
Thank you so much.
Please give my regards
to Mr. Shimazaki as well.
Please excuse me.
-Thank you!
-Thank you.
So I'm free to go, right?
I'm very sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
It's true that he was at the scene.
If we treat him like a criminal
while the client says otherwise,
then it's proper manners to apologize.
I owe you big time.
Jeez, that hurt.
If you let him off now,
it'll all be for nothing.
She must be trying to hide something.
That must've been why she said
she encountered a purse snatcher.
And you're going to leave it be?
Bodyguards can retaliate from assaults,
but they cannot take the first strike.
Even if you say that,
you're actually scared, right?
As I said before,
-I can't protect anyone if I'm not scared.
-Stop trying to fool me!
You're scared of getting involved
with Kicks Guard…
no, with President Ryu, aren't you?
That's because you can't stay calm.
You won't be able to control yourself!
You're afraid of yourself, aren't you?
I'm here today as Sawaguchi's friend.
I just can't keep quiet about it.
What are you hiding?
Nothing, just as I said.
Good morning.
Ms. Nagiko.
Sawaguchi…
requested our services because
he wanted you to have peace of mind.
Allow me to tell you this
as your bodyguard.
Our mission isn't over yet.
The stalker isn't Chief Omata.
It's my superior.
Your superior?
It's Mr. Iwata, the chief secretary.
Mr. Iwata? If I recall,
he's an excellent secretary, isn't he?
-Ninomiya.
-Yes?
-Check out the meeting room.
-President Ryu favors him…
-Please contact the company.
-and was specially selected for the post.
-Please prepare the slides.
-Just because he's excellent at work,
it doesn't mean
that he never makes mistakes.
How did you know?
You're working hard.
Good work.
If you would like to, how about
having dinner together after this?
-I'm sorry.
-When I stayed back alone to work,
he invited me to be alone with him.
I rejected him and told him that
I was already going out with someone.
From then on, there were times
I found my locker unlocked.
There were also traces of someone
logging into my email account.
LOGGED IN WITH ANOTHER DEVICE
I think he took my cell phone
out of revenge for rejecting him.
I believe he asked Chief Omata
to make sure I won't spill it.
We'll finish it as quickly as possible…
If this matter is exposed,
it won't be just mine,
but even Sei's job will be in jeopardy.
Is that really the reason?
Sawaguchi may get ahead
of himself at times,
but he's not someone
who's scared of things like this.
Even you…
you're going out with Sawaguchi
because you like that part of him, right?
You said that bodyguards
should listen to their clients, right?
Protecting secrets is also part
of a bodyguard's duty.
He threatened to reveal everything.
Please stop this! Get out!
I like you!
I said I like you!
I'm calling the police!
If you report this to the police,
then Sawaguchi will also find out
that I kissed you.
I didn't want Sei to know.
If he started to think
that it didn't end with just a kiss,
what am I going to do?
The stalker won't give up
even if you keep quiet.
Not to mention…
if Chief Omata
took action to make sure you stay silent,
then they have done
something unforgivable as an organization.
Let's fight back properly.
For Sawaguchi's sake too.
Can someone like me
even fight back?
Anyone can fight back.
NAGIKO TSUNODA
YOU HAVE A VOICE MESSAGE.
This is Nagiko Tsunoda.
I would like to speak to you, Mr. Iwata.
I'll be waiting for you
in Conference Room B.
You have to come over.
The target is Chief Secretary Iwata.
ETA, 30 minutes.
-Current time, 13:01. Synchronized.
-Synchronized.
Please make it before 4:30 p.m.
Also…
What?
What's going on?
I'm on duty.
Duty? For what?
It's confidential!
A high-ranking secretary
stalking his subordinate…
For a company that is advancing
into the security industry,
this could be a fatal scandal for us.
I'm very sorry!
I didn't intend to cause you trouble,
Mr. President.
What should we do?
Shimazaki is an excellent bodyguard.
Today, let's show him
what a real bodyguard is all about.
I can feel myself getting nervous.
We're with you.
Yes.
It's five minutes past the ETA.
Mr. Iwata is late.
Maybe he got lost. I'll go fetch him.
Please be careful.
She can be considered a bomb
to Kicks Guard at the moment.
It's dangerous to let emotions affect--
I'm different from you.
I don't let emotions affect me
while on duty.
You actually said that? I'll remember it.
I know you can hear me!
Hey.
Just now on the ground floor,
-I saw Shimazaki and Takanashi.
-Here?
They said they were on duty.
They were with your girlfriend.
That's…
What's wrong?
Never mind, it's nothing.
Hey, isn't that Shimazaki?
Hey!
-Thanks.
-It's been a while.
Shimazaki, over here!
-What's the matter? Is Nagiko--
-She's fine.
It's been a while.
Could you please call
Chief Secretary Iwata?
-I would like to meet him--
-You don't have permission to enter!
This is trespassing!
Yes.
What?
I understand.
What's going on?
Just come with me!
Orders from the president.
Please excuse us.
Oh, Shimazaki.
Please come in.
I was the one who appointed Iwata
as Chief Secretary.
You can talk to me.
I would like to talk
to Mr. Iwata directly.
Please let us meet Mr. Iwata.
For her sake,
I think it would be best
to settle this amicably.
What's the meaning of this?
We expected some sort of trouble to occur.
That's why we had our bodyguards with him.
Please let Sawaguchi leave the room.
I'm sure you know that
he's in a relationship with Ms. Tsunoda.
Mr. Shimazaki.
I'll be fine.
All this time,
I did my best to become
a first-class secretary.
I don't want to give up
because of something like this.
Please promise that
you won't follow me around anymore.
Also, please return my cell phone!
The cell phone not only contains
my private photos,
it also contains backups of important data
for your work, Mr. Iwata.
They're both important to me.
Iwata.
You don't know when to give up, do you?
Stalking is a despicable act.
I'll have you resign
from your position as Chief Secretary.
I'll contact you for a follow-up.
Until then, you have to stay at home.
Sawaguchi.
I will send him off, President.
I will be on duty
for Assemblyman Kuwata after this.
-Let's go.
-Wait!
Are you fine with that?
Is it all over
after he received his punishment?
You've changed a lot.
You still haven't apologized!
If you don't apologize and promise
not to stalk her anymore,
she won't be at ease.
Why should I apologize?
I'm only doing this for the president.
For the president?
What is the meaning of this?
I don't feel anything special toward her!
I just wanted to erase the evidence!
Among the materials that
I've given you permission to access,
there were some files showing
that President Ryu handed over
security data involving politicians
to Assemblyman Kuwata!
If word about this gets out,
things will become a mess!
The reason I followed her
and pushed her down,
it was all pretense!
If it was stalking,
it would just be an individual issue!
Hey!
-What have you been saying?
-Sawaguchi!
You're on duty!
Did you know how scared she was?
Stalking forces one-sided feelings
on another person, that's unforgivable.
But inflicting fear on someone that
you hold no feelings for is even crueler.
This… and that…
It's all for the president!
What shallow thinking…
Mr. Iwata!
There's no way I would do something
so uncouth in the first place!
-Leave with her!
-Stop!
Let go!
What are you doing?
Luckily, it was cold coffee.
But if it was hot coffee
or some other chemical product,
I would've died.
I'm sorry.
Forget it.
That's what bodyguards amount to, anyway.
"It's fine if they are put in danger."
Is it?
What are you talking about?
The reason why Shimazaki left Kicks Guard
was that he found out
I planned the attack during that event.
He was angry that you were attacked,
so he left the company.
He criticized me and told me
to never put you guys in danger again.
Isn't he an amazing senior?
However,
I still don't think I'm in the wrong.
Japanese people have
no sense of urgency at all.
But I want to let them know
the danger around them
so that they'll realize
the need for personal protection.
I cannot agree with your methods
of exposing people to danger
in order to promote your own company.
That day, Sawaguchi and I put our lives
on the line to protect the scene.
You put your lives on the line?
Anyone can say that much.
When a real gun is pointed at you,
can you still stand right where you are?
I'm always prepared to be
my client's shield.
And it's not just me.
Takanashi, Suganuma,
and even Sawaguchi would too.
Five years ago,
a person I loved was killed
during a burglary
at my home in Los Angeles.
The brawny bodyguard I employed then
ran away.
I wanted to forget about the incident,
so I set up this company.
Just when I felt
I had started on a new path,
I suddenly thought to myself,
"Is it really right to
forget the sorrow I felt?"
That's why I decided
to join the security industry.
I don't bear a grudge
toward the bodyguard who ran off.
That's how humans are.
In fact,
humans are incapable of anything.
Yet those who say they'll put their lives
on the line and become shields…
I hate people who say that.
I'm truly sorry.
We weren't able to help you achieve
what you wanted to do.
I gained confidence just from doing that.
I'm resigning from the company.
Thank you. You protected my determination.
You did everything yourself.
How cool.
Hey.
You didn't even tell me anything.
I feel so lonely.
I wanted you to rely on me.
Hey.
Should we take some time off for now?
I wanted to protect you, Sei.
That's why I couldn't say it.
I wanted you to rely on me too.
Sawaguchi must have been shocked.
Sorry.
For what?
I went overboard.
It's just as you said.
I let my emotions get the better of me.
That's not a bad thing actually.
Everyone gets angry
and loses sight of themselves at times.
How is that not a bad thing?
If I get influenced by my emotions,
it'll be better to just quit this job.
Be a little more honest with yourself,
will you?
Hey.
Why are you putting up a guard around you?
That's because I'm a bodyguard.
That…
isn't funny at all.
Oh, Assemblyman Kuwata.
Thank you for all your help.
Is anything the matter?
We've reached the location…
Did our bodyguards offend you in any way?
About the previous incident,
because of your secretary's carelessness,
the data might be leaked, right?
Where did you hear that from?
I can't tell you that.
But if it comes out,
it'll tarnish the Prime Minister's image
since he was the one who appointed me.
Even if the Prime Minister falls,
your name is sure to remain in history,
Assemblyman Kuwata.
What do you mean?
I won't say a word.
I will put my life on the line
and protect you, Assemblyman Kuwata.
What the hell is that?
Who does he think he is?
It's just as you said, Assemblyman.
You cannot trust that man.
That man
only thinks of everyone else as his tools.
Hey.
Good work today.
Please allow me to resign.
You don't have to quit.
I'll assign Iwata to another position
at Kicks Corp. Hong Kong.
President,
you said that
you don't hate bodyguards.
However, I can't help but think
that you despise us.
You're right.
I hate bodyguards.
But it's different from holding a grudge.
Hate can be turned into motivation.
You would probably understand
since you've been in love.
Compared to the lukewarm feeling of love,
hate feels way more intense than that.
If you focus your energy
into that feeling,
you can turn it
into a business of your own.
Welcome!
Sorry to call you so suddenly.
I never expected you to treat me for real.
Well…
are you really fine
with conveyor belt sushi?
Fatty tuna, sea urchin, fluke fin,
prawn, and squid sushi, please!
-That's a lot.
-Thank you!
Surgeons get hungry easily.
All right!
-I'm digging in.
-Please go ahead.
The stalker…
-Did you get him?
-Oh, yes.
I didn't have a bodyguard with me then,
but my husband protected me.
Oh, your husband.
What?
I'm single now.
Oh then…
we're the same.
He was really cool
and really strong.
Maybe even stronger than you, Shimazaki.
It doesn't feel nice
to hear that directly…
He's not someone you can win against--
-Excuse me!
-Yes?
Let's see… sea urchin, prawn, squid,
-fluke fin, and fatty tuna, please.
-Thank you!
Are you angry?
Quite.
It's nice to be angry.
You can only get angry
because you're alive.
I don't like to beat around the bush,
so I'll give it to you straight up.
My husband was a police officer,
but he died
just three months after we got married.
What a cruel man.
He suddenly left you at a time
when the two of you should be
enjoying your lives together.
It's the first time
I heard someone say that.
Everyone at the police station
told me that he died an honorable death
and that I should do my best
to inherit his resolve.
But in reality,
I was so angry.
I thought,
"What the hell are they saying?"
I'm glad I told you this, Shimazaki.
As expected from someone
whose life is always in danger.
Sorry, but please head to the station.
Don't follow me, no matter what.
I'm used to people taking revenge.
Stop this already!
I've seen that man somewhere before.
Please! Protect our curry!
-Where is your husband?
-He was killed.
Be extremely cautious of him.
I know you're dealing with
something very dangerous.
This case is much more troublesome
than we expected.
You're a bodyguard that protects
his clients, no matter who they may be.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu