This is life or death.
My life depends on this.
BEAUTIFUL, NOBLE, GREAT LOVE
A MOTHER'S GAZE
ART MUSEUM ENTRANCE
Hello.
Nobody saw you, right?
-Right.
-Good. This way, please.
This way.
I've brought them.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The SP didn't notice you, right?
Yes, sir.
AKIRA SHIMAZAKI
HINODE PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
AIKO TACHIHARA
HEALTH, LABOR, AND WELFARE MINISTER
GORO MURATA
MANAGER, PERSONAL SECURITY DIVISION
You must be surprised.
I was surprised as well.
I first met Minister Tachihara
when we provided security
for the Civil Party.
I never thought
she'd request security herself.
Is this a personal security request?
I thought Cabinet members
were provided with SP.
That's why I had you come
to this location secretly.
On Saturday, the 10th,
I'm going to see someone
at the Kaylington Hotel.
I'd like you to provide me security.
However, the SP must not know about it.
SP is provided 24 hours a day
for government ministers.
In your case, Minister Tachihara,
your security detail had been increased
since you were threatened.
It's not possible for you
to slip past the SP.
That day, the Minister will be getting
a physical exam at Teiwa Hospital.
She's a close friend
of the hospital director.
You mean...
The trip from Teiwa Hospital
to Kaylington Hotel is under an hour.
The meeting will last one hour.
She will take three hours
to leave the hospital,
attend her meeting, and return.
Excuse me, but why do you have to
keep it secret from the SP?
Do you think I can tell you that?
She's meeting with the leader
of an opposing faction.
If it becomes public,
it would affect the election.
She can't have the SP coming along
to something like that.
I can count on you, can't I?
I told you, I'm fine. I'm eating right.
I wash my uniform myself too.
You-know-who is back.
Who's "you-know-who"?
-I don't know.
-That was your mom, wasn't it?
What does she want?
Does she want you to come home?
No. She and Mr. Odagiri
are all lovey-dovey.
Lovey-dovey? Is that so?
So you know, what is he?
-What do you mean?
-Well, I mean...
How old is he and what does he look like?
That's none of your business.
You've been divorced for years.
He's ten years younger than you.
He's totally cool and rich too.
No...
There's no way she's dating
such a perfect guy.
So maybe she is. What does he do?
Some kind of research.
She says he's really smart
and really kind.
So the exact opposite of me?
Minister, can you tell me
why you met with those people
from Hinode Security Service?
It's better for you
that you don't know, Sakagami.
I see.
I'm here.
We were laughing so hard about you
that we hardly drank at all.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Here.
We think your assignment is
too tough for an amateur.
Sir, I'm not an amateur.
Since you gave me your support,
I've worked as hard as I can.
You're all talk.
You haven't even passed a single bill.
-I'm doing my best.
-Are you?
You need to be more determined.
You need to shed a few tears
at a Diet session.
Sir,
nobody has ever been fooled
by a woman's tears.
Quite the opposite, in fact.
I believe once I cry,
then it's all over for me.
Here.
-Shimazaki.
-Thanks.
We should turn down this job.
There he goes whining again.
Slipping her past SP
and escorting her to
a confidential meeting with God-knows-who?
That's insane!
Since our company accepted it,
we have no choice but to do it.
It's kind of exciting though.
We guys are going to be in charge of
a government minister.
Don't be stupid!
If the SP finds out,
we'll lose our security license.
It won't be exciting. It'll be a tragedy.
-Well said!
-Don't kid around!
This is seriously dangerous!
I know, but every job has some risk.
The client is taking a risk.
That's why they're hiring security.
Reckless clients treat us like hired guns.
That's why bodyguards get
no respect in Japan.
Respect has nothing to do
with this kind of work.
It's more a matter of how hard
we work behind the scenes.
I think people should have
more respect for this kind of work.
That would reduce crime.
That's why I joined
the Personal Security Division.
As for you,
you probably don't want any attention.
Why doesn't he want attention?
I don't know.
I see.
Actually, I believe a bodyguard's job
is to protect the client,
even if the world hates us for doing so.
Good morning.
Oh, you're here too, Mr. Ochiai?
The replacement starts today.
I'm your new bodyguard. My name is Mori.
I'll do my best to protect you.
Nice to meet you.
It's energizing to have
a young man assigned to me.
Yes, ma'am.
He's taking over for Kiyota
starting today.
Minister, I'm sorry I couldn't be
of help to you.
I would appreciate another chance--
Okay, let's get going.
The Minister is leaving.
Ministers must be in good health.
Getting a physical exam
is part of the job.
YOSHIAKI OCHIAI
SECURITY BUREAU (SP), MPD
BG - SHIMAZAKI
BACKUP - MURATA
How can you be so stubborn?
The manager is covering for you!
Hurry up and check on traffic conditions.
Which of us is right?
What?
Me or that old geezer.
Should we accept this ridiculous request?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
Don't you have an opinion?
No, I don't!
All I want to do is use
my physical abilities
to work and make money.
How pathetic.
Who are you calling pathetic?
At your age, you're pathetic
for whining about
why we're taking some job.
Besides, you're practically
an old geezer yourself.
Hello?
Hello, Shimazaki here.
We're at the location
and starting the mission.
No reports of construction or accidents
along the route to the destination.
Roger.
This is exciting. I feel like
we're in the US Secret Service.
Hey!
Be very careful. If SP sees us, it's over.
Yes, sir.
PRIVATE ROOM
What a nice room.
A physical exam
is the only time I get a break.
This is 03.
The Minister has arrived in the room.
This is 01, roger. All normal at Point 2.
Minister, you can be seen from outside.
Please take care.
Thank you.
I'm going to change now.
You must be busy, Mr. Ochiai.
You can go now.
I'll be going then.
She can be self-indulgent.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
-I'm counting on you.
-Yes, sir.
SP leader has left the main guard.
Now heading for Point 3.
Roger. Let me know if you need assistance.
They'll be on the move
in under ten minutes.
Hey, quit goofing around
and check their route.
This is odd.
What is it now?
Aiko Tachihara is
in Secretary-General Igarashi's faction.
So the opposing faction leader
is Zenta Koda.
That's right. What about it?
He's in Niigata today
at a trade board meeting.
Then isn't it that Isomura guy?
Juro Isomura is judging
a political speech contest.
Look.
There are tons
of other politicians out there.
Thank you. I'll be getting a CT scan
and a colonoscopy now.
It'll take three hours,
so go wait in the waiting area.
No, I'll wait in front of your room.
After each examination,
I'll speak with the doctor about
how to maintain my health.
Why don't you have some tea
in the waiting area?
I can't do that while on duty.
Your predecessor, Kiyota,
made my life difficult
because he tried too hard
and was inflexible.
I hope you can work with me
for a very long time, Mori.
Use this to buy yourself some tea.
Well, if you insist.
I promise to contact you when I'm through.
In here, please.
It's this way.
This is 01, I'm with the Minister.
This is 03, I'm with them.
Hello, Sakagami speaking.
I'm at the hospital now.
I'm going to turn off my phone
for a while.
But Minister, what if...
Don't worry. You can take
the rest of the day off.
But...
The Kaylington Hotel.
All the guest rooms are occupied today.
The banquet and wedding halls
are booked too.
That doesn't mean anything.
When I was in Cash Transport,
I transported the proceeds
from a live concert here.
Each floor is wide open
and visible from the others,
so it's a very public place.
A well-known politician wouldn't go here
for a confidential meeting.
That makes sense.
So what do we do?
Inform them, of course.
Don't order me around.
Tell them yourself, Takanashi.
You figured this out.
Why are you so stubborn?
What a child!
Hello, Mori speaking.
Where is the Minister?
She's having an examination,
so I'm on stand-by as she ordered.
Don't just sit around
because she told you to!
Always know where your charge is.
Yes, sir.
SP haven't figured it out, have they?
I think it's all right.
I told them my tests
would take three hours.
Minister, when is your meeting?
At 3:00 p.m.
-Get a move on.
-Yes, sir.
Shimazaki speaking.
The bossy, stubborn old geezer noticed
that several things seem fishy
about this mission.
Fishy?
Is Minister Tachihara
really going to Kaylington Hotel
for a confidential meeting?
Minister?
Minister Tachihara?
I don't know anything at all!
About five minutes ago,
the Minister herself called
to say she was turning off her phone
because of the physical exam.
That's all I've heard from her!
-She may have been kidnapped.
-What?
Did you get a ransom call?
-No!
-You sure you don't know anything?
I mean it. I don't know anything.
Mr. Sakagami, if something happens,
you could be held responsible.
Tell me as soon as you remember anything.
Okay.
Let's order a search.
This could be something serious.
Wait.
Excuse me.
Can you keep it a secret
that I told you this?
Of course.
Actually, the Minister had a list
of guests for a wedding ceremony today.
-A wedding?
-Yes.
For a friend of the Minister?
-Where is it?
-I don't know.
However, a few days ago,
she met with Personal Security people
from Hinode Security Service.
Minister,
why exactly are you visiting
Kaylington Hotel?
We'll keep it confidential.
All right.
I'll tell you.
This isn't a confidential meeting.
It's a secret rendezvous.
What?
I'm single, and I'm in love with someone.
He's married,
so nobody can know about this.
I'm sorry that it's such a trite thing.
Why today at 3:00 p.m.?
If you wanted to avoid notice,
you wouldn't choose
the middle of the day on a holiday.
Why would you do something
this risky and anger the SP
just for a secret rendezvous?
If you want perfect security,
then we need to know your true purpose.
The first time we spent time together
was five years ago today.
We watched the sunset
from the Kaylington Hotel.
I intend to end our relationship today.
That's why I insisted
on meeting him today.
You know where
Minister Tachihara is, right?
What do you mean,
with you guys barging in here?
We know that you met with the Minister.
The other day, I warned you.
Don't forget that security companies
are under police jurisdiction.
You know
where Minister Tachihara is, right?
Yes, we do.
Then you'll assist us?
No.
You understand this situation, right?
It's an unprecedented situation.
The SP have lost sight of their charge.
Hello?
Okay. All right.
My apologies for barging in.
We won't need your help.
On the other end of this tunnel is
Toshin Road near The Kaylington Hotel.
Right.
What's this? There haven't been
any reports of congestion.
Hello. Shimazaki speaking.
Takanashi here.
-I know.
-The SP was here.
Already?
They've set up a checkpoint
near the tunnel exit.
I'm bothered that they're doing this
only on streets leading to the hotel.
I think they know what we're doing.
Roger.
-They've noticed, haven't they?
-Yes.
We have a report of
an unusual checkpoint at the tunnel exit.
They must be really ticked off.
-They might even shoot us.
-That's unnecessary!
Sorry.
Minister, it's not too late to return.
Take me to the Kaylington Hotel.
You could be called
to account for what happens.
Take me to him.
You arranged to meet at 3:00 p.m., right?
-Yes.
-Shimazaki,
what if we're stopped at the checkpoint?
We need to break through
the checkpoint, right?
It's 2:12 p.m. and 35 seconds.
-Synchronized.
I wish us all success.
Haven't you forgotten
to report to me, Ochiai?
I heard something I can't ignore.
Kiyota ordered the local police
to set up a checkpoint.
I certainly hope that nothing
has happened to the Minister.
-That's ridiculous.
-I thought so.
If something had,
it wouldn't just be your career,
but my career as well
that would be affected.
Nothing has happened.
Excuse me, but the Minister is calling.
CHECKPOINT
MPD
Plate number Shinagawa 300 A 80-84.
You're with Hinode Security, right?
Yes, how did you know?
Where are you going?
We're headed toward Yokohama
for a meeting at a client's request.
You're with the SP, right?
You're guarding Minister Tachihara.
Why are you at a local police checkpoint?
That's none of your business.
Is anyone behind that curtain?
-Well, no...
-I'll check it myself.
Hey!
What did you do with the Minister?
What are you talking about?
You're like a mole.
EVACUATION ROUTE
I did road construction security,
so I know a little about these tunnels.
Please be careful.
Every experience in life
is useful, isn't it?
These stairs lead to the surface.
Put this over your head.
-But...
-Hurry.
There's no time to hesitate.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
How can you do all this
for a stranger's secret rendezvous?
You're not a stranger.
You're our client.
Is something wrong?
I...
I bet you saw right through me.
The secret rendezvous was a lie.
I want to see my daughter.
Your daughter?
To be more precise,
a daughter I've never even held.
Back during my second year at university,
I became pregnant.
The father was also a student.
We ended up breaking up.
Once I had no choice but to have the baby,
I pretended to go abroad to study
so I could give birth.
Then for my own future,
I gave her up for adoption
to a physician couple
soon after birth.
Now, she's 26 years old.
She graduated from medical school
and will be marrying her senior,
a doctor from the same school.
So today is...
My daughter's wedding.
Apparently,
they named her Yui.
I've never once wanted to see her.
But it's funny, isn't it?
When I learned that
she was getting married,
I suddenly had to see her,
even if it's just once.
So that's your real reason, right?
You don't seem surprised.
You're wearing formal clothes,
a pearl brooch, and a necklace.
That's the opposite of what
you'd wear to a secret rendezvous.
In fact, it makes sense now that I know
you're here for your daughter's wedding.
Also,
everyone
has a past that they can't talk about.
Let's go.
EMERGENCY EXIT
Hello, Shimazaki here.
We'll be arriving soon.
Immediately find a route
to the banquet hall that's out of sight.
I know where all the hotel entrances are.
There's a pool next to the hotel.
You can reach the banquet hall
by entering that way.
Roger.
Let's go inside the church.
You can see her from there
without the other attendees noticing you.
That was a long stroll you took,
Minister Tachihara.
The wedding will be delayed by 30 minutes.
You postponed it, didn't you?
Minister, return with me.
Hold on!
My mission isn't complete.
The public thinks you're at the hospital.
You must leave here as soon as possible.
Please let me have just five minutes.
This is life or death.
My life depends on this.
TOMIKAWA FAMILY
I'm sorry for the sudden intrusion.
No matter how many times
I've requested a meeting,
you've always refused.
Barging in uninvited at a wedding?
KEICHIRO SAKIYAMA
CHAIRMAN, JAPAN FEDERATION OF PHYSICIANS
You lack common sense.
He's the chairman of
the Japan Federation of Physicians.
It appears you didn't know
what the Minister's purpose was.
I have heard that
you're opposed to increasing
the lump-sum benefits
for childbirth and childcare.
But I believe that
to stop the declining birth rate,
we must increase these benefits.
You just want to improve
your approval rating.
You just want to increase
how much doctors can charge,
which, in turn,
helps your funding sources.
Children are the nation's assets!
That kind of thing won't fool me.
These are the ideas
of a childless, single working woman.
It's completely unconvincing.
THE PARTIAL REVISION OF LUMP-SUM BENEFITS
FOR CHILDBIRTH AND CHILDCARE BILL
Chairman.
The bride, Yui Tomikawa,
is my daughter.
You know nothing about the Minister.
And you think you know her?
At the very least,
I realize that
politicians have many faces.
Yui doesn't know about me.
Of course, it's not public,
and the media doesn't know either.
Then why confess this to me?
When I decided that I wanted
to see Yui on her wedding day,
I found out that you were
one of the groom's guests of honor.
It made me think that my daughter
was trying to bring us together.
Because I had to give up my own daughter,
I want to pass a bill
that will do something for children.
Get out.
If you're going to open up
and beg like that,
then I guess I have no choice.
I'll consider it.
Don't ever get involved
with the Minister again.
If you can promise not to,
then I'll ignore this incident.
We're only doing our job.
Are you still saying those things?
You defy comprehension.
I can't understand you either.
Why are you so hostile?
We're both in the business of
protecting people.
I've seen reckless
private bodyguards get hurt.
When people need security,
unarmed people like you
should obey us, the police.
So gun-toting SPs are better than us?
This is my final warning.
I'm back.
I'll take you to the hospital.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Shimazaki and the others
were only following my request.
Don't punish them or anything like that.
Minister...
my mission is not yet complete.
-Shimazaki.
-Yes, ma'am.
Your mission is complete.
Let's go, please.
-Welcome back.
-I'm so tired.
I'm surprised you made it back alive.
Oh, thanks for that.
I forgot to thank you before.
Nice assist.
I don't agree with your opinion.
Why does he hate you so much?
-Actually, I think he likes him.
-Really? I like him too.
That's not even funny.
-But you're laughing.
-I guess so, but...
-Write that report. Now.
I'll be done with it in a flash.
Nice work.
I'd prefer that you don't accept
this kind of mission again.
Why not?
The Personal Security Division
won't take this kind of incident lightly.
Coming from a former SP,
you're exactly right.
However, the Minister is now in our debt.
When it comes to the business,
this was a success.
I realize I have my own past, but...
who exactly is Shimazaki?
I don't think
he's just a regular security guard.
That's pretty good.
You've been practicing.
-Leave me alone.
-Don't talk like that. Hey, Shun.
Do you want to see your mom?
Not at all.
-Hey!
-I'm going to take a bath.
HITOMI
DIALING
Hi. It's me.
I think I should tell Shun.
He wants me?
Protect me until I leave this time.
Are you deceiving us?
Zaki can't refuse me, right?
That's why I asked you.
Junya Kono is under police investigation.
We won't help you flee.
Get going!
Up until six years ago...