MESSAGE BOARD
[suspenseful music playing]
PLEASE FIND MY SISTER
[woman] My sister…
Her name's Kurumi.
She said she was meeting
someone in Kabukicho.
And ever since then, she's been missing.
Weird things have been happening
in Shinjuku lately, right?
I've talked to the police already,
of course.
I read online about, um,
writing XYZ on the message board.
You two are the last hope I have,
City Hunter.
Do it.
Please find Kurumi.
-[dramatic sting]
-[music swells]
[dramatic music playing]
[reporter 1] A man was assaulted
in Kabukicho today.
Around 4:00 p.m., a pedestrian encountered
a man in violent psychosis.
In an attempt to stop…
[reporter 2] Shortly afternoon today,
an unidentified person…
[reporter 3] At around two o'clock
this afternoon,
a group of teens were attacked
when a young man lifted a vending machine…
[reporter 4] After his violent rampage,
he apparently escaped
by jumping up a twenty-meter-tall…
[cop 1] Assault near
Shinjuku 3-chome intersection.
[cop 2] The suspect is most likely armed.
[cop 3] Send backup now!
[music fades]
♪ Mokkori, mokkori, mokkori babes ♪
♪ Mokkori, mokkori, I have a crush ♪
♪ On all the babes in the sauna ♪
♪ Red bikini mokkori babe
Black bikini mokkori babe ♪
♪ Beige is nice, but I'm losing my mind
For the babe in the white! ♪
-[man] Hey, Ryo.
-[Ryo] ♪ Red bikini mokkori babe ♪
-♪ White bikini, I see you, babe ♪
-Are you listening, man?
Uh, yeah! ♪ White bikini babe
White bikini babe, yeah! ♪
♪ Red, black, beige, and white bikini… ♪
[man] Your focus is on
helping that client, right?
[sighs]
Miss Sweater Melons, I got it.
[man] That's the one.
Get it together, huh?
[Ryo] They're already here.
[sighs]
-[man] You see them? What about the girl?
-[Ryo] Yep, I see her.
Act quick. Ryo, do something.
[Ryo] Ah, well.
Plan B it is.
[whooshing]
You never even had a Plan A, man.
[Ryo] Okay!
Adieu, white swimsuit babe!
[thug 1] We're not leaving
until you tell us.
-[slaps]
-[grunts]
[whoosh]
[glass shatters]
[dramatic music playing]
[distorted swell]
-[upbeat music playing]
-[grunts]
Whoopsie. Direct hit.
Allow me to get you out of here.
Whoa, hey, who the hell are you?
-[Kurumi yelps]
-[groans]
You should give up.
-[thug 2 exhales] Oh.
-[thug 3] Asshole!
[grunting]
[grunts, groans]
Just wait!
Ah, come on!
-[thugs grunt]
-[Kurumi shrieks]
I told you to give up, remember?
You bastard! [grunts]
[grunts, yells]
-It hurts!
-Give up already.
[grunting]
-Whoa!
-[grunts]
[groaning]
Let's call it off, hmm?
-[crackles]
-[grunts]
"Ah, it hurts."
[thugs yell, grunt]
[upbeat music continues]
[yells]
[gun shot echoes]
-[music halts]
-[groans]
No, no, no, no.
You brought something dangerous.
-[shell cases clatter]
-Confiscated.
[upbeat music continues]
[music halts]
-I'm all done.
-[enchanted chime]
[whimpering]
[Ryo] Hmm?
What the…
Hey, Makimura!
The target is on the run!
Hey, what did you do, Ryo?
[Ryo] I was just saying hello!
-[dramatic music playing]
-[phone ringing]
KAORI
[panting]
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Yes, we see him. He's here.
Excuse me one sec.
Hey, let's go, guys. Let's go!
[continues panting]
-[woman] Oh, it's Ryo!
-[man] Oh, Ryo, welcome!
-Mama, you see a girl come through?
-Yeah, she just came through.
Okay.
Whoa, who's this?
[laughs] Oh, this one?
She's a new girl. Koto, say hello.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
-What time are you done?
-[thug 4] Where'd you go, punk?
[Ryo] I'll be back!
Next time, bring your money
and stay a while!
[Makimura panting]
[thug 5] Where's he taking us? For real!
[continues panting]
[thugs yelling indistinctly]
[exhales shakily]
[continues panting]
-[exhales]
-[music halts]
[upbeat music continues]
[loud thud]
-[gasps]
-Ah!
Where'd she go?
[thug 6] Hey, over here!
[thugs yelling]
[thug 7] Right behind you now.
-Six guys.
-[Ryo] No, nine.
Ready?
As ready as I'll ever be, man.
-[all yelling]
-[rock music playing]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[thug 8] This asshole!
Makimura!
Whoa! You hangin'?
Yeah, I'm good. [grunts]
Are you sure about that, huh?
I said I'm good, didn't I?
Yah! [grunting]
[exhales]
[Ryo] Not bad.
-This is my main gig.
-[man 9] Die!
[grunts]
[woman screaming]
[music ends]
-What's going on?
-Sorry. [chuckles]
[bottles clink]
-Ryo.
-[Ryo, Makimura panting]
Huh?
[Kurumi grunting]
[Ryo] How did she…
You follow her. I'll bring the car around!
[Ryo] What do you mean, "Follow her"?
[breathing heavily]
I can do it!
[distorted swell]
Whoa!
-[yells]
-[screams]
-[all yelling]
-[woman] Oh, it's Ryo!
[upbeat music playing]
-[engine revs]
-[tires screech]
[continues yelling]
[glass shatters]
-[continues yelling]
-[enchanted chime]
[rock music playing]
Like a pervy Aladdin.
-[boing]
-[Ryo yells, grunts]
-[brakes screech]
-Hey, man. You okay?
SAEBA CO.
You told me to follow her!
Well, there she goes!
Plan C, then.
Got it.
[Ryo] Sorry! Coming through!
[phone ringing]
[panting]
[brakes screech]
-[Kurumi continues panting]
-[phone continues ringing]
[woman 1] Girls bar upstairs, sir.
-[Kaori] How much longer will you be?
-Sorry, I… I got tied up at work.
Listen to me. This was your
idea in the first place, you know?
I'm on my way.
-Just hold on!
-[phone beeps]
[line ends]
[sighs]
[panting]
Ah!
[continues panting]
[cat yowls]
[shrieks]
[gasps, pants]
This game of tag is over now.
Don't misunderstand.
Your sister. She sent us.
[heart thumping]
[dramatic swelling]
[grunts loudly]
[clink echoes]
[breathing heavily]
[continues breathing heavily]
Huh? [sighs]
[panting]
Ah, dammit!
Makimura, key!
Quickly!
Whoa!
Oh!
Do you care to explain this?
Hold on, Saeko!
Bodily harm, property damage,
gunfire, traffic violations…
My phone hasn't stopped ringing all night.
You know I lose it
when I don't get to see you.
You've been a naughty girl, Saeko.
-Mmm--
-[gun cocks]
Don't make me get naughtier.
Mmm.
[unsettling music playing]
[exhales]
[dramatic swell]
[whistle blows]
[Saeko] Isn't that
Akutsu Syndicate territory?
[indistinct chatter over radio]
Why were you poking around in there?
-It's confidential. We can't say.
-[Saeko sucks teeth]
You do know I've got better things to do.
-Don't you?
-Oh yep, yep.
[Ryo] Mm-hmm.
[groans softly]
You know the people losing
their minds out of nowhere?
We found another one
of their bodies today.
So with that, stop stirring things up
and stay out of my way.
-[Ryo] Mm-hmm.
-That goes for you too.
Whoopsie!
-We get it, okay? Yeah, yeah.
-[man] Ah-ha.
It's you idiots again.
[inhales sharply]
You quit the detective life,
so why keep up this act?
Keep your nose out of it.
Give it a rest, why don't you?
We were only passing through.
Right? Uh, huh?
We're taking you down to the station.
He can go, Officer Ito.
This was voluntary questioning.
That's all, then. You can go.
Right.
You'll jeopardize your career, Nogami.
Oh dear!
Is that harassment, Officer Ito?
Where to, sir?
[sighs]
Oh, get in.
It's her birthday, yeah?
[sighs]
[Ryo] That girl from earlier.
Kurumi, was it?
What was that all about?
Don't know.
How are we gonna explain this
to Miss Sweater Melons then, huh?
[sighs]
By the way,
what did you put in your pocket?
[chuckles]
Are you talking about this?
Apparently, she's a cosplayer.
Thirty thousand followers.
Hmm. I don't care.
The one for me is Miss Sweater Melons.
It's pretty hot, my man.
-I'm not into little brats, man.
-All right. And now?
[upbeat music playing]
[Ryo] Oh. Whoa!
-Sexy, no?
-You butthole, quit it! [chuckles]
-[both yell]
-[tires screech]
[both breathing shakily]
Sorry about that.
Nah, dude.
Um, send me that, would ya?
It's evidence.
[pensive music playing]
[engine stops]
Ah.
[gentle music playing]
Don't hit on her.
That's up to me, isn't it?
-[Makimura sighs]
-[chuckles]
You're gonna tell her, aren't you?
When my dad first brought her
home with him,
she was only, like, this big. [chuckles]
Is telling her really necessary?
So what, you're not actually related?
It's just my dad said
he would tell her once she was an adult.
Well, it's up to me.
I'm glad it's not me.
[both chuckle]
-[inhales deeply] I'm gonna get going.
-Yes, sir.
Hey.
Off-limits.
I don't know. [chuckles]
[Makimura] I am asking you, dude!
-Off-limits, got it?
-I hear you. All right, man?
This way, sir.
Sorry, Kaori.
[Kaori] Ugh.
-I've been waiting for you for an hour.
-Yes, you have.
We could've just stayed in.
[Makimura] No, no way! Sorry.
I was looking for someone's lost pet.
This dog was just running and barking.
And then… [chuckles]
…we finally catch it,
and after all that, it bit us. [laughs]
[Kaori] Mmm.
-What?
-Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking,
"So that's the guy who dragged
my poor brother into this risky business."
Risky?
Searching for lost pets?
It's… It's not risky at all.
The message board.
"XYZ," no?
"Taking on any job, no matter what."
-City--
-Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I got it.
You know, I'm an adult now.
[tires screeching]
[loud whoosh]
[tires screeching in the distance]
So, listen…
Hmm?
What?
Nothing. [chuckles]
Here's to your birthday.
[chuckles] Thank you.
Don't drink it so fast.
[exhales] I know.
So, uh, I have something
I wanted to tell you.
Yeah? Go on.
You're scaring me a little bit.
Oh, come on. What is it?
[chuckles softly]
[exhales]
The fact is…
[glass shatters]
[screaming]
[Makimura groaning]
[loud bang]
[breathing heavily]
[heart thumping]
[raspy exhale]
[squelching]
[raspy exhaling continues]
[Makimura panting]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[continues breathing heavily]
[straining, choking]
[grunts]
[loud slash]
[Makimura continues breathing heavily]
[squelches]
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
-[growls]
-[stabbing]
[grunts]
[stabbing continues rapidly]
[brakes screech]
[Ryo] Makimura.
Makimura!
[Makimura grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[emotional music playing]
[Makimura groans]
Sorry, man.
I shouldn't have taken 'em.
You weren't meant for this kind of work.
[chuckles softly]
[groans]
[Makimura] Ryo…
Take care of Kaori.
[groans]
[emotional music continues]
[loud whoosh]
[music distorts]
[gun cocks]
[dramatic music playing]
[music halts]
MESSAGE BOARD
CONTACT ME
KAORI
[reporter] The man who was confirmed dead
upon arrival at the hospital
has been identified as Hideyuki Makimura,
a thirty-six-year-old
former police officer. [echoing]
The Police are investigating the attack
as just one in a string
of seemingly random crimes
and are searching for the culprit.
-[keyboard clicks]
-Hmm?
Wait, what's that?
[line ringing]
-Hey, it's Ryo.
-Ryo--
[Ryo] I'm currently nursing a boner
and cannot answer the phone.
-Leave your message after the bee--
-[sighs]
-[door opens]
-[Ito] You're watching that again?
It's just like the other incidents.
It's the fourth one this month.
Becoming violent all of a sudden,
improved athletic ability…
Do you think it's some kind of drug?
A virus?
If it's a drug,
then who created it and why?
So, what I'm hearing is no leads?
[sighs]
And watching that won't bring him back.
Partnering with a lowlife
will do that to you.
Am I wrong?
If he'd only stayed a cop,
it wouldn't have turned out this way.
[sighs] Let's just find this guy.
Get the press off our backs.
[door shuts]
[bird tweeting]
[tender music playing]
-[man 1] Welcome!
-[man 2] Hey, handsome, where you going?
You guys can have a great time.
[man 1] Uh-oh!
[indistinct chatter]
Girls' bar.
-Three-day receipt challenge in Shinjuku!
-[teen] Receipt challenge?
-You see that?
-For real? You think?
[pensive music playing]
-Girls in there!
-Sure. Yeah, let's go.
[indistinct chatter]
[girls] The girls' bar is waiting for you!
-The girls' bar is waiting for you!
-[indistinct chatter]
Whoo!
[laughter]
[indistinct chatter]
[women laughing]
[Ryo laughing]
-Let's go to Nagisa's bar!
-Yay! Good for me!
And after, we'll go to
Sakura's place and drink!
-Huh?
-[woman 1] Who's that?
Who's this? Someone you know, Ryo?
Mm-mm. No idea.
-Mmm!
-No smooches.
[all chuckle]
Oh, give me a break!
-Hear that? That's our cue. Bye for now.
-[Ryo] What?
If I hear anything, I'll let you know.
-[Ryo] Sure.
-[women chuckle]
-Bye-bye, beauties!
-[women] Bye-bye!
[Ryo] Bye bye! [laughing]
[grunts]
-What do you want?
-You saw the message board, right?
-What do you mean?
-I wrote a request.
I wanna know who killed my brother
and why they did it.
How do you think I would know?
-Let's figure it out together, then.
-No way.
-"No way"? It was your fault, though!
-Huh?
He was your partner, right?
-You don't feel responsible for this?
-Better yet, I don't feel a thing.
Let's figure it out together!
We can avenge him together!
You listen.
Forget about those who've passed on.
That's the best thing to do.
-Oh, miss! Where are you going? A bar?
-Dickhead!
-[Ryo] How about tea with Ryo?
-Fine! I'll look into it myself!
[Ryo] Ugh!
How about a roasted green tea latte?
Excuse me. Have you seen this person?
-Huh?
-Do you know him? He's my brother.
-Your brother?
-Yes, he's Hideyuki Makimura.
Have you seen him?
Oh, yeah. I know him.
-Seriously?
-I do. I know him. I know him very well.
-Uh, where--
-Hey, you know what?
-We should go talk about it in my office.
-Yeah.
What do you think?
[man] I can get you
a good part-time job.
Ah, there you are! Found you.
This isn't the kind of place you belong.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
-[man] Who are you, huh?
-The brother she was talking about is me.
-[man] Huh?
-Let's go.
-[Kaori] Huh?
-Siblings, right?
-[man] Your sister?
-You troublemaker! [laughs]
Sisters, yeah!
Hey, what's with all
that "brother" stuff, huh?
Go home and sleep, bonehead.
[elevator chimes]
I slept, woke up, and now I'm here.
Huh?
Oi!
Don't just barge in.
-[Kaori] So this is Saeba headquarters?
-The hell? Go home!
My brother was working here, right?
There's gotta be clues lying around.
Touch nothing.
Hey!
[Ryo sighs]
Uh…
[whimsical music playing]
-What's this for?
-What do you care?
Enough! Get out.
-Don't touch that!
-[items clatter]
[music swells, fades]
Argh!
It's research.
Ah, ta, ta, ta. Stop snooping.
Hey!
You little…
[Ryo sighs]
Ugh!
I was looking for this one.
[music halts]
-That's Makimura's gun.
-[gun thuds]
Colt Lawman MK III.
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[sharp swell]
[shell casings clatter]
This was his reality.
It's no place for you to be.
[breathing shakily]
Forget about him.
I mean it. For your own good.
[door shuts]
[cop 1] Hey!
SHINJUKU 3
[sirens wailing]
Roger.
[camera shutter clicks]
-[cop 2] Any personal effects?
-[cop 3] No ID.
[cop 4] Oh yeah? And the body?
[cop 3] Knife wound to the left shoulder
and bleeding from the cranial area.
[cop 5] We're moving him.
[camera shutter clicks]
Talk to the locals.
Yes, sir.
-[cop 6] One, two…
-[cop 7] Coming through! Coming through!
Stand back! Stand back, please!
[cop 8] Stand back!
Okay, stand back! Stand back!
[crowd murmuring]
Stand back. Please stand back.
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathes deeply]
YOU'RE AWESOME, MILK!
SO INSPIRING. PLEASE POST MORE!
BADASS COSPLAY!!!
1 NEW MESSAGE RECEIVED
HI, MILK.
WE ARE REACHING OUT TO YOU ABOUT…
KABUKICHO ICHIBANGAI
[humming]
-[girl 1] Ryo!
-[girl 2] Ryo!
Tsubaki! Hey, hi! Hey! Oh!
Let's go on a date right now, yeah?
-[Tsubaki] Are you gonna pay off your tab?
-[Ryo] What?
-[girl] Let's go!
-Uh…
Actually, about that. Today's no good.
-Oh! Next time, then!
-Say hi to Mama. [chuckles]
[indistinct street chatter]
You really don't let up, do you?
I'll follow you till you accept
the request I made.
Don't be a creep. Go home.
I don't have anywhere to go home to.
Like I care.
[sighs]
If you want to find out that badly,
I can show you.
Introduce you to the world I live in.
[upbeat music playing]
-♪ Ooh, Mokkori show! ♪
-[crowd cheers]
-♪ Mokkori show! Mokkori show! ♪
-[crowd] ♪ Mokkori show! Mokkori show! ♪
♪ Grow, Ryo! Grow, grow! ♪
[crowd] ♪ Grow, Ryo! Grow, grow! ♪
[Ryo] ♪ Mokkori show! Mokkori show! ♪
[crowd] ♪ Mokkori show! Mokkori show! ♪
♪ Grow, Ryo! Grow, grow! ♪
[crowd] ♪ Grow, Ryo! Grow, grow! ♪
Here I go!
♪ Mokkori show! Mokkori show! ♪
[crowd cheering, laughing]
[loud pop]
[crowd continues cheering, laughing]
Ooh, ha!
♪ Mokkori show! Mokkori show! ♪
Whoa! Hey!
[crowd] ♪ Ooh, mokkori show! ♪
[cheering continues]
Mokkori show!
Yeah!
-Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
-[cheering continues]
Now, off to the bathroom
'cause I've got a stomach ache!
Yeah!
[cheering continues]
[man] Come back!
[woman] Whoo-hoo!
[Kaori] Bathroom's the other way.
Ahh, I can never get rid of you, can I?
[scoffs] Keep it in line.
Entry's members only.
Just open the door.
Hey.
[whispers] This guy knows the boss.
He's good to come through.
Sorry about that. Go ahead.
[Ryo] Yep.
[indistinct chatter]
[dealer] Place your bets.
-[laughs]
-[groans]
[indistinct chatter]
-[thug 1] Excuse me, sir.
-[thug 2] You again.
[thug 3] It's that dude
from the other day.
[thug 4] What are you doing here? [gasps]
Hey, she isn't the one, guys.
[gasps]
Go on and say something, jackass! Huh?
[man] Hey!
Old Man, it's the punk from before!
[tense music playing]
-[thug grunts]
-[crowd gasps]
-[grunts]
-[women scream]
[man] Get your shit together!
-[punch thuds]
-[crowd gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
Well, why don't we let go
of that for now, huh?
I haven't had time to educate
the younger ones yet, Saeba.
Looks like you're doing well, Akutsu.
"Saeba," he said? City Hun…
-[Ryo chuckles softly]
-[Akutsu] Eh.
Business is over for the day.
Send our guests home.
[unsettling music playing]
You, there.
Put some pants on for us.
[music halts abruptly]
-[dealer] My apologies.
-[guard] I need to ask you to leave.
[ice clinks]
[thug 5] Here.
It seems you've been investigating
host clubs, cabarets, and the like,
in connection to Makimura.
[Ryo] Could there be
something wrong with that?
Hmm?
I was sorry to hear it.
He was a good one.
And yet died so easily.
[chips thud]
It wasn't us, you know?
Ah, you know that.
You've heard about the people
that lose control all of a sudden.
-[hip-hop beat playing]
-[yelling]
[yells]
[crowd clamoring, laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
-[all yell]
-[glass shatters]
[woman] Ah! What's wrong with his face?
Oh no!
[Akutsu] They're runaway kids
and unhoused people.
They disappear, one by one,
and when they finally show back up,
they turn violent and then die soon after.
The one who attacked Makimura was
also found dead by the side of the road.
It's Kurumi, right?
The girl you've been looking for.
We've been affected too.
Two of our younger members are gone.
A young lady came looking for us, saying,
"My friend has gone missing.
Can we search for him together?"
[laughing]
So, what were you gonna do with her?
Oh, Kurumi, though…
She's the only one who's disappeared
and come back with her sanity intact.
Huh.
So, it is distinctly possible,
well, that she knows who they are
and what they're hiding.
I get it now.
Go on.
[laughs] What do you mean, "Go on"?
We were just getting to the bottom of it
when you two got involved.
Ah.
Ah, well. All fine.
It's your thing now.
So now I'm stuck with it, Old Man?
If we hear anything, we'll let you know.
Listen…
Stay on your guard.
The drugs they're experimenting with
are quite dangerous, so I've heard.
This group…
I don't think that any of them
are right in the head.
Where is the girl now?
[sighs]
That is what we are trying
to work out now, young lady.
We've heard…
she's a runaway and spends most
of her time in the Toyoko area.
Hey, where are you… Argh!
Is that your new partner?
There's no way. Ugh!
[laughing]
[man] Drink with me.
I know you've got time.
-[girl] Oh, that's them!
-[girls screaming]
Excuse me. Have you seen this girl?
-[girl 1] What? Why?
-[boy] Who is this? Someone you know?
You know her?
-[boy] Sup with her?
-[girl 1 chuckles]
She's missing.
-[girl 2] We wouldn't tell you anyway.
-[girl 3] Sorry. Bye! This way.
-[boy] Hey, let's go.
-You haven't seen her?
[boy] Leave us alone.
[Kaori] Huh? [grunts]
Hey! [scoffs]
Hey, are you dense?
-This is the only way.
-There's no way they're going to tell you.
-[girl 4] It's Kurumi!
-[girl 5] What?
-[girl 4] Kurumi!
-[girl 5] What've you been doing?
-Wait, what?
-[girl 4] We've been worried.
-[girl 5] What happened?
-[girl 6] Are you okay?
Do exactly as I… Argh!
Sorry, hey! Uh, hey!
Kurumi-san, right?
-[girl 5] Who's this?
-[girl 6] Who's she?
-[Kurumi whimpers]
-[girl 4] Hey, get away from her!
-[clamoring]
-Hey, listen!
-[upbeat music playing]
-Wait!
What did I tell you?
[Kaori] Hey!
Hey, wait!
[cheering]
[host] One, two, one, two, three, uh!
♪ Show me what you got
Show me what you got ♪
♪ Show me what you got right now, uh! ♪
-[cheering]
-[continues singing indistinctly]
Ow! Yay!
[Kurumi] Excuse me.
♪ Give it to me… ♪
[continues singing indistinctly]
Excuse me.
[gasps]
[gun cocks]
Kurumi, wait!
[all cheering]
[continues singing indistinctly]
[music halts abruptly]
[distorted swell]
[whooshing]
[continues singing indistinctly]
Wait! Kurumi!
-[gun cocks]
-[groans]
Excuse me! Excuse me! Excuse me!
-[gun cocks]
-[grunts]
-[glass shatters]
-[all screaming]
-[man] Run! Run! Run!
-[all clamoring]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
Kurumi, wait!
Wait, okay?
Hey, just listen!
Hey! Hey, please!
Hold on!
[whimpering]
What's wrong, huh? Are you okay?
KENTO
[distorted swell]
[Kurumi] Let me go! Let me go!
[unsettling music playing]
[doctor echoes] Administering syringe.
-[distorted music continues]
-[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[heart thumping]
[screaming swells]
-[screaming halts abruptly]
-[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[gasps]
All right! You're awake?
Oh, sorry. This must be a bit of a shock.
Um, I'm Kaori, and, um,
you collapsed, so I brought you here.
-Oh, do you have a fever?
-[grunts softly]
Sorry.
I'm leaving.
[gasps] No.
-Are you okay? Oh!
-[whimpers]
Leave me alone.
[Ryo] You shouldn't be up yet.
Rest a bit more.
[Kaori] Sit here.
I need the two of you
to stop following me everywhere.
Oh, well, we weren't following you.
It was your sister. She made a request.
She had asked me to track you down.
She's worried about you.
Who? "Sister"?
I don't have any siblings.
Hmm?
You know, your sister, with the sweater?
I'm telling you that
I don't have any siblings.
Whoa.
[sighs]
[Ryo] Bamboozled!
She managed to trick me again!
Damn her assets!
[Ryo sobbing]
-It's pain!
-Hey. Kurumi, let me ask you.
Were you abducted by those people?
[Ryo] Oh, I've been had.
If there's something you know,
please say it.
You know, those guys?
Did they take you somewhere?
I know nothing!
Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Kurumi] How do…
[Ryo] My late partner had it.
Her older brother.
[tender music playing]
You dropped it, didn't you?
Kento.
Kento is my friend.
He was gone, out of nowhere.
I went looking.
Some strangers grabbed me and…
They injected me with something.
And then I went unconscious.
I know I need to tell
somebody about all of this.
So, I took it with me and ran.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry you went through that.
I gotta go.
Uh, but, Kurumi…
You shouldn't be… Oh, Kurumi, you should…
-[grunts softly]
-Are you okay?
It's not safe out there.
You should stay here for a while.
Lie down here.
[ominous music playing]
We did find her.
And we…
We took out Makimura, but--
Shh.
Does it hurt, Brown Bear?
Please, sir. Give me a cha--
[man] You lack ambition.
[electronic beeping]
[breathing shakily]
[sloshes]
[ominous music continues]
We're under pressure from the homeland.
I need you to bring me
the last piece of the puzzle.
For the good of the Union.
[dramatic swell]
[dramatic music plays]
ANALYSIS REPORT
Keep your things out of my mailbox.
[Ryo] Oh, I thought you might like it.
Well?
It's a match.
The composition matches what
we found in the other suspects.
[Ryo exhales]
Including the one who attacked Makimura.
Apparently, it affects the brain first,
giving the subjects
a super-human level of strength.
The subjects become extremely aggressive,
the effect wears off, and they die.
Angel Dust. Could be it.
You've heard of it?
It was used in warfare long ago.
[boy panting]
[Ryo] It was eventually banned
for being inhumane.
This one must be a more potent version.
[Saeko] Someone kept working on it.
Do you think targeting Shinjuku
was an intentional move?
A kind of advertisement.
If they eliminate the side effects,
it could be sold worldwide for warfare.
And Kurumi is the only one
to survive it so far.
[Saeko] That's why
they tried to kidnap her.
[Ryo] It all ties together.
It's not something
the human race should be capable of.
[pensive music playing]
Those two from the club…
If you hear anything, let me know.
[music continues]
Hold on.
[distorted swell]
Come to think of it,
something similar did happen
in Japan once before.
[tender music playing]
Twenty years back, a man lost his mind
and attacked a detective,
who ended up having to kill him.
CRIME SCENE INVESTIGATION REPORT
The detective…
was Makimura's father.
INSPECTOR NOBUYUKI MAKIMURA
His father decided
to take the dead man's daughter in
and raise her as his own.
The child was Kaori.
FILED BY: HIDEYUKI MAKIMURA
For years, he looked for the drug
that drove the guy nuts.
He never found it.
[tender music continues]
[music fades]
[Kaori] Yeah, good! Uh-huh! Amazing!
Yeah, super cute. Make me feel it!
And, action!
[Kurumi] Nice to meet you.
The girl in a carton from Milk Village.
I'm your girl, Milk! Meow!
And cut! Good, yeah.
What did I tell you? This was good.
[Kurumi] You don't think
the flirting went too far?
No, it's your first appearance.
You have to show your character.
-Right, Ryo?
-Uh, uh-uh.
You're looking kinda pervy.
How about shut up? I'm not a pervert.
Hey, Milk, my dear, you had something
you were gonna ask him, didn't you, meow?
Oh yeah?
Come on, come on, come on.
What now? [gasps]
Meow!
-Stop it.
-[whimsical music playing]
Stop now.
Stop i-- [yells]
Will you grant my request? Meow?
What is it, meow?
Oh…
The truth is…
Speak your mind, meow.
Tomorrow, I'm going to be
a cosplayer at a Lore event.
Please protect me.
A cosplay event, meow?
Uh, yes.
Um, Lore, the makeup brand.
They're mega popular right now.
Hmm…
So?
No way, meow!
-Huh?
-It's obvious.
She's being targeted,
and you want her at that event?
[scoffs] But it's Lore!
-Ugh, you're a guy, you wouldn't know.
-Actually, I do.
This kind of opportunity
doesn't come along often.
How could I protect her?
We both will.
There's gonna be so many eyes
on the event. What could happen?
-Don't act like you know things.
-I want to support her.
You got a DM asking you to appear, right?
It's a great opportunity.
There's a lot riding on this for her.
-[Ryo] Mmm…
-[Kaori] Ugh!
All right. Don't worry.
You don't need to come.
-[Kaori] Huh?
-I can go on my own.
If I chicken out and don't go,
I'll regret it.
I guess if they get me, then they get me.
If I die, I die.
No way.
[bag zips]
Your life can't end here.
Don't think like that.
Okay.
You're going tomorrow, okay?
You're gonna get up there,
and we'll protect you, me and him. Right?
-[Ryo sighs]
-And the CEO's gonna be there.
Huh? CEO?
[gasps]
[grunts, exhales]
[clears throat]
Guess I'm going, meow!
Yes! [laughs] Whoo!
-And it's "Meow" with a capital "M!"
-[inhales sharply]
[Ryo] The CEO?
[clamoring]
[journalist] You've established Lore
as a subsidiary of Seta Pharmaceuticals.
There's been no shortage of praise
for your skills as CEO.
Thank you. I'm grateful to hear it.
Can I ask you what the thinking
behind this event was?
The conceit is to express
the concept of nature in a playful way.
We made anime characters,
and we asked cosplayers
to attend this event dressed as them.
In doing so, we hope to introduce Lore
to an even wider audience.
Perhaps the reason
why people like you so much
is your bold approach to your work.
I couldn't say that,
but I try to always strive
to make my late father proud of me.
[girl 1] Am I good?
Uh, yeah. What about me?
Can you see anything?
-A little.
-What?
-Kidding!
-Come on.
-[both chuckle]
-[Ryo chuckles, clears throat]
-[girl 1] Thanks for waiting!
-Oh!
[girl 1] We don't have much time.
-Let's go, let's go!
-[girl 2] So cute!
-[girl 1] Ready?
-[girl 3] I'm ready.
Oh my God, the hotties are everywhere!
-Thanks for waiting.
-Whoa!
Yeah, just patrolling here. All quiet.
Nothing going on.
Then again, there is.
Dear God!
This place is incredible. [laughs]
Hey, do I have to dress up too?
You gotta fit in. Deal with it.
-I love it.
-[Kaori] Huh?
-It looks so good on you!
-[Kaori] Huh? Y… You really think so?
-[chuckles] It looks good?
-How should I know?
[breathing heavily]
Okay, here. Hold this.
-It's way too much.
-[Kurumi] Come on!
-No, no!
-Okay, and hold it like this. You know.
Oh, is this it?
-Yeah.
-Really?
-Uh, so, like… like this?
-[Kurumi chuckling]
-Ho!
-[Kurumi] It looks great.
Oh, this feels pretty darn good.
-[Kurumi] It fits you!
-Whoa, watch out!
You are on the clock. Simmer down.
Y… You're right.
And what about you?
[Ryo] Me? [chuckles]
I am always ready for anything.
All right, everyone.
This is a brand-new endeavor.
Let's all enjoy it.
I'm counting on you.
[all] We won't let you down.
-[man] Okay, let's go!
-[girl] Thank you.
It's Milk, isn't it?
-Uh, hi.
-I thought that was you.
Sorry to reach out late.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
I knew that I needed to have you here.
-I begged my staff to reach out.
-Oh, really? Thank you so much.
[chuckles] Give it your all.
[Kurumi] Thank you.
-[Ryo] Howdy.
-[Seta scoffs]
I am Milk's new manager,
the Stallion of Shinjuku, Ryo Saeba.
[women giggling]
[Seta] Manager?
I train talent, I plan events,
all of your magical requirements.
-President, time to go.
-[Ryo] All of them.
-Call me.
-We have a little more to get ready.
-See you later.
Yes, ma'am. We'll see you later, then.
[Ryo whooshes]
Time to get ready.
Yup, Kurumi, yup. Do it up.
-Hey, man, no touching her!
-Ooh! Ah, the hell is that?
-See you after.
-[Kaori] You got this.
[girl 1] There she is.
-[girl 2] Yes, she's here.
-Facial expressions can help you out.
She's looking much more like herself.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
[sighs]
Mmm.
[gasps] Let's go. Guard duty.
-Take this.
-Huh? Oh.
Huh?
[cheerful music playing]
[crowd applauding]
[cheering, applauding]
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[cheering continues]
Welcome to Lore's big
and bold cosmetics presentation
here at Cosplay Wonder Fest Odaiba.
We'd like to…
Hey, you guys, don't be nervous.
It'll go great. Let's do it, okay?
-Yes, we'll do our best.
-[Rosiel] Yeah, we got this!
I'll be your presenter, Ami Yamazaki.
It's a pleasure to be with you all today.
C'mon! Ami, let's go! You're doing great!
[dramatic sting]
[engine revs]
[sharp sting]
[crowd cheering, applauding]
[Ami] Next up.
Beautiful clear skin with Lore's serum!
Smooth skin, just like Milk.
Her reputation precedes her.
She's the girl in a carton
from Milk Village!
Making her event debut
as a cosplayer, it's Milk!
[applauding continues]
[man] Milk!
It's nice to meet you, everyone.
I'm Milk.
Meow!
-[camera shutters clicking]
-[all applauding]
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct yells]
It's great to see you, meow!
You're amazing, meow!
-[girl 1] I'm rooting for you, Milk, meow!
-[girl 2] Look this way!
[all cheering]
[man] Adorable!
[upbeat music continues]
Nothing seems weird so far.
-[Ryo] Yuh-huh.
-Huh?
Those dicks.
Where? Where? Where?
[Ryo] Three of them. At 12 o'clock.
[unzipping]
They're coming! [grunts]
Watch and learn.
This is how a pro gets things done!
[upbeat music playing]
[all] One, two…
-[camera shutters click]
-[Ryo] Ha! Huh!
[all] I can't see!
-Get out of the way!
-Sucks, to be you, huh?
[man 1] Shit!
-Over there! Right there!
-Yeah, there! Over there!
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[Ryo grunting]
-You suck.
-Damn it!
[man 2] Over there, over there!
[camera shutter clicks]
-[man 1] You suck!
-[man 2] Knock it off!
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[Ryo grunting]
[man 1] Hey, horse asshole,
would you get out of the way?
-[men clamoring]
-Ugh. Are you serious?
-[clamoring continues]
-[man 3] Move! Come on, get out of here!
[unsettling whooshes]
[dramatic swell]
[grunts]
-[dramatic music playing]
-[gunshot]
[Ryo grunts]
[exhales]
-[gunshot]
-[Ryo grunts]
[grunting]
[whispers] What are you doing, Ryo?
Neigh.
[man] Show me your smile.
Uh, Miss Black Leather, would you mind?
Oh, uh, you're taking it off.
Go ahead, then… Uh, excuse me…
Uh, these back shots are also great,
but uh…
[dart whizzes]
-[Kurumi] Saeba-san, that's…
-Get on.
-[Kurumi] But--
-Just do it. Let's ride!
-Wait! Wait!
-Whoa!
[Ryo neighing]
-[man 1] Where are you going?
-[man 2] Come back!
Scorpion.
Are you okay? What happened?
[breathing heavily]
How I've missed you,
my sexy Miss Sweater Melons.
Very astute, Ryo Saeba.
It isn't in me to forget such a sexy babe.
[dramatic music playing]
Wow. [exhales sharply]
Help her.
Find my sister.
You role play.
[scoffs]
-[crowd yells]
-[whip cracks]
-[Kurumi shrieks]
-[Ryo grunts]
-[grunts]
-[crowd shrieks]
Kurumi, this way! Come on!
-Wait! Don't go that way!
-[whip cracks]
[thrilling music playing]
[crowd cheering]
Saeba-san!
Go! Go on! Go!
[exhales] Kurumi, let's go!
[sucks teeth]
[grunting]
[crowd gasps]
[man] Yes, miss! You get him!
-This way! Hurry!
-[Seta] Oh, Milk!
What's wrong? He's with the police.
-[Kaori] Ah, good!
-What happened?
Oh, she's being targeted.
Can you keep her safe?
Understood. Let's get you out of here.
[Kaori] Thank you! [exhales]
-[dramatic music continues]
-[grunts]
[grunting]
-[groans]
-[crowd continues cheering]
[grunting]
[dart whizzes]
[grunting continues]
-[groans]
-[dart whizzes]
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[both breathing heavily]
Opportunity attack!
Stay back!
-[glass shatters]
-[music halts]
[grunts]
-[gun clicks]
-[slow whooshing]
[groaning]
[Ryo breathing heavily]
[breathes deeply]
Your arm…
[tense music playing]
I said stay back.
[Brown Bear] Uh, Scorpion…
Retreat. Stand down.
[exhales]
[loud clank]
We're still in the middle of our date.
[tense music continues]
[breathing shakily]
[grunts]
Who's this group you're with?
[grunting]
[knee cracks]
[groaning]
[crowd gasps]
Don't keep me waiting for it.
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
Give it up, will you?
For the good of the Union.
[inhales sharply]
[distorted ringing, whooshing]
[exhales shakily]
[breathing heavily]
Saeba!
[dramatic music playing]
[music halts abruptly]
[all] Whoa!
[applauding]
My, oh, my!
Oh, my!
Thank you! Look at that.
[cheering continues faintly]
[grunts softly]
[cheering continues]
[Kaori] You okay?
-[Ryo] How's Kurumi doing?
-She's safe with an officer.
Officer?
[female detective] Are you okay?
Are you awake?
Are you sure he was really an officer?
Yes.
-He was carrying a police badge.
-And his name?
I didn't think to ask him.
It's okay.
Kaori, you didn't do anything wrong.
I'll question her
about anything else I need.
Hey, bring her in.
-Yes, ma'am.
-[male detective] Yes, ma'am.
[female detective] Hey,
you can stand, right?
[male detective] Excuse me.
Make room, please.
[siren wailing]
[sighs] Ito's not answering?
I can't get him on the line.
[sighs] Of all the times,
it had to be now.
[exhales]
You should get ready.
We've got a long list
of questions to ask you.
-[breathing shakily]
-[electronic beeping]
What's wrong with you?
For the good of the Union.
[Saeko] Huh?
[screams]
[slosh]
[unsettling music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[footsteps approaching]
About time you got here.
[suitcase unlocking]
[inhales deeply]
Looks good.
I can go now, right?
And no further contact.
And, men,
don't be too rough with her, okay?
[electronic beeping]
[tense music swelling]
-[dramatic music playing]
-[muffled screaming]
[music halts abruptly]
[Ryo exhales]
[Ryo exhales, inhales deeply]
[items clatter]
[phone ringing]
SAEKO (OWES ME 38 FAVORS)
-[Saeko] Ryo?
-[Ryo] Yeah.
That woman, she died on the way in.
She had some device in her neck.
This group, they're unhinged.
There was one thing she said
right before she died.
Something about a Union.
We never got to question her.
We are at a total impasse.
All right, then.
[phone beeps]
[Kaori] Is your arm okay?
It was my fault, wasn't it?
And losing Kurumi too.
Please say something.
[Ryo] Leave all of this behind.
Go home now.
[exhales]
"Take care of Kaori."
Makimura said that right before he died.
[tender music playing]
I promised that I would look out for you.
Forget about all that.
He wasn't someone I could count on.
My brother was selfish, a terrible liar,
he was always getting wasted.
And even then, he was always promising me,
"I'll protect you, I'll watch your back."
But I thought…
I thought I would be the one
to protect him.
But I couldn't even do that.
I couldn't do anything at all.
It was always about protecting me.
You were there,
holding him at the end of it all.
But me?
I was so scared
that I couldn't go to him.
He reserved a table,
he bought champagne for us to toast.
So what was it for?
I knew that we weren't really related.
But we were always together.
We were family for Gods' sake!
I knew that, of course.
Why couldn't he have just said that?
[whimpers]
[tender music continues]
[sobbing]
I don't need your protection.
I won't forgive them.
I am going to fight.
The people who murdered my brother
and kidnapped Kurumi will pay,
even without you!
Whether I'm alone or not,
I'm gonna take them down.
[door opens]
[door shuts]
[hopeful music playing]
[stimulating music playing]
[Ryo grunts]
I'm accepting your request.
[dramatic music playing]
It's time to get revenge.
Huh? Huh, hey!
Uh, what?
[music ends]
[Kurumi whimpers]
Ah, good.
You're awake?
Good morning, Kurumi.
[Kurumi] Kento…
[woman] Oh, is that the friend
you were looking for?
Kento…
[whimpers]
It's best not to look.
You'll only get hurt.
[man] Miss President.
It really is beautiful.
This is the color of the future.
All we need to do now
is incorporate your DNA.
It will be ready in two days.
[liquid bubbling]
[chuckles softly]
Almost there.
With Lore's tech, and your funding,
and also who we are,
we'll be unstoppable.
[unsettling music playing]
[gasping, straining]
[body thuds]
[straining continues]
[gasping]
[continues gasping]
Your tenacity's second to none.
[glass shatters]
[eerie swell]
[dramatic sting]
For the good of the Union.
[man] Don't shoot!
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
-[line ringing]
-[faint moaning]
[man 1 in Spanish] Hello?
[man 2] It's me.
Get me a chopper.
I'm returning to headquarters
with the girl.
[line ends]
[in English] Time to go.
[tense music continues]
-[gunshots]
-[glass shatters]
[Kurumi groans]
[music halts abruptly]
[upbeat music playing]
[Ryo] It's a tracker.
[electronic chiming]
I put it on Kurumi.
Huh? When did you do that?
When you bashed me with the hammer.
[Ryo] Yup, Kurumi, yup. Do it up.
-[Kaori] Hey, man, no touching her!
-[Ryo grunts]
Well, it's what we call "risk management."
[phone ringing]
Huh?
AKKY
What's new, Old Man?
[Akutsu] Listen,
I found out what the Union is.
Union Teope is an organization
with roots in Central America.
[Ryo] Mmm.
They've got their claws
in the world's economy
and are raking in cash.
Union Teope?
How's Lore fit in?
[Akutsu] The connection is that Lore's
a front for their activities in Japan.
They're apparently mainlining
truckloads of funds into it.
So it's likely that that's--
That that's their base.
We're en route to say hi to them now.
Of course you are, City Hunter. [laughs]
Ah.
When you're back safe and sound,
I'm taking you to… [kisses]
…at a certain club.
Oh, ya' done it now! [chuckles]
[line ends]
[whimsical music playing]
This is for adults only, okay?
I didn't say anything, though.
[music halts abruptly]
[upbeat music playing]
[tires screech]
Whoa, hey! We're going in here?
Wow.
This was under Shinjuku all along?
It's a relic from the war.
[Kaori] Wow.
[music fades]
There's nobody here.
Are you sure this is the right place?
-[Ryo] Here. Hold this.
-What, me? [grunts]
Uh, h… hey, wait! Uh…
[exhales]
[camera shutter clicks]
[cop] Victim is Chief Ito of Tokyo Metro,
Investigative Division One.
[indistinct chatter over radio]
Ando, over here.
[Ando] Ma'am.
Here.
Listen up.
Officer Ito's phone, PC, desk, everything.
Conduct a search now.
[all] Yes, ma'am!
[pensive music playing]
[electrical zap]
[Kaori breathing shakily]
This is horrible.
[electrical zap]
Lore's CEO?
Why her?
She's served her only purpose.
[unsettling music playing]
[electrical zap]
[bubbling]
[Kaori] What is that?
[Ryo] That's a bit over the top
for my taste.
[dramatic music swells]
[loud thud]
[bubbling]
[Kaori grunts]
[Kaori breathing shakily]
[Kaori] Hello?
Anyone there?
Looks pretty vacant.
[breathing shakily]
Uber Eats, guys!
Who ordered the yangnyeom chicken?
[guns cock]
[chuckles nervously]
I'll cancel the order, then.
-[Kaori screaming]
-Go, go, go, go, go!
-What the hell? This is your life?
-All right, then. Plan B it is.
You never had a Plan A!
[shrieks]
[breathing heavily]
[shell casings clattering]
[thrilling music playing]
[Ryo] Next!
-[yells]
-[grunts]
[grunting]
Hi-yah!
-[grunts]
-[Ryo] Next!
[grunts]
Next! [grunts]
[Kaori] Here.
[music halts]
[soldier] Go!
-[tense music continues]
-[soldiers grunt]
[Kaori] Whoa!
[Ryo] They just keep coming.
[soldiers yell]
[grunting]
[Kaori shrieks]
[bullets clanking]
Plan C, then.
Huh?
Whatever.
Plan C, yeah. [exhales]
[soldier] Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Up, up. Let's go, let's go.
Come on, hit it. Hustle! Hustle!
[gunshots continue]
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[tense music continues]
[hissing]
[shrieks]
[soldier grunts]
[both grunting]
[tanks clatter]
[gun cocks]
[music building]
[music fades]
[soldier exhales]
[soldier grunts]
[Kaori breathing heavily]
Not bad.
Yeah, you too.
[bullet ricochets]
Kurumi!
[Kurumi breathing shakily]
[gun cocks]
[Kurumi groaning]
[man] You surpassed
my expectations, Ryo Saeba.
I have good news.
We want you on our side.
A very warm welcome is waiting for you.
You want to live and die
in this sleepy, little town?
You're not like that sorry excuse
for a partner you had.
Are you?
Hit a nerve?
I'm right, though, aren't I?
That loser was weak.
And the weak all end up dead.
Isn't that right, Saeba?
He didn't belong.
I think you've always known that.
That's right.
Come to this side. [laughs]
That's right!
This kind of place
isn't good enough for you.
You sure talk a lot for an insect.
My partner's blood is on your hands.
Shut your mouth
and beg forgiveness from hell.
[gun cocks]
[inhales sharply]
It's all so expected, huh?
[dramatic swell]
[loud clank]
-[Brown Bear breathing heavily]
-[dramatic music playing]
Are you a cosplayer or…
[Brown Bear continues breathing heavily]
[loud clank]
[yells]
Kurumi!
[Brown Bear grunts]
-[Ryo] Go after them!
-[Kaori] Wait!
[Brown Bear grunts]
[both grunting]
[sirens wailing]
[Kurumi grunts]
[Kurumi groaning]
[beeps]
[Kurumi straining]
[Kurumi breathing shakily]
[thrilling music playing]
-[grunts]
-[Brown Bear yells]
[Ryo] Go on ahead. I'll catch up!
Got it!
[grunting]
What is this guy, Hercules?
[Brown Bear grunts]
[Ryo grunts]
I'm ending this now.
[Brown Bear grunts]
[gasps]
[music ends]
[Kaori] Kurumi!
[grunts, groans]
[yells] Open this up!
You've got a whole lot on your plate, huh?
Avenging your late brother,
avenging your late father.
My father?
You don't know, then.
[unsettling music playing]
Really? Is that so? [laughs]
[thrilling music playing]
[Brown Bear continues gasping]
-Let's go, teddy bear.
-[groans]
[yells]
-[Ryo grunts]
-[enchanted swell]
[Brown Bear grunting]
[gunshot echoes]
[thrilling music continues]
[exploding]
[shell casings clatter]
[sirens continue wailing]
[brakes screech]
[indistinct chatter]
-[woman] We got to wait to get in.
-[man] Come on!
[woman] Check the back door.
Find their onsite security.
[helicopter blades whirring
in the distance]
You know, your biological father,
he used to be a member of the Union.
And one day,
he said that he needed to leave us.
He said he'd just had a child.
Ah.
So, of course, I had to rat on the guy.
And they turned him into a test subject.
[exhales]
He was weak.
Hey!
[laughs]
The man who shot and killed your father
was none other than Makimura's father.
After he killed him,
he took you in and raised you.
Hey!
-Small world, no?
-Hey!
[Kaori grunting]
I've murdered two
of your family members now.
-[screaming]
-I wonder who's next?
Wait a second,
you don't have anybody left. [laughs]
-[glass cracks]
-[shell casing clatters]
[Kaori gasps]
You're the next one on my list.
[glass shatters]
[man gasps]
[shell casings clatter]
[gunshots continue]
[glass shatters]
[Kurumi gasps]
[yelling, grunting]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[gun cocks]
[man breathing shakily]
[Kaori] Kurumi!
This way.
Hey!
Drop the ladder!
Hurry up!
Hey!
[man breathing heavily]
[gun cocks]
[man groaning]
Saeba.
[dramatic music building]
[music fades]
Go right ahead.
[breathing shakily]
[groans, exhales]
Right here.
[continues breathing shakily]
What's wrong? No revenge for them?
[Kaori breathes shakily]
For your brother and for your father?
Revenge for the family you lost!
I'll kill you. [inhales sharply]
[Kaori breathing heavily]
-Do it.
-[Kaori grunts]
Do it!
Shoot me!
End it!
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
[sobs]
[gentle music playing]
[sobbing]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[electronic beeping]
[yells]
[slosh]
[body thuds]
[gentle music continues]
[man] A little more. There we go.
[men grunting]
Are you all right?
[Kaori] Yes.
-See to them, please.
-[paramedic] This way, please.
Split up.
Search the first and second floors.
[all] Yes, ma'am.
[sighs]
[pensive music playing]
[Ryo humming]
-[gentle music continues]
-[birds squawking]
I WAS CHOSEN AS THE NEW MASCOT, MEOW
I WANNA WORK IN ALL KINDS OF FIELDS!!
THE COSPLAY WILL KEEP COMING, MEOW
[snoring]
[groans]
-[vacuum cleaner whirring]
-Huh?
Huh?
Is this the earliest you get up?
-What are you doing?
-Just cleaning.
No, no, why are y…
[gasps] No way!
They're gone!
Where did they…
Yep, I threw all of them out.
Why would you?
My most sexy babes! That was research!
I wouldn't be able to live here
if you had all that.
Huh?
You're going to be needing
a new partner now, aren't you?
Don't be stupid.
[Kaori] I'll check on
the message board later.
-No, no, no. Hold on.
-And put some pants on, Ryo.
-Oi! Leave my pants alone, lady.
-[gasps] There's more!
No way, no way, no way. Not those!
You can't throw those away! No!
-[Kaori] Shut up! Calm down!
-Those are vintage!
-[Kaori] What's that even mean?
-They don't sell those anymore!
-[Kaori] Let go! Let go! Hey! Hey!
-Hey! Hey, seriously! I'm serious!
-You cannot--
-[Kaori] Hey, stop!
-Oh, shut up already, you pervert.
-[Ryo] Listen to me.
Why do you have that?
-Can it, big, old sleazeball!
-Ow!
Hey!
-Let's go! Say you're my partner!
-You are a nut!
It's divine punishment
for all your perviness!
-Okay, I get it! Stop! Stop!
-Take this!
[Ryo] Hey! I said stop!
-[Kaori] You can't escape!
-[Ryo] Hey! Kaori!
[Japanese song playing]
MESSAGE BOARD
[music fades]