TAE-O HAS SENT A STAMP
GOOD MORNING
Good morning, Yuri.
Have you woken up yet?
Good morning.
It was so cold last night.
Were you able to sleep well?
I hope you didn't catch a cold.
Did you have breakfast?
I'm making some right now.
TAE-O HAS SENT A PHOTO
What is it this time?
That looks so tasty.
I always have this
after a night of drinking.
I wish I could share some with you.
It's very cold outside today.
Keep warm and try not to catch a cold.
HAVE A GOOD DAY
This is…
kind of a lot.
Let's do our best.
Please wait for me!
Good morning.
Please treat me
like your boss at the office.
I'll only talk about work in the office.
Instead of saying Yuri,
I'll call you Boss.
U-Um, about those texts this morning…
We'll be in trouble if you say any more.
We're at the office.
"We're at the office…"?
What?
In the office,
our relationship is a secret.
Bye.
Wait!
Wait there.
Good morning.
It's not like that!
You've got it all wrong.
What was that?
Nothing.
Yes?
Take a look.
They are behind schedule by a week.
-Try giving them a call.
-Okay.
Tae-o, the Valentine's task
I gave you earlier--
Here it is.
-Thanks, you're so efficient--
-I'm working right now.
Do you need anything else, Boss?
That's okay. Thanks.
Understood!
The new coffee beans
from Colombia just came in!
-Is it really from Colombia?
-I'm positive.
We got three types.
It smells nice.
I wonder what it tastes like?
Let's all try some.
Then I'll--
Sorry.
I'm working right now.
Did his personality change?
It's weird how he acts
differently with the boss.
Could this be…
-Workplace harassment?!
-No!
-No?
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
-Boss?
-What were you saying "no" to?
-What?
-No.
-We're not done yet.
-Oh, right.
Right, right.
Boss?
Yes?
Oh, Tae-o, um…
Can we talk?
I-I'm working right now.
What is this?
Coffee is ready.
-Oh nice.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
-Aihara, can you help?
-Yes.
Tae-o.
This smells amazing.
What? Where are they going?
Be careful.
Yes, I know.
At the office, I'm just an intern.
What?
What do you mean?
Huh?
Well um…
It's almost Valentine's Day.
Our workers tend to
work themselves too hard.
You should take care too.
So that's what you meant.
Thank you, I'll do my best.
Is there anything else?
Anything else?
Like what?
Things on your mind or any issues.
Issues?
Hanaoka told you too, right?
If things go smoothly, you sign with us.
Hanaoka doesn't go easy on people.
He'll cut out anyone who mixes
work and private affairs.
No, nothing at all.
There aren't any issues.
Really?
Everything's totally fine.
-Well then, keep it up.
-Okay.
That was close.
Really close.
-Aihara, thanks.
-Yup.
What happened?
Hanaoka?
What?
Why is she staring?
He'll find out about us.
I don't get it.
Hello, Dolce &amp; Chocolat..
Yes.
Okay.
Um…
Hello, this is Aihara
from Dolce &amp; Chocolat..
It's good to hear from you.
-Yes.
-I can't. Senpai.
Yes.
I really can't go over there.
Right…
Please.
Yes, excuse me.
Hurry up.
My apologies.
We got a call.
What?
They want us to participate in an event.
A call about an event.
-A call about an event.
-An event? From where?
The Chocolat Festival.
Chocolat?
The Chocolat Festival?!
Yes.
Hello, this is Motomiya.
The Chocolat Festival
is finally calling for us.
What kind of festival is it?
A Valentine's Day fair that only invites
the crème de la crème of Japan's shops.
Crème de la crème?
He means the shops
are specially selected.
But it's being held
the week after next, right?
Yes, it seems the shop they originally
chose suddenly dropped out.
How lucky! I'm excited for us.
But we're only allowed to have
a booth on one condition.
A condition?
Before the day of the event,
we need to make a new limited-edition
product for just the event.
A new product?
We only have eight days.
Eight days? That's pretty tough.
But this is our chance
to reach out to new customers.
So, I want to accept their offer.
Any thoughts?
Will we make it in time?
I don't want to settle for
something second-rate.
Is it okay if I think up
some ideas for the new product too?
We need to do market research too.
I'll do everything I can
to think of a new product.
Okay then.
I'll re-examine our past recipes too.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Okay, let's be efficient
and split the work.
Don't try to do it all alone.
-Okay.
All right, let's get to it.
How about this?
Our theme will be the Earth and diversity.
For example,
we'll make animal-shaped chocolate
and use salt-flavored chocolate
to represent marine life.
Well, it's a good idea,
but unfortunately it's missing the most
important thing for Valentine's Day.
The most important thing
for Valentine's Day?
Well, if I had to say it
in one word… Romance?
Romance?
That's true.
This chocolate should give you
a bit of courage.
It must empower you
to tell your crush how you feel.
That kind of romantic energy is important.
Nishina, do you have time?
-Yes, I'll go now.
-Okay.
Excuse me.
"Your crush"…
You have someone you like too, right?
What?
Soondubu. Sea otters. Saranghaeyo.
There's a lot of evidence here.
No, it's not like that.
It's this part here.
Can you check the writing?
Sure.
I can't tell what he's thinking at all.
Romance. Confusion. Anxiety.
Overflowing passion.
Intense jealousy.
Yuri, love is just like chocolate.
Okay.
You don't get butterflies
from predictable flavors.
That unpredictability
is why you get curious,
frustrated, and want to know more.
And when you can't hold back
your curiosity anymore…
You just gotta try it.
How is it? Sweet? Bitter?
Did something happen, Tae-o?
You seem down.
I'm really tired.
Is it that hard being an intern?
The work is fun.
The people at the office are nice too.
But…
But?
Is it what I think it is?
Yes.
It's love. I've fallen in love.
-That's what this is?
-Love?
Is that true, Tae-o?
Seriously? What kind of person is she?
She looks really happy when she eats.
She's scary when she's hungry,
but she's warm-hearted and kind.
Bravo.
That's magnificent, Tae-o.
Congratulations.
Sorry, I got so excited
that the humidity went up.
But it's not going well.
I'd actually like to get closer to her.
I want to have meals with her.
But, even after sending all those texts,
she doesn't reply to me.
How much is a lot?
About once every 15 minutes?
That's a bit…
Annoying.
Annoying? Is that a compliment?
No, I wouldn't say that.
Octopi reproduce only once in their life.
So, to grab hold of
their first and last love,
they must win a fierce fight and do
everything they can to show their charms.
Embarrassingly enough, I'm not well-versed
on human courtship behavior,
but your straightforward personality
is the most charming thing about you.
I know this well.
So, just like this octopus,
why don't you do as you always do,
and dive head first into that love?
Octopi?
Oh, what does she do?
She's a co-worker.
What?
Thank you. I'll do my best.
You're leaving?
Good work today!
Hey, Dad.
Has Mom ever given you
Valentine's Day chocolate?
Is this about the guy
you mentioned the other day?
No, that's different.
This is about work.
Aw, come on.
Isn't it obvious?
Hmm, let me think…
A spoon.
Spoon?
A spoon-shaped chocolate.
In return, she wanted my omurice.
She said that is the message
she wanted to convey.
For real? That sounds so cute.
But that's nice.
A message, huh?
Okay, I'm heading back now.
Yuri, don't push yourself too hard.
Yes, I know.
It's not all bitter.
It depends on you.
Rather than bitter, make it sweet.
Right?
Exactly.
I'll take you back. Here we go.
What does she do?
She's a co-worker.
A co-worker?
2011 HOKKAIDO SURVEY
TWO TOURISTS INJURED
YURI MOTOMIYA, LIGHT INJURIES
MAKOTO MOTOMIYA, SEVERE INJURIES
Yuri!
I bought some magazines.
Are you becoming
a hot spring sommelier next?
That's fine and all, but don't ask me
to bring back hot spring water.
What was that?
FULL BODY PARALYSIS
COMMUNICATION METHODS
CHOCOLAT FESTIVAL
LIMITED EDITION CHOCOLATE
Romance. Message.
I can't do this. I'm so hungry.
ONDOL EATERY
SOONDUBU
Here's your soondubu.
I made some earlier.
It'll energize you.
Here.
I could go for some soondubu.
Yes?
Hello?
What? Why're you here at this hour?
I thought…
you might still be working.
So I brought this.
-Here.
-What?
It's soondubu.
Soondubu.
God!
-No.
-Why?
We're mixing work and private life.
I knew it.
That's why you've been
acting strange all day.
Strange?
What part of me was strange?
All of it.
Well, I wouldn't say strange,
but I want you to act more normal.
Normal?
By that, I mean…
Just like you do with everyone else.
I can't do that.
Why?
I can't treat you like I treat them.
Boss…
Yuri, you're special to me.
Well then, I'll be off now.
You're leaving already?
I got these on the way here.
I picked these up.
Picked them up?
Goodbye, Boss.
He picked these up?
YURI MOTOMIYA
I ALWAYS HAVE THIS
AFTER A NIGHT OF DRINKING
HAVE A GOOD DAY
Maybe I'm annoying after all.
That was delicious.
THANK YOU.
YURI MOTOMIYA HAS SENT A MESSAGE
She texted me!
Thank you. The soondubu was very good.
I feel energized.
Thank you for the flowers too.
Those flowers are called Linaria.
Do you know what Linaria means
in the language of flowers?
"Language of flowers"?
Try looking it up.
Linaria.
Language of flowers…
LINARIA IN LANGUAGE OF FLOWERS
1. NOTICE MY LOVE FOR YOU
2. ILLUSION
That's how I feel.
She read it.
Will she reply?
Will she send a reply?
"This is how I feel."?
1. NOTICE MY LOVE FOR YOU
2. ILLUSION
Which is it?
I don't know.
Language of flowers, huh?
Edible flowers?
If we sell chocolate
with edible flower toppings,
customers can choose based on
the message they want to convey.
It's perfect for Valentine's Day.
A message…
The language of flowers?
Yes.
For example, this red rose
means love and affection.
This one is respect.
Friendship.
Good luck.
Familial love.
This might let us express
feelings that are usually hard to share.
Thoughts?
Mahiro?
Sounds good. I'll make samples right away.
-Our suppliers and the packaging--
-I'll figure that out.
Let's get started.
-Okay.
Kame.
Tae-o, can you erase the board?
Okay.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
Thank you.
Welcome.
As a gift…
-Please take a look while you wait.
-This would suit you…
May we interest you in chocolate
modeled after the language of flowers?
HIBISCUS, NEW LOVE
Would you like some chocolate
with edible flowers on top?
We have samples!
We made it in time.
Give it a try.
Thanks to everyone's hard work.
-Welcome.
-Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
Language of flowers?
I'd love to give this to my crush.
I'll work up the courage
to confess my feelings.
A red rose, please.
-Thank you.
-Nishina, order up.
-Thanks.
We're getting good reviews
on social media too.
Thank goodness.
I'm surprised such a romantic idea
came from Yuri.
-True.
-No, um…
Keep up the good work.
-Thank you.
Please take one, if you'd like.
Maybe I'll buy one too.
But didn't you two break up?
Yes, so it's for whoever I meet next.
But Valentine's Day
is only ten days away--
That's more than enough time.
Then I'll buy this one.
What?
You have someone to give that too?
Yes, I do.
-You do?
-No way. Who?
That's…
a secret.
What? Hold on there. Why?
Tae-o.
Oh, Senpai, you're here!
Who is she?
She's a co-worker, right?
Oh, yeah. I'll introduce you.
Um…
This is our CEO and Mahiro.
Mahiro?
He's my senior at university.
Dr. Onoda.
Doctor?
Hello, nice to meet you.
Thank you for watching over Tae-o.
Nice to meet you.
Would you like a sample?
Please.
Oh, thank you.
HIBISCUS, NEW LOVE
Hibiscus?
Are these edible flowers?
Yes.
They mean "new love"
in the language of flowers.
New love?
I see.
Was it not to your liking?
Oh, it's not that.
I've never had chocolate this good before.
Thank you.
Well then, please take good care of Tae-o.
A doctor, huh?
I wouldn't mind that.
She seems nice.
Give it your best.
Okay.
Thank you so much
for taking on our request
on such short notice.
It's our pleasure.
We've always had our sights set
on the Chocolat Festival.
We're truly honored. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Please enjoy.
This language of flowers
chocolates is lovely.
The customers loved them too.
I'm so glad we invited you.
-Thank you.
-We'll be in your care.
We pulled it off.
What a relief.
I'm really glad.
We finally made it here.
Thank you, really.
I'll finish up here.
Head back to the office first.
Isn't there other work piling up?
Thanks, I'll leave it to you.
-Thank you.
-Please give it a try.
The coffee has an acidic taste,
so it pairs well with this chocolate.
I'm so hungry.
God?
Hanaoka.
-Good work today.
Which do you want?
-Are you sure?
-You still haven't eaten, right?
Thank you.
Then let's do this fair and square.
Rock, paper, scissors…
shoot!
Hooray! Then I'll take this one.
-Okay.
-Yup.
I'm so hungry.
Thanks for the food.
Our profits today
are the best we've ever had.
We gotta keep up the pace
until Valentine's Day.
But be careful.
You've always pushed yourself like that.
If you get sick,
it'll only cause me trouble.
Yes, I'll be careful.
Thank you, as always.
That's cute.
Yeah, it was a gift.
Is that where you got
the language of flowers idea from?
Oh, right.
It's thanks to these flowers.
Coming.
Good evening.
Why are you here, Boss?
This is from the other day.
I still haven't thanked you properly.
Thank you.
For the soondubu and the flowers.
The Chocolat Festival went well
thanks to you, Tae-o.
Thank you so much.
Bye, then.
Hold on!
I'll walk you home.
It's dangerous.
Okay, if you insist.
One second.
How is your health?
Hanaoka said everyone falls ill
when Valentine's Day comes.
I'm fine.
That's great.
I'm glad.
You're finally back to your usual self.
It's because this isn't the office.
Or is this considered the office?
Is this okay?
It's fine.
More importantly, I want you
to treat me normally at the office too.
I want you to call me Boss.
But other than that, I prefer
that you be your usual self.
Really? Is that really okay?
Yeah.
What a relief.
Honestly, I tried really hard.
It was really tiring.
Why'd you push yourself so hard?
I wanted to keep our secret.
Because I don't want to trouble you, Yuri.
Am I annoying?
No, not annoying.
Well, there were a lot of texts though.
How many times can I text you?
It's not about how many times.
Wait right here.
Here. This is for the soondubu.
Oh.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
This is delicious.
Ice cream tastes great
in the winter, doesn't it?
Yes, I know what you mean.
Can I…
ask for one favor?
I did my best.
I did my very best, so…
Yuri.
Please go on a date with me.
I understand that things are busy
right now, so once Valentine's Day ends,
I want to have a meal with you.
A meal?
Well, that much I can do.
Really?
Okay then.
Promise me.
Can I let go now?
No.
Please stamp your seal here.
My seal?
Follow my lead.
Now we've made a copy.
A copy?
This is how we do things in Korea.
This is what we do
when we make an important promise.
An important promise?
Now, let's do it again.
I wrote a sign on there too.
A sign?
What kind?
A secret sign.
Done.
Yaksok.
Yaksok?
A promise?
Make sure you remember, okay?
Thank you very much.
Things turned out great
because of your flowers.
Glad to hear it
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
RED ROSES
MEANING AND CHARACTERISTICS
I LOVE YOU
LOVE AND AFFECTION
Good morning.
LINARIA IN LANGUAGE OF FLOWERS
NOTICE MY LOVE FOR YOU
-Morning.
-Good morning.
-Can you look at this?
Sure thing.
Subtitle translation by: Chul Woong Kim
What should we do for that promise?
-Are you having a meal together?
-I cast a spell.
Have you found someone you like?
Don't abuse your power too much.
Notice my love for you?
Sorry!