Am I not human?
I brought you back to life.
I shouldn't be with you.
There is no place for you here.
Don't you dare try to show off.
Take her from me using your own words.
Please show me who you really are.
Being with someone else…
is already something like
a punishment for being human.
He turned over a new leaf
and came back to work with us again.
Let's welcome Ken Fukashi.
Say, "Welcome home."
We've worked all day. That's enough.
Idiot.
At the end of the day, workers have beer.
Okay. Welcome home.
-Welcome home.
-Let's eat.
Hey!
-Should I drink it?
-Not yet.
Listen. Even if you've had a bitter past,
you can be free of it depending on
how you live your life today.
Even if you were a gloomy man in the past,
don't feel that you still are.
Your beer will go flat if you wait
until he finishes talking.
You have more than
what you had in the past.
I'll kill you if you run away again.
Just drink up.
I want to say "welcome home"
to the you of tomorrow.
That doesn't mean anything.
Say, "I'm home," as the you of tomorrow.
"I'm home," as the me of tomorrow.
He is so obedient.
Tell him that he's annoying.
-I'm used to it.
-Already?
Cheers.
Boss. Look at her.
When your son is here, Murozono
eats with her mouth closed.
Mikoto, you behave like a girl.
Don't you talk to me like that
or I'll kill you.
You mean near my university?
Yes. It was my grandmother.
I mean your great-great-grandmother.
Okay.
She used to live near there.
Her family were landowners
around that area.
You told me that a younger sister
of Great-great-grandmother
had the same symptoms
as my sister and passed away.
Right. My grandmother's name was Kiku.
Her younger sister's name was Saki.
-Saki?
-Yes.
Saki was lying on the mountain
near the university when she was found.
When did she die?
About 120 years ago.
Hundred and twenty years ago?
I didn't know that my university
was there 120 years ago.
No.
The university had not been built
at that time yet.
I heard that there was
some kind of laboratory there.
Try this, Ken. It's tasty.
What is this?
Don't you know natto?
You must be from the west of Japan.
Try it.
It's delicious.
Do you like natto? That helps.
Don't you have to take care
of your husband, Tamara?
No. My husband doesn't eat.
Huh?
Tamara married the president
of an architectural office
who is closely related to us.
He is 70 years old.
He fell in love
and got remarried to Tamara.
He is a man of great ability.
Poor guy. He doesn't know that
you married him for his money.
He doesn't eat at all?
He doesn't eat at night.
He's lost ten kilograms
since he married me.
You want him to starve to death.
He wakes up at 4 a.m.
and he jogs 20 kilometers every day.
You want him to have a heart attack.
He eats a 600-gram steak for breakfast.
And we make love before he goes to work.
You will kill him.
Why don't you ask Seiya to kill you then?
I'll kill you.
Do you mean to put someone to death
when you say, "I'll kill you"?
-Huh?
-That is a bad thing to do.
Why do you want to kill someone so easily?
Are you joking?
She is not serious.
She doesn't really mean "kill".
Don't you know the song
by Miyuki Nakajima?
I don't like singing a goodbye song
But I just don't know any other songs
I don't get it.
Don't make him confused.
Who is this?
Hello.
Mikoto.
Welcome back.
I will kill you!
MONDAY - FRIDAY
13:00-16:00
Here you go.
Ken, will you open the door for me?
Okay.
Thanks.
Tamara hung out your futon
in the sun. It should feel nice.
Ken.
Did you come back because
you wanted to see Tsugumi?
Yes.
You're so honest, Ken.
You fell in love with her.
I know the word,
but I don't know what it means.
It means you love someone.
It's when you want to be with someone,
no matter what happens.
Do you need anything else?
How can I talk to the radio?
Talk to the radio?
Amakusa.
Do you want to call in to a radio show?
Yes.
I see.
Most listeners send messages
by email rather than postcards today.
Can you write?
Yes.
Write a letter and I will
send it to the radio.
Wait a moment.
AMAKUSA
Ken.
You can listen to the radio using this.
It'll be good to learn how to use it.
PARADISE HEAVEN
PARADISE
ASK AMAKUSA
You finished already?
You have excellent handwriting.
Are you sure you want to send
this question to Amakusa?
-Yes.
-Then, let's do it.
What about your name?
My name is Ken Fukashi.
No.
People usually don't use their real names
when they send messages to radio stations.
So…
How about "Frankenstein"?
-Frankenstein?
-Yes.
I think it's a good nickname
for this question.
Let's use Frankenstein as your nickname.
RADIO NAME: FRANKENSTEIN
Frankenstein.
Hundred and twenty years old.
AGE: 120
"Do you think a monster
who is capable of killing humans
shouldn't fall in love with a human?"
Send it?
And send.
Okay. I sent it.
Good.
What's this?
MAIN TITLE
Which one?
Did you press it?
Don't press keys when
you don't know how it works.
Okay.
Let me stop this.
-You good?
-It's okay.
-No. It's too high.
-Lower it.
-Make it lower.
-Lower.
-It's fine.
-It's okay.
No. Make it lower.
You have to put it lower.
Wow!
What's the next thing?
Nameko mushrooms today.
-Haruka.
-Hi, Tsugumi.
-What are you doing?
-I'm working.
Since I am in the hospital,
I shouldn't sleep all the time.
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
The doctor was surprised
that I recovered so soon.
I was just tired.
I shouldn't make you worry.
Sorry.
Do you really not remember anything?
-Do you mean how I fainted?
-Yes.
Well…
I think I saw something strange.
-Something strange?
-Yeah.
It was like a ghost.
I think I had a hallucination
because my senses were muddled.
Let's have some tea.
FUGAKU UNIVERSITY
ENTRANCE
University records?
I want to know about the history
from 120 years ago.
Hundred and twenty years ago?
That's 1897.
What was around here at that time?
There was an institute
of infectious diseases.
An institute of infectious diseases?
There was an isolation ward
because it was in the middle of nowhere.
Do you know if there are
any documents about that?
It will take some time,
but I can look for you.
-Please do.
-Thank you very much.
-Good morning.
-Morning!
Tsugumi.
Here is a new bacterium.
A new bacterium?
It's sticky because of natto.
Natto?
It's considered to be changes
in his cells that created bacteria
because he took natto bacteria.
It's natto mushroom. See?
He ate natto.
The next morning, he released
fungal spores that create mucin,
a viscous substance that made
the natto sticky in his bed.
Did you ask him to eat natto
to check that?
I wasn't experimenting on him.
He can't live without taking in
other bacteria
if he lives with humans.
You're right.
There are countless numbers
of bacteria in the air.
It's the same whether he lives
in the forest or in the city.
His body is constantly affected
by invisible bacteria.
The same applies for humans, though.
But humans don't release
fungal spores like mushrooms do.
He releases a bacterium
that can kill humans.
The question is when he releases it.
-Now.
-Professor!
How can he release them
while he is sleeping?
People become defenseless
when they are sleeping.
Maybe he releases them without knowing it.
Professor Tsurumaru.
Do you think that this phenomenon
relates to his mental status?
I don't know yet.
Is he a monster?
There is no phenomenon called a monster.
This was the first house I built
when I became boss's pupil.
That was 25 years ago.
You must have been
a small child, like this.
No.
You were nothing
but an ex-high school
baseball player at that time.
I can feel the self-growth
while I renovate this same house.
I'm happy.
What does "renovate" mean?
Huh?
He's a good worker,
but he's not very smart.
Idiot!
He is asking the deep meaning of it.
It's a good question, Ken.
To renovate is to follow up on the life
of the person who lives in the home.
Follow up on the life…
Their child was only a baby
when we built this house.
But that child grew up, married,
and had grandchildren.
That's why they asked me
to change the layout.
Do they want to rebuild the house?
Yes.
We rebuild their houses
following up on their lives.
That's our job
as a local building contractor.
That's great, Boss.
Only you can call me "boss" now.
-I will call you boss from today.
-I will too.
Idiots.
Don't copy another person's traditions.
Make your own traditions.
-Yes, President.
-President.
You can call me "master", if you like.
Stop using your mouths, use your hands.
Yes.
Ken.
You can call me master if you like.
Mr.… Master?
Just call me master. Work hard.
Yes.
Ken. Hand me that bag.
What's up, Mikoto? You look blue.
I'm just working without chatting.
I see.
Hello.
-Hi. How are you?
-Good afternoon.
I brought Japanese cakes for you.
Hey, pretty girl. Ken is working hard.
Don't call her that. Her name is Tsugumi.
-Where should I put these?
-Over there.
Hi.
How are you?
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm fine.
How are you,
Tsugumi?
I'm okay.
Work hard.
Yes.
I'll work hard.
FRANKENSTEIN
120 YEARS OLD
Thank you for waiting.
I want to read this today.
Do you want to change it now?
This email caught my eye.
I feel like I shouldn't ignore it.
Let's ignore it.
It's probably a waste of time.
But this Frankenstein seems
to be really pushed into a corner.
I think this is a serious question.
If you ignore it, do you think
he would really kill someone?
No way.
But it would be interesting.
Huh?
Where do you want to go,
and who do you want to interview?
There's a place I have in mind.
-Let's take a break.
-Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Let's eat some cake.
-Thanks.
-Thanks
-Here you go.
-I'm going to tuck in.
-Thanks.
-Ken, you can take a break.
Thanks.
Let's sit down and eat.
-I told you before.
-No…
But I heard that Amakusa
is very popular these days.
Is that the time?
I'm getting bored, though.
Don't say such a thing.
He works on our show.
In the end, I forget what
the listeners have even asked.
-He said he will make it better.
-Really?
He will take a different approach.
He told me so.
That's interesting.
Yes. It's about 3 p.m. now.
Let's call SNACK MAN.
Where is he today?
It's time for you and I
Evolutionary theory for you and I
If you are worried about something
Ask Amakusa
Hello. I am Junpei Amakusa.
Here is an email I received today.
It's from Frankenstein,
who is 120 years old.
"Do you think a monster
who is capable of killing humans
shouldn't fall in love with a human?"
That's a deep question.
I don't know the answer to it.
So, I want to ask someone
who I really respect.
-Hello.
-What are you doing?
This is Minoru Tokachi, a man I respect.
Huh?
Oh my God. You didn't tell me this.
What are you doing?
Tokachi. Will you please
answer his question?
Question?
You weren't listening.
I was. Idiot. What was it?
It's from Frankenstein,
who is 120 years old.
"Do you think a monster
who's capable of killing humans
shouldn't fall in love with a human?"
That is the question.
Please tell us what you think.
-No, of course.
-Really?
This man is making fun of us.
What if this is a serious question?
A person who is serious
would not kill someone.
What if he is really being
pushed into a corner?
What would you say
if you answered him seriously?
Do you think a person who thinks
of himself as a monster
shouldn't fall in love with a human?
First of all, a person who thinks
he might kill people shouldn't live.
It's ridiculous.
Don't get so upset.
This person doesn't say
that he wants to kill anyone.
He is scared that he might kill someone.
Is he a stalker or something?
I can't justify the love of a man
who is a stalker.
He sounds spoiled.
I want to tell him something.
If you think you will kill someone,
don't leave your house.
Don't meet anyone.
Kill yourself
before you kill someone else!
Tokachi, you are too eccentric.
I don't care. This is my radio show.
A person like him can't read
your mind. So, I'm talking straight.
Here is my serious answer.
Kill yourself. That's it.
Amakusa. Say something.
I…
I think he should love humans
even if he thinks he is a monster.
He should live with humans.
Think hard about how he can live
without killing people.
Will you take responsibility
for what you've just said?
He will learn that
he shouldn't kill people
by loving someone.
He will know it
only when he wants someone to live
from the bottom of his heart.
So, a monster should meet
as many people as possible
and find someone that he truly loves.
That's the only way
to prevent him from killing people.
I'm sure he will find
his true love someday.
Even if you are a monster now,
don't be afraid.
I want you to live
and fall in love with someone.
What's wrong?
You really like
listening to the radio.
You…
listened to the radio
in the forest, didn't you?
Yes.
For 120 years.
I didn't have a radio
for such a long time.
What should I think of you?
Are you a monster?
Are you Frankenstein?
That was a nickname for the radio.
My name is Ken Fukashi.
The radio said that I could live
and fall in love with humans.
What would you say, Tsugumi?
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
Will you come back to work?
They're worried about you.
Yes.
I'm heading back to the university.
Work hard.
Great job.
Thank you very much.
Did you do this to get payback?
No. It's not payback.
I really wanted to know
how you would answer.
It was fun. So, that's good.
Are you satisfied?
You set up a surprise attack
on the host of a radio show.
Was it fun?
I…
I thought that you came up
with a good answer.
You are fired!
Get out of here.
All right.
Thank you for everything. Excuse me.
I am very sorry.
Well, it was not an accident.
It was an accident for Tokachi.
I found an old book on the university
that explains a little
about the research institute.
First, it was a hospital
for tuberculosis patients.
Then they built an institute
of infectious diseases there.
Then it soon became a national university.
The research institute was there
for only a short while.
Thank you very much.
You can't learn it in just a day or two.
Practice every day.
You can't shave it straight so easily.
Well, you are a fast learner.
Excuse me.
Dr. Kentaro Fukashi. Nice to meet you.
German?
Excuse me.
The radio said that I could live
and fall in love with humans.
What would you say, Tsugumi?
BUS STOP MIKUTAKE
TOKAI BUS
President.
Please come.
What's wrong?
This is horrible.
KILL
Who did such a thing?
Cover it up now.
Yes, sir.
Mikoto?
Welcome back, Mikoto.
Did you do that?
Don't talk to me like that.
Go away.
Let's go home together.
I came to pick you up.
I want to live together
just like we did before.
I want nothing to do with you now.
Go away!
It's too late.
Many people need you.
You never know what they will do
if you don't come with me.
You will cause trouble to them as well.
Even if I ran away and hid in jail.
You…
What's wrong, Mikoto? Are you all right?
This is none of your business.
Please go away.
What's wrong, Mikoto?
Did you ask for help
from a person like him again?
I'll kill you.
Wait! Let go.
Wait!
-Let go. I'll kill him!
-It's dangerous. It's too dangerous.
-Be careful you're not killed.
-It's too dangerous.
See you again, Mikoto.
Pack and be ready to leave.
I'll kill you!
Mikoto!
Let it go.
What is it?
What happened to Mikoto?
She tried to kill someone.
-Huh?
-Be quiet, Ken.
Mikoto. Explain it to me.
If you think you will kill people,
you should fall in love
to keep from killing.
Shut up!
Don't yell. Ken can't read the situation.
Mikoto. Explain why you want to leave.
It's not only your problem.
He hit on me in the city
and he was my first date.
We broke up because
he started to become violent.
But he began stalking me.
I told him to leave me alone
so many times.
Then he sold me to some
shady people for money.
So, I ran away from him.
While I was running away from him,
you asked me to come to your house.
I just wanted money.
But you told me to work for him
without asking for anything.
That's how I came here.
Then you have no choice.
Just stay here.
But if I stay here,
you never know what he might do.
Then, why don't you come to my place?
Huh?
My husband has many summer houses.
It's easy to provide a place
for you to hide.
That's a good idea.
I will tell him that you left here.
Hide until things settle down.
You guys are crazy.
Didn't you know that?
Boss will go crazy
if my pupils learn to grow up.
Oh, well.
-You're acting like a girl finally.
-Shut up.
In short, have you fallen in love
with the boss, Mikoto?
I'll kill you.
REFERENCE ROOM
Eternal…
EXISTENCE, LIFE, LIVELIHOOD
LIFE ETERNAL
Eternal life…
INANIWA CORPORATION
I will drive Mikoto to Tamara's house.
You take care of my home while I'm gone.
Take care of his home?
Professor, please take a look at this.
This is Dr Kentaro Fukashi's
research paper.
Here is the translation.
Who is he?
He was a doctor of medicine.
Ken said that he was his father.
Where did you find this?
I found it in the forest where Ken lived.
I brought the documents here
that were left in the room.
It's written in German.
This explains about the bacteria
that regenerate dead cells.
He successfully cultured
the bacteria that creates eternal life.
ETERNAL LIFE
In order to study the bacteria,
I built a secret house deep in the forest.
And I successfully cultured the bacteria
that may create eternal life.
Kentaro Fukashi collected all kinds
of bacteria from around the world
and brought them all back to Japan.
By culturing those bacteria
and making several cell fusions,
he happened to find
this particular bacterium.
Did he create a new bacterium?
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
Are you alone, Ken?
I am taking care of the house.
Good evening.
Who is he?
Where is Mikoto?
Do you think you can play
with my girlfriend?
Ouch.
Run, Ken!
Run away!
Darn you.
Don't look at me like that.
I decided to transplant
the bacteria I found into his dead body.
This bacteria will increase power
by conducting electricity.
But the electricity
that humans can generate
was not enough to bring
his consciousness back to life.
I had no choice but to ask God.
With the power of God,
his body cells will regenerate completely.
Wait.
Here you go.
Eat this.
How is this?
-It's electricity.
-Electricity?
The bacteria will regenerate
with lightning.
I got it.
Mental status is electricity too.
Mental status?
Human feelings are transmitted
through the body via electrical signals.
His body may release bacteria…
using the power of electricity.
When his emotions are running high,
he may release bacteria.
Ken.
What are you worrying about?
I…
I may kill a human again.
I tried to kill him just now.
I think…
I wanted to kill him.
I shouldn't live with humans.
You were just trying
to protect me and Mikoto.
We'd feel the same way as you
in a situation like this.
What you felt was natural as a human.
I…
I felt as you did at that time.
-You felt as I did?
-Yes.
If you want to live
with someone and love someone…
you will hate other people
at the same time.
You became closer to being human.
Became closer to being human.
-Yes?
-It's Tsugumi.
Is it okay if I talk now?
Yes.
Can I talk with Fukashi
…alone?
Okay.
I'm sorry to disturb you so late at night.
You asked me if you can live
and love humans.
Yes.
I want to answer your question.
This…
TSUGUMI TSUGARU
You made this for me.
Yes.
I'm sorry that I took it
from here without asking you.
I made it for you, Tsugumi.
I'm glad
that you took it.
I've seen this mushroom before.
It was when you saved me in the forest.
I always found these mushrooms…
when you were with me.
An akanarikamitake mushroom?
But why?
What is this mushroom?
They fall off of my body.
I've never thought that
this mushroom was weird, dirty, or scary.
I've never thought of it in that way.
I think this mushroom is very pretty.
To be honest with you,
I like this mushroom.
If this mushroom is your heart,
I think
you can fall in love with a human being.
you can live with a human being
because you have a heart.
I think
you have many problems…
but will you
live with me?
Come live in the human world
together with me.
I love you, Tsugumi.
You should draw a line
if you want to be loved.
It's not a matter of love.
I can't help it that I fell in love.
I will raise a revolution.
Watch out, Ken!
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION