Amakusa, he's here.
His name is Seiya Inaniwa,
a graduate student at Fugaku University.
He belongs to the laboratory
of Professor Tsurumaru.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello. I am Junpei Amakusa.
I heard that you are
a friend of Frankenstein.
Yes.
Frankenstein lives in my house.
I heard you ask Frankenstein
to contact you on the radio.
Thank you for coming.
What kind of person is Frankenstein?
He is honest. He can't tell a lie.
Can't tell a lie?
What do you mean?
I mean it laterally. He has a pure heart.
Do you mean he is naive?
That's also true.
-Mr. Inaniwa.
-Yes?
Why did you come to see me?
You visited me without telling
Frankenstein, didn't you?
Yes.
-I wanted to know your intention.
-Intention?
Frankenstein is a big fan of yours.
What you say is very important to him.
If he knows that
you are trying to find him,
I'm sure he'll want to see you.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Why is that?
He will accept your advice
with no protest.
He may do whatever you say.
Before he knows,
I want to ask you something.
If you want to tease him
as a topic of conversation,
please don't ask him
to contact you on the radio.
That's what I wanted to ask you.
It's even more interesting.
I would love to see him.
-Yes?
-I want to see him. Please.
He is a real monster.
Huh?
It's dangerous to see him.
What do you mean?
I can't tell.
You told me that you've seen
this jizou statue before.
Was it a long time ago?
I don't know.
I just thought that I've seen it before.
Now I want to thank jizou
that I can spend time with you.
But your sister worries about you.
Will you see her?
I want her not to worry.
I want her not to worry, too.
So, don't tell her the truth.
What do you mean?
Don't tell her that you've lived 120 years
or how you were born.
Is that bad?
Usually, people would think
that you are lying.
I don't tell lies.
Please tell a lie.
You have to tell a lie
in order to live in a human world.
I should tell a lie so that
people won't think that I am a liar?
That's right.
You shouldn't make normal people confused.
Confused?
You don't want other people
to worry or be annoyed, do you?
No.
Then we should keep it a secret.
It's an important secret.
Secret?
OK.
I understand.
His name is Ken Fukashi.
Nice to meet you. I am Ken Fukashi.
I am Kanae, Tsugumi's grandmother.
Are you all better now?
Yes.
I heard about you from Haruka.
As she said, you have a unique atmosphere.
I told you that he is weird.
You are too direct.
But it's true.
Please tell a lie.
Huh?
Your grandmother will be confused.
Don't worry about that.
-You are very interesting.
-Right.
Can I call you Ken?
Yes. Ken is the kanji "study".
May I ask you how old you are?
About 30 years old.
You shouldn't say "about".
Am I wrong?
He thinks that he is about 30.
Because he lived in the mountain
for many years,
he has only a vague memory.
In the mountain?
He has lived in the mountain
without seeing anyone
since he was a child for personal reasons.
Had he been raised by wolves or something?
The Japanese wolf
had already become extinct.
That's not my point.
But he catches up with most of
the things from books and the radio.
You had a hard time, didn't you?
It's a secret.
You don't have to say that.
No. It's a secret.
I mean you don't have to say,
"It's a secret" every time.
So he can't even understand
a normal conversation.
I'm so sorry.
You are a bit strange, too.
Ken may not know much about the world yet,
but he is very sweet.
I've never seen a person who
is as nice and honest as him before.
I am honest, but I can tell a lie.
-Keep quiet for a while.
-OK.
Does he know about your disease?
Yes.
Will you help Tsugumi?
Why doesn't he say anything?
You don't have to keep quiet now.
OK.
I will protect her.
Thank you.
But Grandma,
Ken has some weird problems
related to mushrooms.
-Mushrooms?
-Harumi. Don't worry.
I can take care of myself.
Don't worry about me.
-OK, Tsugumi.
-Grandma!
We should trust Tsugumi.
Thank you.
Thank you for trusting me.
I'm relieved that they trust us.
We told a lie because
we want them to trust what we trust.
Right.
It's a fraud when it becomes
money-related.
Fraud?
Never mind.
It's not about you. You will learn it.
Tsugumi.
Do you think I can be a human
if I tell a lie?
When you lie,
you are not trying to make people
think that you are a human.
Sometimes you lie of your own volition
not intending to hurt people.
Sometimes you lie
because you care about others.
Care…
What's for dinner?
I made a reservation at a restaurant.
Really? How nice!
Both of us…
Let's go home.
They will be waiting for you.
Yes.
-Did you get quite well?
-Yes.
My sister helped him
with the hospital discharge.
That's good.
This is for him, Boss.
OK. Here you are.
This is your salary for this month.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's money.
Money? Fraud?
No, it's not. It's your salary.
It's the money you earned.
My money.
SALARY - APRIL 2017 - KEN FUKASHI
Thank you very much.
It's not bad to pay cash in hand.
President Inaniwa,
thank you for taking care of Ken.
OK.
Did you make up with him already?
We didn't get in a fight.
But you started
a break-up conversation during work.
It wasn't a break-up conversation.
Are you still
not getting together with him?
Was it nothing but Ken's
one-sided confession?
You turned him down once,
but you changed your mind?
We were talking about
the radio program at that time.
Radio?
It's Ken's favorite radio program.
Ask Amakusa--
I'm not asking him anything!
"After rain comes fair weather."
What are you talking about?
Hi, Seiya.
-You were released from the hospital.
-Yes, I was.
I wanted to ask you something.
Let's go to your room.
Hey, eat dinner with us.
You can talk with him here.
It has something to do with Ken's privacy.
Ken is my employee.
He is a member of the Inaniwa family.
Don't go behind my back.
Dinner is getting cold.
-All right, then.
-Are you OK?
It's not something that I should hide.
Thank you for working hard
for me today. Let's eat.
-Let's eat.
So, what is your question?
Eat first. Don't be persistent.
I'm not persistent.
Amakusa is trying to find Ken.
-What?
-Amakusa?
Who is Amakusa?
Ask Amakusa--
You just told me that.
You are so persistent!
What do you mean?
He said he wanted to see Ken on the radio.
More precisely, he wanted
to see Frankenstein.
Who is Frankenstein?
I told you that it's private.
Keep quiet if you don't understand
what I'm saying.
OK. I will play a quiet game from now.
Is Amakusa trying to find me?
Yes. So, I went to see him today.
Why did you see him?
I can't just take Ken there.
Did you see him?
Wait. Why did you go see him
instead of Ken?
What if Ken wants to see Amakusa?
I want to see him.
-Look!
-See? That's because you told him.
Stop creating unnecessary conflict.
I'm not starting a quarrel.
Yes, you are. Right?
Quiet game.
Ken will decide who to see.
You are so persistent.
You are saying it in the wrong way.
Don't worry.
Tsugumi.
We should care about others.
I can see him if I care about him.
You are right.
Care about others?
What's that?
Why did you do that?
I just asked about his intention.
His intention?
I told Amakusa not to see Ken
if he wanted to tease him.
You didn't tell him strange things,
did you?
Strange things?
He is a real monster.
It's dangerous to see him.
Of course not.
He won't believe me,
even I told him the truth.
I know.
I'm worried about you, Tsugumi.
It's dangerous to go with him.
Don't you remember?
Yes. That's why I'm worried about him.
It's dangerous for you to have
too much concern with him.
Do you have feelings for him?
I just want to help him.
Same here.
But I want to protect you more than that.
That's how I feel,
and I want you to remember that.
LISTEN TO AMAKUSA
Amakusa, let's ask him
to come to the radio.
What?
It will be a big topic on the Internet
if Frankenstein shows up.
The listeners will get excited
if he shows up.
Or people will think that it's a fake.
But it's not fun if he is not
an interesting person.
MONDAY TO FRIDAY
13:00 - 16:00
-Amakusa?
-I'm Iizuka.
Hi, Iizuka.
Can we talk?
Come in.
-Amakusa is coming.
-Amakusa?
-He is coming to see me.
-I will go home soon.
Ken. I want you to do me a favor.
Favor?
Please lend me some money.
Money?
I want you to lend me some money.
Why?
My mother is ill.
Ill?
She hasn't paid for insurance,
so it costs a lot of money.
Will she get well?
Yes. If she has money.
All right.
Here you are.
Will you lend me everything?
Yes. Please help her get better.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. I promise that
I will pay your money back.
Will you please keep it a secret?
Secret?
Do you want me to tell a lie?
To be straight with you, yes.
Boss will worry if he knows. Please.
All right.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
Iizuka.
-What did you need from Ken?
-No…
I just lent him some comic books.
I have to go back to work.
-Amakusa!
-I'm not Amakusa.
Is it you, Mikoto?
I am your senior.
What's up?
I saw Iizuka just now.
What did he want from you?
Did he lend you some comic books?
No. I didn't get anything from him.
I knew it was a lie.
Iizuka told me a lie.
It was not a lie but a secret.
Whichever.
You lent him money, didn't you?
It's a secret.
I knew it.
Please don't tell anyone
because we don't want Boss to worry.
Hi, Seiya.
I came by myself as I promised.
Hi.
Let's go then.
Hi, Tsugumi.
This is Mr. Amakusa.
Nice to meet you. I'm Junpei Amakusa.
Hi, I am Tsugumi Tsugaru.
Are you Frankenstein's girlfriend?
He just likes her. It's a one-way street.
-Oh, really?
-Well…
He's looking forward to seeing you.
Excuse me.
Just a second.
How are you feeling today?
I'm fine.
I wish that his wish will come true.
Why are you interested in him?
I don't know the reason.
When I first saw his email,
he said that he was a monster
and he might kill a human.
I thought that he wasn't serious,
but I couldn't ignore him.
Seiya told me that Frankenstein
can't tell a lie. Is that true?
Mr. Amakusa.
Amakusa!
Oh!
Hi, Frankenstein.
-It's a nickname for the radio.
-Yes.
My name is Ken Fukashi.
-Ken Fukashi.
-Yes!
I am glad to meet you, Amakusa.
Ken, this is not the radio.
Call him Mr. Amakusa.
It's OK.
Nice to meet you. I am Junpei Amakusa.
Thank you for listening to my program.
Thank you for worrying about
many things, Mr. Amakusa.
Do you work here?
Yes.
-How old are you?
-I'm 30.
Come on.
You are 120 years old, aren't you?
No.
I care about others.
It's nothing. He is joking.
I didn't get it.
But I'm glad that you met Tsugumi.
It's all thanks to you.
Would you like to go out for a walk?
Sure. Let's take a walk.
-That's a good idea.
-OK.
MITSUKI
SALARY - APRIL 2017 - KEN FUKASHI
Wait, Mitsuki. Would you like some beer?
How dare you!
Did you live in that mountain?
Yes. I have been living alone
for a long while.
Did you live in the forest
and think that you were a monster?
Well, I was more like a plant
than a monster.
-A plant?
-Yes.
I see.
Did you think that you might kill people
although you thought that
you were like plant?
I didn't know people until I met Tsugumi.
Did you meet Tsugumi in the forest?
Yes.
I go to the forest often
for my research at the university.
Tsugumi taught me to live with humans.
And Seiya, too.
You have a very unusual background.
Whitebait sushi is delicious.
It's nice to live by the sea.
Do you like it?
Yes.
This is shrimp.
Shrimp? Is that fish?
It's a kind of shellfish.
Shellfish.
Is this your first time to see fish?
No.
Pacific saury, tuna,
sun-dried horse mackerel.
He eats them at my house.
Mr. Amakusa is asking
if this is your first time
to see live fish, not cooked fish.
Look.
Is that the same as this one?
Did someone kill the fish?
No. That's not how you say it.
Is that a secret?
Don't you want to be his girlfriend,
Tsugumi?
Huh?
Is that a secret?
Let's not talk about that.
That's a different story.
But it was Tsugumi who took
Ken out from the mountain.
Yes.
If Ken had really grown up in a forest
without knowing the world,
you took on a big burden, didn't you?
Or did you take him
out of the forest from curiosity?
I just wanted to save him.
Save him?
What do you think you should do
to save him?
That's what we are figuring out together.
I think Ken just wants to be with you.
What do you say, Tsugumi?
Please stop.
Sorry. I can't help talking
as if it was a radio program.
It's not just that I want to be with her.
I want to make Tsugumi happy.
You told me that it is how
we love people on the radio.
-You are right.
-Yes.
-Thank you for the lunch.
You are welcome.
Thank you.
May I talk with Ken in private?
What?
I want to talk with Ken. Is that not OK?
Well, it's not bad.
Ken will decide what he wants.
Ken, can we talk in private?
-Yes.
-Good.
-OK. Let's go.
-Yes.
I don't think Mr. Amakusa
will cause him any trouble.
I think Ken is having fun
to widen his view of the world.
He is with us not just because
he wants to be with me.
He learned how to tell a lie.
He can tell a lie because he is honest.
It's different from how we lie.
Is this your first time to see the sea?
I've never seen it so close.
Why did you decide to leave the mountain
and go to the city with Tsugumi?
She wanted to get to know me.
What did she know about you?
She knew that I know nothing.
How about you?
What did you know about Tsugumi?
About her disease?
You fell in love with her
because she has a tough life?
-No.
-How?
I can only say that it's not how I feel.
You really can't tell a lie.
Yes, I can.
It's OK. You don't have to deny it.
I want to tell you my story.
I was brought up in a northern town
by the sea.
I had a friend who was also
brought up in the same town.
A female friend.
Friend?
There was a time that
she was my girlfriend.
Did you fall in love?
We moved to Tokyo together
to become musicians.
They make and play music.
It's time for you and I…
That's right.
-We were very serious, the two of us.
-Oh okay.
But we couldn't become popular.
She was always cheerful.
I started to doubt
why she was always cheerful.
I started blaming her and thought
that we wouldn't become popular
because of her character.
I started taking apart from her.
She called me many times,
but I ignored her
and thought that it was a bother.
Although I asked her
to come to Tokyo with me,
I left her alone in the end.
Then…
She killed herself because of me.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes.
I knew nothing about how she felt.
That's what humans are like.
No matter how much you love her,
you won't understand
what she really thinks…
if you are not doing the right thing.
You know nothing about humans yet.
Neither about Tsugumi.
You are like me.
I quit singing after she died.
I tried hard to get a job
as a radio personality.
So, I wonder every day on the radio.
I'm trying so hard to know about humans.
Ken.
Would you like to go on the radio with me?
Let's go on the radio
and try to understand humans.
You have to open your heart wide
to know more about Tsugumi.
It's time for you and I
Evolutionary theory for you and I
Ask Amakusa if you are worried
About something
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Ken.
Can we talk?
Hi, Ken.
Hey, ask him.
Did you lend Iizuka money?
You asked him to keep it a secret
for Boss's sake.
For my sake?
How much did you lend him?
You can tell us now.
I gave him my salary.
All of it?
It happened before
when you started working with us.
You tried to steal the company's money.
Mikoto, it's done.
No! It isn't done.
That's why it happened again.
His mother is still taking money from him.
-His mother?
-She has nothing to do with this.
His mother is ill.
She will get well if she has money.
It's a lie.
What does it mean, Iizuka?
Ken.
You were deceived.
Please stop.
I will pay you back. So it's OK, right?
No, it's not.
-Break off relations with your mom.
-Mikoto! That's too much.
He will do the same thing otherwise.
We'll all go and check
if you return the money to Ken.
I feel like we are making a raid.
Yes, we are. Like the movie.
BAR MITSUKI
Hello.
Hey, Mitsuki.
Excuse me.
I want my money back.
Money?
What is that, Mitsuki?
I haven't seen you for a while.
Hello, Boss.
-How are you doing?
-Hello, Boss.
You haven't come to see me recently.
I missed you.
-Hi, there.
-Do you come here often?
I just came to check on his family.
Would you like to sing at karaoke?
-Not today.
-Why not?
I am their boss.
Please have a seat, everyone.
I'm glad to have so many guests.
What would you like to drink?
We just want you to return the money.
Return the money to your son.
Mikoto. Calm down.
What is it?
Your son deceived someone
to bring money to you.
Don't use your son to give money to a man.
Stop it. It's not my mom's fault.
She will never change
if you say such a thing.
She has to depend on men to live.
You are the same as my mom.
I'm not the same.
-Then show us.
-Hey!
-Calm down. Don't cause Iizuka trouble.
-You're causing trouble.
Iizuka, you told me that
you had been having a hard time.
It's my mom who is having a hard time.
-Because of me.
-You're the one who broke your back.
You have a good son.
Your patience was rewarded.
Just give him the money.
I will pay him back.
I'm sorry, Ken.
I promise you that I will pay.
Did he borrow money from you?
I am not the right person to ask you this,
but please trust him.
He is like my father.
Like your father? He?
Because he taught you how to fight?
You dropped out of high school.
You have been working for him.
What are you? Are you a teacher?
I am his friend.
All of us here are his friends.
You told me that
you wanted to be a carpenter
and live freely without being
involved with anyone.
Somehow, I started living freely.
I'm sure you can do it.
You are working hard.
Not give money to this man, is it?
Mitsuki. Come and drink with me.
No. You will drink with us.
Iizuka!
Mitsuki!
Why don't you quit a stupid job like this?
-What did you just say?
-Hey!
Let's get a horse
and you go on a trip with me.
Right?
Ken.
What are you doing? You look strange.
Did you say thank you to Iizuka?
He said thank you when
he borrowed money from me.
He said it repeatedly.
It might have been a lie,
but he cares about others.
He cares about me.
Do you care about him?
Did you thank him?
Thank you for your advice.
Aren't you going to thank him?
Thank you very much.
-Please stop!
-Get away from me.
Ken!
No!
I'm OK. Calm down.
I love you.
I love you so much.
It's true.
I love you.
So bear with it for my sake.
Please…
Tsugumi.
How dare you!
-Stop it, Iizuka!
-You bastard!
You can have it!
I am very sorry.
BAR MITSUKI
Ken.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it. It's not a lie.
Please let me work with you.
Let's work hard together, Iizuka.
Good.
"After the rain comes the sun."
-Do you want to go to karaoke?
-Yes.
I will go with Mikoto, next.
No way.
Let's go and sing together.
-You sing first today.
-OK.
Ken.
Tsugumi. Thank you very much.
No worries.
Thank you.
I love you.
I love you so much.
PARADISE HEAVEN
No matter how much you love her,
you wouldn't understand
what she really thinks
if you are not doing right.
Ken. You know nothing about humans yet.
PARADISE HEAVEN
ASK AMAKUSA
RADIO NAME - FRANKENSTEIN
AGE 120
I WANT TO KNOW MORE ABOUT HUMANS
Look here, Grandma.
Oh.
I didn't know that there was
a jizou statue here.
My mom took me here many years ago.
It was just before she died.
Do you know why she did that?
I think Saki built this.
Is Saki the woman who passed away
because of white mushrooms?
Yes. I told you that there used to be
a laboratory near your university.
There was an institute
for infectious diseases.
Yes.
Saki had something to do with it.
I heard that she built the jizou
for the patients.
You told me that you've seen
this jizou before, didn't you?
Was it a long time ago?
I don't know.
I just thought that I had seen it.
I think
your mom wanted to
ask Saki to take care of you.
It's a rare mushroom.
I wonder what kind of person
Saki really is.
Hi. How are you?
Professor.
Ken might have lived here before.
Here?
He might have had an infectious disease
and came here 120 years ago.
This might be where he met
Dr Kentarou Fukashi.
As a patient and a doctor?
Maybe he had gone through
an experiment on a human body.
Tsugumi. I have a problem.
-Ken seems to have gone to Tokyo.
-Tokyo?
Amakusa came to pick him up.
Tsugumi. I have a problem.
-Ken seems to have gone to Tokyo.
-Tokyo?
He told Amakusa that
he wanted to go on the radio.
Hi. My name is Ushiku. I am a director.
I am Ken Fukashi.
You don't have to use
your real name from now on.
Please use your nickname.
OK.
I want to show your watch to everyone.
-Right?
-What do you say?
It's almost three o'clock.
Let's call SNACK MAN.
Where is he today?
Hello. I am here. It's Junpei Amakusa.
PARADISE HEAVEN
It's time for you and I
Evolutionary theory for you and I
If you are worried about something
Ask Amakusa
In response to Tokachi
and Ririe's request,
I brought him here today.
Here is Frankenstein.
You must be joking.
Are you Frankenstein?
Yes.
I am Frankenstein. I am 120 years old.
My wish is to protect her.
Are you trying
to cause trouble on purpose?
I didn't know what would happen.
He said that everyone calls him a monster.
Go for it! Go for it!