If this mushroom is your heart,
I think
you can fall in love with a human being.
you can live with a human
because you have a heart.
I think
you have many problems to solve…
but why don't you
live with me?
Live in the human world
together with me.
MAIN TITLE
Where's Ken? He is not in his room.
He went out with Tsugumi.
She came to see him this morning.
With Tsugumi?
He said he's decided to live
in the human world with Tsugumi
and learn about humans.
What does that mean?
Why didn't you tell me that?
There was no point.
I didn't want to disturb them.
What?
I won't help you
just because you are my family.
If you're a man, you'll know what to do
or you will only lower your value.
You've got the wrong idea.
If you feel lonely, ask Mikoto
if she wants to go out with you.
Don't bother asking me.
She is not interested in me.
-That's not…
-That's not true.
Shut up.
Never mind.
But Ken likes that girl, right?
For Ken, it's not a matter
of liking or disliking.
There are many people in the park
on Sunday.
What are they all doing?
Nothing particular.
They're just having fun.
Having fun?
They're families.
Okay!
They're couples.
They're friends.
They're all having fun in their own way.
What we are doing now
is called taking a walk.
-Taking a walk?
-Yes.
Taking a walk is fun.
Oh.
Is that dog having fun?
Yes, of course.
He is taking a walk as well.
-Do dogs have fun?
-I guess so.
Are they having fun?
Please don't point at people.
I think they are having fun.
What are they doing?
-They're hugging each other.
-Hugging?
When people are in love,
they hug each other.
Do I have to do that?
No, you don't have to. Let's go.
This is a station.
Are they taking a walk in here?
They are going a longer way.
They take trains to go far.
Train? I want to take a train.
You have to decide the destination first.
-Destination?
-The place where you want to go.
You'll go missing if you don't decide
on a destination first.
-Missing from home?
-Just kidding.
-Just kidding?
-People laugh because it's funny.
-What is he doing?
-Stop it.
No, I didn't mean it.
My jokes are not funny.
Please stop laughing.
-Okay.
-Right.
This is a shopping mall.
Is this where people take a walk?
No, they come shopping here.
-Shopping?
-Tell me if you need anything.
You work and earn money, which means
you can buy what you want.
If you didn't bring any money,
I can lend you some.
-This suits you best.
-Yes.
Is there anything that you want, Tsugumi?
Fly agaric!
Is this what you want, Tsugumi?
Yes. Let me try again.
Look. I got "Destroying Angel".
Let me try again.
Do you like them so much?
King trumpet mushroom.
I want a young mushroom fruit body.
This is the university
that Seiya and I attend.
-You came here before, remember?
-Yes.
This is where you study about mushrooms.
That's right. You can learn
many other things too.
-A bicycle.
-Right.
I came here when I was a child.
When you were a child?
My mom brought me here.
It was the year before she died.
Join your hands in prayer
in front of jizo.
My mom brought me here because
she was worried about me.
I have the same disease as my mother.
I don't know why I came here
or why there is a jizo statue
in the university.
But I decided to study at this university
because I remembered
that I came here before.
I'm sorry. I don't think
you understand what I'm saying.
It's okay, even if I don't understand.
It's nice to hear you talking, Tsugumi.
I can't talk well like people
on the radio.
You are more interesting than the radio.
That's the first time anyone's said
I'm interesting.
Your jokes are not funny.
Don't worry about it.
I want to know more about
why you are worried.
Worried?
Like Amakusa?
The radio has really influenced you.
My mother's ancestors
used to live around here.
Ancestors for many generations?
Yes.
They lived here about 120 years ago.
Hundred and twenty years ago.
Is it true that you were here
120 years ago?
Yes. I was in the forest.
My dad told me that
there are 365 days in a year.
I counted every year after he died.
So, I'm sure about my age.
This is the 120th year.
I know that you can't tell a lie.
So, I believe you,
even if it sounds unbelievable.
You can believe me.
I envy you a little bit.
When I came here with my mom,
this tree was in full bloom.
But I've never seen it flower
since I started studying here.
Maybe it's dead.
So, every time I come here,
I realize that I will die soon.
I have a heart disease and it's incurable.
The blood vessels in my head
could block or break any time.
My mother too got the disease
at 30 years old and died at 34.
I've had it since I was little
and I could die anytime.
Let's go home.
Okay well I guess this is goodbye for now.
Bye.
Tsugumi!
Where have you been?
I took him out for a walk
and we just came back.
She looks sad today.
She is suffering.
Why?
Seiya. I want you to do me a favor.
Open it.
PARADISE HEAVEN
Click here when you want to send
a message.
-Good.
-Why do you like Amakusa?
Amakusa is like me.
He worries about many things
and wants to know many things.
It's just his job.
Job?
It's hard to explain.
Amakusa.
-I thought I was fired.
-No.
Did Tokachi forgive me?
No, but the listeners are on your side.
PARADISE HEAVEN
LISTENER MESSAGE
ALL THE BEST TO FRANKENSTEIN!
I am very sorry about what I've done.
I know we tried to make the show more fun.
I was a bit childish.
Do you think that a man
who thinks of himself as a monster
shouldn't fall in love with a human?
I want to tell him something.
If you think you will kill someone,
stay at home and don't go out.
Don't see anyone!
Kill yourself before you do something.
I think a monster should love humans.
As I said, I'm glad
that you told me
what you thought in your own words.
Thank you very much.
It was very interesting.
It became a big topic
on the Internet as well.
Why don't you keep it up?
Keep it up?
You should find famous people
and ask their opinions
rather than just do interviews
on the street.
I can't agree with you.
I think Amakusa was not fair.
-Not fair?
-That's enough.
He set up Tokachi to make him say
offensive things.
No.
I'm sure you set up the email as well.
What?
There is no Frankenstein.
You set up the email
and played your own work, right?
-Is that true?
-No.
-We really did get an email.
-Can you prove it?
-She's right. Show me the proof.
-Calm down.
We've got a new email from Frankenstein.
He said thanks
and asked us for more advice.
There is no point in setting this up
for Amakusa.
-Are you sure?
-Look.
It says that Frankenstein
has fallen in love.
I HAVE FALLEN IN LOVE
-Tsugumi.
-Hi.
Are you all right?
I haven't seen you for several days.
I was sick and I couldn't
come to the university.
-Are you all right?
-Yes. I'm fine.
Is it because something
happened on Sunday?
Ken was worried about you.
Ken?
He's worried that he upset you.
There're no such things.
I just…
lose my energy sometimes.
I mean energy to live.
I feel sorry for Ken.
So it's not that he did anything wrong.
No.
-How is Ken doing?
-He's doing all right.
I want to see him.
I have to say sorry. Is he at work?
-I'll come with you.
-Thanks.
Okay.
Get it here.
Here you go.
I'll put it in here.
Thanks.
Guys.
-Let's take a break.
-Okay.
I made churros today.
-Churros?
-Oh, churros!
-What's that?
-Don't you know about churros?
It's not sushi?
She wants to be popular with the men.
-Sorry.
-Thank you.
-Are you the same?
-You are so nice.
You should draw a line if you
want to attract men's attention.
-Is it good?
-Yes.
-They're delicious.
-Oh, I almost forgot.
-You need sugar.
-Right.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I'm glad to see you again, Tsugumi.
You can see me anytime.
If you are worried about something
Ask Amakusa
Hello. I am Junpei Amakusa.
I've received another email
from Frankenstein, who is 120 years old.
-Again?
-They're reading it again.
"Thank you very much for answering
my question last week, which was,
'Should a monster who might kill someone
fall in love with a human or not?'
Thanks to you, I've fallen in love."
That's so quick.
"But she is suffering from
an incurable disease.
What should I do to save the life
of the girl I love?"
This is tough.
A monster seems to have found
the girl of his destiny.
Today, I'm visiting
Mr. Toshibumi Tsurumaru,
who is the author of the book
"You Can Change Your Destiny"
and a professor of life science
at Fugaku University,
and ask him this question directly.
-You must be joking.
-Professor.
May I come in, Professor Tsurumaru?
Come in.
First, let me ask you a question.
What can a man do to save
the life of his girlfriend
when she has an incurable disease?
Will you tell us what you think?
Work on her DNA.
-Her DNA?
-Yes.
DNA is known as life's blueprint or code.
It not only inherits genetic
information from your parents
but also runs the organs in our body,
absorbs nutrition,
and transforms it into energy.
But most of the potential work of DNA
is still sleeping in our body.
It is said that DNA is the key
to curing disease.
Professor, please make it short.
We don't have time.
It is the sender of the email
who doesn't have time, not you.
Do you think I can make short
of such an important issue?
What's the point in being brief?
Make her happy. Entertain her.
Make her want to live longer,
so that she can bring out the power.
The important thing
is to wish her to live long.
If you wish it, will it come true?
It sounds like a religion.
To love someone is to wish
for all the best for the one you love.
Try to make her smile and be happy.
Love is to wish for all the best
for the one you love.
That's how you extract the power
of DNA and the power of life.
So, you should love someone.
Miracles that can't be explained
by science do happen.
Unfortunately, we can't explain
the power of love scientifically.
But you can change the strength
of her DNA if you love her.
In short, do you think
love will create a DNA revolution?
To put it briefly, yes. You are right.
I see.
Mr. Frankenstein,
try to make her smile and happy.
Start a revolution
by wishing all the best for her.
See you tomorrow.
If you're worried about something
at break time…
Ask Amakusa
Okay. It's done.
Professor, thank you. I am so moved.
Thank you.
That was the email
you actually received, right?
-Yes. Why do you ask?
-Nothing.
This is not a fake.
We got this email from a listener.
Good.
Next up is the traffic information.
You sent an email to the radio show.
The speed limit is set to be
30 kilometers per hour.
Please be careful…
I like you, Tsugumi.
I am in love with you.
Will you love me?
I will make you happy.
I will make you smile.
Then you will be able to live longer.
Let's go out for a walk together.
Let's have fun.
Let's wish more.
Don't say such things by yourself.
You can't change things by wishing.
You can't love someone
to make something happen.
I can't love anyone.
I can't be your girlfriend.
I'm sorry.
Ken, are you all right?
Don't worry too much.
There are many other women
in this world. Look around.
Leave him alone.
It doesn't help when he is lonely.
Ken. Bear with it.
-We are on your side.
-Let's work together.
Don't let your heart be broken
during break time.
Seiya.
What is this?
What is this feeling?
It's a feeling that can't be
explained by science.
He is like a child.
Leave him alone.
Okay.
Do you think that the man
called Frankenstein really exists?
What are you talking about?
There is no man who is 120 years old.
Isn't this man a fantasy
that Amakusa made up?
Don't say such a thing.
I think he set up the email.
If so, it's a fake show.
How can she say such nonsense?
Don't you think so?
It'll be a big problem if he set it up.
It means that he's fooling the listeners.
I'm sure Amakusa knows better than that.
-Why don't we make sure of the truth?
-How?
Let's ask.
Frankenstein, please call us
for Amakusa's honor.
Give me a break!
I hope that he calls us.
Mr. Frankenstein, we will be
waiting for your call.
-Are you all right?
-Yes.
I'm all right.
Did you do the interview
because you knew it was him?
I read the email beforehand.
I'd heard of the name Amakusa.
I realized that it was
his favorite radio program.
Then why did you say such a thing?
Such a thing?
You told him to love someone.
Did he fall in love with you?
I thought so.
Then…
Are you annoyed that he loves you?
How can I love him?
We don't even know how to handle him.
Knowing how his body works
doesn't have any relation to love.
No matter how his body works,
his heart is exactly
the same as a human's.
Don't you think so?
We can't control how he feels in his heart
unless we erase his existence,
including his body, from this world.
No way.
I'm not asking you to fall in love.
Since we admit his existence,
we can't ignore his heart.
-Professor.
-Yes?
This is too sweet.
Drink some more, Ken.
Drink and forget it all.
That's what people say.
But the more you drink, the harder
it becomes to forget a lost love.
But you are too young to drink alcohol.
I learned it from my mom.
Mature women tend to drown
in love, alcohol, tobacco, cakes,
and religion, in that order.
That's not true for all women.
A mature man doesn't drink
to forget a lost love.
He drinks to tell himself
that he may forget.
That's the pride of manhood.
-Exactly!
-The pride of manhood?
Men are regretful and become crazy
because they have pride.
Swallow your pride and admit
that you are a loser.
I want to
see Tsugumi.
Well said, Ken!
You are getting drunk.
Maintain your pride.
What should I do to make Tsugumi happy?
You should be grateful, Ken.
I quarrel a lot with my wife,
but the best thing is to be grateful
in the end.
You should be grateful that she exists.
Be grateful.
I don't know if she wants a man
she dumped to be grateful.
Even though your wish wasn't granted,
you can still make her happy
if you are grateful.
How can I be grateful?
-Get her a present.
-Weird.
No. Send an email
and tell her that you are grateful.
-It's easier to ignore.
-Do nothing.
Just wish that her wish will come true.
Don't bother her and wish her
all the best in her life.
That's how you show that you are grateful.
Do you speak from experience?
Today we went out to cheer you up.
To love someone is to wish
for all the best for the one you love.
Try to make her smile and be happy.
Love is to wish for all the best
for the one you love.
Ken is not back yet.
Don't worry. He went out with his friends.
I'm not worried about him.
Does Tsugumi have a disease?
Huh?
Is it true she hasn't long to live?
No, she will.
She has a difficult disease,
but it's not incurable.
Do you still regret that your mom died?
Do you wish to save Tsugumi
for the sake of your mother?
I envy you.
-Because I am popular with girls?
-Because you are so simple.
I can't keep up with you.
I can still hear my mom's voice
-It's ready.
-Let me pull it up.
-Ken, are you ready?
-Yes.
Ken!
Hey!
-Are you all right?
-Ken!
-Call an ambulance.
-Hang in there.
Ken!
INCOMING CALL
INANIWA
Hello?
What?
EMERGENCY ROOM
Do you have any pain?
It's strange. How about here?
Here?
What is that scar on your face?
Did he really fall
from such a great height?
He fell from the top of the third floor,
which is seven to eight meters high.
He doesn't have a single scratch
or bruise.
-Take an X-ray and CT just in case.
-Understood.
Seiya!
Professor! I was about to call you.
How is he?
-He is fine.
-Huh?
He fell from a height
but he has no injuries.
-Tsugumi?
-Haruka.
Professor, this is my sister.
This is Professor Tsurumaru.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm glad that you are well.
-He saved my life.
-What do you mean?
-Nothing.
-Excuse me.
What are you doing?
He seems to be okay.
Is he his family?
He is Professor Tsurumaru,
from my university.
Oh, I've heard a lot about you
from my son.
Ah, I heard that you are a carpenter.
Yes. Just like the famous story of Rakugo.
You will stay at the hospital tonight.
You will sleep in here.
They will worry if we go home too soon.
I have to go now.
Thank you.
How did you fall?
I don't know.
I felt like I saw something.
Saw something?
A jizo statue.
The one we saw together?
-Ken, time to take your temperature.
-Okay.
What is he to you, Tsugumi?
He is my friend, who works
at Seiya's company.
He works for my dad.
I think I've met him before.
-What?
-I think I know Ken Fukashi.
Where did you meet him?
I don't know, but I've seen him.
-He is a thief!
-No.
Did you bring him in?
-Are the two of you in love?
-No.
-Tsugumi.
-I have to take his temperature.
It's the same as humans.
Right.
KEN FUKASHI
BACTERIA GRANTING ETERNAL LIFE
Professor, why didn't Ken get hurt?
I think his speed of cell regeneration
is much faster than humans.
Here is what Tsugumi got.
It's Dr Kentaro Fukashi's
research records.
What?
Kentaro Fukashi?
Is that Ken's father, who was a doctor?
Yes.
According to this record,
he discovered the bacterium
that can produce eternal life
and injected it into Ken's body.
He found that the bacterium
helps other cells to regenerate.
It's not the direct work
of the bacterium itself
but the work of the DNA of the bacterium.
DNA?
The DNA of the bacterium
changed Ken's DNA
and regenerated his cells.
As a result, his body
has a special ability.
His father said that
he found the bacterium
that can give us eternal life
because genetics and DNA
had not been discovered at that time.
It was a time when the electron microscope
hadn't been invented.
Will Ken's cells never die?
Well, we know they last
for at least 120 years.
Then he has to watch everyone,
including the ones he loves, die,
and he will be alone.
It must be tough for him.
It means that he is a monster.
Why?
I can't live long.
He will live long and he can't help it.
What's the difference between us?
Please tell me.
Mr. Ken Fukashi.
Let me take your temperature.
Excuse me.
What's this?
Who are you?
I… I am Ken Fukashi.
This is too weird.
Stay away from my sister!
She is sick and weak.
Tsugumi will die if you are with her.
I have to protect her.
Stay away from Tsugumi!
Don't do anything to Tsugumi!
Is this the same mushroom
that grew on me before?
He is so weird.
I think he did something to me
when I fainted the other day.
Haruka.
He did nothing wrong.
He is always worrying.
He is suffering because of his body.
Tsugumi?
He is the same as me.
Tsugumi!
I think I saw something.
Saw something?
A jizo statue.
Ken.
Tsugumi.
I can't touch humans
because I may kill humans.
So, I can't touch you.
I can't do anything.
I can't even hug you.
But I'm in love with you.
Is that bad?
Is it bad if I am with you?
I don't know
what love is.
It is to love someone and wanting
to be with the one you love.
I think love is more than that.
More than that?
Love is thinking about the one you love
and thinking about what you can do
to help them live long.
I think that's also love.
But I'm not confident.
You can't see love.
No microscope can find it.
I don't want to think about it
and be in trouble.
I can't live long,
but I don't want to think that it's sad.
It's no use loving someone.
I am grateful
that you exist.
I want you to be happy.
I want you to smile and live long.
That's my wish.
I will not let you die.
I will
start a revolution.
Yes.
Amakusa, he's here.
This is Seiya Inaniwa,
a graduate student at Fugaku University.
He works
in Professor Tsurumaru's laboratory.
Nice to meet you.
Hello. I am Junpei Amakusa.
I heard that you are
a friend of Frankenstein.
Yes.
Frankenstein lives in my house.
Ken went to Tokyo.
Do you want to be on the radio with me?
Radio?
I am Frankenstein, and I am 120 years old.
Let's launch an attack.
Thank you so much.
I love you.