You are not suited for my radio program.
It doesn't have to be
wonderful and touching.
I will decide if my program is fun or not.
What you do
makes me feel empty.
I feel so empty.
Hey, you.
Show yourself if you
want to go on the radio.
Please wait.
I doubt if she is really sick.
That's rude to her.
You are rude to me!
Say sorry to my listeners.
I have been working hard
to establish my program.
Shame on you!
You are the enemy of the radio.
What are you doing?
Are you hiding something?
Oh no…
I'm sorry.
Is this who you really are?
What trick are you using?
Tokachi?
What's going on?
Excuse me. Is everything all right?
One of our friends became sick.
Please call the ambulance.
Okay.
What are you doing, Seiya?
I need this in order to help him.
-The ECG is ready.
-Okay.
-Put it here.
Mr. Amakusa.
How is Tokachi?
He is still unconscious.
Is that the heart or the brain?
I don't know. They are checking right now.
Did he fall suddenly during dinner?
Yes.
Don't tell me that he was having a fight.
No.
-But…
-But?
The monster showed his true colors.
What?
Why did he grow a mushroom
that had never grown on him before?
Maybe because Ken had an emotion
that he never had before.
That's possible.
I can't prove it, though.
He…
He said that what I did
made him feel empty.
He said that I was an enemy of the radio.
I didn't like that.
Then it happened.
That is called pride.
Every human has pride.
We have to have it.
Everyone gets upset if our pride is hurt.
But you shouldn't get upset,
no matter what happens.
You must control yourself.
Don't worry, Ken.
He will be fine. We will save him.
Professor.
What's happening with my body?
Please tell me.
You are a carrier
of a huge number of bacteria.
Bacteria?
Even now, you are taking in
bacteria in the world.
Some bacteria are harmful
to human bodies and some are not.
But you can carry all of them.
Your body has a function
to take up bacteria to cells,
make them relate to your feelings,
and discharge when you get excited.
Dr. Kentaro Fukashi modified your gene
using genes from bacteria
of a mushroom that he discovered.
You got this function
from your pride or your vanity.
Your heart will learn
various kinds of feelings,
such as pride, jealousy, envy, and hatred.
That's how you live with humans.
Those emotions you feel will produce
new responses in your body.
You need to bear it in mind.
Ken, Tokachi will get well soon.
Don't worry.
Please take care of him.
Okay.
Please save him.
INANIWA CORPORATION
Ken.
Are you all right?
Are you all right, Tsugumi?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
I…
I am worried about myself.
I am scared to be with you.
I will do the same thing again
if I am with you.
I'm sorry.
Did you make the medicine
with Professor Tsurumaru?
Yes.
I can't reveal it to the public, though.
What are you hiding?
I didn't know that you are home.
Do you have to go on radio today?
No.
Everyone starts working now.
I will hang the futon out.
What are you doing?
This will kill bacteria.
You don't grow mushrooms
in your bed these days, do you?
That's because I use this
anti-bacterial spray every day.
ANTI-BACTERIAL SPRAY
Wait for me outside.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Hello? Ah, it's you.
Ken? Wait a minute.
Ken, are you there?
Yes.
He is calling you.
I don't know what happened,
but there is no use feeling down.
Here you go.
Hello?
Ken.
Tokachi was saved from death.
He will be fine.
Okay.
I understand.
Thank you.
His body carries harmful bacteria.
Sometimes he discharges them
out of his body.
Why are you hiding such a dangerous thing?
You mean that he is a carrier
of a disease-causing bacteria
and people can be infected.
Tokachi was infected
with a virus from him.
Tokachi will get well soon.
Are you going to save all the people
if they are infected?
We haven't expected that he would
expand his world so quickly.
Are you blaming me because
I push him to go on the radio?
No.
I am blaming myself.
It's my fault.
I was with him but I couldn't stop him.
But how could Ken live without problem
although he is a carrier?
Because he died once.
He died and came back to life
120 years ago.
What are you talking about?
What he said on the radio was all true.
No one will believe that.
You must be joking.
No one will believe it.
So, we can't reveal it to the public.
We never know what kind
of bacteria he will discharge
if he gets the attention of people.
Are you serious?
Yes. It's all true.
But he has a human heart.
He is even more generous than a human.
He won't do anything
if he doesn't get hurt.
Are you watching him?
Do you think he won't get hurt
if you are with him?
If you are serious,
I think you are an arrogant person.
I am arrogant.
I think that the bacteria
he discharges has a huge possibility.
Is that why you keep it a secret?
Some science in this world,
we shouldn't use.
Please give me a break.
I can't follow what you're saying.
You talk on the radio
and you work on the human heart.
I think the human heart
can be explained by science.
Please don't use his heart
for your own self-interest.
Don't make a show of him.
I trust your heart.
This is all what I wish.
-It's a sunny day. Work hard.
-Yes.
-I can't hear you.
-Yes!
How is it going, Ken?
Don't you think it's nicer to work
than talk?
People shouldn't go easy.
I'm sure it's fun to go on the radio.
I wish I could talk on the radio.
But you never know true happiness
if you don't work hard.
Mr. Shishikui.
It's not just fun when I talk.
Why do you want to go on the radio, then?
It's not only the radio.
People have a hard time
talking to each other.
Sometimes we hurt those
who we love by words.
Are you talking about love again?
It's hard to tell when you love someone.
Shut up.
I'm not talking about you.
Why does a man think that
a woman will know that he loves her
without telling her by words?
It's not only a problem of man.
Don't you think so, Murozono?
Yes.
Are you talking about me?
Wait.
Did you see that?
People become lazy if you think
about unnecessary things.
You guys! Work hard!
Look.
Here comes a lazy man.
Rome was not built in a day.
An old woman was not made
in a day, either.
Stop being silly. How is Ken doing?
He is working hard.
A carpenter is not made in a day.
Don't worry.
Ken is working hard.
It seems that he is back to being himself.
I hurt his pride.
Huh?
I told him not to get upset,
no matter what happens.
It's like I asked him
to swallow his pride.
You can't help it.
Ken is not a normal human.
I think now you understand.
Come on, guys.
Let's finish the one over there.
Yes, boss.
I'll start this now.
Tell them that we will be done by noon.
Did you have any problems?
-Hey, can I get some help?
-Sure.
I mean, with Seiya and Tsugumi?
No.
Don't think bad of Seiya.
I mean, he is a smart man,
but when it comes to love,
he is a bit clumsy.
You love Seiya.
What did you just say?
-You love Seiya.
-Don't repeat it.
-We all know that.
-She loves him.
Shut up. Go back to work.
I don't think bad of him at all.
I appreciate him.
-Do you?
-Yes.
Do you like that wood a lot?
Huh?
Oh.
Hey.
I want you to do me a favor.
Okay.
I want you to be a radio personality
until Tokachi is back.
Huh?
Ririe, please help him host the show.
Since Tokachi is still
in the hospital, I have no choice.
It's too sudden.
Cheer up. It's a chance for you.
What chance?
It's a chance for growth.
What about a relay broadcast?
We'll skip it and do
the Q and A at the studio.
-Huh?
-You can make a show as you like.
Let's do our best, Amakusa.
We will do the public broadcasting
on this Friday as we planned,
even if Tokachi is not here.
Bring Franken to the studio.
PARADISE HEAVEN
LIVE PUBLIC BROADCAST
Show him to the listeners.
They will be so excited.
Wait a minute.
I don't know if he is coming.
Why?
After what happened the other day…
What happened?
You didn't explain it enough to us.
Don't forget that you can't host
the show without Franken.
The listeners wouldn't be content
if Franken is not coming.
You told us that the monster
showed his true colors.
I think he should show who he
really is to the listeners, too.
Who he really is? I want to see that.
Bring Franken to the show, no matter what.
It's too tight.
Really? This side is loose.
I'll do it again.
Are you working overtime?
-Welcome home, Seiya.
-Hi.
What are you making, Ken?
What am I making?
You are helping me build my study desk.
A study desk?
Yes.
I was a lazy student.
Really?
I can teach you anytime.
-Are you sure?
-Anytime.
Good for you, Murozono.
-Work hard. No chatting.
-Understood.
So, you want to study?
Yes.
I want to be a first-class architect.
Thanks.
I don't think I can teach you that.
Come on. You've got a lot of guts.
It's not just about guts.
I think it's great that you want to study.
Ken is trying hard to expand his world.
I have to do what I can do.
Ken is really good with his hands.
He will be a good carpenter.
Why didn't you become like your dad?
A carpenter?
My mom died when I was a child.
I have been wishing that
there was no disease in the world.
You've got a lot of guts.
Just kidding.
Actually, my dad started bringing
many young strangers to our house
after my mom died.
I studied hard because
I didn't want to be like them.
I'm just kidding.
I'm sorry. That was not a good one.
I envy you.
You didn't stray from being right.
I think you are very smart.
No one had ever told me that.
Most people say that
I am cute but not smart.
I see.
Murozono, it fits right.
Well done.
Good evening.
Mr. Amakusa.
What's wrong?
Will you please go on the radio
this Friday?
What are you saying?
We will do the public broadcasting
this Friday.
Many listeners who are supporting you
will come to see us.
They will be disappointed
if you are not there.
-The timing isn't right.
-Why?
Why are you opposing me now?
You should have known what would happen.
You wanted Ken to do as he wants freely.
That's why Ken could have found
a place where he can be himself.
Don't worry.
I'll be careful so there won't be
an accident on the radio.
An accident?
Nothing.
Ken…
needs to be Franken on the radio.
I think you should keep it up.
Many people are supporting you.
Hello, Ken.
Tsugumi, Ken is coming.
Good evening.
Where is your sister?
She is at work.
She is so noisy when she is here.
She is so worried about Tsugumi
and she wants me to stay here.
-Please have some tea.
-Thank you.
I always listen to your radio program.
Thank you.
How should I say?
I think the song "Ask Amakusa"
is not right.
Why don't you make a new song
with Amakusa?
Grandma.
Let's talk about it some other time.
You are right.
I have to go to the convenience store.
Sorry.
-Please take your time.
-Okay.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry about what I did.
Huh?
I said something bad to you.
I'm scared to be with you.
I will do the same thing again
if I am with you.
It's okay.
I said something bad to you.
I told you not to get upset,
but it's impossible.
Amakusa asked me to go on the radio again.
Huh?
He said I should keep doing it.
But…
You haven't decided yet?
Do you think it's okay to go on the radio?
I thought you liked radio.
Until I met you, all I had was the radio.
I learned that there were many people
who were worried about lots of things
and listened to the radio
because they wanted to get to know people.
I want to cheer them up.
By making people happy,
I can feel happiness being with you.
But…
I am scared I might betray you again.
You never betrayed me.
You were so nice
when you were on the radio.
I thought you were true to yourself.
I think I was arrogant to think
that I could do something to you.
You can do anything by yourself.
You have to live by yourself
in order to live with other people.
I forgot about that.
Do you think it's okay to go on the radio?
I think it's okay if you like the radio.
I am supporting you.
Please remember that
I am your biggest fan.
I am supporting you more than anyone.
I'm sorry.
What was I trying to do?
You were trying to hug me.
What is this feeling?
I should call it a desire.
What is that?
This is it.
So?
What are you trying to tell me?
I want you to keep it a secret.
What are you talking about?
I think you would be in trouble
if people knew
that you brought a strange monster
to the radio.
You put him before the public.
I didn't want him to go on the radio.
Are you threatening me?
Is that what a baby professor would do?
Hey.
What was that?
Was it something within him?
Even if you don't want me to tell anyone,
my job is to talk.
Please.
If you promise me that
you will never disturb my show,
I will think about it.
Thank you very much.
You never know what he would do
if you talk about him on the radio.
He really is not human.
-Which room is Tokachi staying in?
-There.
-Hey.
-Yeah.
-Who did you see just now?
-Never mind.
-This is for you.
-Oh, ouch.
Why did you bring a potted plant?
You don't look too bad.
You look just as bad as you are.
Shut up.
I'm glad that you look fine.
Tell me what happened.
I don't know what happened.
Don't see Franken anymore.
I can't. He is very popular now.
Mr. Yugawara is up for it.
Don't get closer to him.
Don't get closer?
There is a public broadcasting.
Stop it.
He is dangerous.
He is not human.
What happened? Tell me.
Ken.
Look at us if it gets hard for you.
Okay.
I will.
Please take a look at the sales booth.
Ririe Ohmiya's photo book,
Victory Against Poison,
now on sale.
Thank you very much.
This is the first photo book
after you left the idol pop group.
You don't have to hide my past.
I think they want to hide it
because this photo book is too sexy.
It's not a nude photo.
I can call it a nude.
It's close but not yet.
How did you decide the title
Victory Against Poison?
I am always fighting against
Tokachi's poison.
He says he is sick today.
He must be lying.
I see. You won't be beat
by Tokachi's sharp tongue.
I don't have a sharp tongue.
Do you know why the subtitle
for this show is "Clash"?
Because they say there's a clash
of personalities between me and Tokachi.
Isn't that so rude?
There is no clash of personalities
between Tokachi and I.
I don't know.
By the way, a monster came from
the forest to buy your photo book.
Is that the famous monster who is in love?
That's right.
-Let's call him.
-Sure.
PARADISE HEAVEN
Everyone is alone at some point
The world is always a pantheon
If you know that, I will be there
Amakusa will be there
Ask Amakusa
Thank you very much.
It was the third verse of Amakusa's song.
Let's call him.
Here is Frankenstein,
the monster who is in love.
Nice to meet you. I am Frankenstein.
I was wondering why there were
so many female fans,
despite this being the launch day
for my photo book.
Please sit here, Franken.
Okay.
Here is a message for you, Franken.
Mito Washelt, Ibaraki, 23 years old.
"My ear gets itchy
when my boyfriend hugs me.
How do you feel when you hug
your girlfriend, Franken?"
Is the person who sent this message
in here today?
Here! It's me.
Hello.
Wave at her, Franken.
-Hi!
-Hello!
What did you think about this question?
I haven't hugged her. I don't know.
-You haven't hugged her?
-No.
That's like Ken.
It's pure-hearted love.
Right.
Let's move on to the next question.
I have a question from Tokachi,
who is in the hospital.
"What have you done to me, Franken?"
Ririe?
What did you do to Tokachi?
I heard that Tokachi lost consciousness
when he had dinner with you.
That's because you did something
to him, right?
Yes.
But I didn't mean to do it.
He said that you spread poison.
Wait, Ririe.
Is that true?
Did you spread poison?
No, I didn't.
Don't push him into a corner.
You didn't do anything to him, then?
Can you swear it in front of everyone?
I…
Did you spread poison because
Tokachi said something to you?
What are you talking about?
I just want to know the truth.
Did you spread poison?
No, I didn't.
You did it, right?
You just said that you did something.
Shut her up.
Amakusa, introduce the song.
I am asking Frankenstein
what the truth is.
Show who you really are
in front of everyone.
It's dangerous.
Amakusa. Don't take it wrong.
I won't do anything.
Never.
Ken! Look at me!
Excuse me.
Here is the traffic information.
What happened?
There is a traffic jam
in the Metropolitan Expressway.
Grandma.
Did you listen to the radio?
Radio? Is it that time?
I heard a scream.
Scream?
Something may have happened
to Ken Fukashi.
Tsugumi is with him now.
What is that?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What happened?
Hit-and-run.
Hit-and-run?
It was actually a man
who was hit and run, not a driver.
What is he doing?
He is sleeping like a child.
What happened on the radio show?
He needs to get some rest now.
Okay.
Dad, hold his feet.
INANIWA CORPORATION
IS IT TRUE THAT FRANKEN POISONED
MINORU TOKACHI?
I SAW FRANKEN SPREADING
SOMETHING LIKE POWDER
DON'T TELL ME THAT IT'S POISON
MINORU TOKACHI WAS ABOUT
TO BE KILLED BY A MONSTER?
ANTI-BACTERIAL SPRAY
What are you doing?
Ken.
Seiya.
I may be able to kill the bacteria
that live in my body if I drink this.
Wait a minute. I don't think so.
Let me try.
Wait! Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Tsugumi.
Seiya.
I am sorry for what I have done.
You helped me a lot.
You taught me a lot of things.
I'm sorry.
I will kill the bacteria so that
I can live in the human world.
Wait! It's not like that.
Don't take it wrong.
I put you on the radio.
I encouraged you
to go on the radio.
I wanted to keep you away from Tsugumi.
I thought Tsugumi would come to her senses
if you caused trouble on the radio.
So she wouldn't love you.
She wouldn't fall in love with you.
So, I met Amakusa.
I told him that you are a monster.
I wished that you would cause
trouble like today.
Ken.
I am not…
human.
I will tell the truth to everyone.
We've got so many phone call
complaints to the radio station.
Let's run away from here.
I will always be with you.
Ken, promise me you will be back.
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION