Plagued by low approval ratings,
the Watanabe Cabinet is
now facing a crisis.
The Democratic Constitutional Party
submitted a motion of no confidence
yesterday,
accusing the Watanabe Cabinet
of ignoring the opinions of its citizens.
A no-confidence motion was expected
to be submitted during this session…
NO-CONFIDENCE MOTION SUBMITTED
…but the timing of it,
right before this weekend's final vote
on the Global Bill,
has left many politicians stunned.
The Prime Minister's Cabinet responded
with a detailed--
What are you thinking?
There is something odd about this.
The opposing camp would not do
something like this, unless…
they made some sort of deal with someone.
Is it Saijo?
Don't jump to conclusions.
However, something is happening
out of my sight.
What should we do?
I'll have a talk
with Secretary-General Takeuchi.
Do you think he knew about this?
He must have.
However…
he did not say a word to me.
Prime Minister Watanabe will resign,
and the Global Bill will fail.
I'm pregnant.
I'm carrying your child.
Really?
I'm really happy.
Really, really happy.
Me too.
I was afraid of what you'd say.
-Why would you be?
-[chuckles]
Doesn't it complicate things?
I know it will.
Actually, it's the opposite.
Will you divorce your wife?
Yeah.
I don't love her. I'll get a divorce.
Does that mean
we can get married right away?
No.
You're not ready to?
I am.
I just need to figure things out.
[Nami] But you're scared because
you don't know how your family will react.
What era are we living in?
I know.
I know in my head.
I don't want this child to grow up
looking at a father he can't respect.
What happened?
Well… [chuckles]
…I'm not exactly sure myself.
[Ogami] You kept
the motion of no confidence a secret.
I never knew about it. Believe me.
Are you telling me to believe
you weren't the one
who convinced them to submit it?
You must believe me.
So, who will be the next prime minister?
I can't say for certain.
It's a complicated
and confusing situation.
Prime Minister Watanabe has
lost her power,
and I cannot predict what will come next.
What will your faction do?
Formally, they will
vote for me.
[Ogami laughs]
Yes, they will.
[chuckles]
[door closes]
[breathes deeply] Wow, that looks amazing.
It was yesterday's dinner.
[sighs]
I'm so sorry.
But, I really need to get
right back to work. Sorry.
Work?
Yeah.
There's a lot going on.
It's an important time.
I really need to go now.
I really have a lot to think about
these days.
But everything will be
finished by this weekend.
Okay.
[Kageyama] I'll get going now.
Wait.
What?
Never mind.
It's nothing.
[sighs]
On top of Maruyama's dumb antics,
Saijo has been lurking around
like a hyena.
There is no one I can trust anymore.
-[sighs]
-[Ogami] Was it Secretary-General Takeuchi
who gave the opposing party the suggestion
to submit the motion of no confidence?
I don't know.
Saijo could have made a deal with them.
Isn't this the first time
you were completely in the dark?
This is not a problem with me,
but with you.
Do you really think so?
Aren't you jumping to conclusions?
You should take the time
to look in the mirror.
And you?
Me?
I always do
what I think is right.
[clicks tongue, sighs]
So, how much trust can you give Takeuchi?
Why ask now?
I'm thinking about who would
benefit the most from this.
[sighs]
Listen. It all depends on you.
On me?
What do you mean?
In any case, you think I'm the problem.
That's why… [whispering]
…that man created a way out for you.
Not for me. For you.
Hey, this is a problem you made.
Partying with women at your age.
Not thinking about your position.
What else would it be but reckless?
This would never have happened
if you weren't so stupid.
[Masashi sighs]
It's not like I'm always partying.
Everyone has to let loose sometimes.
And you say I'm stupid?
Then what about you?
Look in my eyes and say
your integrity is spotless.
[skateboard clatters, echoes]
You'll vote just as that man told you to.
Your first election was a scam.
But the world will never know
anything, will it?
Except that Hiroshi Maruyama's brother
went to jail for assaulting a hostess.
[child, in English] Wait for me.
-[child 2] Hey!
-[child 3] Loser.
[child 1] No. No.
[speaking indistinctly]
Hey, do you have business with that guy?
-Uh, yeah, we're just--
-Oh, okay.
[child 1, child 2] Hey.
[child 3] Three, two, one.
-[children exclaiming]
-[Murata] Shut up!
[children jeering, chattering]
-Run. Run, run.
-[laughing]
Trust me.
[Murata] You guys better leave me alone or
I'm gonna go out there and kick your ass!
[gasps]
-Hey.
-Sarah?
-Can we talk?
-[sighs]
Who is that?
[Sarah] This is Ryu Ogami.
-[scoffs]
-Oh, Max. Come on.
[Murata] You brought an Ogami
to my office?
[Sarah] He's a friend.
-Max, please. This is important.
-[Murata sighs]
This is so fucked up.
You both are fucked up.
I mean, we're all fucked up.
-That's right.
-Show me more a bit more excitement?
[Murata] Mmm. Mmm!
[grunts] You guys are something.
It's not gonna end well for you.
Double homicide.
Double suicide for you two. You know?
I'm just joking, but, you know,
just you guys dating says something.
Does your dad know?
Yeah.
[Murata] Wow.
-And you guys are still dating?
-Okay.
-And you're still alive? [laughs]
-[Sarah] Not important.
You guys are dating.
Okay, well, you should have some.
All yours.
These are the best burgers
since Georgetown.
So you went to Georgetown?
Yeah, why? What else do you know about me?
Okay, calm down.
We all have the same goal.
Bring down the government?
No. To get to the truth.
[Murata] Hmm.
Okay.
What do you wanna know?
Manabu Takeuchi.
All I know about that Manabu--
That thing stunk so bad.
It was like all the fish of Tsukiji's fish
going bad all at once.
Then the guy arrested gets whacked?
What, he committed suicide?
That's bullshit, man.
That guy got whacked.
You have evidence?
Evidence? Did you just get off the plane?
You're in Japan.
There is no evidence here.
Ninety-nine percent conviction rate.
They don't even present evidence in court.
All they get is confessions.
Hey, we think you did it.
Now, put your John Hancock here,
and everything is solved.
Everyone, everyone, everyone
gets to save time and money,
crime rates are low,
everybody looks the other way,
and life goes on.
Okay, can we go back to Manabu?
What do you know about Five Winds?
[Murata] What's that?
Should I know something?
Five Winds is a company that was
registered under Manabu Takeuchi.
[Murata] Yeah, so?
Doesn't exist.
We went to the offices.
There was nothing there, didn't exist.
Just a sign on the front door.
Nothing else.
And my NPO has been sending money to Five
Winds, a company that doesn't even exist.
Oh, so Manabu and Takeuchi set up
a company, and there's no company.
And a governmental NPO sends money
to a nonexistent company.
And then Manabu gets killed
in a bar fight,
and the murder suspect commits suicide.
So, someone had Manabu killed,
and to cover it up,
someone had the suspect killed.
But there's no way somebody's gonna
get killed in a bar fight.
Or commit suicide in fucking prison.
You think it's something
to do with the drugs?
Rumor was Manabu was
involved with a drug trade.
Drugs? Manabu?
I mean he partied hard and, generally,
he was an asshole,
but he stayed away from drugs.
No, no, no. Manabu? No way.
[inhales deeply]
So, Manabu didn't do drugs?
[Murata] No, he didn't.
There are rumors that they swept
Manabu's drug use under the rug…
[inhales sharply]
…to protect Takeuchi's reputation.
Who's they? Takeuchi and your father?
So, Takeuchi asked your father to fix
Manabu's drug issues.
And Manabu doesn't even do drugs.
Holy shit.
[Sarah] What?
Takeuchi had his son whacked.
He had his own fucking son whacked.
Manabu was gonna blow the whistle
on the Five Winds slush fund.
Takeuchi whacked him.
In order to cover it up,
he killed some poor bystander.
And your father
helped him get away with it all.
Mmm… [chewing] …these are really good.
You guys sure you don't want any?
[person, in Japanese] Did you read
the e-mail I sent the other day?
[person 2] Yes, well…
Hello.
This is Mr. Nakagawa.
He's the head of the investment strategy
department that manages prop trading.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. I'm Yumiko Kageyama.
You were working here
until you got married?
Yes, that was ten years ago.
As I've reported, she was
a very talented colleague.
I've had a hard time hiring
new, young employees who can work hard.
Especially women.
Is that so?
My department needs to
aggressively hire more women.
After all, it is a part
of the company's strategy.
It's part of the CEO's
business reformation plan.
I was told this company made approximately
1.2 billion yen in profits last year.
Prop trading usually makes up
ten to 15% of a company's profits.
Therefore, this team was responsible
for making profits of
120 to 180 million yen a year.
Mr. Nakagawa, I will be frank.
Your team does not have
a top-class trader.
Your investment strategy is too
conservative and shows little experience.
What would someone who hasn't been
in the business for ten years know?
My husband works in finance.
Was there anything wrong with what I said?
What are you trying to say?
If you hire me,
I will do everything in my power to
increase your department's profits.
Saying and doing are two different things.
I'm sure Mr. Nakamura has told you
of my track record when I worked here.
Yes.
Past achievements do not guarantee
future success.
Isn't that what you
always tell your clients?
But when it comes to actually making
those transactions,
in what do we place our trust?
If you don't learn from your past,
it is impossible to achieve
any future success.
[chuckles]
All right. Let's work together.
As they say, bearing children is
easier than worrying.
[chuckles]
Giving birth is much more difficult
than making money.
Thanks to that, I've learned a lot
while taking care of my family.
[Ichiro] What a wonderful restaurant.
It's all going smoothly.
That is good. It's truly an honor
to be a part of this.
All that's left is to do my best.
[Taka] So everything is done.
City planning, food hygiene,
you've met all the regulations.
Are your employment policies in order?
Of course. You will be able
to quickly recover your investment.
Yes.
Because I only choose winning investments.
[both laugh]
[Ichiro] Thank you.
TRAFFIC SAFETY CAMPAIGN UNDERWAY
WRITTEN REPORT
[Masashi sighs]
MARUYAMA
[kicks desk]
You think this is a joke?
Quit screwing around, Maruyama!
[detective] Hey! You bastard!
-Take him away!
-[exclaims]
Come here!
[panting]
[Kageyama grunts]
[gasping]
[moaning]
[Kaori] You like my body?
Of course.
It's so beautiful.
[chuckles] Right?
Did this tattoo hurt?
[Kaori] Very.
But it was worth it.
Why a peacock?
Because I'm not your average woman.
-[Kageyama] That's true.
-[laughs]
Isn't it amazing?
The peacock is a symbol
of hope, pride and respect.
Males use their beautiful feathers
to woo females.
That's how it should be.
I also
like beautiful men.
[sighs]
[camera clicks]
[phone ringing]
HIDE
You're calling me this late at night?
This is important.
So, how did it go?
Good.
You got it, right? The password.
-Yeah.
-[laughing] Yes!
Great! That's great!
1.5 billion is in our hands. [laughs]
You're truly amazing, Masahiro.
[exclaims]
What? Did something happen?
No, everything's fine.
You got the pictures, right?
Can you send them to me?
I'll check it with the public code.
Can we meet in person?
Let's input the code together.
Of course.
Let's meet up tomorrow to do it.
[chuckles, exclaims]
[sighs]
-Excuse me. Another round.
-[bartender] Coming right up.
I can't see you anymore.
I really like you as a friend.
But I've found someone I'm serious about.
That's fine.
Is it that guy we ran into?
That weak sissy?
Yes, it is.
But he's a good person.
He's working hard to succeed
with his own strengths.
I got it. [sighs]
But I'll still see you at the club?
I'm going to quit.
Because he asked me to.
Then this is the last time
we'll see each other like this?
Yes.
[sighs, chuckles]
-[Shigeo] Thank you.
-[Nami] You don't have to see me off.
-[Shigeo] Keep the change.
-Yes, sir. Thank you.
I want to do this.
I live here together with him.
-I don't care!
-Go home.
Hold on. You know I love you, right?
-You know that, right?
-[Nami] Please. Please.
-I beg you.
-Leave.
-You bastard!
-[grunts]
[both grunting, exclaiming]
[Ichiro] I'll never give Nami to you!
You bastard!
[Shigeo] You--
[both gasping]
-Stop it! Stop!
-[grunting]
-Stop!
-[grunts]
Stop fighting!
What's wrong with you two?
Sorry… [pants] … for making a scene.
[coughs]
But I…
need to do this
-for my honor.
-[passerby] That's enough. Get up.
[grunts]
Nami.
I will definitely…
become a father my son can respect.
And I want to be a man…
who is also respected by my son's mother.
-Don't do this here.
-I mean it!
I love you.
Will you
marry me?
Thanks for waiting.
[Kageyama sighs]
Shall we start?
[grunts]
The passcode?
Okay?
I'm going to click it.
For our future.
Did you lie to me?
What? No.
I don't know what happened either.
Damn it.
What the hell is this? Tell me!
-Hold on.
-I can't wait any longer!
-[gasps]
-[grunting]
-[strains]
-[assailant grunts]
[exclaims]
[grunting]
-[assailant 2 laughing]
-[grunting continues]
[choking]
[Kageyama laughing] You almost did it.
[Riko] How did that happen?
[Kageyama] Watch out.
[Kaori] Oh, you're awake?
[TV continues in background]
I'm sorry for doing this to you.
-[grunts]
-But you know why I had to.
[panting] What is this?
Since you tried to take my money.
Why are you here?
Even though I told them to go easy on you.
Who were those guys?
Where's Hide?
-[Kaori laughing]
-Huh?
You never thought a woman like me
would be friends with thugs like them?
Hide is that salaryman trash of a guy?
They'll probably take care of him
on their own.
Did you think you were the first
to come after my crypto account?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault. I was wrong.
But I didn't take your money.
I'm telling the truth. There was no money.
Attempted robbery and robbery are
the same thing.
You know that, right?
What should I do?
It's simple.
You were someone
I couldn't get my hands on.
And you really loved your wife and kids.
You would never leave
your family for me. Right?
But not anymore.
We are accomplices.
You tried to rob me.
So I'll rob you too.
What are you saying?
What I want…
is your heart.
[chuckles]
Where are we?
I'm sorry.
I was told to bring you here.
What the hell?
[grunts] I'm getting out. Open the door.
We've been waiting. This way.
Do you plan to vote
for Secretary-General Takeuchi?
[Maruyama] No one will vote for him.
Not even himself.
What do you mean?
You're not the only one
pulling the strings.
-[ice rattles]
-[breathes deeply]
Saijo?
He's just a coward.
And Takeuchi? He's more scared than Saijo.
So what about me?
I'm the weakest of us three.
There is a man.
He wants
to see you
at your hideout.
Where you keep your owls.
At your villa filled with secrets.
You'll probably learn the truth there.
The fixer is
always
looking to make things right.
Masahiro hasn't come home.
He's not answering his phone,
or responding to my texts.
I'm so worried.
Should I call the police?
Let's leave that as a last resort.
But I'm uncomfortable
with asking Father for help.
Why?
He's more trustworthy than the police.
[sighs]
What should I do?
Let's wait.
Won't we be able
to learn something if we wait?
38K FOLLOWERS
[Ken] Risako. The response is amazing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I didn't sing "Aurora."
Forget it.
I'll release it at a better time.
Do you have plans after this?
Want to have lunch with me?
I have plans with my mother.
But you need to eat. I know a good place.
Sorry, I have to go.
Okay.
-Look at the numbers go up.
-Refresh it. Look, it went up.
Bye. Thank you, everyone.
Good job today. Bye.
[Mashima] How was your talk
with Mr. Maruyama?
There were a few surprises, but
otherwise, there were no problems.
Actually, he called me
to ask if he can see you one more time.
Did he?
Shall I go?
Yeah.
Find out what he really wants.
I'll be at the villa.
[Taka] The owl is dead.
The fixer is always looking
to make things right.
That is why I gave you a problem to fix.
Who are you?
Your child.
A child you created.
A miserable child who swore to get revenge
for your terrible sins.
What are you saying?
Who exactly are you?
Does a man like you, who knows everything,
also know what it feels like
to abhor one's own father?
My father
abused my sister and I.
But one day,
he miraculously disappeared.
He died after getting involved
in a scandal.
The world believed he committed suicide,
but even I, young as I was,
knew it wasn't a suicide.
My father would never
choose to take his own life.
He was killed.
And I learned this later,
but the man who had him killed…
was called the Owl.
The Owl has no weaknesses!
He knew everything!
Including all the different methods
of getting what he wants.
Is that why you swore to get
-your revenge on me?
-[Taka chuckles]
Life is a complicated thing. More so
than something as simple as revenge.
I was really happy when my dad died.
But my father was still my father.
[inhales sharply] He was my family,
so why was the one who killed him…
[shouting] …beyond reproach?
[laughs]
That's what I couldn't forgive.
Then I discovered
that all-powerful Owl's
one, single weakness.
I've bugged the phones
of everyone in your family.
And by peeking into
all of their online activities,
I was able to learn more
about your family than you ever could.
Like what they wanted and when.
Your family told me everything
I wanted to know.
But you still stubbornly stuck
to your old ways of gathering information,
believing no one would dare lie to you.
Are you going
to kill me here?
I never thought of killing you.
I wanted to be you. I looked up to you!
I only wanted to try
manipulating your family.
So,
I found the only method
to make my dreams come true.
You'll commit suicide,
and I will become you.
[assailant grunts]
[grunts]
[exclaims]
[choking]
This is your will.
At the bottom of the hearts
of the Japanese
lies a deep connection
with patriotism and the artistic beauty
of taking one's own life.
I have dedicated my all
to my family, my country, and my soul.
My greatest desire
will be fulfilled if this world becomes
a better place with my death.
Doesn't it sound familiar?
You know, don't you?
It is the exact same thing
you wrote when my father
left this world.
[breathes deeply]
Translated by Annie Chen