[owl chirps]
[owl hoots]
[rat squeals]
[tapping]
[phone ringing]
[grunts]
Pulled an all-nighter?
[Ryu] Yeah.
The world won't end
just because you went home and showered.
Why don't you go get some fresh air?
I just have my own way of doing things.
Then your way isn't very efficient, is it?
Collaborating with the team
is also part of your job.
Looks like you forgot the Japanese spirit
of cooperation after your time abroad.
That's not what I meant.
You should go home, take the day off.
[Ryu sighs] But I've still got so much
left to do.
I'm so sorry.
Uh, no, it's my fault.
Here.
Uh, I'm Ryu Ogami.
Sorry for bumping into you.
[in English] That's all we have?
A phone call from a conspiracy theorist?
His name is Max.
And Max is this guy
who stays up late in the dark
and posts mysterious things
going on in Japan.
Kind of. He seems like a pretty legit guy,
just a bit crazy sounding.
Yeah, I think there's a story there.
Oh, come on. Just give me a chance.
I think it might be worth investigating.
There's no proof, evidence, nothing.
Yeah, but in a country
where everything's kept a secret,
where else am I going to get my leaks?
[sighs] So this is the same guy
who told you
about the mysterious fixer character guy?
The Owl? That you're interested in?
Same guy.
And apparently, that guy fixed
this thing too, according to Max.
Seems like a busy guy, this Owl.
Yeah, seems so.
All right,
that's a more interesting story.
Mysterious fixer in Japan who pulls
the strings of the politicians.
Didn't you say
you were going to talk to the son?
Yeah, um, that didn't go anywhere.
[Ryu] There it is.
Oh, wow.
What a beautiful night.
[Ryu] Tokyo Tower was modeled after
the Eiffel Tower.
And then Godzilla made it famous.
Got a bit of its own charm.
All those French giving away
the Statue of Liberty, Tokyo Tower.
What are we Americans giving?
Freedom, democracy, liberty,
values most people in the world
don't enjoy.
Japan has them.
Don't be fooled.
Japan isn't as free as you think.
Don't kid yourself about America either.
We're not that free. Especially with some
of the clowns that have run our country.
America is full of dreamers,
and dreamers create change.
And you can't make changes here?
Nothing changes here.
It's not a bed of roses in America,
you know.
College tuition is basically unaffordable,
medical insurance is insane,
the rich get richer
and the poor get poorer.
Re: elections? Don't even get me started.
But you have free speech.
And that's where it all starts.
No one speaks up in Japan.
Everyone conforms while a small group
of men tell us what to do and not.
But in America,
you have journalists like you
who work to keep the politicians honest,
report about corruption and scandals.
You bring justice to America.
That doesn't happen here.
Maybe it does, you just don't see it.
Or maybe it doesn't, so I don't see it.
Or maybe someone needs glasses.
[both chuckle]
Let's take a picture.
LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
[Saijo, in Japanese]
Thank you for your time.
[onlooker] Mr. Saijo!
[onlookers giggling]
I got a visit from that man.
Ryutaro? He's always moving
behind the scenes for the prime minister.
Therefore,
he'll definitely be backing So Takeuchi.
[assistant] Manabu Takeuchi's death
only made him more popular.
What do you plan to do?
Bide my time.
I'll wait until they make their next move.
Something is bound to happen.
That's how things work.
That's when we make our move.
And Hiroshi Maruyama?
He has the swing votes.
He's your typical opportunist.
Give him a little push,
and he'll do whatever we want.
Let's go to lunch.
Yes.
[sighs]
The majority of my supporters
will vote against the bill.
I know.
That's why I'm speaking directly with you.
[chuckles] But that will end
my political career.
We'll back the prime minister
until the very end.
Then that person
will owe us a lifelong debt.
But it's all over
for Prime Minister Watanabe.
The Bill has nothing to do with that.
And that's even more of a reason
to stand with her.
So I can't remain neutral.
In that case…
I'll need to consider a few things.
If you join our side,
you'll be guaranteed a brilliant career.
Now, have another glass.
[sighs]
-Hi.
-Hey.
How are you?
Good. You?
Good.
Did something happen?
Suddenly taking me out to lunch.
I should, every so often.
I'm happy you asked me to lunch.
But I was surprised
since you almost never do.
It's your present.
What is it?
Just something small.
Thanks.
You're not opening it?
I was going to open it later.
But I'll do it now.
I like it.
Do you know what it is?
Isn't it a necklace?
But I still think this isn't like you.
[Ogami] What isn't?
Taking me to lunch, giving me a present,
remembering my birthday,
even though it passed.
Is there something you want to ask me?
Right.
I wonder what your hopes and dreams are,
what you want to do?
I want to be a singer.
Singer?
I'll tell you since you're asking.
I've always wanted to be a singer.
I see.
The entertainment industry
is a dangerous place.
It's not as dangerous as boxing.
We're not beating each other up.
No.
It's even more dangerous.
You'll be hounded by fear.
[Kyoko] How was your lunch with Risako?
She said she wants to be a singer.
Yes. She's quite talented.
But you probably didn't know.
Risako is all grown up.
She can take care of herself.
You know she has a boyfriend, right?
No, I didn't.
How old is he?
Go and ask her yourself.
She seems to really like him.
I see.
For someone who knows everything,
you don't even know
who your daughter is in love with.
Love?
It's something that happens
every so often when you're young.
You can be really old-fashioned sometimes.
I plan on going to the villa.
Would you like to join me?
[instructor] Asami,
you're moving too fast.
Okay.
[producer] What about Risako's account?
[assistant] We already combed through it.
I'll email you the details.
Things are going to get busier.
[producer] It went well.
[Risako] "Well"? What did they say
about my singing?
[producer] That it was amazing.
-However--
-However?
You're a little too old for a debut.
[scoffs] I'm only 25. That's too old?
-For an idol.
-[scoffs]
It's so dated to be picky about age--
That's why we're considering
the talented diva angle.
For real?
Yeah. Isn't it a good start for you?
[sighs]
And?
You'll work with Ken, that composer
you met. He wants to write a song for you.
You'll get signed
and record your own song.
Wow.
This is amazing.
-But wait a minute.
-What?
I also write my own songs.
I've got a few that I wrote, so maybe--
A hotshot composer is going to
write your songs.
-Don't do anything unnecessary.
-[sighs]
Your private life is more important.
What?
Is there anyone you're seeing?
Why are you asking?
If there is, break up right now.
I don't understand.
[producer] There's no way you went
to all these fancy dinners
and resorts alone, right?
Look.
Men are a dime a dozen,
but you only get one chance
at your career.
The agency will be managing
your social media account.
No more dating.
Don't go out in public alone.
And don't do anything stupid.
[sighs] That's
how you'll become a star.
-Can I think it--
-No.
That's the basis of this industry.
-I FOUND A GOOD RESTAURANT
-TAKE YOUR WIFE
NAMI
PHOTO
CREDIT COMPANY - CALL
BCCJ CARD - CREDIT CARD COMPANY
WHY WOULD CREDIT CARD COMPANIES
CALL YOU?
[assistant] Yes,
this is an orchid.
-Yes?
-[customer] Do you have air plants?
[assistant] Yes, we have plenty
over there. Please take a look.
Yumiko! It's been so long! How are you?
I'm so busy with the kids and the house,
but I'm doing great.
-That's good.
-[customer 2] I have a question.
-[assistant] Sorry.
-No.
Give me one second.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This plant here? Okay.
You seem even busier than me.
It's that time of year.
It'll get even busier soon.
You should hire somebody.
You're right,
but it's really hard to find someone good.
So that will be 3,600 yen.
-Okay.
-Here.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-I'll pay with this.
-Okay.
TOTAL - 3,600 YEN
PROCESSING
INSUFFICIENT FUNDS
Sorry. This thing acts up sometimes.
-Let me try a different card.
-Mmm.
Here.
Go ahead.
[machine beeps]
I'm so sorry.
What's wrong with this thing?
[machine beeps]
Just give me a second. Uh…
-[clerk] Welcome.
-[door closes]
[Kageyama] Do you buy used watches?
Of course we do. Do you have it with you?
Yes.
Do you have the box and warranty?
Is it possible
to use it to get a loan?
This watch?
Yes.
How much can I get?
I'll examine it.
It will be a million if this is real.
[sighs]
Audemars Piguet's Royal Oak…
Patek Philippe's Nautilus,
and Rolex's Cosmograph Daytona,
Explorer I
and Submariner Date.
How much will all of these be?
[Yumiko] How did you get into a fight?
Shin got beat up.
Quiet, Riko.
What happened, Shin?
I was trying to stop this kid
from taking my rare card,
and we got into a fight.
Didn't your teachers try to stop it?
I don't know.
That's horrible.
Who was the boy?
It wasn't a boy.
It was a girl.
-Shut up.
-Stop moving.
Shin, tell me what really happened.
It wasn't just one,
it was a bunch of them.
They snuck up behind me and hit me.
[sighs]
And the teachers didn't do anything?
He might get expelled.
I told you to shut up.
-Stay still.
-Stop.
-You'll get blood on the sofa.
-Shin.
-Go to Mama and get it cleaned.
-Why?
[footsteps approaching]
Mr. Maruyama's not budging.
He won't support the prime minister.
Looks like this beam has termites.
I'll need to fix it soon.
You said Mr. Maruyama's not budging?
Yes.
He's keeping his distance
and observing the situation.
He's determined to remain neutral.
That is not possible.
But if he were to choose a side,
he would probably stand with Mr. Saijo.
I will not allow
someone like Mr. Saijo
to be in power.
[piano playing jazz]
I'm in a great mood.
My restaurant is finally starting
to take shape.
I signed the contract and want
to celebrate this occasion with you.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It's a first for me.
With this, I can finally stand on my own.
I did it all with my own skills.
You didn't ask your father for any help?
[laughs] I wanted to make him happy.
And you too.
Of course, I'm happy.
This will be a new beginning.
[phone vibrating]
Shouldn't you answer it?
It's fine.
Saho.
The two of us, let's start over again.
[inhales sharply]
What about your business capital?
You have the funds, right?
It's not a problem.
I've arranged everything.
Are you sure there are no issues?
Don't you trust me?
[phone vibrating]
[phone vibrating stops]
I trust you.
Roppongi-dori Ave.
-[R & B music playing]
-[hostesses] Welcome.
[customer laughing]
-[customer] I get it. I get it. [laughs]
-[Nami laughs]
May I have a drink with you?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
[customer laughing]
You have amazing breasts.
[hostess] Oh, stop.
[customer] But I prefer Nami's.
Yes, thanks.
[customer] Tea cup! It's a T!
Isn't England the land of tea?
I want a look at Nami's tea cup.
-[Nami] You're so bad.
-[customer laughs]
-[slams bottle]
-[hostess gasps]
[customer, laughing] My crush
is crushing my shoulders.
-[hostess giggles]
-I apologize for interrupting.
Nami, do you have a moment?
What? A moment?
We need to talk.
Is that okay? Really?
Stop acting like an idiot.
This is against the rules.
What are you doing?
What? This is work.
This is my job.
[laughs]
What a horrible job.
Don't you dare cheat on me!
What? Who's cheating on whom?
It's not like you'll leave your wife.
You're just using me to fool around!
You're right.
That's what I came to say.
What?
[scoffs] I'm going back to work.
[Nami grunts]
Let go of me!
What's wrong with you?
♪ It's not so easy
To give my trust to you ♪
♪ But I'll keep listening ♪
♪ To the flutters of my beating heart ♪
♪ In this world, in this time ♪
♪ So full of ugly little lies ♪
♪ I fell in love with you ♪
♪ Only these feelings of mine are true ♪
♪ With each new piece of you I find ♪
♪ I see a brand new heart of mine ♪
♪ Embracing me, the aurora ♪
♪ Changes colors as it shines in the sky ♪
[music stops]
[in English] Great.
-[in Japanese] You're on fire, aren't you?
-Yeah.
- Right?
- Yes.
You've got a great voice.
Thank you.
Okay, let's continue tomorrow.
That's enough for today. Good job.
Thank you.
Can I get the converted file?
All right.
[producer] Sheena.
This girl is?
Risako.
We just signed her. She's pretty good.
[Sheena] Mm-hmm.
You know Sheena, right?
Of course, I do.
I've always looked up to you.
Thanks, honey. Much appreciated.
I'm writing a new song for her.
Ken's an amazing producer.
I guarantee it.
High schooler?
No, I'm 25.
We'll get along just fine. [scoffs]
Since I'll show you everything.
Thank you. It's like a dream.
I know exactly how you feel.
I was like that too, once upon a time.
[producer chuckles]
I'd appreciate any advice you give me.
Why did you lie?
Did you think you'd get away with it?
You did two bad things.
Fighting and lying.
Want to tell us what happened?
Like I said, they hit me first.
You're still lying.
[Shin] I'm not lying.
Then is the principal lying?
He said you've been starting fights
with the other kids.
Who will you believe, Mama?
I'm done.
I can't do this anymore.
Shin.
Get your act together.
Sit up straight.
Will you tell the truth?
Aren't adults always lying?
Why am I the only one
who has to tell the truth?
Adults don't tell lies.
That's what I mean. You just lied.
[restaurant bustling]
[in English] Mmm. I love these things.
Yeah?
You know that's fish sperm?
You're kidding.
[chuckles] I'm not. You said you wanted
to try something adventurous.
Oh, my God.
What do I do now?
-It's good.
-Mmm.
It's called shirako.
Yeah, shirako.
I know my sperm sacs when I see them.
In Russia, they call it moloka, I think.
Moloka?
And Americans call it milt.
But I don't think you guys eat it.
There you go. Just change the name
and it becomes a delicacy.
Sperm, milt. Venison, Bambi.
You're very funny.
And you're very smart.
How did you know
what fish sperm is called in America?
[both chuckle]
I'm just curious, that's all.
Mmm.
Let's see you eat it, sir.
Sure.
Yeah, I don't think America's going to be
serving sperm burgers anytime soon.
Well, their-- their loss.
This stuff is good.
-Nice.
-Mmm.
SEAFOOD - FRESH FISH
FRESH SEASIDE GRILLED FISH
-[chuckles] What are you doing? [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
[owl hooting]
[panting]
[in Japanese] You came all the way here?
[Ichiro] It's not something I should say
over the phone.
Do you know what the owls are doing?
[Ichiro] No.
Are they hunting?
[Ogami] Courting.
Really?
We'll see a new owlet soon.
[Ichiro] Father.
I've never done anything worthy
of being your son.
But now, I will devote
the rest of my life to you.
Devote? To me?
Insufferable!
Just live for yourself.
I truly apologize for everything.
I'll become a son you can be proud of.
Please forgive me!
Lift your head.
You chose to run from your duties
as a husband?
Be a decent human being!
I'm sorry.
[thunder rumbles]
[Ogami] Looks like rain.
Prime Minister, what do you mean?
You want this country
to be a slave to others?
-[politicians] Exactly!
-[speaker] Silence.
Please quiet down!
This bill will pave the way
for Japan's future.
It will make us
internationally competitive,
remove barriers,
revitalize and stimulate the economy,
and take this country into the new era.
[politician] What country
are you talking about?
[politicians jeering]
Stop lying, Prime Minister!
[politician 2] Be quiet.
[politician 3] You shut up! Let them talk!
-[politician 4] You ignoring me?
-[politician 5] Prime Minister--
[speaker] Minister of Finance,
Sosuke Saijo.
[applause]
To add to the prime minister's arguments,
this bill will indeed benefit
some of our citizens.
However, there is a possibility
it will negatively impact everyone else.
[politicians murmur]
She spoke of our competitiveness,
but that will only enrich
the small number of billionaires.
Will they then help
-this nation's farmers and fishermen?
-[snoring]
-[Saijo] No.
-Wake up.
[Saijo] Loosening the policies
will force them into dire straits.
It will take away our true national power.
[politicians clamoring]
Exactly. Well said.
It is extremely risky
to pass this bill
without properly debating these issues.
-[politicians] Yes. Exactly.
-[applause]
That's right.
I agree.
-[audience cheers and applauds]
-[music plays]
[fan] Masa!
We've been waiting for you!
-[fan 2] Amazing!
-[fan] You're so cool!
[singing "Season in the Sun"]
Boss!
Yeah!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
[music stops]
-Keep singing, Masa!
-[music resumes]
[huffs]
Let's have another toast.
To the upcoming election.
[together] Cheers!
[karaoke playing inside]
We're the police!
Everybody stay where you are!
Don't touch anything! Don't move!
I said don't move!
Get it together!
Nobody touch anything.
Right. Exactly.
-[phone buzzes]
-Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
[caller] I just received word
your brother has been arrested.
[policeman] Nobody touch anything.
Don't even move!
[caller] Seems he was having a party
at a karaoke bar.
Translated by Annie Chen