[panting]
[train passing]
[heavy breathing]
[breathes heavily]
NO STYROFOAM ALLOWED
What do you want to talk about?
How far are we going?
ENTRANCE - TSUKIJI UOICHIBA
Who the hell are you?
Public Safety Bureau?
[stranger] I'll start
with what you already know.
A few months ago,
an office worker paid off someone
who blackmailed him with pictures
of him and a woman entering a love hotel.
That woman is a friend of yours.
Do you have proof it was me?
Then just arrest me.
[stranger] I'm neither a detective
or an officer of the Bureau.
Nor am I from the syndicate.
[worker] Then we are done here.
[stranger] Sit down!
This is the blackmail letter
Secretary-General Takeuchi received.
CONTAINS SENSITIVE DOCUMENTS
SECRETARY-GENERAL SO TAKEUCHI
It demands money
in exchange
for not reporting his son to the police
for his involvement in a bar fight.
That is what I know.
Your eyes--
You must be…
…that man.
The one who sees everything.
The man who controls all money and power.
You are…
…the Owl.
[Owl] There is no such man.
-[slams into door]
-Shit.
[grunts]
[breathes heavily]
[slams into door]
[grunts]
[tires screech, sirens blaring]
[police chattering indistinctly]
[chuckles]
ONLY SON
OF SECRETARY-GENERAL SO TAKEUCHI
PASSED AWAY
WAS HE INVOLVED IN A BRAWL?
To lose your only son like that.
Mrs. Takeuchi must be devastated.
Manabu was friends with Ryu
when they were in kindergarten.
Don't you remember?
Will Ryu be coming tonight?
I let him know his father
is having a birthday party for once.
What did he say?
We haven't talked since he called
to say he came back from America.
I wonder who he takes after.
Please don't mind me.
What time should I leave for the funeral?
I'll send a car for you later.
He was so young.
It's too cruel.
Everything…
happens…
…for a reason.
[panting]
[grunts]
I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
-Sorry about that.
-[groans]
[in English] It's broken.
I'm so sorry. It's totally my fault.
It's an accident. You speak English?
Yeah, from my time in the US.
Oh, where in the States?
Boston, mostly. Um…
So, I don't have enough cash
on me right now and I gotta go.
Can I meet you later
so I can pay you to get your phone fixed?
Oh, sure. Thanks.
Um, how can I, uh--
Oh, uh--
Sarah. What's your name?
Ryu, Ryu Ogami. Thank you.
I don't have a card on me,
but I'll call you later.
All right. You promise?
I promise.
[alarm clock beeping]
[beeping stops]
-[in Japanese] Morning.
-Morning.
I'm going to be late.
What about today?
You have work again.
[person] What about you?
[person 2] Audition.
I'm meeting a producer.
[person] And tonight?
My dad's birthday party.
Ryutaro Ogami's 70th birthday.
I've never had a birthday party
for my old man.
Want to come?
I've got work to catch up on.
-I knew it.
-[chuckles]
But you have to meet him one day.
Will he like me?
Absolutely not.
I thought so.
He doesn't like anybody.
Especially if they're my boyfriend.
People change eventually, you know.
Not my dad.
Honey…
what do you think?
-For tonight?
-Yes.
It's your father's birthday party.
Do you want him to think…
I married a hostess?
I thought you'd like it.
Do you have any idea
what kind of family we Ogamis are?
It's always like this.
What is?
Don't you hate everything I do?
Take a good look at yourself.
You're the wife of the eldest Ogami.
Then why don't you go alone?
What are you saying? Just dress properly.
[child giggles]
-Make sure you have everything.
-Okay.
[student] Yeah, they'll figure it out.
[parent] All done.
Papa's not here yet.
We'll be late.
You're right. Shall we go?
Let's go without him.
All right. Let's go.
Let's go.
-He's here.
-Sorry I took so long.
Hey! Okay, let's go.
You didn't forget about tonight?
My father's birthday party.
I have an important meeting tonight.
You know this is important too.
I'm sorry.
This isn't your average birthday party.
I can't do anything about it. It's work.
Your father will understand.
His generation gave up their holidays
to work.
Right, Shin?
Yep.
Good morning.
METROPOLITAN POLICE
There are no witnesses at this time.
I'll have the police report
and autopsy results later today.
The drug test?
I've taken care of it.
The police will report he tested negative.
But there is one thing.
There are rumors of a pesky reporter
questioning if Manabu was a perpetrator
instead of a victim.
The reporter's name?
I'll inform you as soon as I know.
-Are you on your way to the funeral?
- Yes.
For someone like that
to ask for your help…
The line separating enemies and allies
is never straight.
FUNERAL OF MANABU TAKEUCHI
10:00 A.M. FEBRUARY 17
TAKEUCHI FAMILY
FUNERAL HOME
I am sorry for your loss.
Thank you for attending today.
I will be relying on your support.
Come in.
[monks chanting]
[speaker] Today,
I wish to say a few words of farewell
to Manabu Takeuchi.
As the son of the secretary-general
of the Liberal Frontier Party,
he had a strong sense of justice
and deeply respected his father.
He prioritized creating a better society.
His passion for public service
led him
to actively help clean public spaces
and volunteer in care facilities.
His parents may never recover
from their grief.
Manabu would have become
-someone even greater than his father.
-[phone vibrates]
To lose him is…
[accomplice] There is a small problem.
What is it?
That reporter.
His article of how Manabu Takeuchi,
the son of a high ranking politician,
got violent when drunk
and was killed in a brawl he created
will be released nationwide
this afternoon.
We won't be able to bury the drug test
once they start investigating.
The public can tolerate acts of violence,
but not drugs.
This will create issues for Mr. Takeuchi.
What will you do?
We will proceed as planned.
Manabu was killed by accident
when he tried to stop a fight.
That is the story the people
will know.
And the reporter?
Find him immediately.
I'll talk to him myself.
Understood.
[chime rings]
[monk praying]
[monks pray in chorus]
[person] Who does he write for?
There is no need to worry.
[sighs]
If he releases that article,
I will lose any chance
of becoming the prime minister.
I'll be destroyed.
I'll take care of it before the sun sets.
[accomplice] I found the reporter.
Izumi Tanaka from the Daishin Times.
What a small world.
Do you know Izumi Tanaka?
Yes. From long ago.
Mr. Saijo has his hands
in the Daishin Times.
This is a plot to crush Mr. Takeuchi.
Should I look into Mr. Saijo?
No need for now.
Mr. Saijo is very sharp.
He might notice it.
The reporter comes first.
Why are you helping Mr. Takeuchi?
I don't have any answers for this nation.
I am only choosing
the lesser of two evils.
This is what I've always done.
I will do what I must
for the future of this country.
JCIAA:
SPECIFIED NONPROFIT ORGANIZATION
Hello.
I'm Ryu.
I'm Akira Hino.
I'll be showing you the ropes.
Don't be nervous.
We're all friendly.
Sure. Thank you.
You graduated from an elite US school?
Well, yes.
Everyone here is working hard
for their dreams or passions.
What about you?
I hope I can be of help to someone.
So you're not too interested in money.
Right.
That's good. The pay isn't very good here.
But you'll love the work.
Yes.
Come in.
[Hino] You can sit here.
[Ryu] Okay.
Let's get started.
All the information related to the new law
is here.
We need to rewrite it
so the elderly can understand it.
All right.
-Leave it to me.
-[Hino] Thanks.
That will be your first task.
Are you planning to expand
your restaurant?
Yes, I'll repay the loan in six months.
Great, however…
500 million is chump change to you.
Chump change.
If you don't have it,
I'll find someone else.
There are plenty
who will gladly give it to me.
I've heard your father is very well off.
What about him?
Why don't you go ask Papa?
Goodbye.
I can give you the loan, if--
If what?
Two conditions.
One. You agree to the interest rate
we discussed.
Two.
We become good friends. No, like family.
In business, we sometimes need bonds
that are stronger than family ties. Right?
That is true.
DAISHIN TIMES
[Owl] Please, have a seat.
Sorry, but have we met before?
[sirens playing in recording]
[reporter] We still do not know
the cause for this deadly incident.
-[phone ringing in recording]
- Witnesses in the area reported
a strong smell…
-[phone continues to ring]
-…before experiencing dizziness.
Hello. This is Izumi.
[Owl] This is important,
so listen carefully.
Who is this?
It's an act of terrorism using nerve gas.
If this is a prank, I'm hanging up.
The police aren't moving fast enough.
Your scoop will get the government to act.
Why are you telling me--
Hello?
So that was you.
That story got you a promotion.
But I couldn't prevent further tragedy.
The results would've been different
if the government had moved quicker.
Why are we meeting today?
It's about Manabu Takeuchi.
Who told you?
People love to talk.
You should be more careful.
I'm just doing my job.
Are you sure you have all the facts?
Of course.
Then haven't you wondered
if all the information you know
is hiding a terrible misunderstanding?
I don't think so.
I have a trustworthy source.
I know everything.
I'll start
with what…
you already know.
-Look at them.
-[person exclaiming]
Take it off!
-[hostess] Look at them.
-[Manabu] Come on! Strip!
Do it!
-[hostess 2] What are you doing?
-Get on your knees!
Do it, you bastards!
[Manabu, hostesses laughing]
Look up.
[shouts]
[hostesses cheering]
-[Manabu] Drink it. Drink!
-[hostess] Drink it.
[hostess 2] Who's that?
-[glass smashes]
-[hostesses exclaim]
[Manabu groaning]
[grunts]
Get outta my way!
[breathing heavily]
[panting, whimpering]
[assailant grunts]
[Manabu groaning]
[assailant screams, grunts]
[Owl] That's the story
you believe is the truth.
There is no need for you
to make this story public.
BANK STATEMENT
Can you tell me why you received
such large sums of money?
You're not the one
who decides which stories to publish.
I do.
Manabu Takeuchi unfortunately died
while trying to stop a brawl.
That is the entire story.
[assistant]
I will keep my eyes on him for now.
Good.
[assistant]
Was Mr. Saijo really behind it?
There is no doubt.
[in English] Well, I'm glad you came,
and this is for you.
Wow, thank you.
Japanese people are so nice.
If this was New York, my phone would be
on sale at a corner pawnshop,
and you'd be long gone.
It's the right thing to do.
It's not because I'm Japanese.
You mean you're not Japanese?
Well, I am Japanese. Although,
sometimes I do feel like I'm a foreigner.
Oh, I know. I do.
That's because you are a foreigner.
No, I… [chuckles] …I mean sometimes
in America I felt like a foreigner.
I guess that's one of the reasons
why I came here.
What do you do?
I just got back from the States.
I'm working at an NPO right now.
Are you saving the whales?
Sorta. Saving people.
Which is even harder.
The NPO helps the elderly
with housing and assisted care,
especially in rural areas,
and create balanced life programs
in urban areas.
Part of implementing agricultural reforms.
That's nice of you.
And you're a journalist.
Yup. Um-- Japan,
but some reporting on Asia too.
That's interesting.
So you're just a nice, good-looking,
rich guy who likes to take morning jogs?
[chuckles]
I'm none of those. Well, perhaps nice.
Well your family's got to be rich
to send you to school in America.
I actually got a scholarship.
I didn't think they give those anymore.
[scoffs] They only take your money
these days.
That's one of the reasons
why I feel like I need to give back.
[person, in Japanese]
What will happen to the suspect?
[Owl] That depends on you.
[person] What's the best option?
[Owl] I can end his life
in the holding cell.
He killed my son.
He deserves to be punished.
I'm the one
who made Manabu the way he is.
The fault lies with Manabu.
You're wrong.
I'd feel better if I believed that,
but I was the one who raised my son.
No.
We made him that way.
Mr. Ogami.
We both thought only about our country.
Paying no attention to our children.
Didn't we?
I don't want you to suffer as I have.
Manabu was truly a kind child.
He used to stay up late
waiting for me every night.
But I never came home.
You are not responsible for his death.
I turned a blind eye
to everything he did.
Aren't you the same, Mr. Ogami?
Am I wrong?
My children are all grown-up.
No, they're not.
They will always be our children.
I've had it. I'll just marry someone else.
[sobbing] I'm already past my prime.
[sighs]
[slams hand on table, sniffs]
Do you hate me now?
I can't wait anymore.
Nami!
Will you take me to your father's party?
[footsteps approaching]
I can't write the article.
Why?
[Tanaka] That man is too powerful.
That man?
You already know.
I'm sorry, but I can't do it.
My husband is also
responsible for my son's death.
Isn't this enough?
The killer will be punished.
You and your husband will receive
the public's sympathy.
I don't need their sympathy.
I want my son back.
[sobbing] I want to see my son
alive again.
[sobbing continues]
[camera clicks]
[phone dialing]
I discovered something unexpected.
You don't need to come tonight, Saho.
What do you mean?
It's a family event.
I'm family too.
Direct family.
Blood relations only.
Go see your friends.
What?
You complained about my dress
this morning, and now you're saying this?
I don't mean anything.
But you can't come.
What?
[dog yelps]
Please get in.
[Mrs. Takeuchi]
You already know everything.
Why destroy everything you built
with your husband?
He did it all himself.
It has nothing to do with me.
You are husband and wife.
A family.
What family?
You're no different from him.
My husband drove my son to his death.
I was powerless to stop him.
Manabu often played with your Ryu
when they were young.
Would you be just as calm
if it was Ryu who died?
-I apologize--
-I don't understand.
Why would you want the world to know?
If you make it all disappear…
If you make it all disappear,
the people will know nothing
and make So the next prime minister.
Is that the right thing to do?
Nothing can be changed now.
The killer will receive his sentence.
Manabu will be remembered
as a hero who sacrificed his life.
And So?
That will depend on you.
However,
it all depends on God.
God.
You mean you, Mr. Ogami?
[guests chattering]
-Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
[children chuckle]
Father.
-Happy birthday, Grandfather.
-Happy birthday.
-[Ogami] Thanks.
Happy birthday.
[guest] Best wishes on your birthday.
Thank you very much.
I'll see you later.
Is the prime minister really coming?
Yes. Mr. Ogami is why she got that seat.
[guest 2] Happy birthday, Mr. Ogami.
[guest 3] Happy birthday.
Thank you.
[announcer] We will now give a toast.
I ask everyone to stand.
The toast will be given
-by Prime Minister Shiori Watanabe.
-[door opens]
[guests applauding]
[applause continues]
[applause fades]
Happy birthday, Mr. Ogami.
Japan and the world
have changed so much in these 70 years.
You have always stood behind
this country's development, providing
your support for the prosperity
of the nation and its citizens.
I thank you and your wonderful family
from the bottom of my heart.
[announcer]
Please have your glasses ready.
I truly wish you a happy birthday.
Cheers!
[all] Cheers.
The rumors were true.
The nation owes a debt to Ryutaro Ogami.
Thank you, Prime Minister.
RYU OGAMI
Where's Ryu?
[guest 4] This is good.
I don't know. He hasn't said anything.
What a horrible son.
Not attending his father's
70th birthday party.
The next time I see him…
Stop it. How embarrassing.
Who are you to talk?
This is a party for Father.
-Kyoko.
-Yes?
Where's Ichiro's wife?
Not sure. He never talks about her.
[Ichiro] Did you want some champagne?
[Nami] I'm fine.
Father. Sorry, I haven't introduced her.
This is Nami Kawabata.
She's my assistant.
She is my guest tonight.
Thank you for helping Ichiro in his work.
[chuckles] It's my pleasure.
Happy birthday.
Can I speak with you?
Yes.
-[grandchild 1] I'll go get some juice.
-[grandchild 2] I'll go with you.
It's always the same thing.
What is?
Never mind.
You won't understand it yet.
Don't treat me like a kid.
I'm not.
Acting like you know everything.
Why are you saying that?
It's impossible for me
to live a perfect life like you.
Where's Saho?
She didn't feel well. I'm sorry.
Is that why
you brought your mistress to this party?
She's not my mistress.
She's my assistant.
Does your father look like someone
who can't see past your flimsy lies?
No.
You can't even think about
what people will say of you
when you do something like this?
[guests chattering]
[Ryu] Father.
Happy birthday.
And what else?
Sorry. I'm back home.
Good to have you back.
Ryu. Where have you been all this time?
Long time no see.
Yeah.
Now the entire family is here.
Let's take a family photo.
[photographer] Get ready. Smile.
You didn't need to come all this way.
It's only natural.
I should do this much.
It's too risky to meet you in public.
I'm really indebted to you.
Truthfully, there is one more reason.
I have a favor to ask of you.
[classical music playing]
The drug test was clean.
Did you tell Mrs. Takeuchi
about the drugs?
No.
It is not a truth a mother should know.
I'm glad you were able to finally see Ryu.
Yeah.
But I was surprised he came.
People can change.
They don't change so easily.
Only the situation changes.
Ryu is very intelligent.
And very naive.
The prime minister asked for a favor.
[fire crackling]
This will be my last time.
Your last?
Cleaning up this country's problems.
How should I spend
my final years?
For myself?
Country?
My family?
-[kissing]
-[heavy breathing]
[sighs]
[Ichiro exhales deeply]
THIS IS THE BEGINNING
OF THE OWL'S
DEMISE
THIS IS THE BEGINNING
OF THE OWL'S DEMISE
[keys rattling]
[grunts]
Translated by Annie Chen