[fairground music playing]
[pedestrian] Ouch. That hurts.
[pedestrian 2] I'll take you there.
[pedestrian 3] The 2,000 yen
for two hours spot is now 1,500.
-[pedestrian 4] That's cheap!
-[Nami grunts]
-Let's check it out.
-[pedestrian 5] Give us a discount.
Good evening, Nami.
Doesn't look like anyone followed you.
That's right.
Thank you.
Were there any problems?
Problems?
Naturally, I'm asking about
our mutual friend.
He's really dense, so he had no clue.
SETTINGS - ICHIRO OGAMI
DEVICE INFORMATION
ICHIRO OGAMI MODEL - S-Phone10
Well done.
Hey, you could just go after his father.
Why involve his family?
[stranger] Mr. Ogami's power
lies in his connections.
He can even connect
this country's richest billionaires
with the poorest of the poor.
He's one of the few people
trusted by both the exploiters
and the exploited.
That's why he keeps himself hidden.
He lurks in people's shadows,
and rarely shows his face.
And Ichiro?
A dim light.
A dim, foolish light that shines
on all the ugliness.
Mr. Ogami's only weakness is his excessive
devotion to his children, his family,
and this country.
History makes it very clear.
The empire will always fall
when power is passed to the descendants.
Even Mr. Ogami wouldn't be an exception.
I have one more question for you.
What?
You're not in love with him, are you?
[scoffs]
Of course not.
[stranger] That's fine, then.
This is not the time to get emotional.
Only when everything is put back in place.
You can do whatever you wish
when all the wrongs are made right.
I pray you'll find a beautiful love.
WHERE THERE IS A WILL
THERE IS A WAY
PRIME MINISTER YOZOU WATANABE
Sosuke Saijo is basically a child.
He wants power like a child wants a toy.
I feel so relieved you chose So Takeuchi.
He'll at least steer the country
towards the right path.
I'm confident
you'll give him your support.
The Global Bill.
Officially, it's a government-initiated,
comprehensive bill
to revive Japan with foreign investments.
A bill my late father
tried to pass ten years ago
with your help, but failed.
Yes.
Next week, I will announce
a 50 trillion fiscal reform plan.
As long as the Bank of Japan
has its hands tied,
a difficult political decision
must be made.
[Ogami] It's not the policy I believe in…
but you, yourself.
That is fine with me.
My approval rating is the lowest
it's ever been since I took office.
I have lost the party's support.
Before the bill gets passed,
they'll take my head if nothing changes.
Saijo will pretend he doesn't know
anything and take me down himself.
But this is something I have to do
for the future of Japan.
I'll give So Takeuchi
the prime minister's seat
after I pass the bill.
To do that,
I need that intangible power of yours.
[assistant] From 7:00 to 8:15,
a meeting with Deputy Chief Cabinet
Secretary Matsumoto,
and a cabinet meeting at 8:16 a.m.
[Watanabe] All right.
Cooperation within the party is important.
I'll hold the press conference
in a few days,
so have everything ready by then.
I will, Prime Minister.
You'll have no issues with my faction.
And Mr. Maruyama?
It's almost done.
You'll have their support in a few weeks.
-[Ogami] The prime minister…
-This is the Bill's final chance--
…will likely lose her seat at this rate.
You'll have their full support.
[Ogami] Mr. Takeuchi, Mr. Saijo,
and Mr. Maruyama.
One of these three will be
the next prime minister.
LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
[speaker] The lives of everyone here,
the heart and backbone of this nation…
SOSUKE SAIJO
NATIONAL POLICY BRIEFING
…should not be destroyed
by sudden and unforeseen changes.
[all together] That's right!
I may be a member
of the prime minister's Cabinet,
but I must be honest with you.
SOSUKE SAIJO
MINISTER OF FINANCE
LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
Do not be deceived by the new Bill.
[Ogami] Sosuke Saijo
has his own hidden agenda.
Above all, we must protect
the heart of Japan, its agriculture…
[Ogami] He desires for power,
and is overly confident
of his abilities to take it.
-Good luck on your candidacy.
-Mr. Saijo!
So Takeuchi.
The prime minister's
Comprehensive Japan Recovery Bill is…
SO TAKEUCHI - SECRETARY-GENERAL
LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
[Ogami] So Takeuchi is
rapidly gaining support within the party
as well as with the public.
…is without a doubt, a progressive policy.
The two of them…
[Ogami] Hiroshi Maruyama
has no desire of becoming
the party's leader or prime minister.
HIROSHI MARUYAMA
PARLIAMENTARY VICE-MINISTER
OF HEALTH, LABOR AND WELFARE
Nor does he have the disposition for it.
So Mr. Maruyama's faction
holds the swing votes.
Yes.
I'll take care of him first.
The bill and the next prime minister
all depend on that Maruyama.
[assistant sighs]
Ichiro brought a woman with him
to my birthday party.
He called her his assistant,
but she is not.
If he only would exercise some discretion.
I want to know who she is.
[assistant] Understood.
There was something odd…
about the way she looked.
[musical record playing]
CONTACTS - ICHIRO OGAMI
NAMI
CALLING… - NAMI
-[phone clicks]
-[Ichiro] Hi.
[Nami] Hi.
[Ichiro] What were you doing?
[Nami] Just sitting in my room.
[Ichiro] Okay. I just finished my meeting.
[Nami] You must be tired.
TARGET PHONE - OGAMI ICHIRO
[Ichiro] So you were just sitting?
[Nami] Yeah, just sitting here.
[Ichiro] Can I see you?
When?
Tonight.
I have work.
I'll go to you.
In that case, sure.
When do you start?
[Nami] When it opens.
[Ichiro] Okay.
I'll be there at 9:00.
Okay.
See you then.
Bye.
Love you.
[Nami] Yeah.
Bye.
OGAMI ICHIRO - WATCHING
[music continues upstairs]
[news anchor] In other news,
Prime Minister Watanabe is pushing
for a speedy implementation…
-[phone rings]
- …of her 50 trillion fiscal reform bill.
RYU OGAMI
NICE TO "BUMP" INTO YOU.
WONDERING IF YOU WANT TO
SEE A MOVIE SOMETIME?
…trump card to strengthen
her administration.
However, her approval ratings dropped…
I'D LOVE TO
…six points to 26%,
making it the lowest approval rating
ever for Prime Minister Watanabe.
General-Secretary Takeuchi,
a candidate for the next prime minister…
GENERAL-SECRETARY TAKEUCHI (LFP)
SPEAKS ABOUT
THE DEATH OF HIS SON
…spoke with reporters despite
the recent death of his son.
He spoke of the shock of losing…
-[in English] Jesus.
-[phone ringing]
Shit.
Hello?
[caller] I told you this shit
was gonna happen. Didn't I tell you?
- Are you gonna listen to me now?
-Whoa, slow down.
Tell me what?
Those fuckers. I told you they covered
the whole thing up. I told you.
So it's nothing.
Except that Takeuchi’s son was--
No, no, no, not that. You don't get it.
The guy accused of killing Takeuchi's son.
They weren't going to let him live,
they weren't going to have him go to jail.
They needed him to shut up. You get it?
That's a lot of speculating.
Shit. I gotta go. I gotta go.
I'll call you back later.
Wait, hold on.
Hello?
Jesus.
PRIME MINISTER
SHIORI WATANABE
-[knocking on door]
-[sighs]
[door opens]
-[assistant, in Japanese] This way.
-[Takeuchi] Thanks.
How is your wife doing?
Well,
she's managing.
We are both trying to move on.
I'm really sorry for your loss.
I'm truly grateful for all your support
during this difficult time of mine.
Thank you.
Have you spoken with Mr. Ogami?
Yes, of course.
I begged him for help
to get this bill passed.
Those who want my head are
already sharpening their knives,
but I will surely get this bill passed.
I believe Mr. Ogami will do everything
in his power to make that happen.
You need to be careful as well.
I will.
But that Saijo.
He's just dying to sit in this chair.
Yes, he is.
I'll be counting on you,
of course.
Leave it to me.
I'll pull Hiroshi Maruyama to our side.
I wonder if you can.
[Ben's mother] I divorced
my husband when Ben was six.
My husband returned to Guam right away.
And ever since…
Ben has been my whole world.
I only want to say this.
He would never, ever
kill someone.
The police said it was your son.
I admit Ben couldn't be thought of
as a great man.
I have no money
and struggle every day to get by.
We live in a different world from you.
But still, Ben…
did not kill your son.
I swear to God.
He didn't kill himself either.
How do you know?
I just know.
I'm his mother.
Why did you agree to meet me?
Because at least I understand
the pain of losing your child.
[customer] Hey, excuse me!
Yeah?
[customer]
I ordered some sake a while ago.
Right.
Hey, you. What's with this crappy service?
I'm very sorry about that.
-I ordered two bottles.
-[waiter] Okay.
-Bring them here.
-Right away.
[customer] You.
How can you be so stupid?
Can't you do anything right?
Hey!
You just ruined all the food.
Say something, you shithead! Come on!
[hitting, shouting]
You ain't wiping it up? Wipe it! Now!
This dumb shit.
Look at me. Hey.
Hey.
What the--
[grunting]
[groaning]
[child] Stop it!
Don't hit him! Please.
He's my dad!
Dad!
-I'll be good!
-[father groaning]
Dad!
[stranger's father] Keep your arms up!
[crying]
Didn't I tell you to stop crying?
It's not his fault.
[child] Dad! Dad.
I'm sorry.
I'll sue you. I'm calling the cops.
-[child] I'm sorry!
-Get lost, you bastard.
I apologize.
[child sobbing]
I hope
you'll both cherish,
respect, and be more considerate
of each other.
[child] Sorry, Dad.
Dad.
APPROVAL FOR PRIME MINISTER
WATANABE FALLS TO LOWEST 26%
I'm worried about Ichiro and Saho.
I'll try talking to Ichiro.
I want to do something for Shin and Riko.
The grandchildren?
Yes.
What a wonderful idea.
Why don't I ask Yumiko
when they can make time?
Okay.
Risako's birthday is tomorrow.
Did you forget?
I remember,
but I haven't decided what to do.
How about a present?
I'm having lunch
with Risako and Yumiko tomorrow.
Why don't you join us?
Wouldn't I just be in the way?
Have you ever once
acted like a father to Risako?
You were even more indifferent to her
than to Yumiko.
She's too young for me.
[sighs]
You know, I know how to skip. Watch.
I'm fast, right?
Be careful.
I can run faster than you!
[Yumiko] Slow down.
Stop!
[horn honks]
Shin!
[tires screech]
Thank you.
What are you doing? Didn't I tell you?
[driver] Sorry. He came out of nowhere.
Is he okay?
It wasn't anybody's fault.
Luckily, nothing serious happened.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Thank you for saving him.
There's no need. I just did what I had to.
Thank you, really.
That's why I always tell you
to look where you're going.
What if that truck had hit you?
[Shin] Sorry.
What a good boy.
You'll be fine as long
as you listen to your parents.
Thank you so much for your help.
I'd like to return the favor.
What are you saying?
There's nothing more magnificent
than a happy and healthy family.
[Yumiko] Let's go.
[Ogami] You didn't come to the party.
I'm sorry about that.
I wasn't feeling well that day.
I should have let you know.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, thank you.
Come find me
anytime you're having trouble.
I love Ichiro.
I always have.
You are a part of the Ogami family.
Yes.
But you're still keeping
something from me.
What happened?
Ichiro told me not to go to the party.
I know he's having an affair.
He doesn't love me.
I'm the only one suffering.
I expect you'll be honest with me
from now on?
Yes, I will.
I'll talk with Ichiro
and make the issue clear.
No, that's not why I--
Don't worry.
I'll have a talk with him.
[phone rings]
[Yumiko] Hello?
This is Matsumura from BCCJ Credit Card.
Is this Mr. Kageyama's home number?
Yes, it is.
I'm calling to inform you we couldn't
process this month's withdrawal.
The bank notified us
of the insufficient balance.
I tried calling the number we have on file
many times,
but no one answered.
Sorry, what is this about?
This is also to inform you we will attempt
to make the withdrawal again tomorrow.
I'm very sorry,
but I think you've made a mistake.
There should be enough money
in our account.
I'd appreciate it if you could
confirm your balance once again.
All right. I'll ask my husband.
Thank you very much.
[call ends]
[piano playing]
♪ This wide blue sky ♪
♪ Shining in my eyes ♪
♪ And these honest ♪
♪ Emotions of mine ♪
[in English] ♪ I believe myself ♪
[in Japanese] ♪ And it feels as if ♪
♪ It will all begin if I just believe ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
[in English] ♪ I believe myself ♪
[in Japanese] ♪ These warm lights ♪
♪ Will shine the right path for me ♪
[in English] ♪ I believe myself ♪
♪ I believe myself ♪
[piano stops]
[typing]
[in Japanese] That was good.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Sorry, but I'll do it again.
No need. It's good.
How old are you?
I turn 25 today.
Oh, it's your birthday.
Happy birthday!
Thank you.
[sighs]
She's a little too old for a debut.
Then let's lie and cut a few years.
Does it matter?
We can market her as a talented diva
instead of an idol.
I'll let you decide.
Good job. Let's call it a day.
I'd like to do it again.
[sound engineer] No, we're done. Good job.
-[phone ringing]
-[indistinct office chatter]
[worker] Got it.
Akira, do you have a minute?
What's up?
I reviewed the application
for the elderly housing subsidy program.
And I think there's a more efficient way
of providing the subsidies.
How?
Our current application window is
only until April. That's just two months.
Right now, before they can even apply
at the federal level,
they need to get accepted
at their local municipal level first.
But that's only a month.
We help them with the application,
but if the waiting period for the
results is extended to six months,
we can quickly distribute the subsidies.
I see. That's a good idea.
But only 23% were approved last year.
And those 23% were only approved
after multiple applications.
That was an issue
we struggled with in the past.
This system was created to prevent
fraud and double payments.
That's true.
I still think streamlining it will make it
more efficient to distribute subsidies.
You're right.
I'll think about it.
Thanks.
[phone vibrates]
I'D LOVE TO
How many can be seated on this floor
at full capacity?
Let's see,
it will depend on the table arrangement,
but it can accommodate
a maximum of 70 people.
And…
will the servers have room to move freely?
Of course they do.
[cell phone rings]
Hello?
Okay, I see.
I'll be right out.
[Ichiro]
I'm sorry you had to come here, Father.
I'm starting a new restaurant,
and will remodel the old embassy building
into a fine dining French restaurant
that specializes in farmed Fugu dishes.
I'm here to view one popular restaurant.
What are your plans with that woman?
She's nobody important.
I won't bring her
to family gatherings again.
I apologize for what I did at the party.
It was stupid of me.
She really doesn't mean anything to me.
Let's talk about the restaurant.
I knew it.
You're even deceiving yourself.
What do you mean?
[Ogami] You are utterly insincere
in your relationships with others.
What do you want me to do?
Straighten up your behavior.
Do only what you think is truly right.
I deeply apologize for my mistake.
It was a mistake to take her to the party.
It was a poor decision.
I won't do it again.
I promise.
I don't need your promises.
[customer] So pretty.
This one's really cute!
-Which one?
-This one.
Look at that price!
But it's so cute.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
If it's not too rude,
may I ask how old your daughter is?
Well, she's in her 20s.
Does she have any preferences?
For example, does she prefer
cute or cool styles?
Do you have anything you recommend?
Yes. This one is quite popular recently.
This is a piece
from the Wish Upon a Star Diamond series.
It symbolizes your wish
for her dreams and hopes to come true.
It's a good gift for someone you love.
[Ogami] I will take this.
Thank you. It's a wonderful gift.
Shall I wrap it up for you?
Please.
Well--
Yes?
What is it?
It's a necklace.
I see.
I will go wrap this for you.
-Thank you.
-Please wait a moment.
[Kageyama] You almost did it.
[children] Rock, paper, scissors.
[Kageyama laughing] I couldn't help you.
-You need to hurry.
-[Shin] Help me, Sis.
[Kageyama] Oops!
[Shin] Got you!
Darn. You got me.
-Okay, time out. I'm pooped. Time out.
-[Shin] Why?
[Kageyama] Come on, go play on the swings.
-[Shin] Okay.
-[Riko] Okay.
[sighs]
I got a call from the credit card company.
They said
they couldn't make the withdrawal
because our bank account
didn't have enough money.
You keep looking at that. What is it?
Work.
Did you hear me?
Oh, right.
I transferred some money into our stocks.
I should've been more careful.
Everything's fine now.
It was embarrassing
to not have enough in the bank.
Don't worry about it.
It was just bad timing.
I keep a minimum amount in the bank
and put the rest into stocks.
Okay.
But be more careful next time.
CHART - BITCOIN
[footsteps approaching]
Oh, you are--
This is the man who saved Shin.
That was you?
Thank you so much.
You saved my son's life.
Protecting the children
is our responsibility as adults.
They are our future, after all.
Yes, you're right.
Are you here with your child?
No, I'm single.
But I'd like to have a family one day.
A daughter and a son,
like your amazing family.
I'm really so jealous of you.
We're far from amazing.
It's a perfect family.
But every light has its shadow.
You should take extra caution
in times like these.
I meant be careful of cars and
other things that can harm the children.
Please be careful of those as well.
Of course.
-[Riko] Papa.
-[Shin] Papa.
-[Riko] Time out's over.
-[Shin] Hurry up.
-[Riko] Let's go play.
-[Shin] Come on.
Faster, faster.
[fairground bustling]
[announcer] Let's start the game.
[Shin] I got it.
-Bull's-eye.
- You have 20 seconds.
Aim for the robot's red--
-Do your best.
-[Shin] I'll try.
Here we go. Whoops.
I can't believe you got that doll, Shin.
It's all mine.
I want to eat a hot dog.
-Me too.
-[Ogami] Hot dog?
-Where?
-[Riko] Are there any?
[vendor] Here you are.
[Shin] Hurry up, Grandpa.
[Ogami] Where to next?
Merry-go-round!
Wait for me, Shin!
Grandpa, hurry up.
Hurry.
Oh my.
I'll ride this one.
Then I'll ride this.
Sir, are you all right? Let me help you.
Sorry.
-Be careful.
-[Riko] Hope it's fun.
Yeah.
[Riko] Shin, what do you think that is?
Doesn't it look yummy?
[Shin] Yeah.
Translated by Annie Chen