-Ryu, let's do it!
-Yeah.
[both grunting, panting]
-[shouts]
-[Younger Ryu yelps]
What will it be, Ryu? Will you surrender?
I surrender.
This makes you a member
of the Five Winds. Got it?
Yeah.
Then get up.
We'll fight together
to defeat the bad guys.
[Younger Ryu] Yeah.
I changed my mind. I'm not joining you.
I'm going to fight you!
Get ready! Manabu.
Do you think you can defeat
the Five Winds?
[shout]
Father.
What happened?
[breathing heavily] Saho is…
[Ogami] What happened to Saho?
[Ichiro] She's not moving.
She fell down the stairs.
Is she alive?
I don't know.
Call an ambulance.
But…
Do it right now!
Just do it.
Call me once you know
which hospital she'll be taken to.
[line clicks]
What happened?
It's Ichiro and Saho.
[siren wailing]
TOKYO FIRE DEPARTMENT
[paramedic] I'm opening it.
You first, sir.
-Careful.
-Sir, please come this way.
-[paramedic 1] On three.
-[paramedics] One, two, three.
-[paramedic 1] Okay.
-All right.
-Take her in.
-Are you okay? We're moving you.
Can you hear me?
You'll be fine now.
You're at the hospital.
Please watch your step.
[rhythmic beeping]
[doctor] I'll go back now.
How is she?
Well,
she hasn't regained consciousness yet
but she is not in a coma.
We stopped her bleeding,
and she is stable.
For now, she's doing fine.
However, since it is a head injury,
we will need to keep a close watch on
her tests and vitals for the time being.
Are you her family?
We're her in-laws.
I see.
I don't think there is anything
you can do right now.
It will be good to stay
by her side tonight.
Please excuse me.
Thank you very much.
[doctor] Don't mention it.
Take care.
Doctor, the police are here to see you.
-[doctor sighs]
-I know you're busy,
but I'd like to speak with you
about your patient.
[doctor] Sure. Let's talk over there.
[Ogami] What did you say to the police?
[Ichiro] I said it was an accident.
It's all my fault.
You took your wife's kindness for granted.
He said Saho will be fine.
Thank goodness.
We were lucky.
I'm sorry.
It really was an accident.
I'll contact everyone
and tell them she had an accident,
but she's doing fine.
That is not necessary.
You really don't change, do you?
We will keep this between us.
We are a family.
We shouldn't keep secrets from each other.
There will always be secrets
between family.
[phone ringing, buzzing]
NAMI
[ringing, buzzing continues]
[pop-jazz playing]
Thank you for having us over.
It's my pleasure.
Plus I got to meet your boyfriend.
It's really hard to make good friends
working in this industry.
This is the first time Sheena's
given a newbie so much attention.
That's because she's so talented.
I can tell.
Koji.
Let me tell you.
Your girlfriend is a true genius.
Thank you.
But how did the two of you meet?
Well,
it was at a boring business party.
I don't really know why Risako was there.
But I couldn't take my eyes off of her.
So you made the first move?
No. She approached me first.
I felt something special from him.
It's hard to put into words.
What about you two?
-[chuckles]
-[giggles]
Sorry. He's not familiar with
the music business so he didn't know.
It's refreshing. I like it.
So there was someone who hasn't been
poisoned by the gossip rags.
I apologize if my question was rude.
[Sheena] Not at all.
No need for apologies.
It's all in the past.
Have some more, Koji.
Ken was a married man.
I met Sheena
when my marriage was falling apart.
[Sheena sighs]
To put it simply,
he had a disgustingly messy divorce.
Talking about it like this
makes it seem like
it was such a long time ago.
I'm sorry I didn't know.
Not at all.
I'm happily in love with Sheena now.
Still, I'm so sorry.
He doesn't know anything
about show business.
[whispers] That's why I apologized.
More importantly…
who would like more wine?
It's a Château Haut-Brion.
From the 2009 vintage.
To a shining future
and a happy ending.
Cheers.
[all] Cheers.
[Koji] It's an honor to meet you both.
Same here.
Why does it matter?
The two of them didn't seem to care.
You knew about the huge scandal
with Ken and his ex-wife, didn't you?
I didn't know the other woman was Sheena.
Yeah, right. That's no excuse.
I'm sorry.
Didn't you do it on purpose?
Of course not.
I don't know why, but you wanted to
make them feel bad.
Why would I?
Because you felt inferior?
What?
Inferior to them? 'Cause they are famous?
Is there any other reason?
Because I don't want you
to turn out like them!
Stop being so jealous. It's so stupid.
-Excuse me.
-[driver] Yes?
Stop the car here. I'm getting off.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
KOUSEI CHUO HOSPITAL
JR YAMANOTE LINE
[yelps, grunting]
[Mashima] Hey!
[hostess continues coughing, gasping]
[coughing, gasping]
Are you okay?
[stammers, sobbing]
Sorry.
Yes.
This monetary easing measure, well,
will increase jobs and raise wages,
creating a "schmooze" path
for Japan's economic growth.
Thank you all for today.
What about the Global Bill?
I need to review it some more.
It's doubtful whether
it really is beneficial for our nation.
-Are you changing your stance?
-No comment.
Will you oppose the prime minister?
No comment.
-Please say something.
-No comment.
Please.
I know you're trying to get me
to say a few words.
But it won't work. [chuckles]
Do you remember Kaori?
The hostess.
The girl who was really into you.
Welcome to our bar. How are you?
Good. I'd be surprised
if you didn't remember her.
-What about her?
-Did you sleep with her?
What? Of course not.
Be honest. No need to be embarrassed.
It's the truth.
But it's not like
the opportunity didn't come up.
Do you remember she had
a peacock tattoo on her back?
Yeah.
And Tetsu?
Wasn't he Kaori's friend?
The one making money online.
Yeah. A yakuza who allegedly
makes his money online.
He's really obsessed with tattoos.
What are you trying to say?
Listen to the end.
Tetsu's been investing
in Bitcoin since the beginning.
He was also giving them out
to the hostesses like candy.
And his favorite girl was Kaori.
Okay.
I heard that he tattooed
his Bitcoin password onto Kaori.
[chuckles]
Is that true?
I don't get why he would tattoo
his password onto a hostess.
There's no special reason. He was drunk.
Apparently he has
1,000 Bitcoins in that account.
It was only worth 300,000 yen at the time,
but today, a single Bitcoin is
worth over 1.5 million.
1.5 million times 1,000 is…
-1.5 billion yen.
-[scoffs]
Kaori has no idea she has
a tattoo worth 1.5 billion on her body.
So?
Why don't you go find and copy
that password from her body?
That's crazy.
Don't you need money? So do I.
-That's a crime.
-She doesn't even know she has it.
If I steal the password and take
his money, what will that yakuza do?
It's a crypto asset. No one will find out.
You just need the password.
[sighs]
How will we split it?
It seems Mr. Maruyama
will side with Mr. Saijo.
What will you do?
[Ogami] It is now our turn to make a move.
INNOVATION - SHIORI WATANABE
[Watanabe] Yes.
All right.
I understand.
PRIME MINISTER
SHIORI WATANABE
The Bill will fail if Maruyama's faction
votes against it.
And I will go down with it.
That's right.
We cannot afford to lose.
How much do you trust Mr. Ogami?
He has my complete trust.
Why do you ask?
He won't betray me.
But is he as powerful now
as he was in the past?
His former strength?
Yes. He's too pure-hearted.
There is no one
who believes in this country
as much as he does.
And that is Mr. Ogami's weakness?
I'm not sure.
But his end will come one day.
Isn't that right?
[Takeuchi] The prime minister is furious.
The man you promised to convince,
Maruyama,
has switched sides.
And the situation has become
something we never expected.
It is not over yet.
I can make Mr. Maruyama change his mind.
Are you sure?
He is a man
who easily flipped his position
after once giving his support to the Bill.
We can simply give his arm a twist.
[Takeuchi] However,
he already made a public declaration.
Even if it's Maruyama,
he can't reverse his position again.
No.
It is not impossible.
TAKING RESPONSIBILITY AND ACTION
FOR THE FUTURE OF JAPAN
CASH BOOK
DINNER - HIROSHI KIMURA
(GIFT CERTIFICATE) - 100,000 YEN
GIFT CERTIFICATE
100,000 YEN
JCIAA
-Sorry.
-Check on that.
Got it.
[grunts]
Where were you?
We have a ton of work to do.
Sorry. There was a family issue.
I'm sorry for not informing you first.
It will take you a lot of time
to go through all these applications.
Finish them by the deadline.
Okay. Even if I have to do overtime,
I'll get it all done.
I'm counting on you.
Is everything okay?
Yes. Why?
Nothing.
You just seem a little different.
I took photos and retrieved one
of the gift certificate booklets.
I have yet to look into the others.
All right.
The real names of businesses
and public officials were in the ledger.
Surely you can get
a few of them to testify.
I have everything we need.
Good.
However, that hostess, Miki.
As of last month, her credit card debt is
thirteen million yen.
It seems she met a man
at the club she works at
who told her how to make extra money
by filming Mr. Maruyama for blackmail.
Who was it?
She
doesn't know.
[staff member] I will delete
the questionable posts.
And give suggestions for future posts.
Like frequently reacting to
current news, and books
and products released
by other celebrities.
We'll mix posts about your work
and your private life
to increase your viewer
and follower count.
Your opinion on the posts will
always be respected.
It may be annoying, but in the end,
it's the easiest and safest method.
Trust me.
You'll be trolled
if you do it on your own.
Just hold on.
You told me to stop posting.
Now you're telling me to post more?
I'm saying the risks are too high
when you post on your own.
Your official social media account
will be managed by the company.
Then how do I stay in touch
with my friends?
Like normal.
However, you'll need to
go through us first.
They might take a screenshot of it.
My friends won't do that.
Never forget there are people
who will do anything for money.
From now on,
don't recklessly post about
where you've been or what you ate.
Are you still dating that guy?
-Yes.
-Break up. Don't make me say it twice.
Hey. You only get one shot
at becoming a star.
Remember, we're all in this together.
Bear with it.
Don't you want to be a star?
Yes.
[in English] You mentioned the other day
that you've got people
who can protect you.
What do you mean by that?
[sighs]
[in Japanese] Can we sit there?
Go ahead.
-Welcome.
-[in English] Thank you.
Sarah, there are things in this country
that are not open.
Everything from the outside looks nice,
polite and orderly, but--
that's not what really happens here.
Okay, would you like to share?
[grunts]
Trust is earned, Ryu.
[waiter, in Japanese] I'll be back
to take your order.
A coffee and black tea, please.
[waiter] Coming right up.
[in English] You need to
play straight with me.
Family is
very strong. Powerful.
This is the moment where you tell me
your family is yakuza, right?
No.
My father, he's…
He's what we Japanese call a kuromaku.
He's the power behind the power.
They stay hidden from the spotlight.
Very few things happen in Japan without
the approval of these power brokers.
It's been like this for centuries.
No one ever talks about
what my father does,
not even his family.
But the prime minister showed up
at his birthday party.
That says everything you need to know.
And you?
I'm just someone who's trying to
figure things out.
And you need to be careful.
You're a journalist. And my father is
at odds with the media.
Especially the foreign media.
[keyboard plays]
[sighs]
DON'T BE RUDE TO SHEENA
I KNOW I KNOW
STILL ANGRY?
I WANT TO SEE YOU
I'M RIGHT OUTSIDE
[door opens, keys rattle]
I'm sorry.
♪ In this world, in this time ♪
♪ So full of ugly little lies ♪
♪ I fell in love with you ♪
♪ Only these feelings of mine are true ♪
-Let's stop here.
-[audio engineer] Okay.
That was really good.
Try singing it while expressing
how you feel right now.
-Okay.
-[Ken] Okay, let's try it.
♪ In this world, in this time ♪
♪ So full of ugly little lies ♪
♪ I fell in love with you ♪
♪ Only these feelings of mine are true ♪
Okay.
[in English] Fantastic!
It's getting better.
[in Japanese] Thank you.
[Ken] Let's take a break.
Sure.
-All right.
-That part earlier…
Thank you.
This part.
-Can we talk?
-Sure.
Okay?
I'm sorry for what happened last time.
Still thinking about it?
Anyway, he seems like a good person.
[Risako] He is.
But it was wrong of him to bring that up
and make everyone feel bad.
You get used to things like that
when you become famous.
It comes with the job.
You will too, one day.
Okay.
You'll be fine, Risako.
Anyway,
there's a party with
a lot of VIP guests next Tuesday.
I'm thinking of having you sing there.
What do you think?
Of course I will do it.
-If you think I should.
-Okay.
There will be a lot of big shots there.
I'm really excited about it.
Let's debut Aurora at that party.
Okay.
I'm so happy.
[staff member] Ken, you have a minute?
Coming.
-Then we'll do it.
-Yeah.
DINNER - HIROSHI KIMURA
GIFT CERTIFICATE - 100,000 YEN
I convinced a few people
to testify about his vote buying.
They will say Hiroshi Maruyama
and his brother bought his votes
by giving bribes.
-The police do not know of this yet?
-Right.
I told the witnesses to stay quiet
until we give the signal,
or else…
Good.
What is our next move?
A talk with Masashi Maruyama.
JCIAA
RYUOGAMI - LOG-IN
ERROR
EXCESSIVE LOG IN ATTEMPTS
What?
-Mayu.
-Yes?
Can I ask you a favor?
What is it? Anything I can help with?
I got locked out of my account.
That's a problem.
I want to print out a few reports,
can you do it for me?
Sure, which ones?
An application status report.
Okay.
Can you come over here?
JCIAA
MAYUSHIMIZU
LOG IN
CLIENTS - APPLICATION STATUS MENU
APPLICATION STATUS MENU
Which one?
Let's see.
I want the report
on rejected applications.
I'd like to confirm
why they were rejected.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Thank you. You're a big help.
JCIAA
MAYUSHIMIZU
LOG IN
LEDGER
ORGANIZATION - DONATION - DEPOSIT
FIVE WINDS CORPORATION
540,331,861 YEN
[Younger Ryu]
I'm going to fight you! Get ready!
Do you think you can defeat
the Five Winds?
[Ryu] Then tell me about Manabu.
He got
involved with a brawl and died.
However, traces of drugs were
found in his system.
Translated by Annie Chen