[heavy breathing, whimpering]
[thumping]
[groans]
-[grunting]
-[glass cracking]
[groans]
[interrogator]
Masashi Maruyama, state your occupation.
Did I do anything wrong?
The music at your party was too loud.
Complaints were made.
All that fuss just for that?
You made it seem like
I murdered somebody or something.
We were only doing our job.
Once again, Mr. Maruyama.
What is your occupation?
CEO of Maruyama Construction Corporation.
Your place and date of birth?
I was born in Fukui.
October 2, 1967.
How many employees do you have?
About 200.
Who did you attend the party with?
My friends and clients.
Why would a reputable man like yourself
party with young women so late at night?
They are all hostesses.
I was trying to show
my friends a good time.
I see.
What exactly are my charges?
Help me understand.
What do you want?
I wonder if it's true
that everyone was having fun?
Was there anything…
unusual at the party?
[phone ringing]
[assistant] It didn't run in today's news.
The reporters are also staying quiet
about Mr. Maruyama's brother.
I see.
Who called the police?
[Ogami] It was not a coincidence.
Arresting his brother is
a trap for Mr. Maruyama.
Do you think it was Mr. Saijo?
We don't know yet.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Yes, sir.
There's one more thing you should know.
Max Murata is becoming a problem.
He's been rehashing
the Takeuchi son's case,
posting online that it was a setup.
No one will pay him any attention.
It seems he's been in contact
with a foreign reporter.
Look into it.
Yes, sir.
MASAHIRO KAGEYAMA
ACCOUNT BALANCE
-2,923,222 YEN
I have no idea what's going on.
Do you need money?
Then what's wrong?
[Yumiko] Masahiro keeps saying
everything is okay whenever I ask.
But I need to do something.
[Kyoko] The times have sure changed.
Meaning?
In the old days,
it was unheard of
for women to walk ahead of men.
My father was so scary,
I couldn't even go near him.
Japanese women were expected
to only serve tea.
But not anymore.
[chuckles] You've never made
a pot of tea in your life.
But I've never taken a sip
before your father did.
The world has changed.
Men are not like that anymore,
and neither are women.
Do you understand my words?
Sort of.
Both you and Ryu were such smart children.
And you were much better than Ryu
at handling yourself.
Your father and I thought
you were a genius.
Especially at math.
That was when I was young.
You're still quite young.
You need my help for the holidays?
Yes.
The shop's gotten so busy these days.
So I'd really appreciate it
if you could help me out.
Can you start this afternoon?
If you're fine with me, then okay.
Really?
But will your husband mind you working?
Not at all.
In fact, he's supportive of me working.
Then I'll see you this afternoon.
Yeah, I'll be waiting.
[Ichiro] Where should I start?
Have we been seeing
each other for a year already?
Six months.
It's been six months?
Oh, okay.
Would you like more mineral water?
We also have sparkling water.
Mineral is fine.
These six months have been my happiest.
I mean it.
Thanks.
[sighs]
I love you. And I always will.
But this is where you say the usual
"I can't leave my wife" line, right?
No. She's not the reason why.
Then what is?
My responsibility to my family,
to the Ogami name.
Right.
Nami, forgive me.
Sure.
Goodbye.
Wait. Let's talk, okay?
Talk? About what?
Do you have more to say?
I do!
Please, I beg you.
You've already told me your answer.
I don't want to hurt you.
-You made your decision. So I will too.
-What?
How I'll live my life without you.
No, wait a minute.
Don't say that. We can meet up anytime.
As friends.
Why do I need to be friends with you?
I'm sorry.
Are you an idiot?
Nami.
[Maruyama] Why are you telling me this?
[Saijo] Your brother is
one of the four in police custody.
[Maruyama]
He was only partying with some hostesses.
But four smart, seasoned men
got out of control drinking
with young hostesses
and got themselves into quite the mess.
Apparently, they were more wild
than anyone imagined.
What of it? It's his life.
I'll do what I can as his brother.
Go ahead.
But of course
he should be tried for his crimes
if he spent his days breaking the law.
A very admirable stance.
-It was like a speech for the Diet.
-[laughs]
What are you saying?
I only want to get to the truth.
The truth is always beneficial
to the country.
It is my brother's problem. Not mine.
Unfortunately, it is yours.
Your brother, your family,
they are all tied to you.
What would they find
if there was a full investigation?
I am innocent.
I am privy to a lot of information.
Because I have faith in you,
we should hold each other's hands.
As politicians.
And as good friends.
TEITO SECURITIES FRAUD
ALL OKURA DOCUMENTS OBTAINED
PROOF OF
TAKASHI NAGASAKI'S GUILT
CORRUPTION FRAMEWORK
[projector clicking]
Say something if you're coming up.
Ichiro will come back to you eventually.
You think so? I don't think he will.
He's a very weak-minded man.
Keep your distance for now.
But he doesn't tell lies.
It's the same for you, right?
Are you all right?
Absolutely.
I'm going to get on with my life
with someone else.
I'll leave that up to you.
MINISTER MARUYAMA ASLEEP
OPPOSITION DEMANDS PUNISHMENT
The opposition party has filed a motion
demanding disciplinary action against
Minister Hiroshi Maruyama
for attending the recent debate
on Prime Minister Watanabe's Global Bill
while hungover,
causing him to snore and fall asleep.
Even more are questioning
Prime Minister Watanabe's leadership
as her approval ratings have dropped
to a new low.
They dare to criticize my leadership
by playing the video of Maruyama snoring
all over the news?
PRIME MINISTER
SHIORI WATANABE
They need to stop taking me for a fool.
Exactly as you said.
I agree.
Why was Maruyama's brother arrested?
I've only just heard about it.
I don't have any details yet.
I also. I'm just as clueless.
This is no time for games!
They could dig up
all kinds of dirt on him.
Since the press is having a field day
with Maruyama's snoring,
I assume his brother's arrest
hasn't been leaked yet?
-Yes.
-I believe so.
Don't you dare use this incident
to attack each other
to gain a political advantage.
-Do you understand?
-Of course.
Yes.
That is all.
Get me Maruyama right away.
I promise that
it will never happen again, Prime--
[clears throat]
-[door opens]
-It's me.
[door closes]
I apologize for this incident,
Prime Minister.
[inhales sharply]
I promise that it will never happen again.
The camera happened to be on me
when I was nodding off for only a moment.
-I'm very sorry--
-That's enough.
That's not why I asked for you.
I see.
What kind of mess
did your brother get himself into?
Even I'm not sure.
Have you spoken with him?
Yes. He said he didn't do anything wrong.
Has anyone reached out to you?
No.
Come over here.
Look me straight in the eye.
Can you swear you and your brother
have done nothing wrong?
Yes, of course.
I mean, yes for myself.
But truthfully,
I don't know what my brother has done
or what he's involved in.
So you're saying you're innocent?
I've done nothing to be guilty of.
All right. I'll trust what you say.
[Maruyama sighs]
Well, can you--
I mean, is it possible
to put a stop to the police investigation?
It's true what they say.
You really are stupid.
Forget I asked. I was a bit flustered.
The debate on the Global Bill
will continue.
It will soon be your turn
to state your position.
Yes.
You'll be supporting the bill. Right?
Well…
Make your decision.
I will. I'll support you.
-Thank you for your purchase.
-[customer] Thank you.
-Please come again.
-Thank you.
[assistant] Thank you.
[customer 2] Excuse me,
can I get some help?
Sure. Yumiko, can you?
Okay, I'll be right over.
Thank you for waiting.
-[customer 2 chuckles]
-Oh, hasn't it been a while?
You're right. It's been so long.
-Have you been well?
-Yes. And you, Yuki?
Same as well, thank you.
Thank you for always helping my husband
with his work.
[chuckles] No, it's not a problem.
He's such a workaholic.
It's all he thinks about.
But he has made it this far thanks to you.
[chuckles] Thanks.
Which one did you want?
Let's see. How much is this one?
This is…
Do you work here?
Yes, but only part-time.
I'm helping my friend with her shop.
It's quite refreshing
to get out of the house.
That's true.
And how is he?
Is Masahiro doing fine?
Of course he is.
I'll tell him we ran into each other.
I'm glad to hear that.
-Is this okay?
-Yes.
Are these to congratulate someone?
I believed Masahiro would get
back on his feet in no time.
Did he already find a new job?
A new job?
The flowers are for
Masahiro's replacement, my new manager.
It's been six months since he quit, right?
[gasps]
Yes.
Time sure flies.
He's taking some time off
before looking for a new job.
I'm glad to hear that.
He was so kind, the best manager I've had.
I really miss working with him.
He was really sorry about it too.
How is it?
Really good.
I want to spend more time with you.
-And you?
-What's going on?
I finally realized something.
In order to do great work,
first, I need to be a great son.
And a good husband.
And one day, a good father.
Having a wonderful wife…
will make it all possible.
Let's go to your favorite
sushi place in Ginza.
And take a trip to the hot springs.
Come here.
I also want you to know more
about my new restaurant.
-Right now, I'm--
-[gasps] Sorry!
What's gotten into you?
[sighs]
I want to make up for my past.
I want
to rekindle our relationship
as husband and wife.
Something doesn't feel right.
This isn't like you.
[sighs]
What's so strange about it?
-[moaning]
-[panting]
[moans]
[moaning continues]
-Cheers.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Looks like you're investing
a lot into that Risako girl.
She's got a good voice.
She'll be a star in no time
with a few of my songs.
Well, I haven't had any hits for ages.
Let's not go there right now.
I remember you said
the same thing about me.
You said my voice was the best.
That you'd make me a star.
And you did.
You became a great star. You still are.
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
Put your hand right here.
Spread your fingers.
Don't you trust me?
[chuckles] My hand moved on its own.
[both chuckle]
Do you trust me?
Stop it. This is dangerous.
Shee.
[chuckling]
[laughing]
[gasps]
[panting]
[Sheena sighs]
I trust you.
-[mover 1] Ready?
-[mover 2] On three.
[movers] One, two, three.
[chattering]
[mover 2] I got it. Okay.
[all] Heave ho.
-[mover 3] Here's the next one.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
-Here you go.
-Hi.
-[mover 4] Hello.
[water dripping]
[chattering]
[worker 1] Can you hold that side?
[worker 2] Okay.
-[worker 3] This side is okay.
-[worker 4] Thanks.
You. What's all this?
Sir.
We found a leak.
In the first place, this building was
already full of structural issues.
[Ichiro sighs]
Now wait a minute.
What does this mean?
We won't make the opening date.
And this is a bit difficult to say,
but there will be additional costs.
We're on a tight budget.
How much will it be?
I can't say for sure yet.
[sighs]
Okay.
I understand.
Please fix it right away.
I'll cover the cost somehow.
But we're already over budget.
It's fine.
I'll get the money.
-[clicks tongue]
-[water splashes]
[phone buzzes]
TAKA - HE'S GOING OUT FOR SUSHI
TOMORROW AT 7:30 P.M.
AT THE USUAL SUSHIDOKORO ABE
SHIGEO
I MISS MY NAMI
WANT TO HAVE DINNER WITH ME?
SUSHI
SUSHIDOKORO ABE
READ
[lock beeps]
[sighs]
-I'm home.
-Welcome back.
The kids? Are they asleep?
How was work?
The same as always.
What's for dinner?
That's right.
I ran into Yuki at the flower shop.
Oh, I see.
When were you planning
to tell me the truth?
I didn't want to make you
and the kids worry.
Who shamelessly told his son not to lie?
[sighs]
♪ With each new piece of you I find ♪
♪ I see a brand new heart of mine ♪
♪ Embracing me, the aurora ♪
♪ Changes colors as it shines in the sky ♪
[music stops]
That was good.
Let's take a ten minute break.
-[staff] Okay.
-Sure.
-Good singing.
-Thank you.
-[staff 2] Great job.
-[staff 3] Good work.
What's up?
Nothing.
You were really good.
Well, you know,
since we're on break, would it be okay if…
Yeah?
…you could listen to a song I wrote?
Sure. I've got time.
-Give her a fresh tape.
-Thank you.
[Watanabe]
This bill is the future of Japan.
-[minister 1] What future?
-[minister 2] Yeah.
[Watanabe] It will remove the barriers
limiting this country.
We need more open policies
regarding immigration
and free trade with other nations.
-[minister 3] That's empty talk.
-[minister 4] Exactly.
The economic policies of the
previous administration have failed us.
There's nothing more
the Bank of Japan can do.
We are now forced
to make a difficult decision.
I yield the floor.
-[minister 5] She's right!
-[minister 6] Nonsense!
[Speaker] Silence!
[clamoring]
I ask for your silence!
Parliamentary Vice-Minister of Health,
Labour and Welfare, Hiroshi Maruyama.
[applause slowly stops]
-[minister] Don't fall asleep.
-[ministers laugh]
The Prime Minister stated
this bill will help the farmers,
our agriculture,
and create a better future for this nation
while protecting its traditions.
The subsidy program will continue,
and we will enter
a new phase of prosperity.
I will…
-endorse the Prime Minister's plans.
-[minister] What?
-What are you saying?
-[detractors clamoring]
-[supporters applauding]
-[Maruyama] This bill will take Japan…
-[clamoring, applauding stops]
-…into a new future.
I am in full support of the Global Bill.
[minister] Just wait a second.
-[clamoring]
-[applauding]
[Speaker] Silence. Silence.
Silence. Please return to your seats.
[crying]
[panting]
DON'T MESS WITH THE FIELDS
YOU SCAMMERS
[person 1] Hey.
-Old man.
-[person 2] Old man.
[grunts]
[person 1] Watch out.
[pants]
You are all scammers.
A bunch of damned liars!
Damned liars!
-[gasps]
-[people scream]
-Make way!
-[clamoring]
-Let's calm down.
-Stop!
[clamoring]
-[protester] Swindlers.
-[officer] Stay back.
-You jerks are all scammers!
-[screaming]
-Swindlers!
-[officer] Out of the way.
-[protester] Scammers!
-[officer] Quickly!
-[officer] Calm down.
-[people screaming]
[protester shrieks]
Scammers. You swindlers!
[grunts]
Let me go.
[pants] Let me go!
[sirens wailing in distance]
[sighs]
[music starts playing]
♪ You know sometimes
I wish you'd scream at me ♪
♪ Have a fit
And throw your clothes on me ♪
♪ Be inconsiderate and ignore me ♪
♪ Or just laugh along and smile with me ♪
♪ Show me your face so I can read better ♪
♪ And know exactly
What you're thinking yeah ♪
♪ Cause I'm exhausted
Trying to impress you ♪
♪ Even though I know I don't have to ♪
[In English] ♪ Baby ♪
[in Japanese] ♪ Every little thing
I do is just for you ♪
[in English]
♪ I wanna see you rise, yeah ♪
[in Japanese]
♪ So open up your eyes, yeah ♪
[in English] ♪ And baby ♪
[in Japanese] ♪ I hope it makes me
Want you more than yesterday ♪
♪ So tell me do you like, yeah ♪
♪ Can't read between the lines, yeah ♪
[in English] ♪ I wanna get a rise ♪
[in Japanese]
♪ Do you know how much I put down on ♪
♪ That piece of lingerie I wore ♪
♪ Don't want a smile,
I want you on your knees ♪
♪ Letting me know how you feel so lucky ♪
♪ I know sometimes
It's hard to keep focus ♪
♪ Don't want you leaving me
With no notice ♪
♪ So I overcompensate for it ♪
♪ Give me a little more to work with ♪
[in English] ♪ Yeah, baby ♪
[in Japanese] ♪ Every little thing
I do is just for you ♪
[in English]
♪ I wanna see you rise, yeah ♪
[in Japanese]
♪ So open up your eyes, yeah ♪
[in English] ♪ And baby ♪
[in Japanese] ♪ I hope it makes me
Want you more than yesterday ♪
♪ So tell me do you like, yeah ♪
♪ Can't read between the lines, yeah ♪
[in English] ♪ I wanna get a rise, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, rise ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ I wanna get a rise, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, rise ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ I wanna get a rise, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, rise ♪
♪ Yeah, rise ♪
♪ I wanna get a rise ♪
Translated by Annie Chen