Welcome to our bar.
How are you?
Why?
Was there a reason you had to do that?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why did you lie to me?
ONE YEAR AGO
[laughing] Drink whatever you like.
Thank you.
The way to make even more money is to
go all in if there's a chance
to make a fortune.
Then you want cryptocurrency.
-Bitcoin?
-Yes.
Your money will double in a week.
But it's too risky.
It's the same as investing in stocks.
Except you can make a ton in no time
because of the extreme price fluctuations.
And lose a ton in an instant.
But you can hedge the risks, right?
No, our company doesn't deal with crypto.
Isn't it possible if you do it externally?
Externally?
Bitcoin just passed $5,000.
How much do you think I just made?
500 million?
It'll keep going up, you know.
500 million isn't enough?
Look, all this is someone else's money.
Shouldn't you start
making some for yourself?
[laughs] So I should bet my own money?
You're in currency trading
at a trading company.
I sit in the deal room of a mega bank.
I'll make an account
for the payouts at the bank.
And use that money to
invest in crypto assets.
No one will find out
if you put the principal back.
But isn't that…
Illegal?
Isn't it?
No one will know if you return the money.
That's skirting the law.
[associate] It fell 50% this week.
Yeah.
What do you want to do?
It'll go up again.
[associate] It's at $6,000 now.
It'll go up to $20,000.
It'll be fine if I double the bid.
How do you know it will increase?
Because that's my job.
[reporter] After Bitcoin reached
a record high of $19,783 a year ago,
data from Coin Research released today
shows that crypto assets have…
BITCOIN TAKES A DIVE
…fallen 37% this month.
This is its biggest crash since
prices fell 39% in August 2011.
We won't press charges
if you resign immediately.
I'd take this deal if I were you.
Since I wouldn't want to go to jail.
Please forgive me!
[Yumiko] Why did you lie to me?
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to hurt you.
Or make you worry.
Don't worry.
I'll make the money back.
[phone vibrates]
[singing, in English]
♪ I wanna get a rise, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, rise ♪
♪ Yeah, rise ♪
♪ I wanna get a rise ♪
[in Japanese] That was good.
For your first song.
Thank you.
Okay, let's resume recording.
-Once more from the top.
-Okay.
-Got it.
That was the best song I've heard
from this studio in the last ten years.
Why won't you make
these kinds of songs for me?
What do you mean?
You haven't written
a hit song for me in years.
That was something Risako wrote.
I see.
I get it.
It's not my place to interfere,
but you should let her sing her own song.
Eventually.
We need to make her famous first.
And what did she say?
Do you want to be famous?
Or a true artist?
It's okay.
Tell me what you really want.
Can't I wish
to be both?
[laughs]
You're so young.
You'll find out one day,
but that's impossible in this industry.
You can only choose one.
Sorry I'm late.
Something unbelievable happened.
You made me wait 30 minutes.
That's what I find unbelievable.
Sorry.
Sheena came to the studio
while I was recording.
-The singer?
-Yeah.
That Sheena.
And?
She heard my song.
She told me it was really good.
[sighing] Okay.
Aren't you happy for me?
[sighs]
Be careful of anyone in show business.
Even Sheena. You don't know
how vicious she could be.
She seems like a good person to me.
She said she'd help me.
That she'd give me a hand.
Why would she take on that responsibility?
Because she said I have talent.
And you really believe her?
Is it weird?
I'm not sure.
But it's suspicious.
What did the producer say?
He liked my song too.
Stay focused on what you need to do.
Don't get carried away like a kid.
[Ogami] I see.
[assistant] The police aren't saying
anything about Masashi Maruyama.
One of the hostesses at the party is
accusing him of sexual assault.
That's all they'll say.
There are too many
overlapping coincidences.
If the police raided the place, then…
Was it really Sosuke Saijo?
No.
Mr. Saijo is probably
still investigating the details.
However, he will certainly
use this incident to his advantage.
Should I have a chat
with Hiroshi Maruyama?
No, let's wait a little longer.
We'll make our move
only when Mr. Saijo approaches
Hiroshi Maruyama again.
And right now?
Masashi Maruyama and that hostess.
I want their information.
Understood.
And I looked into
that American journalist.
Yeah.
She hasn't been in Japan for very long.
She's in the API's Asia bureau.
Do we have contacts with that news agency?
Yes.
But it's not a very good one.
All right.
There is a problem.
What is it?
It appears she and Ryu are dating.
Oh, I see.
Has Ryu said anything?
No, he hasn't.
API is still investigating
Manabu Takeuchi's death.
Keep your eyes on that reporter.
I will.
What will you do about Ryu?
I'll speak with him.
IN PAYMENT
-Thank you.
How many years?
Since we've been out together?
[chuckles]
[Chef] Welcome.
Long time no see, Chef.
-Long time no see.
-Well.
[server] Hello, welcome.
Do you want to order sake?
Are you listening?
Oh, yeah.
What would you like?
[stammers] Champagne.
Certainly.
[Shigeo, Nami laughing]
Oh, dear.
Where's your wine?
-Hi, excuse me.
-Yes?
Since it's wine o'clock,
can I get a glass?
A glass of wine?
The most expensive one you have.
Only the best of the best for
my beautiful girlfriend.
I'll bring it right out.
I'm sorry. You can just ignore his jokes.
What do you mean?
Is that how you tease little ole me?
I was just joking around.
So when did I become your girlfriend?
You will soon.
It's just a matter of time.
-Cheers.
[indistinct dialogue]
[Nami] No way!
[Nami laughs]
[Saho] I met your mother the other day.
She said you've turned over a new leaf.
-A lady.
-A lady? Oh, that's you.
-Are you listening to me?
-[Shigeo, Nami chattering, laughing]
Sorry. I'm listening.
What are you looking at?
It's nothing. I'm sorry.
Those people are so loud.
I wish they'd tone it down.
And look at that man.
Flirting with someone
much younger than him.
How embarrassing.
Yeah.
Right?
Can we go?
But your wine o'clock isn't here yet.
I'm not feeling very good.
Can we cancel the wine?
I'm so full.
Of course.
I want to go somewhere else.
Sure.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Please cancel the wine.
She's not feeling well. Sorry about that.
Was it not to your taste?
No, the sushi was very good.
Thank you.
-It wasn't a big deal.
-Thank you.
-You're right.
-Hey.
Have we met before?
I think you're mistaken.
[Shigeo]
I've definitely seen you somewhere.
I don't remember meeting you.
Sorry. Let's go.
-I don't feel good.
-Right, let's go.
My apologies. Looks like I was wrong.
Enjoy your meal.
[footsteps depart]
Someone you know?
Didn't he say it was a mistake?
Sounds like you're avoiding the question.
Of course not.
Let's order. Excuse me.
Yes?
What's wrong?
It's probably the stress
from working too much.
I can't do it.
You look tired. Let's go to sleep early.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'll go take a shower.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
[phone vibrates]
MONDAY MARCH 6 - NAMI
UNREAD MESSAGES BELOW
I STILL HAVE THESE AT MY PLACE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO WITH THEM?
[sighs]
You never show your face
around here anymore.
I missed you.
I've gotten older.
Everyone ages just as equally.
That is not an excuse.
I have a favor to ask of you.
What a pretty girl.
Who is it?
Ichiro's mistress.
Ichiro hasn't changed one bit.
Did he get himself into trouble?
Ichiro is trouble itself.
[laughs]
He's carrying a burden
that is too heavy for his shoulders.
He's carrying a great responsibility.
However, he doesn't realize it himself.
Enjoy.
If only he could just live
within his capabilities.
I'll look into this girl for you.
[colleague]
I'll head over there before going home.
-I'll go first.
-Bye.
-Good night.
Hello, good work today.
My name is Mayu Shimizu.
Nice to meet you, Mayu.
Are you going home?
Yes.
Which department are you in?
Accounting.
I'll give you a ride.
I hear you're dating someone
from a news agency.
Why didn't you tell me?
You had me followed.
I was watching over you.
Since I'm your father.
Normally, I wouldn't stop you.
But she's a reporter.
What do you want me to do?
Think about why she approached you.
You really don't trust anybody.
I choose who to place my trust in.
You should do the same.
I'll make my own decisions
about who I see.
Are you sure you're not misjudging people?
What about you?
Are you someone who can be trusted?
I don't hold any lies
in my heart.
Then tell me.
What?
About Manabu.
You don't trust me?
He got involved in a brawl and died.
However, traces of drugs were
found in his system.
The forces hostile to
Secretary-General Takeuchi
tried to leak it to the press.
I rewrote the truth.
There was no reason to
bring down the Secretary-General
and destroy his career.
What happened to the man who was
suspected of killing Manabu?
What needed to be done was done.
I…
do not trust this country's…
or your justice.
Here he is.
And how much more additional funds
will you be needing?
100 million.
[sighs loudly, sucks teeth]
We'll need another collateral
for the additional loan.
This is a high-risk investment for us.
The restaurant is
guaranteed to be a success.
There is no doubt about it.
Doubts can be beneficial for oneself.
I don't need something like that.
A bold attitude is
what's important in doing business.
How about using your home
as collateral for the sum of your loan?
My home?
Do you have anything else to use
as collateral?
No.
Since it is a large amount…
Oh, my.
Your face is telling me
you are doubting yourself.
Of course, I'm not.
Okay, let's do it.
Okay. We'll draw up the contract.
Please prepare everything
impeccably for Mr. Ogami.
-Yes, sir.
-Yes.
Thank you.
Our pleasure.
Ichiro.
Aren't we already the same as brothers?
[footsteps]
[Sarah, in English]
What are you thinking about?
Sorry. I've been a bit distracted.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Family issues?
Why would you ask that?
Well typically it's family, work,
relationships, or friends.
I said family figuring that there was
a 25% chance I'd be right.
I see.
[Sarah] Do you know why I came to Tokyo?
When I was, um, six,
my father left
my mom and I in rural Oregon.
He just got up and left.
No goodbye, no note. Nothing.
And then when my mom realized
what was going on, she was a mess.
I'm… I'm sorry.
I remember her laying
on the kitchen floor screaming,
"You fucking asshole."
"Son of bitch."
And I just went to my room,
I curled up in bed and I thought,
where is the furthest place
in the world I can escape to?
That was Japan.
That's why I'm here.
Why did you go to America?
[Ryu]
The Japanese don't confront you directly.
Instead, they whisper.
So eventually you hear them
from others and not from the source.
America was an escape
from the dark whispers circling my family.
So, um, how's work going? Better? I hope.
At the NPO?
Well, yeah,
unless you're doing some secret undercover
work you're not telling me about.
Well actually, there was something strange
that happened the other day.
What?
A farmer came in protesting,
but he was bloody,
like he'd been beaten up or something.
What was he protesting?
I didn't understand his complaint.
But farming is
a protected industry in Japan.
The government works with various
agricultural associations to protect them.
Do they have subsidies
from the government?
Yeah, they do.
Then why was he disgruntled?
That's what I couldn't figure out.
Well as they say,
where there's smoke, there's fire.
Yeah. Maybe.
We should look into this further.
But it will give me purpose,
and I need a story.
[in Japanese]
Is who he decides to date that concerning?
He might be in the right, you know.
She's a reporter.
And a foreigner.
And that's why you don't trust her?
That's not it.
You just don't like
the idea of them dating.
It's better to keep
a safe distance from her.
Your beliefs are outdated.
The times have changed
since we were young.
There are no annoying boundaries
in today's world.
It's still better to be safe.
Please leave Ryu alone.
He's young. And isn't he in love?
You need to let him go.
They are all adults now.
You can't protect them forever.
[driver] Thank you.
[driver] Thanks.
-Nami.
-Oh, my God!
What are you doing?
-I want to talk.
-There's nothing to say.
Please. I'm so lonely.
'Cause you can't have sex?
Because I miss you.
This talk is pointless.
Can't we start over?
-Let me go!
-I beg you!
Don't you already have someone at home?
[footsteps depart]
[hangers clattering]
[sniffs]
You really smell.
PAGE 4 - PAGE 3
[sighs]
[panting on laptop]
[person] Yes, what is it?
I got a really early Christmas present.
Translated by Annie Chen