[Mashima, in Japanese] I can go with you
if you need me.
It is just a visit to an old friend.
-All right.
-[engine starts]
I want to phone
Hiroshi and Masashi Maruyama today.
Please make the arrangements.
Understood.
Anything else?
Looks like it will rain.
How troublesome.
Please come again.
Thank you.
Sorry, can I take a break?
Yes, of course.
[gasps] Sorry.
Ms. Ogami?
It's Kageyama.
I changed my name when I got married.
It's nice to see you again, Mr. Nakamura.
We haven't met since you quit, right?
How are your children?
-They are well. Thank you for asking.
-[chuckles]
And your husband?
He's fine too.
Are you working here?
[sighs] Only for a little bit.
It's better than staying home all day.
I see.
You still look the same.
I'm glad you're doing well.
You too.
How is everyone at the office?
[chuckles]
Same as always.
But they are all doing well.
It was really tough after you quit.
You were the only one who could
keep the numbers organized.
[chuckling] That's all in the past.
Yeah.
Let's keep in touch.
Call me here at any time.
[sighs]
I'll be right back.
HARU NAKAMURA
MASASHI MARUYAMA
080-8049-938
Isn't it your job to fix it?
-But, sir-- [sighs]
-[phone rings]
[phone continues]
[phone beeps, stops]
Yes?
[Ogami] Is this Masashi Maruyama?
And you are?
Minister Maruyama's brother?
If this is a prank, I'm hanging up.
[Ogami] I will keep it short.
This is about your brother
and the charges against you.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
I'll go back to work.
And?
A hostess is accusing you of assault,
isn't she?
That is your personal indiscretion.
On the other hand, despite the difficult
circumstances of your company,
you have been spending money like water,
handing out lavish gifts wherever you go.
The recipients exchange your gifts
for cash and in return,
place their votes for your brother.
It is a scheme to maintain
your brother's power
and prevent your company
from falling into bankruptcy.
GIFT CERTIFICATE
Buying votes with bribes.
This is a serious crime
involving your brother.
Who the hell are you? That's all bullshit.
You already know
that this is the truth.
Which story should
be revealed to the public?
Either way,
your company will never survive.
Leaving you with
only a single problem.
Whether or not you can protect
your brother's reputation…
you will need to take the fall.
Are you
the Owl?
There is no such man.
What do you want from me?
It is very simple.
Confess to assaulting the hostess.
It won't be a heavy charge.
And we can keep your vote buying
between us.
Please give me some time.
No!
LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
Congratulations, Prime Minister.
[chuckles]
It's still too early.
I wonder how the Owl will react?
Who cares? It's no longer an era
where the government moves just because
he's scampering about.
You are unfortunate.
[Saho] Yes?
I apologize for not speaking with you
in person.
I'm not in Tokyo right now due to my work.
I completely understand.
But…
You will only continue to be unhappy
if you stay with Ichiro.
Why don't you go back to your parents'?
Wouldn't that be your best choice?
Have you told this to Ichiro?
I will call him after this.
In other words…
Divorce is the only answer.
I'm not sure. I need to think about this.
Sure.
I have added extra funds to your account.
It was just an accident.
Everything was kept private.
If anyone asks,
tell them you and your husband were
not a good match.
Will that do?
Yes.
[chuckles]
[in English] Are you sure it's here?
Not a place you would think
a chemical company would be headquartered.
So we're looking at it.
That's the registered address.
DESTINATION
FOR SALE
ASAHI BATHHOUSE
There are several companies that
keep coming up on NPO's accounting files.
One of the vendors
is a company called Five Winds.
So they're pre-vetted by the government?
Yes, as subcontractors.
And Five Winds?
They received almost 500 million yen
in one year.
500 million yen?
An NPO with that kind of money?
And next to the chemical company
the farmer talked about.
Thank you.
And there's more.
What do you mean?
It was also the name of the gang that
my childhood friend and I made up as kids.
Okay. So what?
The politician, Takeuchi,
his son was killed recently.
My family was close to theirs.
The son, Manabu,
we were childhood friends.
And I made up the name of the gang.
We called it Five Winds.
You think it's related?
That it's his company?
Maybe.
All right.
There's a lot of news around that.
He tried to break up a fight at a club.
Got killed in the brawl.
Then his killer committed suicide
while waiting for his trial.
And no one investigated?
No, nothing happened.
[Nakamura, in Japanese] Mrs. Kageyama.
Sorry.
I was just in the area.
Wait.
Please forget everything
that happened in the past.
I know.
It was my fault.
I've changed since then, you know.
I have a husband now.
I know that too.
When I said you can come back anytime,
of course it meant working here.
I mean it. If you want to,
I'll happily help you.
[sighs]
[Yumiko] Not yet.
Because of my children.
You were really good at your job.
-You didn't have to quit.
-No. I did.
Just to get married?
That's not how you felt.
[scoffs]
I was an idiot back then.
I need to go.
Think about it.
My husband will not like it
if I went back to my old company.
And if you'll be my manager again,
he'll hate it even more.
You're right.
I'll ask them to place you
in a different department.
Aren't you working part-time?
I can tell it's not just to pass the time.
It's temporary. Until my husband
gets back on his feet--
You should come back.
Japan's society has changed.
I'll cooperate in making it easier
for you to return to work.
[phone rings]
[phone buzzes]
[Maruyama] Yes, hello.
[Ogami] Mr. Maruyama.
Is this Mr. Ogami?
I won't take up much of your time.
Sure.
Are you alone?
[stammers] Please give me a moment.
Hello? Sorry for the wait.
I know
you and your brother are
buying votes.
I haven't done anything.
I have no clue what my brother is doing.
Listen carefully.
Yes.
I know everything.
I won't make
your vote buying public.
Your brother will plead guilty
to sexual assault.
And that will be the end of it.
And then?
You know very well
your faction has the prime minister's fate
in their hands.
So what do you want me to do?
Think about what benefits you.
Then act on it.
In other words,
side with Secretary-General Takeuchi.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Shin, let's clean up.
Yeah.
[Riko] Let's go play upstairs.
Okay.
I'm thinking of going back to work.
What do you think?
Only temporarily,
until things settle down.
Working in finance isn't as easy
as you think.
Shouldn't you be happy?
Well,
I'd be happy if it's just for you.
But I'm the one who is responsible
for this family.
What will I become if you start working?
You-- Then how much longer do you need?
A few days.
Everything will be resolved in a week.
Then I'll give you a week.
-[phone buzzes]
-[sighs]
Yeah.
So which company were you thinking about?
My old one.
[chuckles] You can't.
Why?
There was a reason you quit.
That's why you can't go back.
I quit because I was marrying you.
No.
Your boss was sexually harassing you.
How can you even bring that up now?
I'm going back to work for this family.
I said that
I'm responsible for this family!
[phone buzzes]
Another blunder from the Watanabe Cabinet.
Vice-Minister Hiroshi Maruyama is
receiving criticism once again
after mistakenly saying "schmooze path"
instead of "smooth path"
during a press conference last week.
He was already under fire
for falling asleep
during a parliamentary meeting, leading
many to question his qualifications.
VICE-MINISTER MARUYAMA'S
SCHMOOZE PATH
[door closes]
What do you think
of the current politicians?
We weren't like this
when we were in office.
Did I owe you any favors?
For you to come this far to see me.
I will have Saho divorce.
My daughter is not…
one of your chess pieces.
It is for her future.
The fault lies with my son, not Saho.
What happened?
My son is not good enough
for your daughter.
An affair?
A man will have one or two affairs.
Saho only needs to grin and bear it.
You are wrong.
She has a right to live a happy life.
Saho will divorce my son
and return to this house.
Even if she becomes an abandoned divorcée?
This is the best solution.
She will only bring shame to this family
if she returns after a second divorce.
It is her life.
She should decide for herself.
Divorce is nothing special in these times.
It is different from when we were young.
You should stop thinking
everything will go your way.
You are a politician.
A well-respected politician
with a good reputation.
I live in the shadows,
never stepping into the light.
Not a single soul knows who I am,
or who my family are.
So?
It will only hurt you and your family
if she stays in this marriage.
Ending it quickly is for Saho's sake.
No.
It's all for you.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
WATARU MGR
[Wataru] Hello?
If it's that photo you asked for,
I'll send it to you later.
I can't even put on my lipstick
properly right now.
A car will pick you up in an hour.
Okay. I'll be ready.
You'll have a rehearsal, right?
Ken will start by introducing
you to the audience.
And the event will take about an hour.
Okay.
After that will be your song.
I know.
Break a leg. It's a big opportunity.
I know. I'll do well.
Where will your boyfriend be tonight?
Well, I invited him.
I knew it.
Don't.
I want him to see me.
He's only going to watch me sing.
Damn it.
Doing whatever you want.
Then never say a word about
you dating him.
He'll only stand there and watch.
Don't even talk to him. Don't go near him.
That's my prerogative.
I'll see you later.
Just stand there and watch?
Ignore him.
Are we in a prison?
Is this what your dream is?
You can just ignore it.
Look, I don't want
to fight with you over this.
Go and sing.
I'll stay home.
I don't want to get involved
in these petty things.
But I want you to be there.
You don't have a choice, do you?
No.
I make my own decisions.
Okay.
I need to finish my makeup.
And send my manager that petty photo.
[photographer] Get closer.
[in English] Three, two, one.
Risako.
[in Japanese]
He's from the marketing agency.
-Smile. Smile.
-Okay.
Pardon me.
This is our newest singer, Risako Ogami.
I'm Risako Ogami.
She will be singing tonight.
-I can't wait.
-Me neither.
-I'd love to see it.
-I'll do my best.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
Ken is here.
Congratulations.
Wow!
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Did you meet Mr. Sato?
No? Not yet?
-Go say hi first.
-Okay.
Long time no see, Mr. Sato.
-Thank you for coming today.
-Not at all.
This is Risako Ogami.
She's making her debut soon.
She's going to be a big hit.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Sato is the vice president of
Muse Music. He's a legend in the industry.
No, you're exaggerating.
Don't be so humble.
[people clamoring]
-[person] She's so pretty.
-[people clamoring]
-Mr. Sato!
-Sheena.
How long has it been?
I'm so happy to see you.
Good to see you're well.
You too, Mr. Sato. I'll talk to you later.
I'm happy to see you too.
Honey, you look gorgeous.
Didn't I say that dress is perfect?
Yes, thank you so much.
You surprised me.
I didn't know you were coming.
I can't miss such an important day.
And? What will you sing?
The song Ken wrote for me.
We're debuting it here.
Really?
Even though you could sing your own song?
Ken is the one who chooses the song.
Don't you want to sing the song you wrote?
Of course I do.
If it's okay with Ken.
Okay.
I'll try to talk to him.
CONGRATULATIONS
RISAKO OGAMI - SHEENA
Risako, did you hear you're
-…singing your song?
-Really?
That's what I was told.
What happened?
Sheena did it.
[laughs]
Will you be okay?
Yes.
[person 1] Mic check. Mic check.
[person 2] It's taking too long.
Sheena.
Why did you do that?
It's a good song.
This will be good for her.
But it's not her debut song.
There's no need to be scared
even if she is more talented than you.
It could just be beginner's luck.
I don't get it.
It's fine.
Be sure to give your new singer
a good introduction.
Okay?
[in English] Ladies and gentlemen.
[in Japanese] I am very happy to introduce
a wonderful artist to you tonight.
[audience clapping]
She will mesmerize you
with her beautiful voice.
Making her debut tonight
singing an original song, RISE,
is Risako Ogami.
♪ You know sometimes
I wish you'd scream at me ♪
♪ Have a fit
And throw your clothes on me ♪
♪ Be inconsiderate and ignore me ♪
♪ Or just laugh along and smile with me ♪
♪ Show me your face so I can read better ♪
♪ And know exactly
What you're thinking, yeah ♪
♪ Cause I'm exhausted
Trying to impress you ♪
♪ Even though I know I don't have to ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Every little thing I do
Is just for you ♪
♪ I wanna see a rise yeah ♪
♪ So open up your eyes yeah ♪
♪ And baby ♪
♪ I hope it makes me want you
More than yesterday ♪
♪ So tell me do you like yeah ♪
♪ Can't read between the lines yeah ♪
♪ I wanna get a rise ♪
♪ Oh, rise ♪
♪ Yeah, rise ♪
♪ I wanna get a rise ♪
[audience cheering, applauding]
So…
Why didn't you call me?
I was too busy.
It's always, "I'm too busy, I'm too busy."
I finally made time.
Well,
why don't you answer a riddle?
It's free for you, but precious to me.
And
it's something only I can give,
and something only you can break.
What is it?
I wonder.
My heart.
[person] Did you see the tattoo, Masahiro?
A little.
It's like I said, right?
You'll do it, right?
Is the money really there?
Can you take me back to Tokyo?
[driver] Yes.
I've changed my mind.
[phone ringing]
[phone beeps, stops]
Father.
It seems Saho will agree to the divorce.
You have ruined everything.
That is why I cleaned it up.
Father, you can't.
Let me take care of it. I can do it alone.
I will have a good talk with Saho.
Take a long, hard look at yourself.
Please…
let me handle it.
It is already done.
Saho will go back to her parents
after the divorce.
And you will stay away from that mistress.
I know everything.
I will not accept
any more lies from my oldest son.
[crying, sniffling]
I will do well.
I will
be a son you can be proud of.
You can't.
You are too weak.
And? What should I do?
Do you love Ichiro?
Probably.
Then, do this.
Send a message to Ichiro.
A sweet message.
Tell him you're worried about his wife.
It will be a perfect scenario.
Just like the one you've dreamed of.
Then ask if you can see him.
At his favorite place.
Your makeup that day should look special.
Be sure to make yourself look
especially beautiful and enchanting.
Go early and wait for him.
At a place where he can see you.
When he arrives, take his hand
and tell him how much you've missed him.
Then say, "Let's take a walk."
Talk about your memories
of when you first met.
And the troubles you overcame together.
Then turn around
and tell him you have
something important to tell him.
Say, "I pray that our relationship will
never change."
And finally…
I'm pregnant.
Translated by Annie Chen