LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
[sighs]
-Next is at 4 p.m.?
-Yes.
No comment.
Mr. Maruyama. Mr. Maruyama!
I might be able to help you.
What is it?
[panting on phone]
[Tanaka] This is the hostess accusing
your brother of sexual assault.
By the way, is this your brother?
-Isn't this Masashi Maruyama?
-Where did you get it?
I'm a veteran reporter, so…
Turn it off.
What does this have to do with me?
Everything.
It has everything to do with you.
Oh, really?
If I take this to the police, they will
continue investigating your brother,
and sooner or later,
he'll be found guilty.
After that, they will thoroughly
investigate all related parties.
Like his family
and you, his brother.
How much do you want?
It's not about the money.
You're telling me to side with Saijo?
[farmer] It was originally
3.2 hectares wide.
-[Saijo] Okay.
-[farmer] And there is
a total of 375 paddy fields here.
-Wow. All of this?
-Yes.
And since they are on a slope…
Those people are only concerned
about their own profits.
They don't understand
that our agriculture is
Japan's heart, spirit, and its future.
I may be a member of the Watanabe Cabinet,
but I absolutely must say this one thing.
This country will never truly rise again
if we don't protect the people
supporting our agricultural industry.
[reporter on radio]
When asked by reporters,
Finance Minister Sosuke Saijo
made it clear he is against
the Global Comprehensive Bill
currently in debate in parliament.
He stated the Bill will only lead
to the destruction
of Japan's primary economy.
Can't we do this over the phone?
Tanaka from the Daishin Times came to me.
He showed me a video of you with
a hostess. A video I never wanted to see.
[panting on phone]
What?
[gasps]
What the hell is this?
-She tricked me.
-[panting stops]
But why didn't she give this video
to the police as evidence?
For money.
If she wanted money,
she would've gone directly to you.
Why involve someone else?
She wouldn't get a cent
if the cops got their hands on this.
It would be extortion
if she sent it to me.
You mean she's indirectly threatening you
by using Tanaka?
Tanaka's a dirty reporter.
Everyone knows he's in bed with Saijo.
That dumb hostess wouldn't even think
of doing something like this.
What if it wasn't her? But Takeuchi?
Takeuchi?
[inhales sharply] Wait, didn't you say
you hold the party's swing vote?
It's not about me.
Someone's using me to pressure you.
Isn't all of this your problem?
If you hadn't done something stupid,
this would never have happened.
[Masashi] It'll get worse
if they keep investigating.
Then it'll be all over for you.
Stop it.
We're both in the same boat.
Don't forget that.
This isn't my problem.
Aren't they targeting you
and your swing vote?
It doesn't matter how.
Just fix it.
[server] Have a seat here.
[Shigeo] A bit more.
-[Shigeo chuckles]
-[Nami chuckles]
He's looking this way.
Who?
[chuckles] The man you saw
at the sushi place.
Yeah, he is.
Want to kiss?
What?
-[person gasps]
-[whispering, chuckling]
[inhales deeply]
-[chuckles]
-[Shigeo breathing heavily]
[laughs]
That's enough for today.
I'll be right back.
[clicks tongue]
[retches]
[breathing shakily]
Who was that man?
Do you like him?
Nami!
Are you a stalker?
[shouting] Who is he?
[laughs] Why?
Did you sleep with him?
That dirty old man?
Are you an idiot?
It has nothing to do with you!
Because you're a married man.
[breathing shakily]
[panting]
[gasps]
[panting continues]
[Ichiro sighs]
Hey.
[informant]
You won't switch to a smartphone?
[Ogami scoffs]
The modern phone knows more
about its owner
than even his friends or lover do.
-[chuckles]
-[informant] Yes. That's true.
Carrying all your information with you
everywhere is too careless, isn't it?
[both chuckle]
The girl you mentioned
the other day, Ichiro's mistress.
[Ogami] Yeah.
[informant] She's from Fukuoka.
She came to Tokyo six years ago.
She's always been alone,
barely dating anyone.
That's why everyone was so surprised
when she suddenly started seeing Ichiro.
Really?
And her father killed himself
when she was young.
Her mother passed away
a few years later from cancer.
She was living with her grandmother
and brother before coming to Tokyo.
Her father's name was Kentaro Kawabata.
He was a government official in Fukuoka.
Are you sure his name was Kawabata?
Was he someone you knew?
Only a faint memory.
Kawabata was the name
of the official who committed suicide
during the bubble era.
His subordinate was arrested for taking
bribes from a major securities firm.
The police were investigating his office.
Mr. Kawabata
took his own life
before the police could question him.
Anything else you'd like to know?
This is enough for now.
Thank you.
Only a "thank you"?
I'll be grateful…
to you until I die.
[informant chuckling]
Another drink?
Sure.
[tires squealing]
[engine revving]
-[tires screech]
-[gasps]
[door opens]
[door slams]
[gasps]
[driver] You happy?
Am I done?
I've got another job for you
if you want it.
Please don't post that video anywhere.
No need to worry.
There's no more use for it.
It won't be leaked.
[door closes]
[car departing]
Did you talk with Ryu?
Yes. He's a stubborn one.
Do you think he's in love with her?
That would be concerning.
[door opens]
Hello, Kenichi.
Madam.
You forgot this.
I'll be away for a few days.
[grunts] I see. I had no idea.
This is more important than work.
Call me if anything happens.
I will.
Have a good trip.
[footsteps approaching]
I'm not sure about you working.
[sighs] Isn't it better to have
some income? No matter how small?
[chuckles] To be working at a flower shop…
I also have a plan, you know.
Soon, I'll have a talk with Hide
about starting a new business.
Oh, really?
Then what will we do in the meantime?
Don't you hate asking my father for money?
I'll be at the flower shop all afternoon.
So be sure to pick up the kids.
[Sarah, in English]
So, I read somewhere that Japan had
the second highest adoption rate
in the world.
Second behind the US.
Well, I don't know
anyone who's been adopted.
Right, 'cause here's the catch.
Ninety-five percent of Japanese
adoptions are adult adoptions.
So Japan has one of the lowest
adoption of children,
but one of the highest
in adoption of adults.
Okay. You mean mukoyoshi.
-Yeah, that. Mukoyoshi, yeah.
-Yeah.
Japanese do it to pass along lineage
and business successions.
-So, muku -- Mukoyoshi.
-Yeah.
It's only with men, right? Like,
I can't expect Japan to mukoyoshi a woman.
Right.
Actually, some of the biggest companies
in Japan have been run by adopted sons.
Even if they have biological sons?
-Yeah, some.
-What?
If they find out
their biological sons are incapable.
Wow.
That must suck.
Imagine your dad is like,
"Uh, son, you suck, so…
[inhales sharply] …I'm gonna adopt
this guy who's better than you
to run our company and be our new son."
Japanese are sometimes
practical about things.
Blood matters. Until it's about money.
Here we are.
[in Japanese] Anyone home?
[person] Yes?
I'll be right there.
Who are you?
Nice to meet you. My name is Ryu Ogami.
I work at the NPO, JCIAA, in Tokyo.
I am very sorry for what my husband did.
-But I have nothing more to say.
-[stutters] No.
That's not why we're here.
I can't help you.
Please leave.
[protestor] I've lived here my whole life.
Working the land.
Before me it was my father, grandfather.
All my ancestors farmed this land.
But
there is no one to take over
after all my children left for Tokyo.
Even so,
I must protect this land
that's been in my family for generations.
All I have is this land, and now
they are trying to take it away from me.
There should be something we can do.
That Global Bill.
If it passes,
it will be the end of farming.
Greedy politicians and businesses
will swoop in to take the land.
They'll take everything.
He's been struggling all alone.
Please forgive him.
I don't care what happens to me.
But
don't force me off my land
and make me die elsewhere.
I'd like to help you.
Who wants to buy your land?
They aren't nice enough to just "buy" it.
It's practically robbery.
They offered a good price for it.
It's not about the money!
I will
never sell this land. No matter the price.
I don't think there is a need to sell it.
You're protected by the law.
As if the law is on my side.
They've been
destroying this land to make it unusable.
To force me to leave.
What do you mean?
Can you see that construction site?
It will be a chemical factory.
If they dump their waste here,
it will pollute the land
and make it impossible to grow anything.
When that happens,
I'll be forced to sell this land.
That's what they want.
Who?
Who's the one doing that?
The NPO you work for.
[Ogami] Thank you.
-Welcome.
-Take the luggage, please.
Yes, sir.
-[staff 1] Welcome.
-[staff 2] Welcome.
[staff 1 gasps]
We've been waiting for you, Madam.
-Long time no see.
-[staff 1] Come in.
I'm so happy to see you again.
[in English] You good?
I thought I was doing some good.
Maybe he wasn't telling the truth.
Doesn't have a reason to lie.
The farmer was alleging fraud.
It's not something we can leave alone.
Well you're an insider now.
You have access to information at the NPO.
Hey.
We can do this together.
No. You should keep clear of this.
What do you mean?
You're not from here.
You could get into trouble.
And that doesn't apply to you?
I'll have people to protect me.
Like your family?
And others.
You know what I despise the most?
Chauvinism disguised as chivalry.
I didn't mean it like that.
Then what did you mean?
[Ryu exhales sharply]
Japan is one of the safest places
in the world.
If you mind your own business.
If you get involved,
it's one of the most dangerous.
'Cause no one will help you
once the tides are against you.
[phone ringing]
[ringing stops]
[in Japanese] This is the most beautiful
I've seen this place.
You're right.
Be sure to take care of your health.
Have you seen Yumiko recently?
No. Did something happen?
It seems like she's having some problems.
I see.
Is it something I can help with?
Please go see her.
She started working
at her friend's flower shop.
Flower shop?
She's the most mature out of the four,
but that's because she keeps it all in.
Be sure to talk to her.
All right.
[phone ringing]
[Yumiko]
I cannot take your call right now --
[beeps]
[ringing]
How about this?
[customer] It's so pretty.
-[phone buzzing]
-How cute.
-[Yumiko] What do you think?
-It's beautiful.
[ringing continues]
[Yumiko] I cannot take your call --
[beeps]
[phone rings]
[in English] Hello?
[Murata] Hello. Now do you trust me?
-Oh, wait-- Hold on, hold on.
- Right? Trust me?
What?
As I mentioned before,
the Japanese reporters are not safe.
Do not trust them.
All righty, I gotcha.
What do you have for me now?
And that murder of Takeuchi's son,
that did not go down
like everything was reported.
The mother of the guy was saying
he didn't commit suicide.
I mean, committing suicide?
That's a fucking joke. He was murdered.
How do you know this?
Everyone knows this!
Not everyone, come on. I need evidence.
[laughs]
No one in Japan is going to talk to you.
So how am I meant to write
a story about this?
Expose the man behind everything.
The man who makes the orders. The Owl.
-[Sheena, in Japanese] Red.
-[Risako] Red.
[Sheena] Hmm.
Not red.
Wouldn't a simple design like this work?
Guess not.
[chuckles]
[giggling]
Don't we have anything else?
-[assistant] Well, what about this?
-Hmm?
That might work.
Hmm. Gorgeous.
What do you think?
It's gorgeous.
You like it?
Of course.
-Take it.
-[Risako gasps]
But isn't this really expensive?
You need to wear good clothes
since you'll be in the spotlight.
-But this is still--
-Don't think so hard about it.
Just trust me.
This way please.
Fashion is just like men.
Choose the one that fits you the best.
Not the other way around.
Even Ken?
[chuckles] That's even simpler.
I'm not dating his musical sense.
I think he's a great songwriter.
So they say.
But he's better in bed than in the studio.
[chuckles] Look, I'm already at this age.
It will take some time
for you to get your freedom.
[chuckles] Okay. This is yours too.
You really look good in it.
[door closes]
[lock beeps]
LIBERAL FRONTIER PARTY
HIROSHI MARUYAMA
Do you have an appointment?
[no audible dialogue]
-[contact] We'll talk later.
-Okay.
I'm Tamaki.
We spoke on the phone.
I'm Kenichi Mashima.
Nice to meet you.
Is there a place
where we can speak privately?
This way.
What did our CEO do?
Have a seat.
He's in trouble, isn't he?
Or someone like you wouldn't be here.
He hasn't come to the office
in the past few days.
Everyone here suspects
he's in some sort of trouble.
I'm investigating Mr. Maruyama
and his case.
I see.
How's the company doing?
Operationally?
[sighs]
Masashi's been spending money
like we're the most profitable in Japan.
And in reality?
[chuckles, inhales sharply]
There was a time we couldn't pay
the employees.
Which forced us to downsize the business.
Then I was told we were doing well,
but half the employees were
suddenly let go last week.
And your government contracts?
[stutters]
Construction projects?
Uh--
Even indirectly, all our projects are
government projects.
Was Hiroshi Maruyama involved
in those contracts?
No, but he frequently visited our office.
Were they involved in anything?
Well-- [chuckles, inhales sharply]
Neither of them are that stupid.
But Masashi is always bragging about
having a brother who's a great politician.
Saying he can get anything
if he asks his brother.
"Get anything"?
-Like what?
-Anything he asks for.
He was telling everyone to call him
if they run into any problems,
ordering Miyazaki beef at company parties,
and giving expensive gifts
and trips overseas.
But the company was deep in the red.
It's a complete mess.
I see.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[stranger] Mr. Maruyama?
[Masashi] Yeah.
Who are you?
[stranger]
Were you expecting someone different?
No, I wasn't really.
[stranger] Don't worry.
I know exactly why you're here.
What do you mean?
You want to do something about that woman
accusing you of assault, right?
So, should I just shut her up?
Or make her want nothing to do with you?
What will it be?
I only want her to withdraw
her accusation.
[stranger, in English] Okay.
[in Japanese] That's easy to do.
Hey.
[in English] You must be kidding me.
What do you mean
you can't print the story?
-[sighs] Look. There's no story…
-[scoffs]
-For fuck's sake.
-…okay. It's just speculation!
You have no proof it wasn't a suicide!
So it just disappears?
[sighs]
Who said disappeared? There was
nothing there in the first place.
Okay. Story about the cover-up.
I don't know. Was there a cover-up?
In Watergate, the cover-up was bigger
than the actual crime.
A story about the cover-ups in Japan.
You're just speculating now.
There's no story. There's no cover-up.
The informant told me the government is
eager not to have anything--
And I mean anything,
rise up as a scandal right now.
They have people keeping everyone quiet
on these kind of things.
Well, if you have anything more than
an unconfirmed informant
about the government cover-up,
yes, we can print that.
But you don't have anything!
[in Japanese] Where were you?
Working.
Dinner with the investors. I texted you.
Guess you didn't see it.
[inhales deeply]
Were you drinking?
At least shower before coming home
after you've had sex with another woman.
I-- [chuckles]
[laughing]
What?
[sniffs] I'm a real idiot, aren't I?
I really believed you had
a change of heart.
Who is she?
You're very drunk.
I'm going to bed.
[glass smashes]
[shouting] Who is she?
[Ichiro sighs]
I think I have a right to know.
Hey. Who are you having an affair with?
Tell me! Who is she?
Say it!
Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
Tell me! Who is she?
Hey!
[panting]
You're not half as good as your father.
You don't even deserve
to call him "Father."
[gasps]
[glass smashes]
[breathing shakily]
Saho?
[gasps]
[phone ringing]
RECEIVING
ICHIRO OGAMI
What's wrong?
[Ichiro] Father.
What happened?
Saho,
I think I killed her.
Translated by Annie Chen