[pop music playing]
[wind whistling]
[owl hooting]
[mortician] The preparations for
the bone collection ritual is complete.
Please proceed inside.
THE LATE RYUTARO OGAMI
MEMORIAL TABLET - MARCH 28, 2023
[mortician] We will collect the rest of
the remains for you.
10 DAYS EARLIER
[Taka] You did well.
Thank you.
[reporter] The Watanabe Cabinet resigned
en masse yesterday
after the Diet passed its
first no-confidence motion in 30 years.
With this,
the Liberal Frontier Party will vote
for a new leader
before the set date
to choose the next prime minister.
The prime minister responded to
her Cabinet's mass resignation
by stating she regrettably failed
to gain the public's…
[laughing]
… understanding of her reformation plans
as she sincerely attempted to resolve
the nation's issues.
She asked the people to give
their full support to
her successor.
[pop music playing]
[Nami] Taka?
Let's go, Nami. Hurry.
[Nami] What? Why?
[phone vibrating]
Isn't it a great morning?
[Takeuchi] Is it done?
Yes.
So the Owl has
finally met his end?
[chuckles]
It was a long time coming.
How do you feel?
[sighs]
I am finally
free.
[laughs] Didn't I tell you
it could be done?
As long as you trust me.
[Takeuchi scoffs]
Next is?
[Taka] I'll take care of Saijo.
Watanabe will still have
some influence even after she resigned.
The party will be all yours.
You no longer need to rely on
Ryutaro Ogami's power.
What will happen…
to his family?
I still have plans for them.
[Ichiro] This is the main floor.
-Amazing, right?
-[Nami] It is.
-Hello, sir.
-Hello.
Nami.
Continue your work.
Yes, sir.
[sighs]
Are you Ichiro Ogami?
Yes, I am.
The owner?
Yes. What is it?
This area isn't zoned for business.
We're here to confirm it.
What? No, I've checked everything.
This area is a business zone--
The area was rezoned a few months ago.
You should've received a notice
at the time of your purchase.
No, there wasn't one.
In any case,
you will not be permitted
to conduct business here.
This restaurant cannot be opened.
-[gasps]
-Please read this.
Have a good day.
What does this mean?
Don't worry.
Some politician is just trying to
make an impression on me.
It happens a lot.
Oh, it's you.
[Taka] How are things with Masahiro?
Those gangsters you lent me
weren't as violent as I thought.
They left his pretty face alone.
[Taka] Didn't I tell you Masahiro
will be in your hands?
And now?
Let's give him back.
He'll be yours until you're tired of him.
But he is also mine.
Until I get what I want.
And you want…
His family.
[indistinct chattering]
[in English] What do you know
about my dad?
The legendary kuromaku.
The kingmaker.
The man in the shadows.
Now pretty epic stuff, man.
And then Sarah?
Foreigners coming to Japan and suddenly
asking all these questions about the Owl?
Sarah was asking you about my dad?
Yeah, I mean,
that's why it freaked me out, you know?
I mean, you guys are now dating, right?
It's crazy shit. It's insane.
The girl you're dating is trying
to dig up a story on your dad.
What do you mean digging up
a story on him?
When she reached out to me, she asked
a bunch of questions about you too.
So I thought she was
investigating you as well.
When was this?
I don't know. A few months ago.
I mean, she was asking me
how she can meet you and shit.
How to meet me? That doesn't seem right.
Yeah, so I said no,
why don't you just bump into the guy?
I thought that was kind of funny,
you know?
Because no one's going to
introduce her to you. You're the son.
Oh, shit.
I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
[Ryu] I see.
[Murata] How did you meet her, anyway?
[TV blaring]
[in Japanese] Hello, Mr. Kageyama.
How are you feeling?
Who are you? How do you know who I am?
I came to save you.
To get you out of here.
What did Kaori say?
Nothing special.
She said it's fine as long as
she can become your mistress.
She will give you a call when
she wants to see you.
You will go back to your family
and live your life just like you used to.
What are you saying?
[grunts]
The mistress is usually the one
catering to the whims of the man, right?
But not Kaori.
She wants to be a mistress that has you
catering to her whims.
You're…
Rock, paper, scissors.
-[gasps]
-Yes.
We've met before, haven't we?
At the park.
Now, please go back to your home.
The empty home filled with lies,
a home that perfectly matches you.
[whimpers]
-You have at least five pencils?
-Yeah.
-And an eraser?
-Yes.
Okay. Next is your towel and tissues.
You packed them?
-Yes, they're here.
-Okay.
-Next is…
-Books?
-And the books, and…
-Let's check.
I forgot to fold this.
[Riko] Okay.
And this.
[Riko] And do you have three books?
[Shin] Yeah, I got them.
[Riko] Okay. Now check your money.
-I'm back.
-[gasps]
-Papa.
Hey, Shin. Were you doing okay?
Okay, should we get ready to go?
Were you good too, Riko?
Yes, I was.
Okay.
So, what are we doing?
Here's your bottle.
-Oops. It's usually you who forgets it.
-Good job, Shin.
You have everything?
[Ichiro] Can this be fixed?
I confirmed your purchase contract
when I invested into your restaurant.
It was written that any zoning changes
are your responsibility.
[sighs]
It's my responsibility?
The recent zoning changes
were clearly written right here.
It needs to be rezoned
back to a business zone.
I don't have the time to
push back the opening date!
Oh, my.
Isn't there something I can do?
That's right.
Doesn't your father have
that kind of power?
How about going to him for help?
No.
I won't borrow his power.
But you need to do something!
You have loans to repay!
I hope you won't default on your loan.
No.
That will never happen.
It's written in the contract
that your assets can be seized
if you default on your loan.
You won't be able to avoid this!
What the hell.
[Taka] What?
You didn't have your lawyer look it over?
[elevator dings]
Can't we do something?
I will help you.
My sister is here.
She is my business partner.
Let me introduce you.
Nami?
Oh, why are my brother
and fiancé here together?
Brother?
Yes. Didn't I introduce him to you
when you were looking for a loan?
He's your brother?
Yes, he is. Didn't I tell you?
You'll get more and more confused
when exciting things occur all at once.
It seems Ichiro is having a few problems.
But don't worry.
Since we will soon be a family.
Nami.
You never told me. Right?
Would anything change if I did?
I don't know.
Actually, it wouldn't.
This is now a family problem.
Ichiro, let's solve this together.
Of course.
[waiter] Enjoy your drinks.
[in English] Okay, so I did
some more digging on Manabu
and I think there's
more to it than we know.
But Max was right.
His dad set up a company
and was funneling millions into it.
It was a huge Takeuchi slush fund.
I want you to stop your investigation.
What do you mean stop?
-This is huge.
-Please.
It could expose the corruption, bring
down the government, it's what we wanted.
Just stop.
What's wrong with you?
Do you know something
you're not telling me?
Do you want me to believe
that everything just happened by chance?
What are you talking about?
You bumping into me at the park.
That was an accident?
I mean, I…
No.
You're interested in my family.
Everything just fell into your lap,
how convenient.
You were going to get your story one way
or another using the son of the kuromaku.
I'm sorry.
-But that's not--
-Not what?
I didn't mean to hurt you, or your family.
But you lied to me.
What's between you and me is not a lie.
Yes, I'll admit.
I wanted to meet you
at first to write a story.
And yes,
I set up that encounter in the park,
but everything after that was
real and honest.
Honest?
How can a relationship begin with a lie?
[sighs]
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you,
I just didn't know how or when.
This is not your country, Sarah.
I told you Japan can be a dangerous place.
You're in over your head.
I suggest you go.
What do you mean, "go"?
I mean stop the investigation.
Go back to America.
I'm not going to be there
when someone comes after you.
Okay.
And us?
There is no "us."
[phone vibrates]
[in Japanese] Hello?
[Kyoko] Yumiko? Your father…
What?
…was found
dead.
What do you mean?
Just…
Just please come over as soon as possible.
[Masahiro] What happened?
She said my father…
is dead.
Suicide?
He would never do that.
Yes.
But there are more than
a few people who hated your father.
The will?
Probably a fake written by someone.
And the police?
[Kyoko] They won't be of any help.
[Risako] I can't believe this.
[Ryu] Who found him?
[Kyoko] Kenichi.
What was he doing
when Father was
killed?
When did he find the body?
Two days after he died.
Normally, that would be suspicious.
Didn't Father tell you anything?
Of course Kenichi and I
were worried about him.
[knocks]
Madam, Mr. Mashima has arrived.
Let him in.
And the current situation is?
An autopsy is being conducted
to determine the cause of death.
We know how he died.
I thought it was best to be sure.
To be sure.
Why didn't you come here first?
I determined the autopsy
took first priority.
Why did you go to the villa?
I was worried
because Mr. Ogami never contacted me.
How did you know where he was?
Instinct.
Then who did you first call
when you found his body?
The Madam. Immediately.
-That was yesterday?
-Yes, that's correct.
Ryu.
I will do what you ask of me.
Please. Thank you.
[Tanaka] There's a rumor
that Ryutaro Ogami is dead.
What?
That's impossible.
Rumor has it,
his body was found hanging in his villa.
He would never hang himself.
Someone must have set him up.
One of his own people?
One of his own?
Or it could be Takeuchi.
Weren't Takeuchi and Ogami
working together?
Ogami was going to make
Takeuchi the next prime minister.
Yeah.
That's why no one would suspect him.
In that case,
the one who could be
under suspicion would be…
you, Ogami's enemy.
Have a drink.
Who was behind it?
What do you know?
There are no clues.
Everyone's in shock and aren't speaking.
Will our family be in danger?
I hope not.
I don't know why
this happened.
Most likely for power.
You should be careful.
The killer might go after you next.
I am already a dead man.
A dead man cannot be killed.
I will definitely
avenge his death.
That is why you're the one
in the greatest danger.
This is not the end.
This is only
the beginning.
[sighs]
This isn't politics, but war.
Have you heard anything?
No, not a thing.
Was it Saijo?
Saijo, Maruyama.
And even you were rumored
to be the killer.
[sighs]
There are too many groundless rumors.
We need to uncover
the truth.
We will probably never find the truth
without Mr. Ogami.
We don't know that yet.
Saijo has stepped over the line.
[Takeuchi] There should have been
a way to take Saijo down.
It may take time,
but it was possible with his power
and influence.
But it's all too late now.
What an ending this is.
There's nothing you can do now.
Didn't you also know Mr. Ogami
for many years?
[sighs]
To think there is someone
who would do such a horrible thing.
I will take my leave now.
In just four days…
the no-confidence vote, Mr. Ogami…
Like a vulture, the enemy strikes
in an instant, doesn't it?
[Takeuchi] No matter who,
a person's true purpose will be revealed
when the time comes.
[door closes]
[sighs]
[Ryu] You were the one who
found my father's body.
Yes.
Do you think he really did it?
Commit suicide?
No.
I will definitely…
make them pay for this sin.
Be careful.
There were many who lent
their strengths to your father.
But since he is now dead,
most of his allies have
turned into enemies.
What about Father's closest ally?
I can only tell you
to believe what you see.
I have always been loyal to your father.
And I will continue to be.
Whether he is alive or not.
You are not family.
And you will never be family.
You didn't know anything about me
or your father. Am I right?
[door closes]
What are you saying?
[Ryu] There is no doubt
this is about politics.
But it could only be done with the help
of someone close to him.
So what?
Kenichi found Father's body.
Two days after he disappeared.
All of his actions are suspicious.
Kenichi
was more loyal to your father
than anyone else.
He would never do something like this.
Even loyalty
has its limits.
[Takeuchi] Have you gotten
your faction behind you?
[Maruyama] Yes.
They will vote for you, Mr. Takeuchi.
And that thing Mr. Ogami found out about?
As promised,
it will be completely buried.
[sighs]
What will happen to my brother?
I'll make arrangements
to have him released soon.
-That easily?
-[Takeuchi] Right.
And Saijo?
What about him?
What will you do about Saijo?
He is already
out of my sight.
Who are you bastards?
Who the fuck are you?
I wanted to tell you a story.
[Saijo] Do you think
you'll get away with this?
Do you know who I am?
Yes, of course I do.
Former Minister of Finance, Sosuke Saijo.
You bought votes
using Masashi Maruyama's company.
And embezzled billions of public funds.
You've achieved both fortune and power.
What are you talking about? I don't know--
Before the truth came out,
you unfortunately chose to end your life.
That is the official story.
You will be the one who killed the Owl,
Ryutaro Ogami.
You started the war.
Mr. Ogami's allies
will never leave you alone.
Three days after you killed
Mr. Ogami by hanging him,
you jumped off a building
leaving behind a letter.
This will cleanly end it all,
leaving behind two murders
no one will investigate.
That is the unofficial story.
[panting]
So what will the citizens be told?
Two men took their own lives,
protecting everyone
from shame and dishonor.
Move! [grunts]
Stop! You won't get away with this!
Stop!
DEATH OF MINISTER SAIJO
One of the candidates for prime minister,
Minister of Finance Sosuke Saijo
of the Liberal Frontier Party, was found
dead after falling from his hotel.
The police are investigating
his death as a suicide.
The sudden death of Minister Saijo
has thrown the LFP's race for
the next prime minister into turmoil…
[in English] First the Owl's found dead,
now Saijo?
This is some fucking crazy shit.
What the hell is going on?
It's Takeuchi.
It has to be.
He found a new kuromaku.
Or more accurately,
another kuromaku has found Takeuchi.
Is Ryu in danger?
That whole family's fucking in danger.
…the political world was
shocked by his death.
Shit.
[in Japanese] Madam,
I must tell you something.
What is it?
I had said I didn't drive
Mr. Ogami to the villa.
Yes.
The truth is,
I don't remember anything
about the day he died.
When I woke up, I was in Mr. Ogami's bar.
I think I took him to the villa but…
You don't remember if you actually did?
I am very sorry.
I can't remember clearly.
Have you told this to anyone?
Yes.
Kenichi was there when I woke up.
Kenichi?
Yes.
[in English] Hey.
-So sorry for your loss, Ryu.
-Save your condolences.
I never wanted to harm you
or your family. Please believe me.
I thought you were leaving Japan.
Just hear me out and I'll leave you alone.
It was Takeuchi and a new kuromaku.
He killed your dad, he killed Saijo.
Made it look like suicides to cover it up.
Now you have your story.
No.
I'm telling you this because I think
you and your family are in danger.
The Ogamis have been around
since the founding of Japan,
we can take care of ourselves.
I care about you.
You should take care of yourself.
Ryu.
Please hold it carefully from the bottom.
Please take the photo.
My condolences for your loss.
Thank you.
Let's go.
OGAMI FAMILY
[Kyoko] Come in.
Is there anything you need from me?
[Kyoko] Yes.
Let's take a walk.
You were like one of the family.
You were probably even more like family
than our real family members.
Yes.
But I don't know what is happening.
Or who to trust.
I will definitely
uncover the truth of what happened.
[sighs]
Ryutaro was killed.
Saijo was also killed.
Everyone is saying it was for revenge,
but only one person could have done it.
You!
I swear.
It wasn't me.
I have told you all I know, Madam.
Then why did you lie?
You found his body.
You also met the driver
who took him to the villa.
Why did you tell the driver
not to say anything?
And then, his biggest enemy,
Saijo, has also died.
Can you say you weren't involved at all?
Why did you…
lie to me?
Tell me why you lied to our family.
Or else.
Tell me.
Tell me!
Because that is what Mr. Ogami ordered.
[Ogami] Kyoko.
I'm sorry for putting you
through such a difficult experience.
Will you listen to my story?
What?
Is it you?
Are you really
alive?
Yeah. I'm still alive.
I was ambushed by some men at the villa.
They tried to kill me by hanging me.
When I thought
this was how it will all end,
my life flashed before my eyes.
My marriage.
The children's birth.
This country's growth.
My life should have ended
along with those memories.
-[grunts]
- But…
[strains]
No matter how weak,
a connection is still a bond.
Those bonds will
be the strength of this family.
If anyone knew I was alive,
my enemies would have come
to take everything away.
Including our family.
If you aren't dead yet…
then I can kill you myself.
Pretending I was dead
was the only way to find
the person pulling the strings.
All of this
was the work of Takeuchi
and Kawabata.
[cries] That's too…
Forgive me.
Is it really…
truly
you?
Let's get our revenge.
[pop music playing]
[wind whistling]
[owl hooting]
[owl shrieks]
[gasps]
[panting]
Translated by Annie Chen