You're the one I want to marry.
I can't present this.
- What are you saying?
- This project...
belongs to Kensuke Satonaka...
and Marketing Section.
"Questionnaire on marriage"
You think you can do this
to me, Temp?
This isn't good.
Who's throwing trash here?
"Questionnaire on marriage"
What?
What is this all about?
What are you looking at?
I found it in the lobby.
It says "Would you like to marry
Takeshi Shoji?"
What?
"Example of search system"
What's going on?
What's this?
The reply shows "No".
State the reason.
"I don't want to marry
the temp's enemy"?
Did Chief Shoji propose to someone?
He got rejected.
I see.
Should we go ask him?
He's not back from his presentation.
I wonder who the other person is.
There's a phone number written here.
Oh yeah.
Everyone, let's get to work.
Yeah, back to work.
Should we call that number?
- Please don't.
- Let's call it.
We should make things clear.
True.
Okay, I'll call the number
since I found the paper.
Yes, please.
What are you doing, Mori?
A shredder?
Why did you do that?
What?
Marketing Section.
Sure. Chief?
It's Director Kirishima.
Okay.
Satonaka.
Come right away.
You want me to be there?
Could the person
who Chief Shoji proposed to be...
Mori?
No way.
It's not, right?
What's wrong if it was me?
She admitted it.
What's going on?
Were you going out
with Chief Shoji?
Impressive.
Okay, understood.
The large meeting room? Okay.
I'll be right there.
We've got a problem.
I have to do the presentation
on behalf of Chief Shoji.
Please hurry, Chief.
I'll be back.
So it was her?
Not her, but her?
Wow, now you have my respect, Mori.
Tell us how you got him to propose
in just two months?
Tell us.
You're surprisingly good
at this, Mori.
So what if I was?
You, hourly wage thieves
and salary thieves!
Get back to work now!
Here she goes.
But...
you said no, right?
All right, calm down, Asano.
Let's get coffee.
Yeah.
She said no.
Haruko.
Was I helpful to you at all?
I have my phone turned off
when I'm at work so it won't ring.
Problem?
Of course.
I was desperately trying to
protect your personal information.
You were no good at first...
but you've grown up in two months.
Proud employees will have a fall.
Companies won't survive without
temp workers now.
For example, Haruko Omae here.
"Impossible" and "social skills"
are not in her dictionary.
She shuts down all
troublesome relationships
and disappears after three months
when her contract ends.
But why did the super temp worker
Haruko Omae
decide to be
a non-permanent employee?
That's still a mystery.
"The Pride of The Temp"
I'm Satonaka from Marketing Section.
"Super Temp's Past"
We in Marketing Section
want to make our customers happy.
So we had 1,000 temp workers
answer our questionnaire.
Please see the document
in front of you.
Chief?
Did it go well?
Yes.
Our lunch box project
passed the final presentation.
We'll have a sales event
next weekend.
What?
Chief Shoji gave the project
to our team.
With our hands,
we can realise this project.
Chief!
That's amazing, Mori.
I'm so happy.
Let's celebrate.
That curly hair...
I don't like him, but he's not bad.
Satonaka.
Yes?
As for this project,
you'd better get results.
Yes.
I'll do everything I can.
Also...
about Shoji...
He suddenly...
submitted a letter of resignation...
and disappeared.
He threw the presentation
in my face.
It was humiliating to me.
It feels like my own dog has
bitten my hand.
Sir,
please put the letter on hold.
Please.
"Takeshi Shoji"
Did you hear about it?
Yeah, Temp's Lunch Box
got selected, right?
Apparently, Chief Shoji handed
the project to Marketing Section.
Why? He seemed so motivated.
When we actually made
the lunch box, it cost 1,000 yen.
That's too much.
Chief.
Please go see a nurse
if the wounds on your face hurt.
Since you're a midwife,
are you also a nurse?
Yes. So?
No.
It's fine.
Any idea for the sales event?
There were 10 different side dishes
in Omae's lunch box.
Everything was great.
Of course it tastes great, since
she's the one who made it.
Ten side dishes are a bit too many.
Even my wife's lunch box doesn't
have that many.
Her love for me
makes up for it, though.
No bragging, please.
To reduce the price to 500 yen...
How many should we pick from these?
If it had the same thing every day,
we'd get bored.
That's not true.
You're not normal, though.
You must have miso mackerel!
Haruko.
You really love miso mackerel,
don't you?
I have an idea.
Out of these 20 options,
they can pick three of them.
What do you think?
That way we can reduce the price.
Chief, the proposal
for the sales event is done.
I'll make copies.
By the way,
Curly Hair is not in today.
He should be here by now.
I like that it's so quiet.
Asano?
Hey there.
Nasuda. What are you doing here?
I'll join this company in April
as an employee.
You barely graduated.
Don't worry.
That's not important.
Is working fun?
She must be a mean lady.
No, she's not.
Haruko Omae, a temp.
I'm sorry.
What's a temp?
I'll take a lunch break, Chief.
Go ahead.
Out of my way.
What?
Satonaka.
Hey there!
Shut up.
Did you hear about Shoji?
Yeah.
Take a lunch break now.
Come with me.
You're super cute.
I'll be an employee starting April.
Please throw a welcome party for me.
I'll probably be gone by then.
You'll be married?
No.
She's a temp worker.
What's a temp?
A worker sent from a temp agency.
I don't really get it, but
not a permanent employee?
Can I at least have
your email address?
Masuda.
You want a tour of the company?
- It'd be quick.
- Come, let's go.
It won't take long.
Let's go.
How did he pass the interviews?
An employee, huh?
Mori.
I hope your contract
will be renewed.
I want to make Temp's Lunch Box
with you.
I've been calling him, too.
But no answer.
I...
I'll punch him next time I see him.
Kuroiwa.
Because...
he submitted the resignation letter
without telling any of us.
Resignation letter?
Chief.
Is that true?
"Cafe Cantante"
The economy is better this year
so it's much easier to find
a job than last year.
My friends all told me that
they found jobs too.
Okay. So what?
I can't believe how unlucky I am.
Haruko.
Why is the world so unfair?
That's such a stupid question.
Well...
Like the guy Asano knew,
some people find a job
without making much effort.
He clearly had a connection
with the company.
I feel bad for employees who will
have to deal with that idiot.
Good evening.
- Good evening.
- Welcome.
Hi there.
Is the curly hair guy not coming?
He submitted a resignation letter
and went missing.
What? Missing?
We can't get a hold of him.
He left no clues.
Did he...
by any chance call you?
No. So what?
I'm sorry.
But can you call Shoji?
Why me?
That is...
Yeah, if you call him...
Oh yeah.
He said that he wanted to marry her.
I knew it.
He proposed to you, huh.
What?
It wasn't Mori?
It was Omae?
Oh... I had no idea.
Don't be shy, Haruko.
Call him.
He threw away my personal info
which got in someone else's hand.
He's less than a fly.
I don't care if he disappears...
or goes missing.
So this is Chief Satonaka.
This is the unlucky beauty Miyuki
who likes Chief Satonaka.
Asano is the boy who likes
the unlucky beauty Miyuki.
The curly-haired boy
is currently missing.
But he likes Haruko.
Although she rejected him.
Okay, so...
who do you like, Haruko?
Don't put me in that group.
Wow.
"Shoji"
Should we wait here
until he comes back?
He'll probably call us.
When we first joined the company,
Shoji was constantly complaining.
That's true.
Whenever we went out for a drink,
he was always the organiser.
He said that he'd be the president
and told everyone to follow him.
He was the most loyal to the company
and now he's gone.
It's discouraging.
Sorry to bother you today.
Actually...
until Temp's Lunch Box
gets solidified,
S&amp;F would like you to continue
working at their company.
How long have you been my manager?
Yes,
I know well that you don't
accept contract renewals.
But for this time,
please reconsider, for Mori.
At the first consultation,
Director Kirishima told me that
they would take Mori
if they could also have you.
So...
if you could stay at the company,
Mori's contract would
also be renewed.
So Miyuki Mori is just an extra?
If that's the case, your job is to
educate her to be fully competent.
Understood.
However--
In any case,
I'll be gone after this month.
That's all.
Okay, if you ever change your mind,
call me.
Haruko.
You used to be like Miyuki, too.
You were clumsy.
You tried so hard
but it was all a fruitless effort.
Why don't you help her?
Temps join an unfamiliar
company all alone...
and make a space for themselves...
and work on their skills alone.
I could keep going
because I had no one to rely on.
If I gave her a hand,
and she started to rely on it,
that'd be the end of her.
Excuse me.
Omae.
Good morning.
We've never taken the same bus
in the morning before.
A while ago,
you grabbed me by my necktie
and made me stand up from my seat.
Do you remember?
You know...
I already asked Ms Hitotsugi, but...
have you thought about
renewing your contract?
At least
until the project takes off.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have talked
about this on the bus.
You probably know by now
why I only stay for three months.
No.
Please tell me.
Because I don't want
employees to bug me
like you're doing now.
"Play the voice message(s)?"
"Calling"
You have one new voice message.
Hello? Ken?
Shoji!
Sorry I made you worried.
The company must be collapsing
without me.
Or maybe not.
Were you surprised to hear
about my resignation letter?
I bet you were.
Actually, a different company
gave me a job offer.
And I accepted it.
I'm quitting S&amp;F,
and will try to reach
a higher level.
Also, this is between you and me.
But I proposed to Turtleneck
and got rejected.
Who does
she think she is to do that?
In any case, I'm fine.
I'm a tough guy with wavy hair,
after all.
I'll be busy so I won't call
for a while.
But I'm working hard now.
Good luck on Temp's Lunch Box, Ken.
Use Turtleneck if you need help.
She can do anything, except for
fixing cars and getting married.
Don't get too deep in love.
Bye.
Chief.
Here's a quote for white
and brown rice for the event.
All right.
Thank you.
Shoji.
The presentation went well.
We'll see you at the event.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Haruko.
It's Haruko, right?
Long time no see!
It's been 10 years?
Maybe even longer?
I didn't know you work here.
Now that my kids are
in elementary school,
I started working as a temp.
How have you been?
I'm working, so will you excuse me?
What?
Haruko?
I'm glad that you're a certified
food sanitation supervisor.
It's very helpful.
Please.
Any certificate wouldn't
surprise me anymore.
Right?
She's also a licenced chef.
That's no surprise.
Excuse me...
but can you come with me, Omae?
Sorry.
Well...
Wear this, like
the Valentine's event.
Don't get carried away.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
This is the PR script.
You can rewrite it, of course.
Shoji...
Is he not coming?
It feels strange not to have
Chief Shoji argue with Omae.
I'm happy that the annoying person
is gone now.
Problem?
Turtleneck!
I'm sorry.
Don't push yourself, Chief.
It doesn't suit you at all.
Everything is ready.
Please come take a look.
This way, please.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Two side dishes...
White and brown rice.
Okay.
Is everything okay?
Yes, it's fine.
I think it looks great.
Miso mackerel.
Hey, Curly.
Curly, wait.
Hey there!
What are you doing here?
Kirishima told me to come check out
your sales event.
Why did you bring a dog?
My family is on a trip, so I'm
the only one taking care of him.
He's been trained, so he's fine.
Sit down.
Nasuda,
you can't bring a dog
to a food event.
Really? Curly can't be here?
Chief Shoji?
- What?
- You just...
said Curly, right?
Yes, that's his name.
We named him that because his tail
was curly when he was a puppy.
Isn't it cute?
That's so confusing.
Take him away.
That way.
What's wrong?
Let's go, Curly.
This way.
Come here.
I advertised it to other
temp workers.
Thank you very much.
Can you keep an eye on Curly?
What? Did you find Chief Shoji?
What happened to him?
I don't get this.
Everyone is so weird.
Here, take him.
What?
Hey, you can't just
leave a dog here!
Come here.
Hey.
"From Shoji"
Please give it a try.
This is Temp's Lunch Box.
Please try Temp's Lunch Box.
Please give it a try.
It's this way.
Temp's Lunch Box, 500 yen.
Please try.
It's 500 yen.
Thank you. This is Temp's Lunch Box.
Please check out our lunch box.
You can't work hard as a temp
with a hungry stomach.
Today's lunch is so good
that I can't take it.
S&amp;F's Temp's Lunch Box.
Please come and try it.
We asked 1,000 temp workers
and found their 20 favourite
side dishes.
You can pick three dishes
out of the 20.
Shockingly, it only costs 500 yen.
If you are frustrated
about your contract ending soon,
we recommend Tofu Burger Lunch Box
that contains a lot of calcium.
For people who are health conscious,
we offer brown rice.
If you're upset about
a mistake you made,
get our Don't Mind Lunch Box.
If you want to go to Thailand,
get our Chiang Mai Lunch Box.
Did Chief Satonaka
really write this?
So he likes jokes, too?
Temp's Lunch Box,
made with lots of love.
Limited numbers available!
I've heard that expression before.
Omae,
was this script written by Shoji?
He sent a fax earlier.
Problem?
I see.
Shoji wrote this.
Chief?
Don't Mind Lunch Box
and Chiang Mai Lunch Box
are stupid, so can I cut them?
Well...
Shoji thought this through,
so please keep them.
You can't work hard as a temp
with a hungry stomach.
Today's lunch is so good
that I can't take it.
S&amp;F's Temp's Lunch Box...
Here's your shrimp
and broccoli stir fry.
Here you go.
Here.
There you go.
Thank you for waiting.
Miso mackerel is good, too.
I'll have the tofu burger, hijiki
and egg rolls, please.
Would you like white rice
or brown rice?
Please come and try.
If you're upset about
mistakes you made,
get our Don't Mind Lunch Box.
If you want to go to Thailand,
get our Chiang Mai Lunch Box.
S&amp;F's 80th anniversary...
We need this.
Understood.
Welcome.
Omae.
At this rate, we'll be sold out
before lunch break ends.
Please take a break.
Excuse me.
Is that Haruko Omae?
Yes, that's right.
Well, ah...
They were sold out so quickly.
Haruko is such a talented announcer.
Mori!
I'm sorry.
The dog that you left me with.
He disappeared.
- What?
- Curly did?
Curly?
Over there.
Curly!
Haruko and I
joined Tokyo Central Trust Bank
at the same time.
But the bank had a merger,
and both Haruko and I got laid off.
I had no idea.
I got married right after that.
I heard rumours that
Haruko started working as a temp.
She looks so different now.
I was shocked to see her.
What?
Well...
What was she like back then?
She was very cheerful.
She loved karaoke.
You could always hear laughter
around Haruko.
When I made a mistake at work,
she put her tasks aside to help me.
Not just me.
Everyone one counted on Haruko.
Everyone counts on her now, too.
Oh, really. I knew it.
Sit.
Good boy, Curly.
Long time no see.
You still remember me.
You were terrible
when I trained you.
Good boy.
There, there.
Good.
Good boy.
Here you go.
Haruko.
That dumb dog is listening to her.
Oh yeah, I forgot
that Omae is
a certified dog trainer.
She trained police dogs
and seven dogs got awards
after getting trained by her.
- Awards?
- Seven of them?
She never stops surprising us.
So what?
Excuse me.
Our lunch boxes were sold out
in two hours at the event.
Our customers loved the lunch boxes.
Now we have to figure out
how to reduce
the 650 yen unit price to 500 yen.
I see.
Don't place the goal too high.
Be realistic.
Try to get it launched
as soon as you can.
Understood.
What are you doing?
Director Kirishima told me to
clean up this desk.
Those are Shoji's,
don't throw them away.
What about these?
Please keep them.
What is Nasuda doing?
Chief.
Can I borrow this dumb dog?
What?
Curly.
On your feet.
Starting over isn't
as easy as I thought.
Maybe I'll be a temp.
Did I say, "temp"?
Oh, no.
This is terrible.
Wow!
What's happening?
What?
Stop.
Turtleneck.
What are you doing here?
Clean up after yourself.
You can quit all you want
but don't leave behind these nasty
things for other people to clean up.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Good job finding him, Curly.
Curly?
It's the dog.
The dog?
Curly is a dog that's
smarter than Curly Hair.
He scared me.
Don't give him a confusing name.
Tell that to the owner.
What do you want?
Sit.
You can't bring me back.
I...
I've been approached
by head-hunters.
Stop trying to make yourself
look good.
Nobody would ever want
to hunt your head.
I'm not talking about my head.
They can't just hunt my head.
Then I'd be all bald.
You always have the last word.
I'm telling you this.
Short-tempered people like you
wouldn't make it as a temp.
For you to keep your
curly hair forever,
you can only survive
at that company.
It's none of your business,
Haruko Omae.
I love my curly hair.
Leave me alone.
You also love your company.
For you, your company
is who you are.
You may think you made
a great escape from that company.
What were you thinking
with this script?
You clearly miss your job
and this script is too silly.
Did you cut
Don't Mind and Chiang Mai?
Chief Satonaka told me that
you thought it through
so he didn't let me cut it.
I see.
Chief Satonaka is
so worried about you that he looks
like a lost puppy every day.
I see.
Go back to your old nest,
Curly Hair!
You go back to your house!
Hey.
Wait there.
Turtleneck.
I'm not a dog.
I left Curly with you, Miyuki.
What's going on?
I'm sorry.
Nasuda,
where have you been?
I went shopping.
Mr Asano, do you think
I'll be in Marketing Section?
I wouldn't like that. You guys suck.
Miyuki's a temp so she'll be gone.
Nasuda.
You're out of line.
Apologise to everyone.
What?
Apologise to Mori, too.
It's fine.
She says it's fine.
Nasuda!
I'm sorry.
Apologise properly.
That's what it means
to be a grown-up.
I'm sorry.
All right.
Go home, you're distracting.
Asano will no longer be considered
a new hire as of next month.
Chief.
I found Chief Shoji.
He's at Uchibori Park.
How did you find him?
I'm going to lunch now.
I'll go for lunch, too.
I see.
You guys sold out?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
We only have three weeks left.
When I think about that,
I get so stressed out.
In three weeks,
everything will be over, right?
Temp's Lunch Box
and working with our team members.
Oh well.
After all,
I'm still jealous of Nasuda
who had a connection.
Is the world really unfair?
For a temp, your family,
your education, your GPA
are not at all important.
Employment exams
are like dice used for gambling.
People who manage to get hired
are tied to the company for life.
The ones who didn't pass the exams
find another path.
That's all there is to it.
Even if you fail,
it doesn't mean your life will
disappear from that point on.
Even if you pass the exam,
it doesn't mean you'll have
a bright future.
You haven't tried your luck...
just yet.
You have just...
made it to the starting line.
I've just made it to
the starting line?
Shoji!
Ken.
Shoji.
The resignation letter.
It's put on hold for now.
What?
Let's go apologise to him.
But it was you who's
been against our director.
You know...
this is all my fault.
Are you kidding me?
You're overthinking it.
In any case,
I read the script that you wrote.
It touched me.
Turtleneck hated it.
She said it was silly.
Shoji.
Let's work together.
You always told me...
that working together
is living together.
Ken.
Let's try once again.
What?
Seriously?
Turtleneck's phone number?
You didn't see the back side?
So what's her number?
I have no idea.
It got shredded.
Seriously?
Are you kidding me?
Omae...
Before she became a temp,
she worked at
Tokyo Central Trust Bank.
Really?
Her old co-worker told me
that she was cheerful
and loved karaoke.
Is that right?
Everyone counted on her even then.
Why did she quit?
She was laid off.
I see.
That's why she's all twisted now.
Well...
I don't think that's it.
At different companies,
she saw things we don't understand
and developed her own worldview.
Would that make her
that arrogant, though?
She's actually clumsy
and lonely, I think.
She's lonely?
You're glorifying her too much.
You think so?
Ken,
you were the kind of guy who would
always help out
a transfer student, weren't you?
Weren't you the kind of guy...
who bullied girls you liked?
In any case,
if I summarise my thoughts,
I don't understand her at all.
She's like...
a defeated soldier in armour.
She's always alone.
True.
She completely rejected me...
but you haven't tried yet.
If she's so lonely,
shouldn't you keep her from leaving?
Omae.
Can you...
come to karaoke with me sometime?
What?
Omae...
I assumed that you'd also
be a good singer.
You're saying that assuming
I'd say no, aren't you?
I...
I still...
don't know anything about you.
The reason why you're
not opening up to us...
is maybe...
so you won't get hurt anymore?
So what?
At different companies,
you must've gone through a lot.
I can't imagine how hard it was.
The reasons why...
you learned all of these
skills that you have...
I don't know why, either.
After only three months,
without getting to know each other,
I don't want us to go separate ways.
I suddenly felt that way.
Please don't go.
Please stay with us,
and work with us.
I...
I need you.
"To be continued..."
"Next episode, The Series Finale"