Please don't go.
Please stay with us
and work with us.
I...
I need you.
98 companies...
What?
That's how many company
I've worked at...
as a temp.
That many?
That includes a company
that fired me in one hour
because of my attitude.
Out of those 98 companies,
I've never met a boss
who would tell me...
something like that.
You can be overly optimistic,
but you are a wonderful boss.
Thank you.
But I'll be gone after three months.
Why?
Because it's my rule.
Rule?
Rules for me to keep living...
as a temp.
I get that you don't want to be tied
to a company as an employee.
However,
you still refuse
to renew your contract
even though I'm begging you to stay.
Why?
First of all,
if I work for more
than three months,
because my skills are
incredibly high,
it will create a gap between
me and employees.
Secondly,
employees will start to rely on me
and become even more useless.
What?
Thirdly,
asking this kind of question
is really not appropriate.
For three more weeks,
I'll work hard enough
for my hourly wage.
Proud employees will have a fall.
Companies won't survive
without temp workers now.
For example, Haruko Omae here.
"Impossible" and "contract renewal"
are not in her dictionary.
She shuts down all
troublesome relationships
and disappears after three months
when her contract ends.
However, the real reason
why the super temp Haruko Omae
always leave after three months
was something else.
"The Pride Of The Temp"
"The Final Episode"
Everyone,
we have the launch date
for Temp's Lunch Box.
"Contract ending!
Super temp's final skill"
As a new launch product
for the first half of 2007,
we'll launch it on
Monday, April 2nd.
If it's April, Mori and Omae
might be gone.
it's not "might,"
I will be gone.
Chief.
Can you move up the launch date?
If it's a corporate decision,
we can't change it.
That's true.
I'm sorry.
More importantly,
did you solve the cost issue?
We'd still be in red
if we sold them for 500 yen.
If we're specific about healthy
ingredients and rice,
it'll cost at least 600 yen.
"Email received"
- But...
- Dear Ken,
Sorry I made you worry, but
I decided not to quit my job.
I'm from the corporate
Sales Department.
My name is Takeshi Shoji.
Nice to meet you.
You know,
having someone from the corporate
might be intimidating.
But let's try to get along.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
It hurts.
I'm sorry.
I've never talked to someone
from the corporate.
I couldn't help it.
I'm working hard in Nagoya
like I'm made to do this.
You'd be in trouble
if Turtleneck leaves, right?
So,
I've come up with a plan
to keep Haruko Omae.
She loves miso mackerel.
Her body is made of miso mackerel.
Team up with Yojiya,
and make a free miso mackerel pass.
The pass should be valid from April
for an indefinite period.
With that,
I'm sure she will
renew her contract.
"Free miso mackerel pass"
Thank you.
Will you use it?
Here.
- What's this?
- A gift for you.
Free miso mackerel pass?
Yeah, this is great.
So happy.
Awesome.
Is that really?
Do you want some?
That looks good.
What's that?
"Email received"
I messed it up.
Ogasawara ended up with the pass
for some reason.
What are you doing, you stupid?
A subsidiary in Nagoya, huh?
I wonder if he's doing OK.
He just sent me an email.
He's doing fine.
Really?
Good to hear that.
It was so sudden, we couldn't even
throw a farewell party.
Yeah.
But Shoji will be fine.
He'll accomplish something wonderful
and come back here.
Sure.
Dear Ken,
Here's the next plan.
Turtleneck is very competitive
with permanent employees.
Stir up the competition, and she'll
surely renew her contract.
Now that I'm gone, only Kyoko
Kuroiwa can compete with her.
Use her.
Get Kyoko involved in your tasks.
Kuroiwa.
About the price of this seasoning...
Why is salt this expensive?
Omae worked on this quote.
It's natural salt with
a good balance of minerals
If you compromise, it would affect
the flavour of the food.
Problem?
I see.
Fine, we shouldn't compromise.
Here.
Take this.
It appears that Ms Kuroiwa
thinks highly of Ms Omae.
Apparently, their work styles
are similar.
Surprisingly,
Omae, who never smiles,
smiled at Kuroiwa.
What?
Turtleneck smiled?
What? She seems to be having fun
without me.
Hey.
You, Necktie!
You're getting paid a lot right?
So work.
First impressions are important.
Don't let him underestimate you.
True.
Let's start looking
for your next job.
Well...
It's fine.
If you can complete S&amp;F's contract,
that's a big step for you
who had no experience.
Be confident.
Sure.
Yes. Hi there.
Yes?
Really?
That's great.
Yes, we'd be happy to have
her contract renewed.
Thank you.
You can work there
for three more months.
What?
Chief Satonaka tried hard and
convinced Director Kirishima and HR.
- Chief Satonaka did?
- Yes.
Congrats on the contract renewal.
Thank you very much.
- Great news.
- Chief.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
You have to be there
for Temp's Lunch Box.
Tada.
This is...
a celebration gift for you!
I hope you like it.
- It's for me?
- Yes.
I always talk about you at home
so my wife made it
so you won't be cold.
It's so cute.
It's a blanket?
Not wool underwear?
Please continue exercising.
My wife was trying to finish it
but now it's spring.
But you can use it
when it gets cold again.
She'd need to renew her contracts
so many times, then.
It's fine.
You're part of
Marketing Section now.
Asano.
Let's do Omae Exercise together.
Good idea.
Yeah.
I'll join today, too.
It's nine o'clock.
Are you OK, Chief?
We can't get ingredients
any cheaper.
Using rice plastic...
might not be possible.
But that's the theme
you've been working on.
Kon.
That's it!
"Rice lunch box, my lunch box"
My rice box?
Is this another joke?
We'll have our customer buy
these for 100 yen.
Once customers pay the 100 yen,
we can sell the lunch
for 500 yen, excluding the box.
It's a reusable lunch box.
It's eco-friendly
and there'll be less trash.
We can achieve our cost now.
The director approved it.
I'll make an order
at our Nigata plant.
Let's go, Asano.
Please go to the market tomorrow.
Tsune the tuna man will
negotiate with a mackerel broker.
Thank you.
Let's go.
We'll be back.
See you later.
Hey.
This way.
Tsune.
- Thank you.
No need to thank me.
It's Haruko's favour. I'll make
sure to find the best mackerel.
Hey.
They look great.
They're Haru's co-workers.
How about 1,000 yen per kilo?
1,000 yen?
They are Haru's co-workers.
Then... 1,200 yen!
Deal! 1,200 yen.
Thank you.
Ms Omae worked here for one year?
Yeah.
While she worked, she learned
how to handle tuna.
She also worked at the auction.
People here
can be rough
but also compassionate.
She fit right in this environment.
Why did she leave?
The employer had a problem
and she was suddenly laid off.
Haru lost her parents
when she was very young.
She was all alone.
Tsune...
I thought I could stay here forever.
I don't want to leave.
I don't want to say
goodbye to everyone.
I don't want to.
No.
Right then,
I realised that...
Haru is really
a compassionate person.
That's what I thought.
The reason why Ms Omae leaves
after three months
maybe because it'd be hard to say
goodbye if she stayed longer.
Why not become
an employee, then?
But she said that she doesn't
believe in companies.
Hello, Hitotsugi?
This is Mori.
I'm sorry.
Well...actually...
I'm so sorry after you worked
hard to keep her here,
but Mori won't be renewing her
contract due to personal reasons.
I'm very sorry.
My parents want me to move back.
Mori...
I'll come help for the launch
of Temp's Lunch Box.
Of course.
I understand.
For Mori,
let's make this project a success.
We'll need four gas burners
for this.
We'll need to reconsider
the kitchen-to-seating ratio.
What's in this space?
Too much oil.
Excessive calories.
Please check.
It's not enough sake.
It's a bit sour.
Sour?
This is the new design
for our poster.
What do you think?
"Opening on April 2nd"
Place that over there.
If I send this,
Ken may become worried.
Delete.
Hey, Necktie.
Nobody told me that
I was working night shift tonight.
- What?
- No "what" about it!
- Oh, no!
- What?
What?
What's going on?
Oh no.
This is Marketing Section.
That voice. Is this Turtleneck?
Yes. So?
The last person I wanted to talk to.
Yes, this is the last person
you wanted to talk to.
What do you want?
Let me talk to Ken.
He's not here.
All the employees are out.
OK.
Can I talk to Miyuki Mori?
Please hold.
This is Mori speaking.
How can I help you?
Is this Mori?
Your voice sounds different.
Do you think so?
What's going on, Chief Shoji.
Would you like to talk to Haruko?
Well...
It's fine.
I actually sent an email to Ken
that I wasn't supposed to send.
Can you delete the email for me?
What?
An email you weren't
supposed to send?
Don't read it, just delete.
It can't be leaked out.
I'll tell you his password.
Alright.
The password is...
K-O-I-N-U
Koinu.
I understand.
Chief Shoji,
are you sure you don't want to
talk to Haruko?
Does she want to talk to me?
Not at all. Bye.
Then don't ask!
"Enter password"
Dear Ken,
I...
Actually,
I feel unbearably left out
and humiliated.
I'm the only employee here.
Those truck drivers call me Necktie.
They tell me that I'm cheeky
and bossy.
I feel like an unpopular
transfer student...
or a temp.
It's awful that now
I get how a temp feels.
What do you think, Ken?
Ken, you wouldn't leave me,
would you?
Right?
How pathetic.
"Delete"
- We're back.
- Hi there.
One day left.
Good morning.
Finally, it's the last day of work.
Yes. So?
The media is excited
about our lunch box idea.
Magazines and newspapers
will be there at the launch.
It'll be a good advertisement.
Yes, we'll do our best.
Good.
By the way, is it
Omae's last day today?
Yes, Mori's too.
Sir, a new temp is here
for a consultation.
To replace Omae,
we might need five temp workers.
Everyone is quiet today.
I'm sorry.
I'm the only one
renewing the contract.
There are a lot to finish today,
so please don't talk to me.
OK.
Please finish your work
on time today.
For the farewell party,
I've reserved a place where
we can do karaoke and eat.
Great.
Chief.
Yes?
You've already thrown me
a farewell party, so it's fine.
Mori.
Don't say that. Please go.
Both Mori, and Omae as well.
I'll definitely come
help on April 2nd.
I'm definitely not coming. Problem?
Everyone,
thank you for everything
you've done for me.
It was only three months,
but you taught me the joy and
difficulties of working.
I'm sorry that I made
a lot of mistakes.
Haruko?
My contract has ended.
See you later.
Just like that.
Not even goodbyes?
OK, I'll get going, too.
Thank you for everything.
You waited until
the work ended.
Good for you.
You used to run into the restroom
during work to cry.
You've grown up a lot.
I...
I'm not going back to Gunma.
I said I would follow you forever.
But...
I realised that
it's not possible for me.
I...
I want to work there forever.
But...
at some point, I will have to leave.
They're wonderful people,
so it makes it even harder.
No matter how much
you work on your skills,
if you always feel this way...
So I'll stop working as a temp.
Nobody asked you to be a temp.
You go your own way.
You've learned how to be brave...
after working there
for three months.
It's fine now.
Be true to yourself.
Be brave and start walking.
Working is living.
Haruko.
Nice work.
Haruko. He's here.
My contract has ended.
What do you want?
I'm sorry.
Earlier,
I overheard you speaking to Mori.
Shoji used to say the same thing.
Working together is living together.
Yes. So?
I respect both you and Shoji.
You two are similar.
Both of you...
Just like you love your life,
you love your work.
Yes. So?
The one who's
facing oneself the least...
is you.
You still don't understand?
I think you're in love with Shoji.
Satonaka.
Thank you for saying that.
Click, beep.
What?
Deleted.
People at S&amp;F
are no longer in my life.
So I deleted them from my life.
You can delete me but not Shoji.
Who's that?
Omae.
Please never come back.
Haruko?
Let's drink.
Haruko's always like that
when her contract ends.
That's not true.
This time, it's different.
You think so?
She never worked overtime before,
but this time she did.
She also tried her best
to connect to you guys.
For the past three months,
the time she spent was
something special.
Really.
It was a special company for her.
You think so?
Let's make a toast.
Alright.
- Cheers.
It must've been tough for you
to work with Haruko.
"Curly Hair's phone number"
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Alright.
Good.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Good morning.
Did you get the lunch boxes
from the factory?
They should be arriving soon.
I hope they will.
What?
You didn't see the news?
It's snowing heavily in Niigata.
Hello? This is Satonaka from S&amp;F.
Will the delivery be OK?
The road is blocked due to snow?
It's snowing heavily around Niigata.
The transportation is also
affected by this snow.
The Kanetsu Highway
between Yuzawa and Nagaoka
is closed due to snow.
"Bus ticket counter"
I heard about the heavy snow.
Are lunch boxes here?
Well...
At this rate, they won't
arrive by 11 AM when we open.
The media will be there.
We can't do this without
the rice plastic boxes.
But sir,
we can't disappoint our customers.
We'll use disposable containers
just for today.
Can you make it in time?
We'll find something.
"General containers"
I see.
Sorry.
Chief.
We can't do it today.
We need to cancel.
I'll call another one.
I wish she was here
to help us in a pinch.
Haruko.
I wonder what she's doing now.
Probably travelling alone.
But I think...
she's actually lonely.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't find anything.
Heaven has abandoned us.
That... What's that?
"Rice Future Inc."
Haruko?
Omae?
The lonely girl is coming down.
What?
Omae.
- Haruko.
- Omae.
I knew you'd come.
Are you OK, Omae?
What's that package?
Could that be...?
Rice lunch boxes!
Oh my gosh!
Thank you, Omae!
No need to thank me.
Skydiving is my hobby.
Problem?
Bye.
She's gone.
She's never honest
with her feelings.
You forgot your parachute.
Omae!
Please wait!
Clean it up.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Our store is now open.
Thank you for waiting.
- Welcome.
Welcome.
These lunch boxes are reusable.
So it's cheaper because of it.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Please try our lunch box.
Please try.
Welcome.
It's healthy and tasty.
Temp's Lunch Box!
"Temp's Lunch Box"
That looks great.
What's this?
Look.
Thank you.
Can an employee buy one?
Of course. Come in.
Employees are also welcome.
- Welcome.
- Amazing, right?
"Lunch Discovery"
"Temp's Lunch Box"
"My Lunch Box"
I'd love to explain
how franchising works.
First, as temp workers,
at an S&amp;F's direct sale store...
"Temp's Lunch Box
starts franchising"
"S&amp;F Chief Kensuke Satonaka"
Satonaka looks very busy.
When you work hard at your job,
one day, you'll see the light.
That's finally happening
to Satonaka now.
Being nice is
the only thing he's good at.
How will he handle this?
Mr Kirishima,
do you want Satonaka to dedicate
his entire life to the company?
Well.
He doesn't have any other choice.
Satonaka.
You have the speech script?
No, my meeting ran late.
What should I do?
Go get humiliated.
Congrats.
"S&amp;F President's Award"
We're starting
the President Award Ceremony
of the first half of year 2007.
This employee planned
and launched Temp's Lunch Box.
Sales Department,
Marketing Division,
Kensuke Satonaka.
Please come up.
Temp's Lunch Box
is a huge success.
Congratulations.
Chief Satonaka,
please say a few words.
"President's Award Ceremony"
Satonaka.
Good luck.
Well...
I thought I'd never receive such
a prestigious award in my life.
So I'm a bit taken aback.
I'm grateful for S&amp;F,
which helped me
realise this project.
Temp's Lunch Box was originally
an idea of a temp worker.
So...
The person who should be
awarded this
is Miyuki Mori, who was
a new temp worker back then.
Also,
Kosaku Kon who worked hard
to realise this project
as well as Haruko Omae,
who saved us countless times
with her incredible skills.
All three of them have left
the company.
After all,
I shouldn't be the only one
receiving this award.
Satonaka.
The true value of Temp's Lunch Box
isn't this kind of award.
It's the fact that employees and
temps overcame many difficulties
and worked together.
Thank you very much.
Satonaka.
It was a great speech.
The lunch box is delicious, too.
Thank you.
Have we met somewhere before?
That's President Miyabe.
I'm sorry.
I've only seen your face in photos.
Why do you think
Temp's Lunch Box became
such a success?
Come to our employee's canteen
and you'll know.
For employees, curry costs 350 yen
but for temps, it's 700 yen.
Another thing.
Sure.
Do you believe that we should
introduce more temps to our company?
I don't know an answer to that yet.
However...
a temp worker once asked me
if we see temps as people or not.
We won't be able to work well
unless we see them as people.
Yeah.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
"Miyuki Mori"
A contract-to-hire
is like an arranged marriage.
One will work as a temp
for a short period of time.
If the company likes
what they're doing,
they could become
a permanent employee.
In your previous company,
what kind of things did you do?
Yes, I worked in Marketing Section.
I'm sorry.
Last time, I lied
at the consultation
so I decided to be honest this time.
You're too honest.
Don't mention losing important data.
I'm sorry.
So you really want to be
a permanent employee?
Yes.
OK, this is the only way, then.
Let's do our best.
Yes.
Kon's next company
uses the Equal Labour,
Equal Pay System.
I'm from Haken Life.
My name is Kon.
It's an ideal job where there's no
gap between employees and temps.
Thank you.
10% of our pay now goes to temps.
It's so demotivating.
"Andalucía, Spain"
This is Haruko Omae.
I'm not available.
Haruko.
It's been a long time.
This is Miyuki Mori.
I went to S&amp;F today.
Everyone is doing well.
Kuroiwa is the new chief of
Marketing Section.
You're no longer a student, OK?
Understood?
Yeah!
It hurts so bad.
She's so scary.
I won't be easy on everyone
like the last chief.
- Understood?
- Yes.
Ogasawara can now use a computer
and he works hard.
Chief Satonaka received
a President's Award.
He's back in the Sales Department.
Both Chief Satonaka and Asano
are very motivated now.
I'm going to Kyoto tomorrow.
Let's get the deal today.
Yes, Chief.
Sir, I'll be off.
Alright.
I tried to get a contract-to-hire
job while working part-time.
Finally, I passed one of the exams.
The company is S&amp;F, where
I've been dreaming to work.
But within six months,
almost half of us
will be considered unfit for
the company and be laid off.
I'll try my best not to mess it up.
I'll become an employee
no matter what.
Too long.
Lastly, about Chief Shoji...
he's not back at the corporate yet.
I wonder how he's doing.
"Curly Hair's phone number"
Sometimes you meet someone
and you become someone
completely different.
Haruko Omae
brought a great impact on my life.
And...
she taught me something
very important.
She taught me
that working is living.
"Hiring drivers and admin staff"
"Person in charge: Shoji"
Excuse me.
Let's go?
Sorry.
Can you tell me where Shoji is?
I don't know.
Who knows?
Let's go.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Ken is really impressive.
I didn't expect this to be this big.
President's Award, huh?
Tsuchiya.
- What?
- You know,
you should be leaving to
go to Fukuoka now.
What?
Fukuoka.
You're so bossy.
I quit.
Let's work, Tsuchiya.
I can't work
for someone like you.
Hey.
Wait.
Everyone. Wait.
Turtleneck.
What? Am I dreaming?
What are you doing here?
Long-time no see.
- You look fine.
- Yes. So?
It's been a while
since I heard that.
You haven't changed.
I'm Haruko Omae.
Wow. That's so moving.
Why are you here?
It doesn't matter.
It's been tough for me here.
Oh yeah.
Let's get pufferfish and talk.
Pufferfish?
You love it to death, don't you?
- Let's go after work.
- No, thank you.
I can prepare pufferfish on my own.
What?
I'm a licenced pufferfish chef.
You've got a new skill?
You're such a hard worker,
I respect that.
If not pufferfish, then...
I'm also a hairdresser.
No straight perm for me.
It didn't work, right?
Don't say that.
Your skin needs care.
It's very smooth.
Any chicks you don't know
the gender?
I don't have any chicks.
Stiff shoulders?
You'll give me a massage?
Land mines and explosives?
What about the massage?
I'm also a midwife.
I already know that.
What about this?
Nuclear fuel?
You can even handle that?
It doesn't make sense.
To me, either.
How many years did it take
to get all that?
- How old are you?
- 100 years old.
Don't tell me such an obvious lie.
Why are you here?
A consultation.
What?
I'll skip some of these,
as there are too many to show.
My contract will be
for three months.
Consultation? Really?
You won't regret hiring me.
What?
This place isn't for a temp
with a high hourly wage like you.
Omae.
I'll work both as a driver
and an admin staff.
My rate will be at least 3,000 yen.
Problem?
Wait.
Any company will hire you.
Why did you come
all the way here?
So that you'll be awarded
the President's Award.
I came all the way here for that.
Problem?
Would you hire me?
Of course.
Please.
Ouch.
So your eyelashes are not curly?
I'll get to work now.
Wait a minute!
Don't pluck my eyelashes.
It hurt.
Apologise!
I don't have my manager now,
so if you're unhappy, deal with it.
Deal with it?
No, I can't deal with that. Wait.
You're here to pluck my eyelashes.
To check and see if they're curly.
- You're here for an experiment.
- Shoji.
- Calm down.
- Ken.
You're here. But not now.
She plucked my eyelashes.
Shoji, everyone is looking.
Everyone is.
Don't look!
What are you doing?
I'm going to Fukuoka.
Problem?
I'm the boss here.
Get off.
Out of my way.
Or I'll run you over.
You're so dangerous.
- Get off, Turtleneck.
- Shoji.
Let's go. It's not safe.
I'll work hard to receive
my hourly wage for three months.
Here she goes.
Hey.
Turtleneck.
She's gone.
She's gone?
Or should we say she's back?
"This drama series is fictional"