"Toshima Ward"
Hey.
What are you doing, Haruko?
I just woke someone asleep. Problem?
- What?
- Shoji!
Can I talk to you?
What?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, look.
Ogasawara is using a computer.
Maybe he's half-asleep?
- What are you doing?
- No, I'm not half-asleep.
HR told me there's an email.
Or something like that.
How does this work?
You've never checked
internal emails?
Not at all.
Ogasawara.
Let's turn on the computer first.
Oh yeah, I need to turn on
my computer first.
- No.
- I see.
- Don't do it.
- Hey, Mori?
How can I turn on my computer?
Can you tell me?
Sure.
Here's how you do it.
This is it. You press here.
Oh, you press there?
Wow, great!
Shige...I mean Ogasawara
used to be a great salesman.
We joined the company
the same year.
We inspired each other
to work harder.
We were like
you and Shoji.
We hung out together all the time.
He's really a great guy.
Yes.
But a company needs
more than a nice guy.
We won't renew his contract
that's coming up next month.
Hard for me to tell him,
so you tell him as his chief.
Sir.
Please.
At least for another year?
HR has decided it.
Hurry.
People from the NTA are here
with the accounting team.
It's so complicated every year.
Yeah.
Is everything okay, Shoji?
No problem.
Satonaka.
Do what you need to do, okay?
Yes...
What's up?
Well...
- It looks--
- Shoji!
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Okay.
We'll talk later?
Click there!
To this part,
please move the mouse.
Ogasawara?
I'm moving my mouth.
Stop that or I won't teach you.
Oh, sorry.
I want to move it a little higher.
In that case...
Go! Make an attack! Move forward!
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Haruko. I'll pick them up.
This is not a computer
class for the elderly.
Yes, you're right.
But please be easy on me.
Proud employees will have a fall.
Companies won't survive without
temp workers now.
For example, Haruko Omae here.
"Impossible" and "overtime"
are not in her dictionary.
She shuts down all
troublesome relationships
and disappears after three months
when her contract ends.
But why did the super temp worker
Haruko Omae
decide to be
a non-permanent employee?
That's still a mystery.
"The Pride Of The Temp"
"Hourly wage invader &amp;
Mr. Sea Cucumber"
Being a temp must be easy.
No need to deal with taxes.
Hey.
I saw you bullying
Ogasawara earlier.
What?
If he's asleep, wake him up gently.
I'm not a certified home care nurse.
I'm not asking you to be his nurse.
Just treat him with respect.
Did your parents throw erasers
at you to wake you up?
Why so quiet?
Why not do the usual?
I'm Haruko Omae.
What are you doing?
All by yourself.
Do things like that on your own.
I don't have time
to play with a fly.
Don't you ever call me a fly!
I'm going to grab you by
your turtleneck sweater.
Shoji.
Is this a good time to talk to you?
Kirishima and HR
are being too cruel.
Why Ogasawara, and not a temp?
Shoji.
I...
I don't know what to do.
Pull yourself together.
We can't lose another
senior colleague.
If you see a promising project,
give it to him.
Get results no matter what.
We need to prove that Ogasawara
is indispensable
to this company.
That's all you can do.
You're right.
A promising project, huh?
Sorry, I woke up late and
didn't have breakfast.
Crab and mayonnaise?
That's such a strange thing to put
in a rice ball.
The best rice balls are
the ones with just salt.
My grandpa loves that, too.
Me, too.
Right? But you can't
find them easily at stores.
There're usually strange ingredients
inside, like mayonnaise.
I'm picky, so those are no--
Sorry, I'm being loud.
Did you manage to
check your emails?
No, not yet.
Alright.
Stop right there.
That's it, Ogasawara.
Let's do that.
What are you talking about?
Salted rice balls.
Let's make a proposal.
I see.
When I eat rice balls with fillings
and side dishes
I sometimes can't tell
what I'm eating.
With salted rice balls, we can set
the price low as there's no filling.
Instead, we use
high grade rice and salt
to differentiate from others.
Let's do a research.
A research on rice balls?
Exactly.
Can you go with him, Omae?
I'm working on something else now.
You can do that later.
Asano and I'll check
convenience stores.
You two check department stores.
Understood.
Let's go.
Ogasawara.
- Let's do our best.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Alright!
Department stores are fun.
It's not fun for me.
This one.
Are you still angry at me?
I like this.
Nice.
Well, I honestly...
can't bring myself
to trust computers.
In the old times, we used to write
everything down by hands.
I liked that because it really
felt like we were doing a job.
I see.
Up to about 10 years ago,
we wrote everything by hand,
including sales slips.
I liked those times.
People felt connected, not
in a superficial way like now.
Now, even toys for kids
look like this.
My grandkids love these things.
Welcome.
Ogasawara?
Why isn't he here?
Cool.
"Iwate Food Fair"
I'll send you a quote
once we get back.
- Thank you.
- Haruko Omae.
Haruko Omae.
This is an announcement
for a lost person.
Shigeru Ogasawara,
62 years old
is waiting for you
at the service counter.
Hey.
Go back to the office.
Alright.
Hey.
Why aren't you looking for
Ogasawara?
I'm doing my job.
Shigeru Ogasawara
62 years old
is currently lost.
Please come to the service counter
on the second floor right away.
Why aren't you going?
Taking care of an lost old man
isn't included in my contract.
Don't call him old.
Ogasawara...
is in trouble now.
Never mind.
It's none of your business.
Okay, I've got work to do,
so will you excuse me?
Tell the lost man
that I left early.
Bye.
"New product, salted rice balls"
"Salted rice balls"
"New Product 'Salted Rice Balls'"
This is done.
Already?
Thank you.
Omae?
Ogasawara isn't back yet.
I had a task to finish
so I left before him.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
I got lost in the department store.
What?
You got lost?
Shoji came to my rescue.
He's very nice, unlike this lady.
He helped me out.
Ken.
She didn't do anything about him
and left early.
She didn't do anything?
You need to act fast.
Yeah.
Here's Ogasawara's proposal.
I'll show it to the director.
It's looking good.
Just hurry, okay?
Mori, have you finished entering
the convenience store data?
Yes, it's done.
You can work much faster now.
- That's true.
- No, I'm not fast at all.
It's easy for young people
to remember things.
Some do forget, though.
Hey, that's enough.
Don't worry, she's right.
At this rate, you guys will treat me
like an oversized garbage
and throw me out on a trash day.
What are you talking about,
Ogasawara?
That's not true at all.
Because he got lost,
I didn't get to eat.
My stomach is growling. Problem?
Sorry, I didn't notice it.
Go get lunch.
Okay.
Omae.
I'm going to lunch now.
Can I join you?
Sir.
Can you take a look at
this proposal right away?
Alright.
You come with us, then.
Sure.
Alright.
Help yourself to anything.
I'm not eating here.
Why?
For permanent employees,
the curry is 350 yen.
But for us, it's 700 yen,
which is double.
Why didn't you say that sooner?
I'll pay for your food here.
No, thank you.
By the way, sir.
What do you want?
It's just between you and me.
What do you think of Ogasawara?
Are you asking a temp
to evaluate an employee?
For you, who's from outside,
you can give us objective opinions
without getting emotional.
It's not my concern.
But if you want
my opinion as a temp,
Ogasawara is...
nothing but a burden
to our Marketing Section.
I see.
Sir.
Is that all you wanted to ask?
I'm so hungry that
I'm starting to feel dizzy.
Please excuse me.
Sir.
Please take a look at this.
It's Ogasawara's proposal.
"New Product 'Salted Rice Balls'"
I understand how you feel.
But it's better to tell him soon.
I'm sure that they'll approve
your rice ball proposal.
I'm sure my grandpa would love it
once it's launched.
I hope so.
I love my grandpa.
And he reminds me of you a little.
Is that so?
You're like my granddaughter, too.
I'm happy I get to work with you.
Let's take good care of ourselves.
Yeah,.
Ogasawara.
Never retire.
It'd be cool not to.
I can't say that
I am good at my job.
But I can say that
I love this company.
See you later.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
She's an invader
pretending to be a temp.
Ogasawara is
an experienced worker.
Why is a temp asking us to fire him?
It's unacceptable, Ken!
"Cafe Cantente"
Not dancing tonight?
I've got a bad feeling.
Really?
Welcome.
Thank you for the other day.
The other day?
Well...
Come on.
We're not drinking tonight.
Hey.
Shoji.
Talk calmly.
That seems impossible.
He has some sort of a grudge
against me.
A grudge? About what?
I can't dare to say that.
Hey.
Don't make it sound
like you turned me down on a date.
Is that what happened?
What's so funny?
I don't like you.
Shoji.
Okay, be calm.
These are on the house.
No need to do that.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
I'll just have one glass.
Let's make a toast.
Nobody seems to be up for a toast.
You're ripping us off with
your 3,000-yen plus hourly wage.
That's why Ogasawara
is going to be laid off.
Also, what did you say
to Director Kirishima?
The company is laying off people?
- Yes.
- I knew it.
You knew it?
If Ogasawara is a burden,
you're an wage invader.
Yes, I am. So what?
A temp should just do their job.
Stay out of the HR matters
of employees.
Permanent employees
are so hard to deal with.
Yeah,. Can you make these flies
go away?
Don't flirt with each other
when I'm talking seriously!
He does have a grudge.
Can't you feel empathy for others
or be sad for others
when they're sad?
Can't you do that at all?
So?
If you were ever dying,
there'd be nobody in the world
who'd save you.
It's fine. I can live by myself.
Right, because you're
a telephone pole standing alone.
That's enough!
Shoji.
Why are we here for?
Tomorrow, I'll have to
give Ogasawara the news.
That his contract won't be renewed.
I'm sorry.
This won't be a problem
for people like you
who can live alone.
But Ogasawara has a family.
He told me the other day,
that he hates rush hours
but it doesn't feel bad when
he thinks about his family.
He's a great person.
You don't have a right
to call him a burden.
As a temp,
every three months
we face the fear
of getting laid off.
He thought the company
would be easy on him
and didn't push himself harder.
Maybe, next time
you might be the ones
getting laid off.
Haruko.
When you're arguing with those two,
you seem to be having fun.
Impossible.
What is this about, Chief?
Official meetings like this
make me nervous.
- Please sit.
- Thanks.
Ogasawara.
Yes?
This is all due to my inadequacy.
They didn't approve
the salted rice ball proposal?
It's fine, don't worry about it.
You have a lot on
your shoulders, Chief.
You're so young and
you're in a managing position.
If you ever want to talk,
talk to me anytime.
Thank you.
Despite how I might appear to you,
with Kiri...
I mean with Director Kirishima,
we have strong friendship.
Ogasawara.
I'm sorry.
We won't be able to renew
your contract.
What?
Are you talking about me?
I'm sorry.
Okay, so that's what this was about.
I wasn't expecting this.
It's fine.
Please raise your head.
Oh, wow.
This was so unexpected
that now I'm hungry.
It's a bit early, but can I take
a lunch break now?
- Sure.
- Great.
Please excuse me.
Excuse me.
Satonaka.
I heard that
Ogasawara is leaving.
Ogasawara is?
Is that true, Chief?
He'll stay until his contract ends.
So until the end of this month?
This can't be helped.
He's getting old.
And he hasn't been very helpful.
That's true.
With this many temps, it leaves
no tasks for Ogasawara.
Haruko.
Is this my fault?
Is it because I've been taking over
Ogasawara's tasks?
Is that why?
Don't be arrogant!
He never got anything done.
You all need to learn some skills
to keep your job at this company.
You're all like sea cucumbers.
Sea cucumbers?
What did she just say?
Shoji.
Yes?
We're in trouble.
Come to Accounting with me.
It's the NTA?
True.
Omae isn't all wrong.
What?
He's just sitting around all day and
getting paid double of what we get.
Double?
Or even more,
compared to you.
Really?
Yeah,.
Ogasawara is impressive.
But he's like a sea cucumber.
Welcome.
Are you not feeling well?
Your white rice
is getting cold.
What?
No, I'm feeling fine.
Okay, let's eat.
We need the delivery receipts for
the flour deal we had in 1999.
What? Now? That's impossible.
What are we going to do?
It should be somewhere,
so look for it.
Tax inspectors are here.
This is like a movie.
Yeah, they've been here for
an inspection since yesterday.
It's about the settlement in 1999.
They're suspecting a fraud.
Slips were hand-written
and were put away somewhere.
We need to submit it to
Accounting by five o'clock.
They're panicking.
It doesn't concern us at all.
- I like this.
- You guys are awful.
Who is she to tell us that?
In our section, please continue
your tasks as usual.
Okay.
Ogasawara.
Where did he go?
I...
I feel better just by looking at
Ogasawara sitting there.
Me, too.
He did a lot for me
when I joined the company.
When I broke the coffee server,
he was very worried for me.
When I'm working with Ogasawara
I forget that I'm a temp.
He's nice to everyone regardless
of their employment status.
Chief?
Can you do something about it?
Ogasawara told me that
he loves the company.
I haven't given up, either.
Before his contract ends,
if Ogasawara can do something
that will change the HR's mind...
Chief.
That's right.
Enough with talking.
Get back to work.
Seriously?
Omae.
Nothing is guaranteed for anybody.
We all need to protect ourselves.
That's why Chief did
what the director told him
and told Ogasawara
about his contract termination.
But I want to help him.
Chief?
If you can't do anything,
then just sit there.
Until retirement,
protect only yourself.
That seems to
fit you perfectly.
Being an employee isn't easy.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Haruko.
The lunch break
is over now.
Wait.
What are you doing, Omae?
Stop that.
Ken.
We still can't find the receipts.
Can you help us?
Alright, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Basement.
All of you.
Okay.
Hitotsugi.
What's going on?
Chief Satonaka.
We're in trouble.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
Omae...
Omae? What about her?
Omae is now completely
out of control!
Please calm down.
I'm sorry.
Of all things, I witnessed her
assaulting Ogasawara.
then dragging him into an elevator.
What?
This must be a mistake.
Assault? In an elevator?
I'm terribly sorry.
She got off on
this floor but I lost her.
What is she, a rebel?
I knew something
like this would happen.
They're not on this shelf.
Just where are they?
Ogasawara? Are you okay?
Where are you?
Ogasawara!
Answer me, Turtleneck.
- Ogasawara.
- No violence.
Hurry up. We'll be out of time.
Turtleneck is beating up
Ogasawara.
Turtleneck!
- Turtleneck!
- Ogasawara
Omae, please stop.
Turtleneck.
Here are the receipts from
the flour deal we had in 1999.
What?
In the old days,
I used to come down here often.
What?
Why is everyone here?
Ogasawara.
Are you working here?
When she dragged me down here,
I didn't know what to do.
Here.
You need these, right?
"Delivery notes"
You're impressive, Ogasawara.
- Ogasawara.
Now, will you excuse me?
Shoji.
Let's hurry.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Sort them by months.
I'll verify with the total.
We only have one hour. Let's do it.
Yes.
Hey, you. This isn't correct.
The total should be this.
You can't read
handwritten documents?
Can you check this, too?
Sure, let me see.
Alright.
In 1999...
Sort these by month, too.
Here you go.
There.
We did it.
Yeah,.
Alright, Ken.
Bring it to the 10th floor.
Okay.
Ogasawara.
Yes?
Come with me.
No, I shouldn't come.
They might have questions.
Only you know the answers.
It has to be you, Ogasawara.
Understood.
Let's go.
Chief Satonaka.
Thank you for making the last days
of my career so wonderful.
Not the last days.
Ogasawara, you are...
needed at this company.
Well...
For us, too.
You mean a lot to us.
That box.
Can I carry it?
Of course.
It's stopped?
It is stopped.
What?
What's going on?
Excuse me.
The two are trapped in the elevator.
What?
The repairing company
is on their way.
It'll take another 30 minutes.
We won't make it in time.
Let's go check.
Yeah,.
Please wait for 30 minutes.
Our employees are trapped in
an elevator with the documents.
Is it another fraud?
No, it's not.
You can go look.
Five o'clock is your deadline.
If you can't provide us with
the documents by then,
we'll report you to the police.
How much longer will it take?
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Hey!
Control panel errors?
We haven't checked it yet.
"Elevator 1"
"16th floor Elevator Hall"
Give me the key to
the emergency exit.
Where are you going?
Hey!
We don't have much time until five.
Isn't the repair company here yet?
Omae!
Are you...
...also a certified ninja?
Stop talking and do what I tell you.
Does she have a certificate
on handling elevators?
Yes, she has
the elevator inspection certificate.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Okay.
I made it.
Throw the rope down.
Okay.
Alright.
Lift it up.
Okay.
This is great.
We made it.
Chief Satonaka.
Deliver it to them.
Ogasawara.
Yes?
You should deliver
the receipts yourself.
What?
Those documents
hold an important meaning
for your career.
I was a hard working salesman
10 years ago.
Hurry.
Thank you for your
consideration, but...
I'm scared, so I'll pass.
Is that okay?
I'm not used to
doing things like this.
Please pull it up, Chief!
Alright.
Here I go.
Will I be okay?
Are you okay?
Don't look down, okay?
I made it, Omae.
Please throw the rope down.
We don't have time.
Okay.
Throw the rope!
Rope!
Don't worry about me. Quick!
Ogasawara!
Shigeru Ogasawara!
What am I doing?
I don't know who you are
but thank y--
Be careful.
Watch out!
You.
You're heavy.
Let me go, then.
Don't be silly.
I don't need your help.
You're so not cute.
Oh yeah.
You can live alone, right?
You're heavy, so come up now.
This wasn't necessary.
Same thing goes to you.
We only needed the receipts.
But you helped Ogasawara, too.
I was just doing my job.
That isn't included
in your contract.
Be a little more honest.
We barely made it alive.
I'm glad you're safe.
Say something.
My hands are dirty.
I'll go wash my hands.
Hey.
Say "Thank you very much,
Chief Shoji."
If you're not happy
about my manners,
please communicate that to
my manager, Hitotsugi.
What?
Do you think you can do this?
Your parents must be awful people!
Hey!
Clean up the rope.
Nice work, everyone.
As for fraudulent accounts,
they found no discrepancies,
so they went back.
Yeah,!
It's all thanks to Ogasawara.
Wow, thanks.
Great job.
Sir.
Shige,
you're staying.
I see.
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you.
Satonaka.
Let's celebrate.
Let's go to Shige's favourite pub.
All of Marketing Section.
Okay.
Please let me join, too.
Great.
- You...
- I'm not going.
I didn't ask.
It all worked out.
Yeah,.
With that woman...
her words and her actions
are not matching up.
What's the matter?
I...
I wanted to protect Ogasawara
but I couldn't do anything.
That can't be helped.
Our life is based on this company.
We can't change who we are.
But she's different.
After all...
we can't change her.
Stop that, Ken.
She's an invader.
If we act like her
we'll for sure be defeated.
We'll be thrown out.
Let's drink until we pass out.
Yeah, let's drink.
I'll take care of you.
Thank you.
Shige.
Do you want to go singing?
How many decades has it been
since we went karaoke together?
- See you later.
- Bye.
See you tomorrow.
Haruko.
This stays between us,
but I've decided that
I won't renew my contract.
It's not my concern.
But why?
Everyone made the last days
of my career so wonderful.
That was all I needed.
Old soldiers should leave.
It's about time.
Ogasawara.
you're a sea cucumber,
so don't act cool.
Sea cucumber?
Are you talking about me?
Leaving a company without hesitation
is reserved for temps.
If you're a permanent employee,
you should cling on to your company.
Haruko.
You should get going
or you'll get lost again.
Ogasawara.
Hi.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Did she bully you again?
- No.
- What did she say?
I'll pay her back for this.
It's fine.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
So are we going to karaoke?
"To be continued..."
February 14 is the best day of
the year to take that chance.
As a temp, should
I hand out chocolates?
We're not here to cheer up
unpopular permanent employees.
Are you...
I'm Haruko Omae, a midwife.