"Marunouchi North"
Hello, Omae!
Haruko.
Good morning.
It's so cold today.
Spring is still far away.
I'll tell you this.
I'm sensitive to cold
so I have wool underwear on.
Wait, you too?
I shouldn't have to talk
about wool underwear with you.
Oh, come on!
That was quite surreal.
I'm sure it was Omae.
Sir...
Good morning.
You two look zoned out.
Well...thank you for last night.
It was quite impressive.
Is he in a bad mood?
Maybe he didn't notice?
I couldn't believe my eyes.
She wore a revealing dress and
danced flamenco like this.
Out of my way.
Good morning, Omae.
Good morning,
Chief Satonaka.
Seriously?
Good morning.
I hate her so much.
Go, Ken.
Sorry.
Hi.
About last night...
What about it?
Omae,
your flamenco was great.
Flamenco? You mean the dance?
Please stop telling me nonsense.
Sorry.
Shoji.
It wasn't what we thought it was.
Of course, it was.
So you act like you don't know?
Was it something
we weren't supposed to see?
It doesn't matter
since you're a temp.
You can have any night job.
You danced like this,
flipping your skirt up.
Olé!
Have fun.
What's that cold reaction?
Don't ignore us.
You want my attention that bad?
I don't care, Temp.
My name is Haruko Omae.
Shoji.
Better to get back.
Don't make her angry
or she'll hang you up
with a crane.
A crane?
Omae uses any means necessary
to get what she wants.
Are you trying to scare me?
Hey.
Hey you, you can't do that.
It's the opposite end.
What?
For documents with
horizontal writing,
get 1 cm from the top,
1.5 cm from the left edge.
Staple at a 45-degree angle.
Like this.
Great to know.
Shoji had a part-time job
where he stapled different things.
Oh really?
It's supposed to be a temp who
teaches these things to a temp.
By the way, staplers
were invented by
Benjamin B. Hotchkiss.
Stapler is an English word.
Normally you staple diagonally
but some bosses might prefer
different ways, so just be aware.
This is horizontal stapling.
This is vertical stapling.
And this is wall stapling.
That's funny.
No, it's not.
What?
You're doing wall stapling wrong.
Wall stapling is when you use
staplers like wall pins
and pin things on walls.
"Be quiet during working hours"
I'll go pass these out.
OK.
Hey, you.
My name is Haruko Omae.
Hey, wait!
Shoji, calm down.
I'll staple you horizontally!
Proud employees will have a fall.
Companies won't survive without
temp workers now.
For example, Haruko Omae here.
"Impossible" and "overtime"
are not in her dictionary.
She shuts down
troublesome human relationships
and disappears after three months
when her contract ends.
But why did the super temp worker
Haruko Omae
decide to be
a non-permanent employee?
That's not clear yet.
"The Pride Of The Temp"
"Pride and Staplers"
I'll be back.
Hey, you.
Turtleneck sweater.
I'll go see a client.
Come with me.
I don't take tasks
from your section.
Ken,
bringing an arrogant person like her
actually helps with
my business negotiations.
Omae,
we're not busy today here,
so please go help Chief Shoji.
Understood, Chief Satonaka.
Thanks.
I'll show her
how good a salesman I am!
"Robinson's"
You don't know this,
but I've been negotiating to be
in this store for half a year now.
Don't do anything, just be friendly.
Smile like a salesperson.
Sales smile.
Be friendly.
Manager Midorikawa.
Hello there.
We're still in discussion
with the corporate, so please wait.
Ms Omae?
It's Omae, isn't it?
Finally, I can thank you.
Your ground-breaking idea increased
the revenue of our store by 30%!
I was a chief back then,
but now I'm a store manager!
Congratulations.
What?
What brought you here?
This employee here told me to
not say anything unnecessary.
She is...
Hey, Shoji.
She's like Jeanne d'Arc to us.
She brought a revolution.
Thanks for bringing her.
Come to my office.
Do you like Mont Blanc cake?
I'll get you some.
All of us want to thank you.
Welcome back.
Hey.
You could ruin this deal
that took me forever to set up!
You're the one who
told me to come with you.
Enough with that.
And call me Chief.
Say that, Chief Shoji.
Thank you very much.
Shoji.
Great job.
Manager Midorikawa just called.
They'll increase our retail space
area by 10 times.
Seriously?
You can go back to
your office now, Ms. Temp.
I guess my last push did work.
Thank you.
Omae.
Manager Midorikawa
gave you his regards.
I see.
Congrats.
Thanks.
Omae.
Nice work.
Thanks. I'm tired.
"Coffee"
That turtleneck sweater.
I'll get her fired in no time.
You think you can?
She's 100 times
more competent than I am.
Be proud of yourself, Ogasawara.
We're permanent workers.
Even the coffee server
stopped working.
This is weird.
The chief wants to see you,
Ogasawara.
I'll be right there.
Thank you.
- Hey, you.
- Yes.
Bring me some coffee.
- Sure.
- For Ogasawara too, so two coffees.
Sure.
What?
Is something stuck?
What do you think you're doing?
Well...
I think it broke.
It's not that it broke on its own.
You broke it.
I'm sorry.
You, again?
After losing those important data?
Good grief.
You bring us bad luck.
I'm sorry.
This is useless now.
What will you do?
I'll pay for it.
This is not cheap.
150,000 yen, at least.
That much?
You said you're going to
pay for this, right?
Well...that is...
Can I pay in instalments?
How many instalments?
Fifteen.
You're dumb, aren't you?
You're only here for three months,
so three instalments.
I'm going broke.
Mori?
What's wrong?
Mori's in trouble again.
Where's my coffee, Mori?
I'm sorry.
I...
- Haruko...
- Don't talk to me for 30 seconds.
Ms Omae.
As I promised you,
I got a temp worker with
high computer skills.
From which agency?
Hi, my name is Kon.
Yes.
Despite his looks, he has
advanced computer skills.
I see.
I'm counting on you.
I'm done with this.
Nice work.
See you later.
Omae...
The restaurant will get crowded
so I'm leaving.
Ms Haruko...
You broke a 150,000-yen
coffee server?
I'm very sorry.
I'll work hard
for three months and pay.
Will you last that long?
Hitotsugi.
I...
I wonder if they won't
need me anymore.
Will I be replaced by
the new temp worker?
No, we don't know that yet.
There's only one way for a temp
worker with no skills to survive.
There's only one way?
Yes.
What is it? Please tell me.
To have unique personality.
Personality?
Be someone that the talented Omae
and Kon are not.
For example, someone who's friendly
who is easy to ask for things.
Make that personality
your selling point.
Be friendly...
Hey! Get in line.
Welcome.
Hi there, Haruko.
Thank you for saving my seat.
Who are you?
You're funny, Haruko.
Same thing, please.
One mackerel set meal.
Brown or white rice?
White rice.
You're quite impressive.
You don't change your attitude
even in front of our director.
You know what?
He and I joined
the company the same year.
We used to call each other
Kiri and Shige.
My first name is Shigeru.
You don't care?
You know...
life can be quite cruel.
That poor temp worker Mori
broke a 150,000 yen coffee server.
You're paid 3,000 yen per hour,
if I remember correctly?
Yes. So?
Well...
I mean...
Maybe you can do something to
help Mori?
It's none of my business.
I know that.
Checkmate.
I'm defeated.
Who broke this?
There's no coffee, Ms. Temp.
Drink some tea, then.
But we want coffee.
Go buy some.
That's not included in my contract.
They always say that.
Sorry, it's my fault, so
I'll go get coffee for you.
- Don't.
- Cafe latte.
- Blend.
- Iced coffee.
Double espresso.
Can you repeat that?
Cafe latte for me.
Blend coffee.
Iced coffee.
- Mori?
- Yes?
Are you OK?
Would you like a coffee, too?
No, thank you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You ordered an espresso, right?
Yes.
Here's your change.
300 yen.
I'm out of cigarettes.
Hey, you.
You don't look busy. Can you go
buy cigarettes? Seven Star.
Sure.
Mild Seven 1mg for me.
Marlboro Light for me.
Can you please repeat that?
Mild Seven 1mg for me.
Marlboro Light. Not the red one.
Alright.
Here you go.
"Ladies"
When you keep buttering up
to those employees,
it's us temps who will
get in trouble later.
They'll underestimate us and
will ask us to do things, too.
I'm sorry.
Don't you have pride?
I'd like to ask you for some advice.
Do you have time today?
No.
Please wait, Haruko.
Where do you always go rushing to?
School for new skills?
It's none of your business.
I want to be a temp worker like you.
Impossible.
Can you tell me one thing?
What's the pride of the temp?
That's such a stupid question.
"Bus stop: Marunouchi North"
"To Kayabacho Station"
Haruko...
"Cafe Cantante"
Welcome.
Is Haruko Omae here?
I don't know where she went,
and I thought maybe she's here.
We've got another "stray sheep".
Are you a co-worker of Haruko?
- Yes.
- I see.
She hasn't been back yet.
But make yourself at home.
Are you Haruko's...?
I am like her mother.
This is my actual son.
His name is Ryuto.
Hi there.
Good evening.
Well...
did you just say I'm a stray sheep?
Yes, you're the 20th one we had.
I've spent half a year building
a connection with them.
I've completely lost my face.
In any case, you have a deal,
so that's great.
Why is it great?
My pride has been shattered.
She makes fun of us employees
instead of making us look good.
When I worked in HR,
I once saw a temp squeezing water
out of a rag into someone's tea.
She might do that same.
No way.
Omae makes good tea.
Are you falling in love with
that turtleneck sweater, too?
That turtleneck!
Haruko doesn't butter up to
permanent employees at all.
She refuses to do
what she doesn't want to do.
I admire her for that.
I'm no good, compared to her.
Oh, thank you.
I have no experience or skills.
I can't take pride in my work
like Haruko does.
I don't get to talk about my pride.
You know...
Haruko does take
pride in her temp jobs.
But she isn't proud
of herself at all.
- Really?
- It's true.
She gets rid of anything
that doesn't benefit her.
That's how she is.
- Right?
- True.
I messed it up again.
Stop there.
Right here.
Wow, awesome.
Thank you, Miss.
Mum.
- Hi there.
- I have gifts.
What are these cute things?
There are so many of them.
You can take one.
The arcade will go bankrupt.
Let me see.
By the way, your co-worker...
Was her name Midori? Miki?
- Miyuki.
- Yeah. She was here.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
She reminded me
of how you used to be.
What?
What? She's genuine and clumsy
like how you used to be.
Thanks for last night.
I like that place.
The owner is nice.
They said you live upstairs.
Haruko?
What you just said...
delete that from your brain now.
What?
If you tell anyone,
I'll beat you up.
I won't.
I promise.
Chief.
The computer security
here is too weak.
What?
What do you mean?
It's quite easy to hack into.
See?
Oh no.
This isn't good.
- This is bad.
- Chief?
I thought you should warn
the system management team.
You did?
- Can you make a report?
- It's done.
This makes no sense to me.
Me, either.
She's right.
Can you come with me?
Sure.
Wait.
That's a permanent employees' job.
Stay out of this, Temp.
I'll go talk to them, Ken.
Nice work.
Hey, can you go get
a yakisoba bun for my lunch?
I'm too busy to go out.
Sure.
Go to Yaesu Bakery,
not a convenience store.
On the other side of the station.
I'm quite picky, you know.
A cutlet sandwich for me.
Me, too. And cafe latte.
Cigarettes, too.
What kind, again?
Seven Star. Remember it already.
Sorry.
Here she goes again.
It's unbelievable.
Hello?
Hurry up.
Go, run.
It's noon, so see you later.
"Restaurant Yojiya"
Thank you.
Sorry.
I made it.
I'm sure she's working as a temp
to attract men.
She should be ashamed of herself.
It's disgusting.
The lunch break will end soon.
Make sure to get proper lunch.
Haruko.
I told you not to do it.
But Mr Hitotsugi told me
that the only way to survive for me
is to have a personality.
I also need to pay
for that coffee server.
All the excuses.
Coffee server, Hitotsugi,
and personality don't matter.
You're just making excuses for
not being able to say no.
You just don't have
the courage to say no.
Serving male employees,
and being hated by the girls.
You'll end up running errands
the entire time.
"It smells bad"
"Don't eat smelly food
at your desk"
Hey, you.
Did you get a call from
Manager Midorikawa?
No.
He's late.
- You sent it?
- Sales Division 2.
Please hold.
- Who is it?
- Manager Midorikawa.
Transfer it to me.
- What number?
- Not for you.
Omae, Manager Midorikawa would
like to speak with you.
OK.
Why not me?
This is Omae speaking.
Yes.
We sincerely apologise,
Manager Midorikawa.
It's his lack of experience.
What?
Manager Midorikawa.
- It won't happen again.
- Let me speak to him.
OK.
I'm not sure about that.
- Let me.
- It's fine.
I'm aware of the retail space area.
- Understood.
- Now.
We're sincerely sorry about this.
Bye.
Don't hang up. Hey!
It was from Midorikawa.
Yes, I know that.
Is this intentional?
You should've let me talk.
The call was for me.
What did he say?
Report it to me.
You made a mistake in calculating
the retail space area.
It's 92 square metres.
He'd like it to be re-submitted
by tomorrow.
Wow, Shoji.
It's not like you.
Are you alright?
And what?
What else did he say?
Tell me all.
He asked if you were trustworthy.
So I said I wasn't sure. So?
- Who does she think she is?
- Seriously?
Don't be arrogant.
All I did was talk on the phone.
Kuroiwa, she's concerned
about our business.
A temp doesn't care
how our company is doing.
She just wants to stand out
so her hourly wage will go up.
Now, will you excuse me
if there are no more questions?
Hey, wait.
I'll let you off the hook today
but stay out of our territory.
You're only here for three months,
so you can't be responsible.
I told you from the beginning
that it was not my job.
I took you because I wanted
them to think I had a secretary.
Stay out of important discussions.
Why don't you focus
on not making mistakes?
Shut up, turtleneck.
You've got a bad perm, too.
This isn't a bad perm.
It's my natural hair.
My natural hair.
- Calm down.
- Stay out of this.
I can't take it.
This isn't good.
Calm down, Chief Shoji.
Why don't we have some coffee?
That'd cheer you up.
It'd be nice.
Yeah, let's do that.
Here, take this and get coffee
for everyone.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Mori?
Well...
I...
You broke the coffee server,
so go buy coffee.
Sure.
That's how a temp should be.
You're easy labour to us.
Easy labour, huh?
Yet you rely on temp workers.
Mr. Employee?
I told you to stop with that name.
I'll do that when you remember
the names of each temp worker.
Alright, let's go get coffee.
I...
I'm not going.
I'll go for her, then.
Ogasawara.
A regular employee
shouldn't do that.
You're encouraging other temps
to have arrogant attitudes!
OK, that's enough.
Get back to work, whoever you are.
I need to hand this out
to all employees today.
Omae,
can you work with other temp workers
and staple these?
Sure.
Sir,
I'll show her how this should
be properly done.
Properly done?
No need. Back to work.
I can't back down now.
It's a stapler battle.
What?
Do as you like.
What do you mean by a battle, Shoji?
If I win, apologise.
And if I win?
I'll shave my head and apologise.
I saw her smile
for the first time.
The battle will be held
at three o'clock sharp.
Understood.
I accept it.
The stapler battle
is about to begin.
Whoever staples
1,000 documents first wins.
- You can do it!
- I'm rooting for you!
Shoji, are you serious
about your hair?
Don't worry.
I'm number one at stapling.
As a student, I stapled
10,000 documents a day.
10,000 documents?
Please do your best.
I'm on your side.
Knock that guy down.
You won't be able to hold a stapler
for the next 30 years after this.
Well said.
Quiet, please.
10 seconds...
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one.
Go!
Yes!
Keep going.
Here.
Go, go!
You can do this.
Great.
She's going fast.
Yes, keep it up.
You're doing good.
Just stay calm.
Yes.
Go.
Hey!
You're so slow.
We'll help.
Here.
Good.
Hurry.
Keep it up.
You're doing good.
Nice.
Here.
Yeah.
Nice.
- Ruler.
- Sure.
What is she doing now?
To avoid overlaps of stapler nails
she's hitting them flat.
That's impressive.
And you, Shoji?
No need.
I'm using
the latest flat clinch stapler.
That's not fair.
Don't be beaten by that loser.
Loser?
Here you go.
Go! Go! Go!
Here.
This is done.
She's quick.
Bring up the pace a bit.
Omae, Omae, Omae.
Last 50 copies.
Alright.
- Go!
- Chief Shoji,
you're running behind her.
I will win no matter what,
for our pride.
There you go.
Alright.
Nice pace.
Good.
Nice.
Here you go.
Almost there.
That's good.
Here.
Nice.
Almost there.
Keep it up.
Focus.
- The opponent is getting tired.
- Here.
Shoji, Shoji, Shoji.
Here's the last one.
I won.
Yes!
We did it.
Hey, are you guys done?
Hi there.
Director.
I won.
You got defeated?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Haruko.
It's fine.
You did a pretty good job.
You were only one copy behind me.
I'll go pass these out
on each floor.
Yes, thanks.
She was just talking big.
Maybe now she'll know
how to shut her mouth.
Excuse me.
Ms. Temp.
Put it there.
Sure.
Excuse me.
I...
I got courageous and
said no to errands.
So I wanted you to win, too.
Your defeat...
is the defeat of my future.
Omae.
I want to ask you something.
Can I?
Earlier,
why did intentionally lose?
You lost intentionally,
didn't you?
Why was that?
Answer me.
That is...
because I'm a temp.
Hurting a permanent employee's
pride in front of everyone
doesn't make me happy at all.
Shoji has...
all kinds of misconceptions
about you.
He thinks I don't mind
hurting other people's feelings.
But so what?
Are you OK with that?
Of course not, right?
It's fine.
I feel better now...
that I said what I wanted to say.
Was there any other way for me
to handle it?
You lost and apologised.
That's not right.
Aren't you upset?
Don't you have pride?
Pride...
My pride isn't...
...the most important thing for me.
What's more important than pride?
What are the things
that are important for you?
That is...
to continue living as a temp.
To do that,
I have to coexist with arrogant
and proud permanent employees.
From now on,
ask me questions during my hours.
Omae.
Shoji.
Omae...
She's quite impressive.
What?
Look.
Not even an one millimetre shift.
It's like bookbinding.
You're right.
Watch out, Ken.
You're not capable of handling her.
I know that.
Yeah!
Not even a good morning?
Omae.
Good morning.
Chief Shoji.
Excuse me.
Hi there.
Sir.
It's nothing fancy,
but please take this.
Thank you,
but what's the occasion?
I heard that Mori broke
your precious coffee server.
I came to apologise.
Mori did?
No, it was me who broke it.
What?
Sir.
Is that true?
Two days ago,
it wasn't working well.
So I kicked it hard and it broke.
Why didn't you tell us that sooner?
Does that mean I won't have to
pay 150,000 yen?
Of course not.
I arranged to get it repaired.
That's great, Mori.
I'm happy for you.
Yeah!
This is great.
The coffee server
the director broke is now fixed.
Thank you.
Asano even made
a donation box for you.
Oh, don't mention that.
What? You made that?
- Seriously?
- Everyone,
thank you very much.
Are you getting sick?
It's extra cold today, so definitely
say no to errands.
Chief.
You don't have
your wool underwear on today?
What are you talking about?
Who wears wool underwear?
Don't worry, Mori.
We'll pretend we didn't hear it.
Why would you tell everyone that?
I'm so disappointed in you.
You weren't helpful at all
when I thought I was in debt.
You lost at the stapler battle.
You're Special A Rank?
It's not that impressive.
Yeah? So?
Besides, you're not
a very nice person.
I'll never want to be
a temp worker like you.
I never asked you to be.
"To be continued"
A tuna filleting show sounds good.
I'll make it successful.
Please.
You shouldn't be asking this
to me. I'm just a temp.
I just want to help them.
What's a real friend?
"This drama series is a fiction"