Managing director
of Takarada Transport.
Mr Tamura...
Oh, come on.
Next.
Sumibishi Trading, Food Department.
Director.
Good job, sir!
- Keep going, sir!
- Amour Store, Managing director.
There it is.
Asada Spice.
Sir!
Internal newsletter is done.
What are you doing?
Hey, Turtleneck!
The director is busy. Don't make him
play such a stupid game.
Stupid?
Here it is.
- It was his idea.
- What?
Organising cards normally is boring.
How interesting.
This is a wonderful idea.
Look how manly and great you look
in these photos.
The title is "Director's Holiday"
It should be changed
to "Director's Dignity".
Here it is.
I love Japanese fencing. I've been
going to a dojo since last week.
Now I'm totally into martial arts.
- Here it is.
- Oh no!
You're distracting me.
I can't concentrate.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
Shoji!
Instead of hanging out here,
make a proposal.
Proposal, huh?
Here it is.
Yeah!
Good job.
Nice.
Here it is.
Omae...
She might intentionally lose again.
Intentionally?
No temps would be so
considerate of others.
Here it is.
Yeah!
Awesome!
Go!
Here it is.
"Omae: 49, Director: 49"
"Shoji Hamada, Takao Yamada"
"Shoji Hamada"
"Takao Yamada"
Kasumino Foods.
Managing...
Information Management Department.
Mr Masashi Hamada.
You lose.
What am I doing?
Mr Kirishima got 50 cards.
Mr Omae got 49 cards.
Impressive, sir!
Incredible!
I knew it.
Yes, I lose.
It was only a matter of one card.
You're not bad at all.
Would you like to play again?
Sir.
Thank you for helping me organise
business cards.
Now, it's time for you to
work seriously. See you later.
How dare you talk like that
to our director, Turtleneck?
Proud employees will have a fall.
Companies won't survive without
temp workers now.
For example, Haruko Omae here.
"Impossible" and "overtime"
are not in her dictionary.
She shuts down all
troublesome relationships
and disappears after three months
when her contract ends.
But why did the super temp worker
Haruko Omae
decide to be
a non-permanent employee?
That's still a mystery.
"The Pride Of The Temp"
"No drama allowed
at proposal competitions"
"Proposal title : Rental cook"
"Proposal title: Metabolic pasta"
"Proposal title: Italian rice"
Everyone,
the deadline for proposals
is in two days.
It's for our 80th anniversary.
A big competition.
Give it all you have.
Yes.
That looks good.
You added the photo of the chef.
Yeah, Mario is a skilled chef
and he's good looking.
Ladies will like him.
Great.
It appears that the director
likes Ms Kuroiwa's proposal.
I haven't shown
my proposal to him.
What's yours about?
Well...
Omae!
Can you give me feedback on this?
Hey, Ken!
Omae is an expert
on making proposals.
Please.
"Rice Plastic"
- No.
- You didn't even read it.
Can you tell me why it's a no?
Sorry.
- Speed reading.
- I've never seen that before.
Too long. Write important parts
in one page,
summarise in 2 to 3 sentences.
If you add notes,
list them up as bullet points.
Good to know.
You shouldn't use kanji
for every single word.
Less than 30% of words
should be in kanji.
That's all for writing a proposal
that's easy to read.
Alright.
I'll do it over.
Don't let a temp teach you
how to write a proposal.
There are three important parts
when writing a proposal.
Title, theme,
and laying the groundwork.
I'll need to correct you.
The third one is timing.
Not laying the groundwork.
Laying the groundwork
is also important, you idiot!
- You're fine.
- Title...
Theme, and timing, huh?
That's strange.
Chief?
What is rice plastic?
We'll make eco-friendly plastic
from old rice.
It's still work in progress.
Is it a bad idea?
It's not the content
but your timid attitude
that makes your proposal weak.
No proposal will be accepted
like that.
Alright.
Who are you to talk about
other people's attitude?
Don't worry, Ken.
See? Now he looks
like a lost puppy again.
Temps can't participate in
this competition, so stay out of it.
No, that's not true.
Here, it says that anyone can submit
their proposals.
This is actually not true.
Proposals from temps
surely won't be selected.
Chief Tokairin.
Are you talking about me?
That's not how you read my name.
You think I'll submit a proposal?
Yes.
I won't waste my energy on that.
That's good to know.
Now, please leave.
And please get out of my way,
Chief Tokairin.
That's not my name.
I don't even know
why I'm always here.
- Shoji.
- Goodbye.
Shunko Daizen.
I'll never come back.
He says that, but he'll be back
in no time.
Everyone,
let's do our best as a team
and make good proposals.
Sure.
Title, theme, timing...
Good morning.
Haruko?
I tried to write something.
Here it is.
Can you check it before
I show it to the chief?
A proposal?
Throw it away.
What?
Never show that to an employee.
Omae.
Why would you say that?
What is it about, Mori?
Well, never mind.
Shoji!
Takeshi Shoji!
I'm very honoured.
System Management Department
thanks you.
Thanks to your report,
they were able to
promptly review our security.
Thank you.
But I pointed that out.
It was Haruko
who made the report.
Yeah.
Best guy in Japan.
As a permanent employee,
I just did what I had to do.
Great job, Shoji.
- Incredible.
- Back to work.
Work.
Thank you.
This is so frustrating.
Yeah, that curly hair.
He'll be back.
What?
Hey, you!
Did you say something about me?
I think I heard you say something.
About my hair.
Shoji.
Ones who pointed out
about the security first
were Omae and Kon.
Let's tell that to the director.
Is that true?
Sorry that I was the only one
who got credit for it.
I'll treat you dinner later.
No, thank you.
The only thing we expect
is our hourly wage.
We're professionals. We don't expect
to receive anything in return.
So you can be right sometimes?
Yes, thank you.
I don't think that's true.
I believe when we're recognised
by other people,
we become better people.
Only employees grow
at their companies.
That's right.
So you do get it.
Sorry, I don't understand.
So...
does that mean that temps can't
submit proposals?
No.
Omae, you're a temp yourself.
So why do you say
these things to Mori?
Because it's not our job to
make proposals.
It's not, is it?
I can't believe how well
we get each other today.
Right, Omae?
I'll be with General Affairs.
Omae?
Mori.
Don't listen to what she says.
Chief, Mori said she wrote
a proposal.
Really?
Can I see it?
Chief...
It might not be useful at all.
Thank you.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Yes, if there were lunch boxes
for temps workers
that were cheap and healthy,
that'd be great.
Mori...
This is amazing.
Really?
Yeah.
You just need to add data
and specific examples.
Make an updated version
by the end of the day today.
- OK.
- Mori,
let me know if I can help.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Alright.
They wouldn't even look at proposals
submitted by temps.
You think so?
The lunch box idea...
only a temp could come up with that.
I'm sure her idea won't be chosen.
I'll tell you this.
Submit her proposal as yours.
Why?
Because...
Hi.
Omae.
Do you think I should talk to her
about my proposal?
Sure.
When we change our ideas
180 degrees, we'll get along.
Why don't we team up?
What?
If we win the competition, I'll ask
the director to give you a raise.
This idea has been on
my mind for a month.
Actually, this wouldn't
work without you.
You're talking too much.
Alright.
I'll tell you.
Title is...
Tada!
Who fillets fish better,
Tsune or Haru?
- What do you think?
- No.
- Why?
- The title is not clever at all.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Mori?
About this proposal,
you should talk to my restaurant.
They have many female customers
who are office workers.
That 500 yen restaurant?
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
They'd be perfect.
Their white rice is very good, too.
Great.
They have that price because
the owner's family has a rice farm.
How do you know that?
The owner has a child who
is the same age as my daughter.
I see.
I had no idea.
Let's use your connection,
and go ask the restaurant.
Can we?
Chief?
Kon, you're willing to help
Mori's proposal,
right?
- Right?
- Sure.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Right now.
Thank you, guys.
We'll be back.
Bye.
Omae.
As part of the research
for Mori's proposal,
everyone went to a restaurant.
OK, so?
The deadline is tomorrow morning
so we want to finish it today.
If you could support her,
that'd be great.
OK. So what?
You can do this task tomorrow.
Please.
Is that a work order?
Yes.
Understood.
His name is Monta?
He's so cute.
So where do you buy vegetables from?
Why is S&amp;F asking a small restaurant
like us such questions?
Well, we're...
in love with your amazing dishes
served at this restaurant.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Here.
You guys.
Don't make Monta cry.
Who is this lady?
Hi, Monta's Mum.
Hi, Nana's Dad.
Please don't bring weird people.
Monta's sensitive and shy.
Go home.
I'm sorry.
But can we talk a bit longer?
Just leave.
Haruko.
Welcome.
Haruko...
Amazing.
What's that song?
Nothing.
It's the sounds in wombs.
I made it into a song.
I just did it quickly.
You can just do that?
Incredible.
Do the research now.
Oh yeah.
First of all, tell us where
you buy vegetables from.
Maybe writing it in kanji makes
it look too stiff and formal?
You think so?
I personally like it.
What about using katakana?
In katakana?
It might make it more trendy.
What do you think, Mori?
Oh yeah.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Yeah, that gives more of
a friendly feeling.
It's done.
What?
Did you type up the proposal for me?
Can I see?
Whose name should I put on this?
Mori, right?
What?
But you all have
been helping me out.
How about we just say
"Marketing Division"?
What about this?
Miyuki Mori and Marketing Division's
team members.
I don't want to be part of this.
OK, what about this?
Miyuki Mori and Marketing Section's
fellow staff
(excluding Haruko Omae).
Too long.
This is perfect.
Ms Mori came up with the idea.
So please put her name.
That's not necessary, Chief.
Do you want this proposal
to be selected or not?
Of course I do.
I see.
I sent it.
I forwarded it to you, too.
Please check.
You forwarded it to me?
She put Chief's name.
I think that works.
He's in charge of
Marketing Section, after all.
Yes, I agree.
Mori...
It should be your name.
Haruko.
Thank you.
You made such a perfect proposal.
We might actually win this.
The idea that I had
might get recognised by the whole
company under Chief's name.
That'd be amazing.
Look at you.
You can push yourself hard
if it's for a man you like?
Yeah.
Idiot.
Falling in love with your co-worker
and getting motivated to
work harder at work.
It's so typical of
an unexperienced temp.
Really?
Don't fall down and cry.
Hey!
"Cafe Cantante"
I'll be out for a while.
You're in charge of the store.
- No problem.
- Yes.
Bye.
What?
I don't know.
Hi Mr Satonaka. Welcome.
Hi.
Welcome.
This is a place
to enjoy flamenco.
Depressed customers are
not allowed.
Sorry.
It just doesn't make sense.
It was Mori's idea.
Temps will only stay for three
months, they can't be in charge.
If this Temp's Lunch Box idea
gets selected at the competition,
Mori will be recognised
and her contract will be renewed.
She can execute her idea herself.
It's not that easy.
You think it's all easy.
You think so?
Omae...
you said that it's only employees
who grow at companies.
Those words
are stuck in my mind.
So you think you can help
Miyuki Mori grow as a person?
Yes, Mori, Kon...
and you, too.
Me, too?
We can help each other
and encourage each other
and become better people together.
Can you protect...
Miyuki Mori?
I will.
It's not that easy.
That's what I'm talking about.
You can't protect temps
or Miyuki Mori's proposal.
That's why I put your name.
No.
I can't accept that.
Excuse me.
Check, please.
No worries. You only had water.
Thank you.
"Temp's Lunch Box"
"Miyuki Mori"
"Send"
Ken?
Still working on rice plastic?
Yeah.
I'm no good.
I can't come up with anything,
like I'm out of battery power.
The director left
to go to a restaurant with
Kyoko to talk about her idea.
This doesn't make sense.
When you think about it,
since Turtleneck joined,
I've been having such bad luck.
When I was the director's
favourite employee,
I was confident and proud,
but now it's gone.
Shoji.
Can you help me out on rice plastic?
Let's work on it together
and submit it with our names.
Really?
I need you aggressive attitude
for this proposal.
Ken.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
You're the only one who says
he needs me.
OK, I get it.
Temp's Lunch Box?
Right.
Young people come up with
such interesting ideas.
If that kind of lunch boxes existed,
I'd want to be a temp, too.
Do you think you'll last
as a temp?
Being a temp is a tough job.
But I heard that
there are so many of them.
Temp's Lunch Box, huh?
This is Kirishima.
The results are already in?
Top five?
Our proposal?
Really?
What? That must be
some kind of a mistake.
We don't have an employee
with that name.
Oh yeah.
Can this be placed on hold for now?
Excuse me.
Sir?
There's a proposal submitted
under the name of Miyuki Mori.
What's going on?
Do you mean Temp's Lunch Box?
It's one of the top five.
We did it!
You're amazing.
Mori.
Congrats.
But we submitted it under your name.
I changed it and resent it
under your name last night.
Chief.
Satonaka.
Come with me.
Sure.
Chief Satonaka is amazing.
I'm so happy for you.
They selected a proposal
submitted by a temp.
This company isn't
so bad, after all.
Really?
They selected a temp's proposal?
This is terrible.
So, you're a big shot now?
We couldn't dare to submit proposals
under our names.
Ken shouldn't be making
a temp look good. Right?
Exactly.
I knew it was a bad idea.
I don't consider it my proposal.
I just wanted to help
Chief Satonaka.
Hey, you.
Don't act like a good girl.
I did it for Chief Satonaka.
For Chief Satonaka?
Seriously?
A love confession?
If that's the case,
say that in front of him.
Enough.
- She'll cry.
- Let her cry.
OK, fine.
You knew that you're in no position
to submit a proposal, right?
So if it's selected, we'll have to
work on a temp's project?
A temp's project?
I wouldn't be able to stand that.
Temp's Lunch Box, huh?
Mori...
I'm sorry for doing
what I wasn't supposed to do.
Mori!
Hey.
She's gone.
That's so loud.
I'm doing my job.
Why don't you
go talk to her?
An employee should do that.
What?
You let your frustration out
on a temp
because you lost to a temp.
You guys are terrible.
The executives insisted on keeping
Temp's Lunch Box.
That means...
we could get strong support
from them.
It's likely to
be selected at the end.
I made Corporate
Planning Department wait.
Submit the proposal again
under your name.
But sir...
I can't do that.
Satonaka.
You should...
be more responsible
as an S&amp;F employee.
You should have never
submitted it under a temp's name.
Is that so?
Sir.
He doesn't understand me.
Explain it to him for me.
I told you many times.
If I used my name,
it's the same thing as
stealing Mori's idea.
It's just a boss using
a worker's idea.
That's all.
An employee needs to be
better than a temp.
This is our
80th anniversary competition.
A temp winning the competition
is unacceptable.
At least you get that, right?
No, this is wrong.
That temp...
she started to cry.
Mori?
In any case,
the more you try to protect her,
the harder things get for her.
Miyuki Mori!
Come out!
Haruko?
Wait until the lunch break to cry.
You still have 45 minutes.
I'm sorry.
But...
I can't stop crying.
I'll forcibly open this door!
During the work hours,
make sure to turn off your phone.
I'm sorry.
Hello? Mr Hitotsugi?
Where are you, Mori?
In the company restroom.
You've been there for a while?
I'm sorry.
It's fine, I understand.
People cry in a restroom stall
the most when getting bullied
and when there's drama
with employees.
Don't worry. It happens.
It's an emergency,
so I'll ask you directly.
Do you have feelings for
Chief Satonaka?
I'm so sorry.
I understand. Can you hear me?
In any case, stop feeling bad
and go back to work.
I'm on my way, too.
Good. You stopped crying.
If it was really your proposal,
don't let those men crash you.
You did it for Chief Satonaka?
I don't believe that.
Kuroiwa?
I apologise for the trouble
Miyuki Mori caused to your company.
She told me
that she wants to fully focus
on her work going forward.
It appears...
that she doesn't
fit in our company.
Well, she's been a temp
for only two months.
I'm sure she'll fit in eventually.
If anything, she's very motivated.
She is motivated,
but not in the direction
that we would like her to go.
She's not a good match for us.
So...
Can you...
please arrange something for her?
Sir.
Please reconsider.
Sorry for making you come
all the way to see us.
Sorry, Hitotsugi.
I feel sorry for her.
Whose decision was it?
Mine.
You want to say something?
You already knew
this would happen, right?
Yes.
With your dignity,
personality,
character...
Given all that I know about you,
I knew this would happen.
Excuse me.
Sorry, let's go.
Sir!
Is it true that you're firing Mori?
Hitotsugi will take care of it.
Don't do anything.
Please wait.
Please explain what's happening.
Is it because of the proposal?
Sir!
I understand.
I'm sorry...
for all the trouble I caused you.
When a temp is fired,
60% of the time,
it's because they don't fit in.
That's just...
false accusation.
I believed in this company.
I'm disappointed with
Director Kirishima.
Hitotsugi...
Please don't be so upset.
It's all my fault.
I'll try finding
your next job quickly.
Please cheer up.
Sure.
Let's do our best.
Both of us.
Sure.
How did this happen?
I didn't know this could happen.
I will withdraw Mori's proposal.
Do you seriously think you could
bring her back by doing that?
I warned you many times.
Shoji.
Tomorrow,
I'll go talk to the director.
Tell me where his dojo is.
Don't do it.
I'm serious.
Don't do it. Oh!
Wow, Turtleneck.
You teleported again.
Were you eavesdropping?
You talk loud, so I can't help
listening even if I don't want to.
Omae...
- I will--
- He said that he'd protect Mori.
But look what he's doing.
That's how much a temp means
to a company.
Once there's a problem,
they're fired.
No.
I haven't given up yet.
Getting fired just because
the proposal got selected.
That's unacceptable.
To protect someone,
risk your body or your life.
Or risk your job.
You can't do that, can you?
Ken did it.
He argued against the director
and now he's also in trouble.
Do you know how hard it is
to be an employee?
I don't want to know.
Problem?
Omae.
Please.
Please tell me how
I can protect Ms Mori.
You can't do it.
If you're just nice,
you can't protect anyone.
I...
I'll show you how.
Omae.
What?
Did she say that she'll
show you how?
This is Haruko Omae.
I'm not available.
Hello?
This is Miyuki Mori.
They terminated
my contract as of today.
I'm sorry that I kept causing
you a lot of trouble.
I thought I could work harder
for a man I like.
That was so arrogant of me.
Next time, I'll try just for myself.
Three.
Four.
- Five.
- Louder.
Seven.
- Eight.
- Sir.
Nine.
Ten.
Good morning.
Why are you wearing a suit today?
I'm not here for the practice.
Seven, eight.
I'm sorry.
He really wants to talk to you.
Three.
I'm sorry to bother you
on your day off.
I know what you want.
Go home.
Sir!
If you're going to fire Ms Mori,
our section will withdraw
the proposal.
Five, six.
Seven, eight.
What an idiot.
I don't have time for this.
I won't leave until you talk to me.
- Ken.
- Sir!
Excuse me.
Omae.
What's going on?
Sir.
Please have a match with me.
Do you play Japanese fencing, too?
I'm only at level four.
Mr Kirishima.
- She looks strong.
- Please have a match!
Please have a match!
Please.
Put your protective gear on.
Right away.
Now.
Let's begin.
Alright.
Now...
Begin!
You're not bad.
- No way.
- Mr Kirishima's getting defeated.
Go! Go!
Don't fire Miyuki Mori.
Here.
If you don't want to get humiliated
in front of these kids,
don't fire Miyuki Mori.
It's not over yet.
What are you doing?
I'm tired so make an attack.
That's it.
Yay!
It looked like she intentionally
let him win.
Yay!
I've got a terrible feeling tonight.
What?
Welcome.
Look at that.
So this is Haruko's bar.
You brought a lot of people tonight.
They're throwing me
a farewell party.
Omae.
Chief Satonaka will join later.
Please take a seat.
Let's sit down.
Chief Satonaka's late.
Why don't we start without him?
That sounds good.
OK, then, a word from our guest
of honour, Ms Mori.
- Yeah!
- Mori.
Go ahead.
Well...
It was such a short time,
but thank you for everything
you did for me.
This way.
OK.
Are you OK?
Hurry.
I didn't have a welcoming ceremony
or welcoming party
when I became a temp.
But...
I met such wonderful people
who'd throw me a party like this.
I'm very happy.
Mori...
Say no more.
When you're old,
things make you cry easily.
Mori.
Hitotsugi.
Chief, too.
Why are you here?
Mori...
You don't need to leave.
What?
Director Kirishima just called me.
He'd like you to continue working
until your contract ends.
No way.
Why?
I'm not sure.
But he suddenly changed his mind.
Really?
I wonder why? What a surprise!
It's no longer a farewell party
but a celebration!
Let's make a toast.
Come on.
I'm so relieved.
I still have my job, then.
Two more glasses and
a bottle of wine, please.
Let's drink.
I'm happy that finally I get to
have a drink with you.
Can you pour me a drink?
I'm drinking by myself.
Problem?
"Temp's Lunch Box"
Sir.
I'll update this proposal
and make sure it'll get selected.
Satonaka and I'll do it.
Not him.
He doesn't understand.
For this proposal,
you're in charge.
Understood.
Let us see it.
I'll do it.
Omae.
Thank you for doing that
for Mori.
It's not necessary for you
to thank me.
I'm not giving up.
about Temp's Lunch Box.
You're still saying that?
"To be continued..."
An arranged marriage?
You still have time.
Here, take this.
Finally, she's opening up to me.
Satonaka will be transferred.
He doesn't contribute
to our division.
So you'll just give up?
Make it happen.