What was he like?
The person who your sister…
The murderer that she was seeing?
There's another reason why
Mr. Kurokawa insists on doing this.
The murderer was…
Mr. Kurokawa's childhood friend.
Daisuke Asama.
That's the only photo
that I took with him
and my late sister, Ayaka, together.
This is Mr. Kurokawa's…
Kurokawa said to me,
"The murderer should be someone else.
I think Asama
was wrongly convicted of murder."
What did you do then?
-I punched him.
-Yes?
He said "should be" and "I think".
The groundless, optimistic
observation made me angry.
I'm a scientist and the victim's family.
Why do you help Mr. Kurokawa, then?
Isn't it because you also think
that Asama was wrongly convicted in
your sister's case?
I didn't want to see his face,
so I blacked it out.
I should've thrown away the photo,
but I still have it.
I don't know why myself.
It's groundless slander to say that
I killed my husband.
Why would I do that?
So this was, as you claimed,
the result of a murder-suicide
committed by your late husband?
Yes.
I tried to run away,
but my husband forced me
to take the sleeping pills and he…
Excuse me.
What? You're being interviewed?
-What are you doing suddenly?
-Anyway, stop recording.
We got a warrant to arrest you,
Mrs. Marina Norikura.
MURDER
What?
Did you find any evidence?
We'll take our time to talk
when we question you.
Hey! Stop the camera!
Sir, can I smoke when you question me?
Of course you can't.
I'll smoke just one, then.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
Mr. Yufuin, she asked you to defend her?
-The wife of Oume's Casanova?
-Yes.
He was Oume's rich man
who died last year, right?
Yeah, but why was he called Casanova?
He owned a local company
and was well known for being a womanizer.
His wife was arrested
and everyone is talking about it.
Look at her cocky attitude.
What? Did you find any evidence?
THE MOMENT THE WIFE
OF OUME'S CASANOVA WAS ARRESTED
We'll take our time to talk
when we question you.
Hey! Stop the camera!
Sir, can I smoke when you question me?
Well, she married him for money
and they had a huge age gap,
so she must've killed him.
Casanova died at 70 years old
and his wife is 24 years old.
Twenty-four years old.
It's like Mr. Yufuin and Miss Wakura
getting married.
What?
But why does she want you to defend her?
Mr. Yufuin, do you know her?
No, I don't know her at all.
What?
But I had worked on a case that
her late husband was involved in.
-You mean the victim, Casanova?
-Yes.
Come on. Stop wasting time and go to work!
-Hirayama!
-Yes!
Although she asked for you,
don't overwork yourself.
Mr. Yufuin, you aren't young anymore.
Kurokawa will give me his assistance.
I will go to have an interview
with her now.
Strength matters when you
work on a criminal defense case.
Miss Wakura, if necessary,
you'll take over--
Ouch! Ow…
Mr. Yufuin! What's wrong?
I was trying to get myself fired up,
then I hurt my back.
-Strained back?
-At a time like this?
-Are you okay?
-Ow…
Sorry! Oh no… Mr. Yufuin,
put your arm around my shoulders.
-Ow…
-Oh, I'm sorry…
I didn't do it.
Even if you're sure
the defendant is lying,
you still claim they're innocent.
If you cannot do that,
you'd better take the badge off.
I wonder what I am
trying to investigate now.
Mr. Kurokawa!
I want you to be saved!
This incident happened on
the 22nd of December 2018,
at 3:45 a.m.,
in the home of the wealthy
Gonzaburo Norikura.
Housekeeper Nobue Towada came out of her
bedroom and came upon Norikura's wife,
-What happened?
-Marina, who collapsed.
What's the matter?
MARINA NORIKURA, SUSPECT
He…
He burned some briquettes…
Is Master Norikura still inside?
No! If you go in now…
Master Norikura?
Master Norikura? Master Norikura…
Norikura
died of carbon monoxide poisoning.
I'm from the Tokyo Fire Department.
Marina and Nobue had mild poisoning
symptoms and were sent to hospital.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
GONZABURO NORIKURA
VICTIM
Marina claims that her husband
tried to commit a murder-suicide,
but the police suspect
that it was a murder
and arrested Marina
two months after the incident.
So, about the reason
the police had suspected you--
-I want to smoke!
-Pardon?
Will you ask the detective?
Tell him to let me smoke.
We can't do that.
Anyway, Mrs. Norikura.
Call me Marina.
Anyway, when will the lawyer,
Yufuin, get better?
I can't believe he sent a substitute.
Well…
Is there a reason
you asked Yufuin to defend you?
No. I just saw him when he was on TV
and I remembered him.
TV?
More importantly,
can you do your work properly?
Of course, we have to
confirm a few things--
Why the police suspects me?
Because the sleeping pills detected
in my husband's body were mine.
The one who bought the briquettes
online was me.
Two days before it happened,
I brought the documents
of the properties away from home
and put them in a safe-deposit box. And…
my husband died, but I survived?
I take sleeping pills regularly,
so it had no effect and I woke up.
Why?
You both just thought
that I did it, right?
We don't know yet.
You were poisoned by carbon monoxide
and were hospitalized,
so I think it was too risky
as a method of murder.
Oh. I think I can rely on you.
I will ask you again.
Your husband tried
to commit a murder-suicide.
In other words,
you did not kill your husband.
Is that right?
I did not do it.
All right, I'll investigate thoroughly--
Tell me at once
if you think you can't win.
I'll look for a better lawyer.
Sure…
I see. She had seen me on TV?
Yes.
In that case, it has to be that program.
Which one?
The show that followed that case.
It talked about the possibility
of a wrong conviction.
I made the documentary when I was a rookie
and I asked Mr. Yufuin to appear in it.
Anyway, fate is incredible.
I happened to be present
-when Mrs. Norikura was arrested
-I have some souvenirs.
and she asked Mr. Yufuin to defend her
because she watched a program I made.
But this happened
right from the beginning.
You can count on us, Mr. Yufuin.
The circumstantial evidence
is against her,
but we have to investigate properly first.
Yeah.
-Miss Arima, what's this?
-Yeah?
Oh, Mrs. Norikura gave me that.
It's the video taken by
the security camera.
It shows their house's corridor
on the day of the murder.
The bedroom, where he died,
is at the back.
He entered the bedroom at around 2 a.m.
3:45 a.m., the wife came out
of the bedroom and met the maid.
It matches the circumstances
reported by the press.
The estimated time of death
of the victim is between 3 a.m. to 4 a.m.
So the suspect also stayed
in the bedroom filled with
carbon monoxide for over an hour.
For now,
it's in the same condition
as on the day of the murder.
The weather strip,
briquettes, and curtains
were taken away by the police.
The curtains were pulled off that night
when she tried to run
and fought with the victim.
There were five briquettes
next to the fireplace.
Which bed was Mr. Norikura's?
The window side one.
He had already passed away when I came.
What?
Mr. Kurokawa, someone passed away.
How can you do that so calmly?
Miss Wakura, go and lie down on that bed.
Why?
I want to imagine the state
of the room during the murder.
Mrs. Marina took some sleeping pills too.
-What?
-I'll do it if you don't want to.
It's fine.
So, did you get anything?
The skylight is bright, but…
The bed is soft.
Miss Towada, you came here
in the middle of the night
because Mrs. Norikura called you
to come the day before?
Yes, she said Master Norikura
wanted to go fishing early morning,
so she suddenly asked me to come at 4 a.m.
But Mrs. Norikura came out
of the bedroom at that time.
The timing is perfect.
Of course, because the woman
planned everything.
-Young master!
-I'm the son
of Gonzaburo Norikura's ex-wife.
You made yourselves quite at home.
Are you the woman's lawyers?
Mr. Kurokawa!
Oh no!
I am sorry.
This is the motive
that the woman killed my dad.
FORMAL WILL - COPY
-His will?
-Excuse me.
It states that the woman will inherit
all the company's shares and properties.
I didn't see it coming at all.
You're saying that
she murdered him for his money?
My dad was an aggressive businessman
and a womanizer,
so maybe his reputation was bad,
but he worked his way up
the career ladder.
He couldn't have left the company
in this young, former hostess' hands.
He must've been deceived!
Just so you know,
there was no weather strip put on
the bedroom's windows that night.
The woman was free to go in and out.
What? Then…
She burned the briquettes
and went outside,
then waited until my dad was dead
and came back.
The police is conducting
the investigation along that line.
It'll only embarrass you if you
continue to defend the woman.
The police found a witness too.
Witness?
If she could go in and out
from the window freely,
the security camera in the corridor
is totally pointless.
The reason that only the husband died
and the wife was saved
can be easily explained too.
-Witness…
-Okay!
This is bad.
Miss Wakura, Miss Kinosaki!
Let's check that out!
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
The trial will finally begin.
I think the turn of events
is in favor of us this time.
The prosecutor's trump card
seems to be the witness's statement,
but we've got something
to prove it invalid.
So their remaining card is only
the circumstantial evidence?
Mr. Kurokawa can prove her innocence
as usual, then.
The public is paying attention
to the case too.
Whoa!
-You startled me!
-What's the matter, Mr. Yufuin?
SHE WAS IN THE SAME ORPHANAGE AS ME
SHE CAME IN 2004 AFTER HER PARENTS DIED
REALLY GLOOMY AND ANNOYING
Witness, your statement states
that on 22nd December, at 3 a.m.,
you saw the defendant at a place
200 meters away from the crime scene.
Is that true?
Yes, I think it is correct.
What do you base it on?
"Base on"? I saw her, so I said I did.
When the police interviewed you,
did they first ask you,
"Did you see a female
in a beige coat at that time?"
Yeah, I think they did.
You answered you did,
so they confirmed it with you
at the police station again, right?
They asked, "Is this the female
in this coat that you saw?"
Yes. I thought it looked like her
and answered them.
This is Exhibit No. 29, the photo
testimony taken after the murder.
On that day,
the street clothes in the bedroom
was this beige coat only.
In other words, the defendant
had to wear this to go outside.
That's why the police
searched for witnesses
that saw a female in this coat
and got them to think
that it was the defendant.
Objection.
The defense lawyer's question
unjustly discredited
the police's investigation.
I asked this to verify whether
the police arbitrarily led
the witness to give this statement.
Objection overruled.
Thank you.
Witness, please sit down.
Yes, Your Honor.
First of all…
it was impossible for anyone
to see the defendant.
Why did you say that?
This is Defense Exhibit No. 36,
a video taken by the security camera.
The security camera shows the garden
of the victim's house.
The light is the security
sensor light at the victim's garden.
If you open the door,
it triggers the sensor light.
And this is the video taken
between 2 a.m. to 3:45 a.m.
on the day of the incident,
and the sensor light did not light up.
In other words,
it proves that the defendant did not
go in and out from the window.
I see!
Also, we deny the possibility
that the defendant
switched the sensor light off.
At around 4 a.m., when the ambulance crew
came and opened the window,
the light was on.
For the above reasons,
the prosecutor's claim that
the defendant went out of the window
and so didn't get poisoned
does not hold.
As the defendant claims,
between 2 a.m. to 3:45 a.m.,
she was in the bedroom, that is, where…
Mr. Kurokawa?
Defense lawyer?
Sorry, Your Honor.
The defendant was in the bedroom,
that is, where the victim died.
They used a witness to frame her!
Kurokawa will prove her innocence again.
We are going to win.
The prosecutor only relied on
an outsider's witness report.
We can win at this rate.
Are you okay, Mr. Kurokawa?
You suddenly froze just now.
We only proved
the prosecutor's claim invalid.
But something more confusing
came up because of that.
What do you mean?
Mr. Kurokawa.
Do you have a minute?
Why did you call me here out of the blue?
I want to praise you
for the efforts you make.
There is only
circumstantial evidence this time.
I admit that the investigation
organization got impatient.
Getting impatient isn't an excuse.
If we hadn't checked,
the statement the witness was led to give
would've ruined the defendant's life.
We can't let it pass if she has
the tiniest possibility of being guilty.
This is our job.
It's the same for you lawyers
in the opposite sense too.
-The same?
-To protect the defendant's benefit,
you do what they want you to.
If they claim they're innocent,
you defend them for that.
Sometimes, even if you're sure
that the defendant is lying,
you still claim they're innocent.
I do not do that.
If you cannot do that,
you'd better take the badge off.
I defend a client to pursue the truth.
Isn't it the reasonable thing to do?
Mr. Kurokawa.
You had said this to me before.
You said you didn't defend someone
for their sake or for justice.
I don't defend someone
I only want to know the truth.
If that is what you really think,
in the case that the defendant lies,
as a lawyer, what will you do?
Wait a minute.
You're talking like you assume
that this defendant is lying.
What proof do you have--
The room was filled with carbon monoxide.
Why did only the defendant survive?
You think it's suspicious, right?
I'll give you advice.
If your motive to defend someone
is to find out the truth,
you'll never be able to do it.
Good afternoon.
Come… ow… and have a look at this.
Investment scam?
It happened in 2004,
which means it was 15 years ago?
It's a case my partner and I
worked on at that time.
A small company fell victim
and the business went bankrupt.
Charcoal-burning suicide?
We had been preparing for the hearing,
but we were too late.
The victim's family made
the decision to end their own lives.
About the investment scam…
Norikura was involved.
The victims were a family of four.
The parents, a daughter, and a son.
The children were saved.
The younger brother's brain was damaged
and a relative looks after him.
HUSBAND, DEAD
WIFE, DEAD
"Marin Suwa".
You can see the resemblance.
Both her name and age
match the defendant's.
That means Marina has a motive
to kill Mr. Norikura?
Kurokawa.
I could not save the family,
so, maybe you…
TOKYO DETENTION HOUSE
Why do you two look so serious?
Do you want to charge more legal fees?
You'll probably win at this rate,
so I can think about it.
Marina.
We found the connection
between you and Mr. Norikura
before you got married.
Yufuin remembered it and your family too.
So what?
You want to say that I killed Norikura
because I have a motive?
No, that's not what we mean.
So, where is your brother?
We heard that he was saved too.
Who knows? I haven't seen him
since I went to the orphanage.
Marina,
you didn't leave the bedroom
on that night, did you?
I told you he made me take
the sleeping pills and I fell asleep.
You proved that I didn't go out
of the window during the hearing.
In that case,
if you stayed for over an hour
in the room where your husband died,
it's a miracle that you were unharmed.
This time, and when you were little,
you escaped death
from carbon monoxide poisoning twice.
Is this just a coincidence?
I have always been lucky.
I could be married to Norikura
because I was lucky too.
Also,
I'm lucky that he died so early.
Why do you look at me like that?
I said I didn't do it.
It's your job to believe what I say
and prove that I'm innocent.
Right, lawyers?
Yes, we had been looking after him
until two years ago
because nobody else would.
Where is he now?
No idea. His sister suddenly came
and brought him with her.
She got quite rich
working at a night club.
Maybe she admitted him to a hospital.
This is where Marina
and her family were living.
Nothing is left here.
Mr. Kurokawa?
Miss Wakura.
I wonder what I am trying
to investigate now.
What?
The room was filled with carbon monoxide.
Why was Marina unharmed?
If we know how she did it…
Miss Arima is calling.
Hello?
She found Marina's brother.
KANTO MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
TAKASHI SUWA
Marina had paid five years' worth of fees
needed for him to stay here.
But he is in
a pretty serious condition now.
Marina gave them
some false contact details,
so the hospital can't get hold of her.
They're at a loss of what to do.
I knew she was lying.
Yes?
She told us she hadn't seen her brother.
TAKU KUROKAWA'S HOME
Mr. Kurokawa hasn't come out.
CRIME SCENE PHOTO
FIRST FLOOR BEDROOM
MANGANESE - IV - OXIDE
HYDROGEN PEROXIDE
In the case the defendant lies,
as a lawyer, what would you do?
It's your job to believe what I say
and prove that I'm innocent.
If you cannot do that,
you'd better take the badge off.
You haven't had lunch, right?
There you go.
Why did Marina first ask
Mr. Yufuin to be her defense lawyer?
He could have realized who she was.
What can we do for Marina?
It's a wonder
that they let us borrow the house.
It isn't unfavorable to the son too.
I don't know what Kurokawa thinks
about this, though.
Mr. Kurokawa,
I think you'd better not do this.
Miss Wakura, stop him with me.
If anything happens…
Thank you.
Everything is ready.
Are you really sure, Kurokawa?
-I'm counting on you.
-Good.
Put this on and go to the bedroom.
Okay.
Seal the door's gaps.
When you've done that, hang the curtain.
Done.
Good. Light up the briquettes.
The experiment starts now.
In a room with burning briquettes,
there are three reasons why
the victim died but the suspect was saved.
The first one is the shape of the room.
When briquettes burn,
the carbon monoxide produced is heated
and stays at the room's ceiling.
BRIQUETTE CARBON MONOXIDE
CURTAIN
The carbon monoxide is cooled
at the skylight,
its density increases and starts to sink.
The second reason is the curtain
that divides the room.
The sinking carbon monoxide
is blocked by the curtain
and gathers on the window side.
CARBON MONOXIDE, SKYLIGHT
CURTAIN, WINDOW
CO CONCENTRATION - PERCENT
DOOR: 0.02 - WINDOW: 0.31
The bed on the window side is filled
with a high concentration
of carbon monoxide
that can cause death in 30 minutes.
CONCENTRATION OF CO IN AIR
AND SYMPTOMS OF CO POISONING
0.32 PERCENT - HEADACHE IN FIVE MINUTES
DEATH IN 30 MINUTES
CRIME SCENE PHOTO NO. 1
2ND FLOOR BEDROOM
But, of course, as time goes by,
its concentration on the door side
increases too.
DOOR: 0.32 - WINDOW: 1.22
Now, the third reason.
Kurokawa, now.
MANGANESE - IV - OXIDE CRYSTALS
HYDROGEN PEROXIDE
She added manganese dioxide
to hydrogen peroxide to produce oxygen.
Why now?
You can't produce oxygen beforehand.
After the victim was dead
and before the maid came,
this is how the defendant
managed to stay alive.
CO CONCENTRATION DOOR - 0.82
Mr. Kurokawa!
Wakura! Open the windows for ventilation.
I thought I would die.
Gosh!
The experiment is done.
This is a well-prepared
and planned murder.
I think…
maybe I'm not cut out to be a lawyer.
I knew that when you were
aiming to be a lawyer.
TOKYO DETENTION HOUSE
We did an experiment to see
why you survived in that room.
These.
We found the manganese dioxide
at the bottom of the bedroom's tank.
The state of the room
when your parents passed away
gave you the idea to use the curtain
as a screen, right?
Your life and your brother's life
were saved because of that.
You saw my brother?
We did.
Then,
will you not say that he was saved
after seeing his condition?
My father put a partition screen
there just by chance.
I'm sure that
he just didn't want to see
the children he was going to kill.
But only I survived because he did that.
Didn't I tell you last time
that I am lucky?
It was my luck that I met Norikura
at the club I worked at.
It was my luck that I became his wife too.
I could admit my brother into
a hospital, thanks to him too.
Why did you kill Mr. Norikura, then?
Because he found out.
That jerk said this to me.
He told me to forsake my brother.
MARINA NORIKURA
COMING OUT FROM HOSPITAL
MARINA'S BROTHER IN HOSPITAL
I have no obligation
to support your brother too.
Please! My brother can only rely on me!
Listen, Marina.
I've been using dirty methods,
as dirty as sipping muddy water,
to survive until now.
I like you because you tried to
crawl your way up from the bottom.
That's why I made you my wife.
If you want to stay with me,
ignore the weak, like I do!
Forget your worthless and useless brother!
Do you hear me?
At that time…
I made up my mind.
For my brother…
for my parents, who died because of him,
I would kill him.
I decided to kill him
and take everything away from him.
If you confess your crime, I can
plead extenuating circumstances.
-What are you saying?
-We'll appeal to the judge
why you did that…
and I'll do my best to
reduce the sentence--
Don't be ridiculous!
If you'll do your best,
do it to prove that I'm innocent!
If you realized what I did,
you should know how to deceive them!
Get rid of the evidence and everything!
We cannot do that.
Are you stupid?
Do you know how many deaths
Norikura's scams caused?
That jerk laughed and said this
when he got drunk.
Fourteen people he'd swindled had died
the same way my parents did.
But that jerk wasn't punished.
He got some good lawyers and ran away
because of la ack of evidence.
You can get away with crime
because there's no evidence.
Isn't that the world of law?
You're a lawyer. Why did you do
something uncalled-for?
Because you asked Mr. Yufuin
to defend you.
You actually wanted someone
to realize, didn't you,
the pain of having your family
taken away and this is your revenge.
-So you asked Mr. Yufuin--
-Go!
You don't have to come again.
Marina.
You are fired.
I want you to be saved!
The job of a lawyer…
is to protect the client's benefit,
indeed.
But…
Is turning your back to a crime
you committed and running away…
something that benefits you?
Even if we win the case…
if you still bear the sin…
you will never be saved.
Wait!
Mr. Kurokawa is removed
from his post? Why?
I see.
GONZABURO NORIKURA'S MURDER
DEFENDANT, MARINA NORIKURA
Are they all the documents?
Please take over the case for us.
I'm surprised, though.
I knew that you've been
in charge of this case,
but I never expected her
to dismiss you halfway.
Our plan of defense disagrees
with our client's.
You could almost prove her innocence
due to lack of evidence.
Why did you disagree?
Could it be because Mr. Kurokawa
messed it up again?
-There you go.
-Oh, thanks.
It's hot!
WRITTEN STATEMENT OF EXPERT OPINION
Shred the document.
Don't leak it to the police
or the prosecutor.
If you do that, your life
as a lawyer will really be over.
Why do you look at me like that?
Are you surprised that I worry about you?
No.
It comes with criminal defense cases.
Sometimes the defendant lies to you,
sometimes the result is hopeless.
Corporate law is nice.
You can work for honest workers
and organizations
and the office gains profits too.
I like to do this more.
No, I am not worried about you.
I thought you would really be fired
and I looked forward to it.
But you said you were very worried.
Idiot!
Mr. Kurokawa,
the hospital that Marina's brother
stays at just called.
Yes?
His condition got a lot worse
this morning and…
I contacted Marina's new lawyer
and asked him to tell her.
COURTHOUSE
CLOSING ARGUMENT
Please un-cuff the suspect.
As shown, all the prosecutor's claims
are mere guesses.
Someone is innocent until proven guilty,
which is against
the presumption of innocence.
You actually wanted someone
to realize, didn't you?
I want you to be saved!
If you still bear the sin,
you will never be saved.
For the above reasons,
I claim the defendant, Marina Norikura--
Wait.
What is it?
I want to say something.
There will be time for you to talk later.
Do you call it
a self-confession in this case too?
I want to say what I did.
Self-confession?
I killed my husband.
Hey…
Be quiet!
What's going on?
What did you say?
Defendant, do you know
what you are talking about?
Yes.
I can explain everything, including
why and how I killed my husband.
Defendant, be quiet!
Your Honor, please adjourn--
-You are fired.
-What?
Will you defend me again?
I thought I needed no salvation.
But…
What made her confess
her crime in court?
It must be Kurokawa again.
Let's do our best to plead
extenuating circumstances.
Mr. Kurokawa.
Did I do the right thing as a lawyer?
Marina made the decision.
Moreover,
if you don't know
whether it was right or not,
that means it could be right.
You're right.
What's the matter?
You haven't had them?
I suddenly want to eat.
Mind your manners.
KAZUTO YUFUIN
I will be in charge of your case
with Yufuin from now on.
I couldn't fulfil my duty 15 years ago,
so, this time,
I hope I can help you.
I am counting on you.
Miss Wakura,
don't be unhappy because
you aren't in charge of her case.
We have other jobs to do.
I know.
And you asked Miss Arima for this, right?
DOCUMENTARY 24, TOUO UNIVERSITY
STUDENT MURDER CASE
THE DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS.
BURNING CHARCOAL IN A CLOSED SPACE
IS DANGEROUS
A death-row inmate imprisoned
for murder 24 years ago
and his daughter.
Don't mess up my life!
You want to file an appeal for a retrial?
Can they save the victims
of the false conviction?
It's unforgivable to take away
their future too.