TOKYO DETENTION HOUSE
HIROMITSU SHIKINE, DEATH ROW INMATE
TO TV NIPPON, MISS SATOKO ARIMA
See you.
-See you.
Mr. Kurokawa, I'll go home too.
See you.
DOCUMENTARY 24, TOUO UNIVERSITY
STUDENT MURDER CASE
I am sorry!
It's hot…
Oh? Miss Wakura, this…
I asked Miss Arima to lend me that.
If you don't mind,
may I borrow it for a while?
Yes?
Sorry, I'll give it back
right after I make a copy.
The documentary was produced
two years after the incident, right?
Mr. Kurokawa, did you not watch it?
I did when I was in university.
Dr. Akiu told me.
"The murderer was someone else.
Asama was wrongly convicted."
That's what you said.
Why do you think he was wrongly convicted?
Oh?
It's not moving.
I can't get the DVD out either.
What? You said you would
give it back at once!
I'm sorry… Okay, the manual…
-It's hot!
-Ouch!
Sorry…
Hello, Kurokawa? Is it okay to talk?
It's not exactly okay
if you ask if it's okay.
I'll get to the point, then.
I would like you to meet someone tomorrow.
HIROMITSU SHIKINE
"Support Group
of the Innocent Hiromitsu Shikine"?
Yes. Mr. Shikine was sentenced to death
in the Itoe Electric Company
House Murder Case.
Itoe Electric Company House Murder Case.
The murder happened 24 years ago.
Mr. Tamatsukuri has been working
to clear Shikine, his ex-colleague,
of the false charge.
She said working, but the support group
isn't really functioning now.
People have forgotten the case
and there are fewer supporters.
Mr. Shiobara, the lawyer who has been
helping us, passed away last month.
He's been working hard investigating
this case for over 20 years.
Mr. Shikine was arrested at 38 years old,
and he is 62 now.
-What are they?
-Me and Mr. Shikine, who is in prison,
have been exchanging letters
since nine years ago.
I tried to send him a letter
and he replied.
The more we investigate,
the more we found how sloppy
the police's investigation was,
so I want to help in some way.
That's a lot of letters.
And this is the latest letter
that I got yesterday.
He said he found that he had cancer
in a regular body check
and he wouldn't spend the 25th year there,
whether he'll be executed or not.
He has cancer.
I want your help.
If Mr. Shikine was wrongly convicted,
I hope you can help him
when he's still alive.
Help him?
In other words, you want to
file an appeal for a retrial?
Yes!
The late Mr. Shiobara had filed appeal
four times in the past,
but they were all dismissed.
I am not surprised.
Being granted a retrial
is so difficult that it's called
the locked door.
Now, to me, hope is like poison.
This case's nature
is different from others so far.
Don't use your half-baked sense of justice
to mess around with my life!
If he were still alive…
"The ghost at the swamp?"
…taking away the future he has
would be unforgivable.
The murder happened on
December 23, 1995, at 5:08 p.m.
The annual Christmas party was held
at Itoe Electric's company house
and the tragedy happened.
Eight people suddenly started
feeling unwell and six of them died.
Analysis showed that the champagne
they drank during the toast
had a lethal amount
of potassium cyanide added.
Judging by the fact that he brought
the champagne
and other circumstantial evidence,
the police arrested one of
the guests, Hiromitsu Shikine.
After being mercilessly questioned
and persistently interrogated,
Shikine confessed to murder.
The confession became conclusive
due to lack of direct evidence.
The accused is sentenced to death.
Shikine was sentenced to death
in the first trial.
He claimed that the police
forced him to make the confession.
Although he appealed twice,
the Supreme Court confirmed
his death sentence in 2004,
nine years after the murder.
I am Hoshundo Law Office's lawyer,
Kurokawa.
I'm Wakura.
I'm Shikine.
Miss Arima and the support group's
Mr. Tamatsukuri asked me to come.
We'd like to investigate the case again
and see if we can request a retrial.
We know it must be painful for you,
but would you tell us what happened
in the case again?
It happened in the distant past,
so it isn't painful.
But I don't think
I have anything new to tell you.
I have already accepted everything.
But you were forced to make
the self-confession, right?
-If we investigate again--
-In the murder,
my wife was one of the six people
who passed away.
She was reliable
and gave lots of support
to a useless man like me.
Six people, including my wife,
passed away.
In the trial, the judge concluded
that it was my fault.
Since that day,
I felt that I'm already dead.
You have a daughter, don't you?
She had been staying with
your wife's parents after the incident…
Mr. Shikine? Mr. Shikine?
Excuse me. Can anyone help?
-Excuse me!
-Mr. Shikine! Mr. Shikine!
What's the matter?
Sorry, but the interview has to end now.
Are you okay? Can you stand?
-Mr. Kurokawa.
-Yes?
Now, to me…
hope is poison.
Poison?
Maybe I can get out and see my daughter.
A hope like that
will rip my heart apart instead
and makes it hurt more.
Please just leave me alone now.
These are all the documents sent here.
Mr. Shiobara had been pretty enthusiastic
in investigating this.
Isn't it going to take a month
just to read all of them?
But if the man himself
doesn't want a retrial,
there's nothing we can do.
Please grand Mr. Kurokawa
and Miss Wakura permission
to reinvestigate the case.
But it's almost impossible
for the two of them to win
the chance of a retrial on their own.
Originally, you should form
a large defense team
and it only works
if you have many supporters.
The support group is still working.
But his only daughter,
the blood relative, didn't join it, right?
So far, their appeal have been
dismissed four times.
Kurokawa, this case's nature
is different from others so far.
I know, but I want to do everything I can
because Mr. Shikine is still alive.
ITOE ELECTRIC RECREATION ROOM
The place hasn't been used
since the murder.
Mr. Shiobara checked what
the party guests had been doing.
The party started at 5 p.m.
Many guests had been
going in and out to take
food and drinks from home.
Mr. Shikine was suspected
because he brought the champagne
and he stayed at the venue
the longest to do the preparation.
But many people
were going in and out, right?
There's no doubt other residents
and outsiders
had a chance to poison the drinks.
This is where the empty bottle
of the potassium cyanide used
was disposed of.
There was a swamp at that time
and rubbish was illegally disposed of
on a daily basis.
The poison used
was the potassium cyanide
Itoe Electric produced for plating.
Mr. Shikine was the head
of General Affairs Section,
so he could get it easily.
But the management of chemicals
was careless at that time,
so everyone could've taken it out
if they worked at the factory.
The factory is a ten-minute walk away
from the house.
Nobody witnessed Mr. Shikine
disposing of the bottle, right?
Mr. Shikine said that he had been
in the residential area the whole time.
But have a look at this.
MR. SHIKINE WAS SEEN CARRYING FOOD
What the other residents said
before and after Mr. Shikine
made the confession was very different.
DOES NOT REMEMBER IT
It's like they were
putting the blame on Mr. Shikine.
Mr. Toba, at first,
you said you witnessed Mr. Shikine
carrying dishes of food at 4:15 p.m.,
but after Mr. Shikine's confession,
you changed your testimony
and said you saw it wrong.
I don't remember it.
It was a long time ago.
KEN TOBA, WIFE DIED IN THE MURDER
The case had been solved anyway.
I was confused when it happened!
Of course, I would make mistakes!
MICHIYO IIZAKA, HUSBAND DIED IN THE MURDER
My husband was killed
and it was tough for me.
I was still in primary school.
YUMI HARUNA, FATHER DIED IN THE MURDER
I was upset after
what happened to my father.
I don't remember giving a statement.
But what you said in the interview
was recorded here.
Maybe my mother answered it for me.
Anyway, I just want to
forget about the case.
Nobody would talk to us properly.
Maybe the victims' family
do not want to talk
but even former residents
who didn't lose anyone too.
Maybe they feel guilty.
They changed their statements
after Mr. Shikine made the confession
because they all wanted a sense of relief.
Relief?
They didn't lie intentionally,
they just wanted the case
to be settled soon.
They wanted to know clearly
who the murderer was and feel relieved.
I think it's the result of such mentality.
And Mr. Shikine's self-confession
was the perfect escape route.
What should we do next?
Let's meet up with Miss Arima
and go to meet Mr. Shikine's daughter.
Hello.
It's you again?
Mr. Tamatsukuri had told me
about my father's disease,
but I don't want anything
to do with my father
and I won't go to see him.
But Miss Matsugashita, if you
help us, maybe we'll find new facts.
Reiko.
The next appeal for retrial
could be Mr. Shikine's last chance.
Are you telling me…
to continue to sacrifice my own life
for my father?
As the daughter of a death row inmate,
do you know
what life has been like for me?
Please leave.
To me, my father died on the day
his death sentence was confirmed.
I beg you.
Please stop putting me in agony.
Even after she started living
with her grandparents,
life had been tough for her.
It was a serious incident,
so the press followed her around.
At times like this,
if makes me feel guilty and helpless
that I am part of the press.
By the way, have you watched the DVD?
Not yet, because of what Mr. Kurokawa did.
Sorry.
When I produced the program,
Dr. Akiu said to me,
"Don't say the conviction
is possibly false without evidence.
Saying this is trampling on
the feelings of the victim's family."
Dr. Akiu said that?
He's always unfriendly to me, right?
That's why.
-Let's go!
-Wait for me!
Then try to catch me.
It's really difficult to win
the chance for a retrial.
Oh no…
Mr. Shiobara spent 24 years
working on the case,
but he has never won an appeal.
The prosecutors and court
have their honor.
If you don't find decisive new facts,
the locked door won't open.
Even if you find decisive evidence,
they don't accept it in some cases too.
"The north of the company house."
"A crying girl?"
"A short while before the party began,
the boy in Room 302 saw
Mr. Shikine's daughter, Reiko,
comforting a crying girl."
So, I am going to die soon!
"A disturbing conversation."
"Die soon?"
-Guys, have a look at this.
-Did you find something?
It's from the house to where
the bottle was disposed of.
Mr. Shikine showed them the way
and the photos were taken there.
THE SUSPECT TELLS
HOW HE COMMITTED THE CRIME.
Do you feel something is wrong?
-Wrong?
-Yeah.
-I got the results.
-What did you find?
The environment at the time of the murder,
the weather on that day,
the time of sunrise and sunset.
When I input all these data,
I found 16 among the 17 photos
were unnatural.
Photo number six, for example,
it says the photo was taken
at this location
on January 29, at 3:05 p.m.,
but the shadow is too long
for a photo taken at that time.
It couldn't be so long if the sun
didn't shine from the west at 4 p.m.
THE SUN
That means it was an hour earlier?
It isn't too early,
it's in the reversed order.
Except the very first photo.
Looking at the sunlight and the angle,
no doubt the photos were taken
in this order.
What does this fact mean?
Mr. Shikine didn't know where
the poison's bottle was disposed of,
so the police first took him to
the swamp, that is, the destination,
and took photos when they
walked back to the house.
Then they reversed the order
in the crime reconstruction report,
so that it looks like Mr. Shikine
was taking them to the swamp.
The evidence was obviously fabricated.
This is a new fact!
Miss Arima,
this could be the decisive evidence
to win an appeal!
Thank you.
There is no reason for you,
a reporter, to thank me.
Great!
Next, I'll report this case
to make an appeal
about the necessity of having a retrial.
We'll go to meet Mr. Shikine again.
Thanks. Kurokawa, please continue
to help on this.
Okay.
Dr. Akiu, we'll go as well.
I have to throw a wet blanket,
but it's hard to win with only this.
Why do you say so?
The prosecution office and the court
work for the government.
They are extremely stubborn.
Moreover, if you want to
clear someone of false charges,
you might have to do it from scratch.
Not everyone is happy about
bringing up a closed case again.
TOKYO DETENTION HOUSE
We found evidence that
the police falsified something
in the investigation.
It's a new fact
that hasn't been found until now.
I see.
You must have put lots of efforts in it.
So, we want to file an appeal
for a retrial.
A retrial?
Mr. Shikine?
Yes?
May we start the preparation?
Yeah. I think it's great.
Thank you.
In a murder 24 years ago,
a man who was 38 years old
at that time was sentenced to death.
New facts were found in the Itoe
Electric Company House Murder.
Death row inmate, Hiromitsu Shikine,
currently has cancer…
I hope it will get everybody
talking about the case.
I think it will appeal
to the prosecutor's office and the court.
Mr. Kurokawa,
you are exactly like
what I heard in the rumors.
Miss Wakura,
I am very grateful to you too.
But we still have to continue
to investigate this.
Whether the sentence was fair or not…
Mr. Kurokawa?
The lawyer for Mr. Shikine…
Sorry.
…is Hoshundo Lawyer Office's…
PUBLIC PROSECUTORS OFFICE
So…
What is the matter
that you called us here for today?
The Itoe Electric Company House
Murder Case 24 years ago.
I wasn't involved in the case myself,
but the prosecutor in charge
is a Chief Public Prosecutor
and my superior.
What about that?
What Mr. Kurokawa is doing is very bold.
The Supreme Court had concluded the case,
but he says no to it.
I think the act itself might affect
the court's impression of him.
Is that a threat?
Saying it's a threat makes me
uncomfortable, Mr. Beppu.
Mr. Ibusuki.
I've never found Kurokawa pleasant.
He keeps pushing me around
and I'm sick of it.
However, even so,
he is one of our lawyers.
Whatever they'll do to defend Mr. Shikine,
I will take the responsibility.
Excuse me.
Mr. Beppu, is this okay to have
a fight with him for Kurokawa?
It isn't okay!
We have to abandon Kurokawa if necessary!
What?
I'm Bonshu Weekly's reporter, Nose.
Mr. Shikine's daughter,
please say a word about the case.
I'm not involved in it. Excuse me.
I'm TV Maicho's reporter.
May I interview you about the Itoe
Electric Company House Murder Case?
We got lots of reactions.
Everyone is concerned about
the forgotten case.
Mr. Shikine agreed to let us file
an appeal for a retrial
and we'll process it at once.
Mr. Kurokawa?
You are pulling a long face.
Oh, I'm just a bit…
That reminds me. Should we tell
his daughter about the appeal?
I'll go to see Reiko myself
and tell her about it.
Reiko?
I was going to visit you--
Who do you think you are?
You did something uncalled-for…
so the press has started
to follow me around again!
Rumors are spreading
in my neighborhood and at my office!
Just cut it out!
Don't…
Don't use your half-baked sense of justice
to mess around with my life!
-Welcome.
-There you go.
Hey.
-You're here!
-You called me out.
-Oolong tea, please.
-Sure.
You won't have alcohol?
Be grateful that I'm sitting
next to someone who will pester me
-when she's drunk.
-All right.
What do you want?
When I produced the documentary
of the case 11 years ago,
you shouted at me, didn't you?
You said I was trampling on
other people's feelings.
Mr. Shikine's daughter said
the same thing to me today.
She told me not to wield
the sword of my half-baked justice.
Did she?
There you go, sir.
When I joined the television station,
I had quite some passion about my dream.
I was enthusiastic and thought
the press existed for society.
But my boss…
he told me to follow stories
that get high ratings
and give the customers what they like.
He kept saying it is what the press is.
But…
I hated it.
I thought solving a case to get the truth
was how to help the victims get revenge,
and it was my mission to do so.
The truth, the press,
justice, family of the victim.
In the end…
maybe I haven't changed at all
the whole time.
No, you haven't changed at all.
But what's wrong with that?
You seem to have mistaken something,
so I'll say a word.
The documentary you produced
was simply of bad quality.
There was no scientific evidence
and it only relied on guesses.
You didn't verify the facts enough either.
It's crap.
But I don't deny that
you have enthusiasm and passion.
That's exactly why
I still help Kurokawa
with his unreasonable requests.
In that case, be nicer to me.
Don't be such a baby.
Emotion and reason are different.
Hey!
Shikine, are you okay? Hey!
Mr. Shikine.
Mr. Kurokawa and Miss Wakura.
Are you okay?
Well, my body doesn't do
what I want it to now.
I can't be lying in bed. It will be
my daughter's birthday soon.
Yes?
I'm thinking about buying her
the bicycle that she wants,
but my wife says it's expensive
and told me to buy something else.
That's right!
I have to buy her a cake too.
Our neighbors' children will come
to her birthday party.
I hope she'll celebrate it
with lots of friends.
Mr. Shikine, actually…
Mr. Shikine,
how old will your daughter be?
Ten years old.
She started to become
a little rebellious lately
and she doesn't talk to me a lot.
Is that so?
But I'm sure she'll be happy
if you buy her a bicycle.
You think she will?
I have to convince my wife, then.
A bicycle will make her happy, right?
Since the interview the other day…
I've been thinking
that he wasn't all right.
I think he has Ganser syndrome.
Ganser syndrome?
He's been living in prison for a long time
and lost contact with the outside world…
so he is mentally exhausted…
and is trapped in his fantasy
and his past memories.
Especially for death row inmates,
they're facing the fear of not
knowing when they will be executed.
Mr. Kurokawa.
Eleven years ago…
my childhood friend killed himself
after he was found guilty.
"If he were still alive…"
It's what I always think.
We would find a way if he were alive.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
I received this today after all these.
The written appointment
of defense counsel is attached.
Thanks.
I wrote a letter to tell him
that I'd ask you to reinvestigate it
and asked him to agree to have
a retrial. This is his reply.
Looking at the date,
it seems that he wrote it
before you went to see him.
He wrote it before he had Ganser syndrome.
THANK YOU, MISS ARIMA
I WANT TO GET OUT OF THIS PLACE
FEBRUARY 27, 2019, HIROMITSU SHIKINE
Miss Arima, Mr. Shikine did feel
your enthusiasm.
Should we start filing
an appeal for retrial?
No.
Only the photos of the crime
reconstruction aren't enough.
We have to find some new facts
that are more important.
Let's inspect the documents again.
Mr. Kurokawa, get all the documents
in your room here too.
Okay, I'll do it now. Excuse me.
-I'll help you.
-Thank you.
Miss Wakura is working towards
the same direction as Mr. Kurokawa
without us realizing it.
Yeah.
I'll go to see the people involved again.
Miss Wakura.
-Mr. Kurokawa, cool down a bit.
-Oh, thank you.
Have some tea, Mr. Yufuin.
"The ghost at the swamp?"
What?
Miss Arima got this letter in June
eight years ago,
when a park was built on the swamp
where the bottle was disposed of.
Did you find something curious?
"I read a news article that says
a park will be built on the swamp."
That reminds me. My daughter
had told me something in the past.
Rumor has it that
there was a ghost at the swamp.
A large shadow floated on the swamp
and you would die if you saw it.
"My daughter was very frightened.
The ghost story is an innocent one,
but I think it will disappear
along with the swamp."
"You die if you see it?"
What's the matter, Miss Wakura?
Mr. Shiobara wrote some notes
when he interviewed the children.
Where are they?
Oh, I think the notebook is on my desk.
Miss Wakura!
Found it!
Have a look at this.
"A crying girl."
Has it got anything to do with that?
Miss Wakura, this could be
important evidence!
If rubbish had been disposed of
around this area…
The swamp is ahead.
I knew it!
The girl saw a ghost because she was here.
The problem is who saw it.
Let's check with Miss Matsugashita.
-Sorry for coming so late.
-Sorry.
What's the matter? I'm busy.
Please tell us about the ghost
at the swamp near the company houses.
-A ghost?
-Well…
When you were in primary school
and the murder happened,
there was a rumor that there was
a ghost at the swamp, right?
It was too long ago and I don't remember.
Wait…
Do you remember the day of the murder?
Didn't a girl who lived in
the same neighborhood tell you that
she saw a ghost at the swamp?
If we know who she is, maybe we can
clear your father's false charges.
What?
Excuse me. Why are we here?
You'll know if you come.
Yumi Haruna?
Reiko?
Why?
They asked me to come here.
We will tell you the details inside.
-The things are ready.
-Okay.
I am sorry about the other day.
Will you explain everything to me now?
What are you going to do here?
What do you think this is?
What?
-Water?
-We reconstructed the swamp.
The swamp one kilometer away,
which is a park now.
What do you do this for?
You'll know when you see it.
Please come with me.
Miss Haruna, please stand here.
Look in front of you.
On the day of the murder,
you saw the same thing as this
at the swamp, didn't you,
Miss Haruna?
What was that?
It is called a Brocken specter.
Brocken specter?
When there is fog on top of a mountain
and strong light is shone from
behind the observer,
water droplets in the air
refracts the light
and forms a rainbow-colored halo
around the observer's shadow.
The phenomenon frightened people
and it was called Brocken-Gespenst,
but actually,
it also occurs on level ground
under specific conditions.
For example, in the evening,
when temperature drops rapidly
and a dense fog forms
on waters like a swamp.
If there is no wind,
other conditions are met
and the light
of the setting sun is strong,
the same phenomenon can be observed.
I'm not surprised that
children would think that
it really was a monster.
The experiment is done.
This is the data of the weather
of the day of the murder.
Temperature dropped rapidly after 4 p.m.
There was only half an hour
after that with no fog and no wind.
The setting sun was shining
on the swamp at that time.
If you had seen the ghost,
it shows that you were at
the rubbish dump at the swamp
from 4 p.m. to 4:30 p.m.,
when all conditions were met.
Wait a minute. Why did you go there?
Miss Haruna.
The report says that
on the day of the murder,
you were at home with your mother
until the party started.
But you actually went to the swamp.
You went there to dispose of the bottle
that contained potassium cyanide.
Yumi?
Is that true?
I am sorry.
Reiko.
My mother told me to go there
and dispose of the bottle.
My father was laid off,
then my mother started to work at
Itoe Electric's factory
and we moved to the company's house.
But our family became a mess
because of my violent father.
That day, my mother didn't allow me
to join the Christmas party,
but in the evening…
Go and throw this away
at the rubbish dump at the swamp.
After you do this job for me,
you can go to the Christmas party.
Wear gloves.
Make sure you don't touch it directly.
I went to the swamp as I was told
and disposed of the bottle.
It was when I saw the ghost at the swamp.
Then, when I came back,
the murder happened.
My mother probably wanted to kill
my father so much that she did that.
I didn't realize that
I helped her destroy evidence
until after a very long time.
What the heck?
What was the last 24 years
of my life, then?
I wrongly assumed
that my father was a murderer…
and I spent all the time hating him,
until now.
CLOSED HEARING OF APPEAL FOR RETRIAL
My mother worked part-time
for Itoe Electric,
at General Affairs Section,
like Mr. Shikine.
It should be very easy for her…
to get the potassium cyanide.
In other words, you're saying that
your mother, Azusa Haruna,
was the culprit
who poisoned the champagne?
Why did you keep quiet about this?
I…
I felt guilty about this…
but I swept it under the carpet.
My mother passed away
ten years after the murder.
And…
I tried to convince myself that
the case was over.
Also…
I thought it would be okay
if I kept quiet.
For my mother's sake,
I thought I shouldn't let anyone know
about the crime we committed.
We know your story clearly now.
We will have a careful discussion
about this case again
and inform you our decision later.
We hope you would give this
a very serious consideration.
Because the witness statement
is very clear.
The court will decide whether
the statement is clear or not.
Your Honor.
May I say a few words before we finish?
Go ahead.
The reason that…
Miss Yumi Haruna came today
to make this painful statement
is because…
she cares about Mr. Shikine
and his daughter.
She can't let them remain
a death row inmate
and the daughter of a death row inmate.
The incident happened 24 years ago.
Maybe many people in the world
have already forgotten about the case,
but Mr. Shikine
and his daughter Reiko
have never forgotten about it.
Mr. Shikine wants help now.
Reiko is suffering because of
the false charges against her father.
Mr. Hiromitsu Shikine is innocent.
Even though he cannot take back
the 24 years he lost,
taking away the future he has…
would be unforgivable.
Please don't be biased by
the wrong conviction in the past
and make a decision based on the truth.
We strongly hope you would do so.
SEVERAL DAYS LATER
I took it out!
The next story.
An appeal for a retrial
of the Itoe Electric Company House
Murder Case 24 years ago
was dismissed by the court.
Dismissed?
The locked door
didn't open this time too.
This is what happened.
It's disappointing.
"The appeal for a retrial is dismissed."
The reason is,
"No new evidence found
has been clear enough
to declare appellant innocent."
It's so bitter!
Reiko.
Reiko?
Are you Reiko?
Dad.
I…
I am sorry!
It must have been tough for you.
Dad!
I am sorry!
I'm sorry that I couldn't trust you.
I am sorry.
You have grown up.
Reiko.
COURTHOUSE
THE DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS
THE FINAL CHAPTER
A murder that is very similar
to the one 11 years ago.
I want to investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
The two separations that came.
Maybe it can be settled.
Who killed her, then?
I think I can share your pain.
-Mr. Kurokawa!
-Miss Wakura!
I never wanted to kill anyone!
The murderer is another person
and they incriminated someone.
Maybe probatio diabolica is possible.
If he really was innocent,
I wish he hadn't killed himself
and stayed alive.
You don't know how cold a dead body is.