Eleven years ago,
on December 16, 2007,
in a ruin in Kanagawa Prefecture,
the dead body of a young woman
covered in stab wounds was found.
She was identified as 20-year-old
Ayaka Akiu from her belongings.
Ayaka was stabbed in her chest
and stomach six times
and a hole was dug deep into her throat.
The police arrested her boyfriend,
Touo University second-year
science and engineering student
Daisuke Asama.
After he was arrested, Asama
denied the charges until the end,
but the victim's blood was detected
on the shoes and clothes
in his locker at the university.
Asama is obsessed with ruins,
and from his laptop,
photos of the crime scene were found.
Asama was prosecuted
due to the many physical
and circumstantial pieces of evidence.
He was sentenced to life in prison
in Yokohama District Court's trial.
He did not make an appeal and…
I AM INNOCENT
…it had been reported that
the victim was being stalked at that time.
WE HAVE INFO THAT SHE WAS WORRIED
ABOUT STALKING AT THE TIME
Was the court's decision
to find her boyfriend, Asama, guilty
actually the correct one?
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
-Let's have lunch now.
-I'll make some tea.
-Mr. Kurokawa, actually…
-Yes?
I bought too much food,
so I packed one extra lunch box.
Would you like to have it?
It is the day before payday.
Thank you.
Let's have lunch together, then.
Sorry, I'd like to do some studying alone.
I guess not today either.
What is it? Kurokawa shut himself
in his room again?
I was going to treat him
to grilled meat for lunch.
Wait. That's my idea.
And I would've been the one to pay.
I want kalbi.
It seems the dismissal of the appeal
for a retrial the other day
is still affecting him.
It made him realize
how difficult it is to reinspect
a case from the past.
So, Mr. Kurokawa wants to inspect
the case from 11 years ago again?
He should be thinking about
a posthumous retrial.
But isn't that more difficult
than a regular retrial?
-Oh, Ms. Arima.
-Hello.
What's the matter?
-Where's Kurokawa?
-He's in his room.
TAKU KUROKAWA'S HOME
Oh, Ms. Arima. Good afternoon.
Do you know that February murder
in a riverbed in Ota City?
I think a young woman was killed
and her body was found?
I saw on the news that
the suspect was arrested already.
The victim was stalked, right?
Yes, the guy confessed to his crime
and has been prosecuted.
But there is a problem.
I can't tell you where I got this,
but it's a photo
of the wound on the victim.
She was stabbed in her throat.
Don't you think it looks like
the stab wound on Ayaka Akiu
from the case 11 years ago?
That's…
TOUO UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDER CASE
I want to investigate the case
thoroughly and fight.
When my son is in agony…
Please be there for him.
It may not necessarily be the same.
Maybe we can clear Senior Asama's
false charges and avenge Ayaka!
Who killed her, then?
You and I are fundamentally different.
The murder happened on
February 6, 2019, around 1 p.m.
Under an overhead railway
in Tamagawa, Ota City,
21-year-old Kyoka Hanamaki,
student of an arts university in Tokyo,
was found stabbed to death.
Before the murder,
the victim had been stalked by someone,
and she had reported it
to the police several times.
After the investigation,
a worker at an auto parts factory
near the victim's home,
33-year-old Junpei Fujita,
was deemed the suspect.
The victim's student ID card
was found in Fujita's home.
KYOKA HANAMAKI
A sketchbook stained with blood was found
at a rubbish dump
near the auto parts factory.
I did not do it.
But we heard that you confessed to murder.
During questioning,
the detective kept torturing me,
so I had to.
But you admit that you
had been stalking the victim, right?
I only watched her from far away.
I fell in love with her when I first
saw her sketching in the park.
Since then, I started taking photos of her
and wandered around near her home.
But I wasn't a stalker.
Hundreds of photos of her
that you took secretly were found
on the laptop at your home, right?
Also, her student ID card
and a sketchbook stained with blood.
I picked up her student ID card
in the park.
I wanted to give it back to her,
but I wasn't brave enough to talk to her.
But I really don't know anything
about the sketchbook.
Mr. Fujita,
you're from Ibaraki Prefecture, right?
Yes.
My parents had passed away,
so I don't really go back.
After finishing high school,
you left your hometown
and started working part-time.
When you were 22 years old,
that is, 11 years ago,
you lived in Kanagawa.
Yes, I did.
Eleven years ago,
there was also a female university student
murdered in Kanagawa.
This case is similar to the one
11 years ago in many ways.
What?
Mr. Fujita.
Eleven years ago,
on December 15, 2007…
where were you, and what were you doing?
Mr. Kurokawa.
What the heck?
Do you suspect me?
Please calm down.
Don't be ridiculous!
I was told that a lawyer
who isn't court-appointed would come,
and I expected better!
This is very important.
Please answer my question.
How would I remember
something from so long ago?
I did not kill anyone!
Not 11 years ago and not now!
All right, then.
Mr. Fujita.
Please let me defend you
as your defense lawyer.
Yes?
I personally…
want to investigate the case
thoroughly and fight.
Mr. Kurokawa.
You never know.
We won't know whether it's related
to the case 11 years ago or not
if we don't investigate it.
For now, there are three…
no, there are four possibilities.
Four possibilities?
One, it's just a coincidence.
Whether Fujita was the murderer
this time or not,
the victim's neck wound and the case
just happened to be similar.
The second possibility is a copycat.
But the wound wasn't revealed
to the public in the case 11 years ago.
Everyone involved knew about it.
The people in the investigation
organizations, the press,
and, of course, the victim's family too.
And…
Fujita could be involved in this murder
and the one 11 years ago.
The fourth and last one
is the real murderer is another person
and they deflected blame.
This time, on the man Fujita…
and on Daisuke Asama 11 years ago.
But the probability of that
is significantly low.
Even if the same person
committed both murders,
they have no reason to wait for 11 years.
Go now if you've finished
what you want to say.
Kurokawa will be in charge of this case.
If the probability isn't zero,
I'll investigate it thoroughly too.
Kyoichiro.
It's the photo we took the other day.
Please put it in your lab.
It's stupid. I don't want it.
You made me go and hang out
with you and I didn't want to.
That's a pack of lies.
You had quite a lot of fun.
Mr. Akiu, you've been
shutting yourself in your lab.
Isn't it nice to go out for a change?
And you two go out too often.
A student's duty is to study.
Okay, we know that.
We'll go have lunch now. Take it.
-Let's go, Daisuke!
-Sorry, Mr. Akiu!
Hello?
Dr. Kyoichiro Akiu, I presume?
Speaking.
I am the Public Prosecutors Office's
Kurokawa.
Sorry about calling suddenly.
Actually, I would like to meet you
personally and talk about something.
It's somewhere around here?
On that security camera,
the victim who came here to sketch
and the suspect who was watching her
were caught eight times in a month.
He said that he found her
student ID card in this park too.
Two weeks before the murder,
they wrote these on their respective
social media accounts.
This is the victim's.
KYOKA: OH, NO. I LOST
MY STUDENT ID CARD… HOW AWFUL
This is the suspect's.
FUJITA: I FOUND SOMETHING AMAZING
SHOULD I KEEP IT OR MAKE IT MY TREASURE?
Excuse me.
FUJITA: THE SETTING SUN
It's here.
Besides the photos of the victims
Fujita secretly took, this photo
caught the prosecutor's attention too.
He thought Fujita came to check out
where he'd commit murder.
-It's unnatural.
-Yes?
If he really was the murderer,
would he upload a photo that might
make people suspect him on purpose?
You mean the prosecutor prosecuted
Fujita without a proper reason?
The same thing happened
in the case 11 years ago.
At that time,
just because Asama had been
to the ruin where Ayaka was killed,
the prosecutor concluded
that he went to check out the place.
I'm sorry, but please return
to the office without me.
What are you going to do?
I want to think alone. I'm sorry.
Is Mr. Kurokawa all right?
He always does things his own way.
I do wonder who he is like!
-Yes, exactly!
-Oh!
Oh, Ms. Wakura! It's been a while
since we last saw each other!
Your friend?
This is Mr. Kurokawa's mother.
This is the first time we've met, right?
I am Taku's mother.
Thank you for helping my son.
I am Kinosaki.
Mr. Kurokawa is the one
who helps me a lot.
What's the matter?
You look like the ducklings
that float in a bathtub!
You're so adorable!
Thank you… I think?
What are you here for today?
I'm here because I haven't been here
to say hello so far,
but Taku is out, so I thought
I would leave at once,
but our conversation got lively!
Yeah, it's been an hour.
Well, two hours already.
-Two hours…
Yes?
Ms. Wakura, do you have a minute?
Ms. Wakura, where is Kurokawa?
He wants to think alone,
so we came back first.
In that case, we'll count on you
to entertain his mom until she leaves.
What?
She is nice and cheerful,
but she keeps going on and on.
We can't even work,
but we can't be rude to the wife
of the SPO's Deputy Prosecutor-General.
I think she likes you pretty much.
She likes me?
Mr. Kurokawa just brought me
to his home against my will
and I only had supper there once.
But from what we've heard,
that isn't the case.
-She mentioned engagement gifts.
-Engagement?
She also talked about the colors
of dresses you'd wear for the wedding.
Dresses? Wedding?
And she wants to have grandchildren soon.
Grandchildren!
Ms. Wakura,
I would like to have a brief look
at the room Taku lives in.
Do you mind?
But I'm not the person
that you should ask.
It's not a problem at all! I give you
the right as the head of the office.
Ms. Wakura, please take Mrs.…
I mean, Kurokawa's mother there!
-Please take her there.
-Well then, please follow me.
-Okay.
That's right. Show her the way…
Wow!
My, my…
I think he should tidy up
the place a little, though.
Yeah.
Oh, this…
TOUO UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDER CASE
It's Dai's case 11 years ago.
Dai?
You know Mr. Daisuke Asama?
He was Taku's best friend.
His mother was my friend too.
This case was what shaped
Taku's current way of life
and his relationship with his father too.
ASAMA FAMILY GRAVE
Dai was two years older than Taku.
Taku was a shy boy and Dai was like
his reliable elder brother.
Let's do it!
I think Dai had a great influence
on Taku's current way of life.
I AM INNOCENT.
Taku was serious to a fault to begin with
and he didn't like to do things
differently than others.
Until the murder happened,
he aimed to be a public prosecutor,
like his father.
Is that why
Deputy Prosecutor-General Kurokawa
is not happy about Mr. Kurokawa
defending criminal case suspects?
My husband complains about various things,
but it doesn't mean he thinks
that Taku's way of life is wrong.
Instead, he worries about Taku
more than anyone else.
And he cheers for Taku.
They are in different positions,
but the enthusiasm
they both have for their work
must be the same.
PUBLIC PROSECUTORS OFFICE
It's the first time
we're meeting like this,
Dr. Akiu.
How can I help you?
Please have a look at this.
It's the confidential document
we have and it hasn't been revealed.
Directly under the Prosecutors Office?
As you know, currently,
we decide whether we prosecute
someone or not based on
the evidence provided by the police.
But there are many problems too.
Their investigation relies
on circumstantial evidence and confessions
or their inspection is careless
and lacks scientific proof.
To improve these,
Mr. Kurokawa plans to set up
this investigation organization.
We would like you to join it
as one of the leading members.
Why me?
The reason that Taku Kurokawa
has been able to win these cases so far
is because you've been helping him.
Dr. Akiu,
since the case from 11 years ago,
you've been having doubts about
how investigations are conducted,
and I understand that.
But the feelings you and my son have
may not necessarily be the same.
Am I right?
KILL ME TOO
MURDERER
Thank you for coming.
-Sorry, I stayed too long.
-Don't worry about it.
But you really aren't going to see
Mr. Kurokawa?
Ms. Wakura.
Please continue to help Taku.
When my son is in agony,
please be there for him.
I'm counting on you.
I will.
See you! I will come again!
Welcome back.
Have you been waiting for me?
Yeah.
My mother texted just now.
Seems that she had been bothering you.
No.
So?
Yes?
You said you wanted to think alone,
so I've been waiting.
I thought you wanted a listener
after organizing your thoughts.
I'm sorry.
Sorry that I kept you waiting,
but I haven't organized my thoughts.
It doesn't have to be organized.
Maybe you'll feel relieved
after you tell me.
Moreover…
I don't know whether I can give you
support when you're in agony,
but I think I can share your pain.
By investigating this case,
you want to grasp some clues
about the case 11 years ago, right?
I think we only have to find
the real murderer.
But…
this idea has a problem, right?
Why do you say that?
Because I wanted to believe…
that Senior Asama was innocent.
After I became a lawyer…
no matter who the suspect
or the accused was…
I've always thought that we had to
find out the truth by investigating.
That's why I know it in my head.
Whether Senior Asama is innocent or not…
is actually unknown.
But if he really was innocent…
I wish he hadn't killed himself
and stayed alive.
Sorry, my thoughts are a mess
and they're unorganized.
What's wrong with that?
Yes?
You want to trust him,
but you don't know the truth.
That's why we'll investigate.
What's wrong with that?
That's what you've been doing so far.
Let's first handle the murder
that happened recently.
If Mr. Fujita is falsely charged,
that means the murderer is someone else
and that person could be the real culprit
of the murder 11 years ago.
And then
you'll be able…
to clear Mr. Asama
of the false charges 11 years ago.
You are right.
We have no time to stop here.
We'll do the pretrial conference
procedure soon.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
The phone is ringing.
Okay.
Hello. Hoshundo Law Office.
Oh, Ms. Arima?
What?
A second dead body?
A young woman was found dead
on a mountain in Ibaraki Prefecture.
The MPD arrested the suspect
Junpei Fujita again,
-who was charged with another murder…
-See you.
-Goodbye.
18-year-old Nana Yamashiro's body
was found a month after she died.
Nana Yamashiro was killed first.
NANA YAMASHIRO: DIED ON 4 FEB
KYOKA HANAMAKI: DIED ON 6 FEB
The case suddenly drew attention
as a serial murder.
But Fujita denies killing both of them.
The shape of the weapon matches
the wound on their necks
and what Fujita did at that time too.
Yamashiro's estimated time of death
was between 3 and 5 February,
and he suddenly returned to Ibaraki.
But would he kill someone while
on a trip to visit his parents' grave?
Maybe he went to visit their grave
while he was there to murder?
Nana Yamashiro was a runaway girl
from Ibaraki.
After she left high school
half a year ago,
she left home and lived in Tokyo.
You don't know her, do you?
I don't know her at all.
You went back to Ibaraki around
the period of time she was murdered.
Did you come into contact with her?
Will things be easier for me
if I admit to the crime?
I've been telling him
that I didn't kill her,
but the detective shouts at me every day.
My sleeping hours are cut down.
If I say that I did it,
will I be relieved from this situation?
Please don't give up, Mr. Fujita.
In addition to Kyoka Hanamaki's murder,
the prosecutor will charge you
with Nana Yamashiro's murder too.
But I think we can still fight.
The police and the prosecutor
think your motive
for murdering Kyoka Hanamaki
had something to do with
you being her stalker.
In that case,
you would have no motive for killing
Nana Yamashiro, who you didn't know.
But you can't prove it, can you?
You can't prove that
I really don't know the girl at all.
We will look for clues.
So, Mr. Fujita, please don't give up.
Okay, we have come as far as Ibaraki.
It's freezing here.
It must be even colder at the crime scene.
It's impossible to find clues to prove
that he didn't know Yamashiro.
It's the so-called probatio diabolica.
Probatio diabolica?
It's easy to prove something that exists.
For example, if we want to prove
Mr. Fujita had seen the victim,
we only have to look for witnesses
or security camera videos.
But if we want to prove
that he had never seen the victim…
There is no evidence, right?
They'd never met in the first place.
That's why, basically, it's impossible.
Maybe we'll notice something
when we go to the scene of the murder.
IBARAKI MOUNT KEIYA MOUNTAIN TRAIL
-Oh…
-Watch your steps, Mr. Kurokawa!
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. There aren't any bears
around here, are there?
I think there are Asian black bears,
but they should be hibernating.
-What?
There's a lemon field nearby.
Let's go and ask
if anyone had seen anything.
Okay.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Wait, young man. It's for you.
Thank you, ma'am.
We didn't gain anything.
But I've gained a lot.
Look!
We aren't here for fun.
But it's really amazing
that lemons can grow
in the cold weather on the mountain.
No, the farmer told me just now
that this area is special.
The temperature
doesn't drop much at night.
Not even at night?
It's impossible to find clues to prove
that he didn't know Yamashiro.
It's the so-called probatio diabolica.
Would he kill someone while
on a trip to visit his parents' grave?
Mr. Kurokawa!
What's the matter?
Mr. Isawa, you did an excellent job.
Maybe probatio diabolica is possible.
FIVE O'CLOCK IN THE MORNING
-Pan it.
-Okay.
TOUO UNIVERSITY
Dr. Akiu, thanks for helping us today.
It's the base station. Launch the balloon.
Roger that.
IBARAKI MOUNT KEIYA MOUNTAIN TRAIL
We launched the balloon
to measure the temperature.
The temperature is minus one degrees C
at 50 meters above ground,
but at 300 meters above ground,
where the body was found,
it's five degrees Celsius higher.
Just as I thought.
Why does that happen?
It's a natural phenomenon
called a thermal belt.
THERMAL BELT
On a clear night,
cold air flows down the mountain slope
and the air on the ground cooled
by radiative cooling
stays on the ground.
The layer of cool air stops
after it reaches a certain level
and doesn't go farther up.
As a result, the temperature
halfway up the mountain
is higher than the mountain's base.
It's the reverse of the usual case.
When the body was dumped,
the mountain's climate could have
caused such a phenomenon.
But the police
should've taken that into account.
When doing the autopsy,
the coroner deduces the temperature
on the mountain based on that at the foot.
It's common practice.
On average, the temperature
on a mountain drops 0.65 degrees Celsius
every 100 meters up.
But in this case,
because of the thermal belt,
the temperature at the crime scene
was much higher than they deduced.
If the temperature was higher,
of course, the dead body
decayed faster too.
In other words,
the estimated date of death
was much earlier.
That means the day that
Nana Yamashiro was killed
is later than
the current deduced date, right?
This temperature difference
should give it a one-week difference.
Kyoka Hanamaki's body
was found on 6 February.
Two days later, on 8 February,
Mr. Fujita was arrested.
The date the police estimated
Nana Yamashiro died
was around 4 February.
If we move it a week later…
Yamashiro's estimated date of death
is 11 February.
2/4 NANA YAMASHIRO, 2/6 KYOKA HANAMAKI
2/8 FUJITA ARRESTED
Then Mr. Fujita couldn't have killed her
because he was arrested.
The real culprit is another person.
The experiment is done.
It isn't related to the case.
It's only about the environment
on the mountain.
Huh?
Dr. Akiu?
There's something wrong with him today.
Wait a minute, Dr. Akiu.
What did you mean by that?
It's literally what I said.
It was only a theory.
If you don't actually inspect
the dead body,
you can't say that you can prove
Fujita's innocence.
But if Nana Yamashiro
was possibly alive after 4 February,
we can look for witnesses
that had seen her--
You'll lose if you can't find anyone.
Even if you can, there's
no guarantee that you'll win.
Kurokawa, this is the limit
of what you can do as a lawyer
and what I can do to help you.
Compared to the evidence
and first-hand data
the investigation organizations have,
it's significantly less accurate.
But so far, we've been able to prove
our point thanks to you.
You were just lucky.
But this is the last time.
Huh?
Very soon, the Public Prosecutors Office
will set up
a specialized agency
to conduct forensic investigations
that's independent from the police.
I was invited to join it.
By your own father.
The Prosecutors Office
is a government organization.
I can conduct experiments that are
much more accurate than before.
But the culprit behind
the murder 11 years ago
and the culprit behind this murder
could be the same person.
We can almost do it. Very soon…
maybe we can clear Senior Asama's
false charges and avenge Ayaka!
Kurokawa.
You don't know how cold a dead body is.
To us, her family,
nobody can replace Ayaka.
She was cheerful, lively,
and she laughed a lot.
The exact opposite of me.
But Ayaka was suddenly taken from us.
She was killed!
Suddenly. In an unreasonable way.
Her body got cold,
and she couldn't smile anymore.
Do you know how trying it is
for us, her family?
Do you know how much we hate
the murderer who killed Ayaka?
But maybe Senior Asama didn't kill her.
Who killed her, then?
Find the murderer right now
and prove that they killed her!
The investigation was careless.
The forensic inspection was imperfect.
That's why we've been unhappy.
But there's a definite difference
between you and me.
You want to believe
that Daisuke Asama was innocent,
but I…
the victim's family,
doesn't mind that Asama
was the murderer as a result.
Instead of the truth,
having a ready answer can stop our agony.
I'm not good enough to be a scientist.
Feel free to be disappointed in me.
COURTHOUSE
Ms. Arisa Nasu.
DEFENDANT WITNESS CROSS-EXAMINATION
On 10 February,
you met the victim, Nana Yamashiro,
in Tokyo.
-Am I right?
-Yes.
ARISU NASA
AQUAINTANCE OF NANA YAMASHIRO
I hung out with Nana from time to time.
Was there anything wrong with her
at that time?
She said she would get a sum of money
and treat me to a meal.
I thought she could've been
doing something risky.
Thank you.
As the video of the experiment about
the thermal belt had shown just now,
Nana Yamashiro was alive
after 3 to 5 February,
the date of death estimated by the police,
and the witness has proved that.
Like Nana Yamashiro, you've left home
and kept moving from one place
to another in Tokyo, right?
Yeah. At my friends' place.
How do you make a living?
I work parttime sometimes.
Or get pocket money.
Pocket money?
-From men?
-What?
Objection.
The question is not related to the case,
and it insults the witness.
Your Honor, judges,
the reliability of her statement
is concerned.
The witness had been caught
multiple times for compensated dating.
What does that have to do with this case?
I only said I saw Nana because I did.
You could've been paid
to give a false statement.
Your Honor, what he just said--
You are the one insulting
the investigation organization, lawyer.
Saying the time of death
deduced by the police was too early
is only a theory because you
hadn't actually examined the body.
In addition,
the lawyer has connected a murder
from 11 years ago in Kanagawa,
which had its final decision made,
to this murder.
I've been informed
that he places the focus on finding
the truth in that case instead.
I have to say that, as a lawyer,
your attitude is very problematic.
Here he is…
Mr. Kurokawa, what's the case
from 11 years ago that was mentioned?
Will you deny all charges
in the coming trials?
No comment. Please let us through.
Do you have any valuable information?
Dr. Akiu.
Hello. Hoshundo Law Office.
We won't accept an interview
about that case.
This is really bad.
After last time,
we're digging up another case
that had been concluded in a trial.
It became the headline
across all kinds of media.
IS A KILLING FROM 11 YEARS AGO
RELATED TO THE SERIAL KILLINGS?
If Kurokawa continues as a lawyer,
he has to go through it someday.
I'm saying that I hope he won't
get our office involved in this.
I mean, I don't want to be involved
in this case again.
This case made my brother die
with regret as a lawyer, after all.
Yes, indeed.
I know you want
to take your mind off this,
but we should go back.
Would you like some snacks?
The trial isn't over yet.
The case from 11 years ago too.
Pull yourself together, starting tomorrow.
Dr. Akiu and Mr. Ibusuki were right.
I don't know how cold a dead body is.
Sorry I asked you to come, but…
would you leave me alone for a while?
Don't drink too much.
SATOKO ARIMA
Wakura speaking.
I'm Arima. Is Kurokawa with you?
No, I just left.
I see.
He didn't answer my call.
I have to tell him something urgently.
Tell him something?
It might lead us to the real murderer.
What?
JUNPEI FUJITA
KOOZ: I AM ALWAYS WATCHING YOU.
AYAKA'S DIARY
RANDOM STUFF IN MY DAILY LIFE
Where is he?
Mr. Kurokawa!
THIS DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS
THE SHOCKING FINAL EPISODE
Ms. Wakura!
The guy who stabbed Ms. Wakura
turned himself in.
I killed all three of them.
He is the murderer!
-Pressure from the authorities.
-You're a coward.
Can the false charges be cleared?
-You framed someone innocent 12 years ago!
-Shut up!
I'll never accept this!
The real murderer was someone else.
Please help me one last time.
We'll prove the convictions in this
and the murder 11 years ago wrong.
Please help us.
The Prosecutors Office and you
will turn a blind eye to it
just to keep your honor?