Misa, can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Misa?
-DC.
-Yes.
Defibrillator charged.
Dr. Unzen.
MENU, TRENDLIST, TRANSPORT,
ASYSTOLE, ALARM
13-YEAR-OLD FEMALE PATIENT
DIES OF CARDIAC ARREST
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
What's wrong, Mr. Kurokawa?
Sorry, I was looking for the pills.
Pills? Are you not feeling well?
Since this morning…
-Hang in there!
-Good morning.
-I just heard a loud noise…
-Mr. Kurokawa!
You finally did it, Miss Wakura.
What did I do?
He made a mess of your desk again,
-so you snapped and beat him.
-My stomach…
Did Miss Wakura punch you?
Or did she stab you?
I didn't punch or stab him!
He just fell down himself!
What?
Anyway, we have to take him
to the hospital.
Hospital?
I don't like hospitals
and I'd have to pay.
You can't afford to say that!
I know why I've got a stomachache.
I got my salary yesterday,
so I got carried away.
What?
He got carried away
and ate pizza, curry, sushi,
ice-cream, pudding, and cake?
Is he an idiot?
Kurokawa needs to improve
his lifestyle a little.
He's enthusiastic about his work,
but he doesn't pay enough attention
to everything else.
Before he aimed to be a lawyer,
he used to be
an organized young man, the exact
opposite of what he's like now.
You mean when he was still a student
and doing science and engineering?
Oh? You know that too, Miss Wakura?
Miss Arima told me the other day.
Kurokawa did science
and engineering, originally.
He wasn't weird.
Rather, his personality changed
at that time, I think.
It sounded like
there was a story behind it.
Did Mr. Kurokawa do something bad
when he was a student
and you defended him?
No, it isn't like that.
We just happened to meet.
FIRST-AID KIT
Here it is.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
Good morning.
Oh, good morning, Mr. Yufuin.
Miss Arima?
What are you here for so early?
I've brought a client here.
To be precise, she's the go-between.
The client's go-between?
MIKI SHIRAYAMA
AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL'S NURSE
Are you okay, Mr. Kurokawa?
Will you go to the hospital now?
I just digested it.
-So quick!
AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
Do you know how it feels as a parent
to have your child's life
taken in an instant?
It is true that
I couldn't save the patient.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
Pull back from this point.
It won't do to say that you'll change it
sometime in the future.
Now, a problem has occurred,
you have to change it.
AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
CAR PARK ENTRANCE
The case happened on November 2, 2018.
On that day, Aogashima Hospital's
pediatric cardiovascular surgeon,
Dr. Kazuhiko Unzen, performed
a mitral valve replacement surgery.
-Suction!
-Yes.
Doctor, her BP is dropping!
-Raise the blood flow rate!
-Yes.
-Gauze.
-Doctor.
-What?
The CPB pump! The machine stopped!
But during the surgery,
the heart-lung machine
stopped for a few minutes.
The patient remained unconscious.
Her condition became critical the next day
and she died of cardiac arrest.
This case was an unfortunate accident.
An accident? You killed my daughter!
Why isn't Dr. Unzen here?
The patient's parents didn't accept
what the hospital said
and the negotiation broke off.
"The police arrested
the surgeon, Kazuhiko Unzen,
for professional negligence
resulting in death."
It isn't common that someone
gets arrested for a medical error.
The police thought he was uncooperative
and could've destroyed evidence.
The hospital didn't even want to
admit the mistake at first.
But I thought the press would make
a bigger fuss of such an incident,
like holding a press conference.
But the girl's parents didn't want that.
I went to meet them once,
but they said they didn't want money.
They only wanted to know
why their daughter died.
But the doctor who made the medical error
didn't explain anything and just ran away?
-It's just too horrible.
-That's not true.
Dr. Unzen isn't like that.
If he had really made a mistake,
he would've said it honestly.
I know because I've been working
with him for a long time.
Miss Shirayama,
could you and Dr. Unzen be…
It is unrequited.
I had told him my feelings once,
but he said we have a large age gap
and he isn't confident about having
a family because he's a workaholic.
In other words, he rejected you.
-Do you need to say it?
-Oh. Sorry.
Anyway,
she can't accept that the hospital
blames Dr. Unzen for the mistake,
so she sought my advice secretly
when I went there for an interview.
On the day the patient passed away, I saw
Dr. Unzen talking to
the medical intern, Dr. Akagi.
It was my fault. I made a mistake.
No, it wasn't your fault.
The medical intern made a mistake?
Dr. Akagi participated in the surgery too.
Dr. Unzen could've covered up
the mistake Dr. Akagi made.
But isn't this unnatural?
Hospitals usually protect
the experienced doctor
instead of the intern.
I thought it was strange too.
It seems that someone blew the whistle,
and that was what made
the police arrest Dr. Unzen.
Blow the whistle?
"The mistake made by the surgeon,
Unzen, was the cause of the result."
Someone called the police and said that.
THE CAUSE WAS GROSS NEGLIGENCE
ON THE PART OF THE SURGEON
Everything could be a false charge.
That's why we would like you
to meet Dr. Unzen himself once.
Will you, Kurokawa?
Please.
Okay, I'll interview him once.
KOKUBUNJI POLICE STATION
I heard that one of the hospital
staff members asked you to come.
Who was that?
Sorry, we have to keep
the information confidential.
But the person is very worried about you.
Could it be Bandai?
KAZUHIKO UNZEN
SURGEON, AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
The Deputy Head Surgeon.
He's my classmate and he's successful.
He's friendly to me, even though
I'm just a workaholic.
TERUNORI BANDAI, DEPUTY HEAD
SURGEON, AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
But if Bandai asked you,
you have to turn him down.
Why is that?
Because it might affect his position.
Moreover,
I don't think there is anything
a lawyer can defend in this case.
You mean you admit that a mistake
you made caused the patient's death?
It's a fact
that I couldn't save the patient.
I told the hospital and police
about everything that happened
in the surgery.
All the facts will be revealed
in the trial.
But there are cases
where all facts don't get revealed.
You didn't tell the patient's parents
anything yourself, right?
I requested to talk to them directly
many times,
but the hospital stopped me.
The parents only wanted to know
the real reason
why their daughter passed away.
Would you let us help you do so?
MINAMI
DO YOUR BEST
Sorry for visiting so suddenly. Today…
It's the result of the hospital's
internal investigation.
The mistake Unzen made
and why our daughter died
are written on it clearly.
Excuse me.
It was submitted to the police too.
It'll be over if Unzen admits
the charge and gets punished.
What do you want by poking
your noses into this after so long?
Do you do this for money?
Is that why you can defend
a murderer indifferently?
No, we…
Our daughter was only 13 years old.
We believed that Unzen
was a trustworthy, good doctor.
Do you know how it feels
as a parent to have
your child's life taken in an instant?
We don't.
Mr. Kurokawa.
Don't be ridiculous! What the heck?!
I'm sorry…
but we don't know if what is
written in the report is true.
That Dr. Unzen really made a mistake…
and took your daughter's life.
At least not yet.
Leave.
Leave here now!
Give me a break.
Hoshundo Law Office?
Yes.
We will defend Dr. Kazuhiko Unzen.
Unzen and I were classmates,
so I'm worried too.
This incident must have
driven him into a corner.
He said he hoped
the facts would be revealed.
He must hate me now.
I'm his boss, but I couldn't protect him.
I don't think he does.
We'd like to check something about
the hospital's
internal investigation report.
Okay. I'll show you the way.
-This is the heart-lung machine?
-Yes.
It was reported that during the surgery,
the pump that circulates blood
in the body stopped.
It says the wrong instruction given
by Dr. Unzen
was what caused the accident.
If the blood-flow volume
in the machine is suddenly raised,
it gets caught in the pump
and the machine might stop.
That happened after the pump was used
according to his instruction.
Who actually operated the pump?
There are
biomedical equipment technicians.
The experts handle the machines
used in surgeries.
It's possible the technician
made a mistake,
but the surgeon's instructions
are absolute.
We'd like to talk directly
to staff members other than Dr. Unzen
who were present at the surgery.
I'm sorry,
but would you do so another day?
We have many emergency cases.
May we at least talk to
the medical intern, Dr. Akagi?
Akagi is out for an academic meeting.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
I don't know where
the washing machines are.
Turn left there
and you'll see the laundry room.
I see. Many things in this hospital
are so complicated.
I am sorry.
LAUNDRY ROOM
I heard that some lawyers are here
for Dr. Unzen's case.
The problem hasn't been solved?
Indeed, I can't imagine
Dr. Unzen making any mistake.
Exactly. There's trouble between them.
Is anything written in the internal
investigation report not true?
The whole report is a lie.
What is, in particular?
There was no biomedical engineering
technician present at the surgery.
Who operated the pump, then?
The medical intern, Akagi.
He had to because we were short of staff.
Of course, I taught him the basics
of how to operate it.
Also, I didn't specify the value
of the blood flow rate he should raise.
-Raise the blood flow rate!
-Yes.
It says here that
I suddenly raised the blood flow rate
to five liters per minute,
but I would never give such instruction!
That means the medical intern
made a mistake
and caused the pump to stop?
No. I checked
the operation record afterwards.
The heart-lung machine turned off
by itself, without warning.
Why do you operate it like that?
Out of my way!
I'm sorry.
-Its power is off!
-I'm sorry.
The technician hurried there,
re-plugged in the pump and it was on,
but the patient had already…
I reported this to my boss
and I said this during the questioning.
The problem is the hospital
submitted this report as evidence.
If a trial is held,
based on this, you'll be convicted
for making a medical error.
No doubt, the hospital wants to
settle the case
as your personal medical error.
In that case, not only did you
not save the patient
but even the truth of her death
won't be revealed.
But the hospital is covering it up
so comprehensively.
How can we reveal the truth now?
I don't know.
But for you and the patient's parents,
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
You said you'd defend him,
but this is quite tough.
The heart-lung machine's
operation record was altered
to match the investigation report.
This is what is difficult
about medical cases.
We're dealing with experts.
They have control over the evidence
and situation before we start.
If we can get the testimonies
of the nurses, anesthesiologist,
and the technician
who checked the trouble…
Impossible. They must've
taken preventive measures.
In that case,
we'll investigate why
the heart-lung machine stopped first.
It wasn't an operation error,
so let's check with the manufacturer
why the power was off.
No!
Mr. Noboribetsu?
-What shouldn't we do?
-Don't check with the manufacturer.
Kurokawa, Mr. Yufuin, come with me.
The heart-lung machines used by
Aogashima Hospital
are manufactured and sold by
Medicarement Corporation.
This is our important client.
They are angry and called this morning
to ask if our lawyers
are really involved in this case.
In other words, the hospital
can't let us investigate this,
so they put pressure on them.
Be careful about what you say.
I'm the one putting pressure on you!
Stop doing something uncalled for!
The suspect said
the heart-lung machine stopped suddenly.
If the patient died because
the machine malfunctioned--
The manufacturer will suffer a great loss
and we, Hoshundo, will as well
because we are their consultant.
I cannot let this happen!
It's my order as Head of Office.
Withdraw from the case.
I cannot.
What?
We haven't found out why this happened.
I have to fire you, then.
-Wait a minute, Mr. Beppu.
-I won't.
I can't keep a lawyer
who makes the law firm
he belongs to suffer a loss!
It's okay if he doesn't
inflict any loss, right?
What do you mean?
If the heart-lung machine is faulty,
the same problem will occur again.
If after we investigate,
we can prove that another reason
caused the pump to stop,
then it shouldn't be a problem.
What if after you investigate,
you find that
the pump stopped because it's faulty?
I'll submit it as evidence.
You…
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Mr. Beppu!
But before the trial,
I'll check all the evidence you submit.
If your conclusion will inflict
a loss to our office…
I've prepared myself for it.
Kurokawa, that was really--
I won't compromise.
I decided that when I became a lawyer.
But if they really fire you…
Fire him?
Mr. Kurokawa, they'll fire you?
They haven't made the decision.
It depends on how the defense goes.
It depends on this case?
Anyway, we have to start
our investigation.
Wait, Miss Arima just called.
She said Dr. Unzen will be prosecuted.
I knew it.
It finally comes to this.
We have to hurry, then.
It's what the report says.
After Dr. Unzen gave the instruction,
the heart-lung machine stopped.
You read the report, right?
I've talked to the superior doctors
and the police many times.
There is nothing I can tell you.
I'm just a medical intern
and I didn't do anything important.
But that's not what Dr. Unzen said.
Sorry, I have to work.
-Wait a minute--
-I'm sorry.
This incident has made
all our staff nervous.
Please.
As we thought,
they all told the same story.
Well, the Deputy Head Surgeon,
Bandai, was present too.
How can you two be so calm?
We haven't found any clue at all!
What's the matter, Miss Wakura?
Why did you get worked up suddenly?
We'll surely lose at this rate!
It might get you fired, Mr. Kurokawa!
It won't affect whether
I get fired or not.
Will we just go to the medical
equipment manufacturer now, then?
They might refuse to see us, though.
We will force our way in, of course!
Just calm down a bit.
-We will go there.
-No, we shouldn't.
-Why?
-The nurse, Shirayama, is calling.
Hello. Kinosaki speaking.
We've just left the hospital…
-What? He'll testify at trial?
-What?
So, the hospital investigation report
isn't true. Am I right?
Yes. There was no technician present
and Dr. Unzen didn't specify any value.
But why would you tell the truth?
Miss Shirayama convinced me.
When I thought that a mistake I made
caused the patient's death,
I get very scared…
but making Dr. Unzen take the blame…
But if you stand as a witness,
it will make your situation
at the hospital worse.
Miss Shirayama, you too,
for persuading him to testify.
Both Dr. Akagi and I will go to work
at another hospital.
If I keep quiet,
the same thing might happen again,
so I'll say everything at the trial.
Thank you.
Are you sure?
Okay. Goodbye.
Bandai.
About Unzen's trial.
COURTHOUSE
-Found him?
-No, he didn't answer my call.
Okay. Goodbye.
I asked the hospital.
They said Dr. Akagi wasn't there.
But the trial will start soon.
Hello, Mr. Kurokawa.
Hello.
It's the first time we compete
in a medical case.
And one that involves death too.
You'd better not think you can win easily.
The judge is pretty strict.
After all, he has not found anyone
innocent in these few years.
I'll go to the hospital now.
You won't make it in time. I'm sure.
Please stand.
ROKURO HIRUGAMI, CHIEF JUDGE
Hello, Dr. Akagi?
It's Kinosaki from Hoshundo Law Office.
-I'm sorry.
-What?
I cannot give my testimony.
You cannot? Why?
Forget everything about this case.
Let's start the examination
of the defense's witness.
Witness, please come forward.
Where is the witness?
Your Highness, he'll be here soon.
I am very sorry.
We can't get hold of the witness
who is supposed to testify today.
Please let us cancel the examination.
Well, this often happens,
but be careful not to impede
the progress of the trial.
Yes, Your Honor.
What happened to Dr. Akagi?
Why did he suddenly say no?
The hospital probably found out.
Well, that must be tough.
Mr. Hirugami.
Mr. Kurokawa,
I've heard a lot about your work.
You're still young.
How commendable of you to aim to wipe out
false charges in criminal cases.
Thank you.
A 13-year-old girl died in this incident.
It must be tough for you to defend
the suspect of this tragic case.
Do try your best.
He has already reached a conclusion.
Shirayama was the one
who requested you to defend me?
She convinced Dr. Akagi
to give his testimony as well.
I had no idea that this would happen.
He must've been told
that he could not be a doctor
if he stood as a witness.
It isn't Akagi's fault.
I caused Shirayama trouble too.
Dr. Unzen, regarding this case--
I knew when I read
the investigation report.
Bandai was ordered to cover
the truth of the incident.
Nobody besides him could manipulate
the report as perfectly as that.
But you were friends--
He's climbing the career ladder.
I work as a surgeon.
Our situations are different.
Actually…
I would like to ask you two for a favor.
Unzen realized that too?
As you said, I manipulated
everything to cover the fact.
Did you do it to protect the hospital?
No, I did it to change this hospital.
Aogashima Hospital is the only
general hospital in this region.
It has many patients
and many problems too.
So, I decided
to climb the career ladder
and change it someday.
Then you shouldn't make Dr. Unzen
the scapegoat and end it like this!
I agreed to cover it up
because my superior promised
to give me a budget
for new employees and equipment.
Even if I have to sacrifice my classmate,
I think it was the best decision
to make to achieve my goal.
I think it's going to rain.
May I go now?
I have to go back to work.
Excuse me.
It's for you.
What is it?
It's the password of Dr. Unzen's
personal laptop on his desk.
He thinks it will help you.
The staff the hospital needs,
new equipment that you should buy,
how to take care of patients.
He wrote down what he realized
should be improved.
Why are you giving this to me?
When you were young,
you used to talk to each other about
improving the hospital's old system.
That's his reason.
Lastly, he would like us
to pass on his message to you.
Promise him you will become the leader
and carry out a reform of the hospital.
What should we do now?
We can't get Akagi's testimony.
The reason of the heart-lung
machine's problem remains a mystery.
AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
You are really going to be fired.
Well, I think you got the wrong idea.
I'll be fired if I inflict a loss
on the office.
It's the office's loss if you lose too.
I mean, to Mr. Beppu,
hiring you alone
had inflicted a loss on the office.
Even my feelings are hurt
if you say it so bluntly.
But…
What is it?
Miss Wakura, are you worried about me?
-Just drop it. Let's hurry.
-Okay…
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-This… Yes…
-Laundry… The laundry room?
It's on another floor.
You have to go to the first floor.
Where on the first floor?
I think after you exit the lift,
turn right, and…
-I'll take you there.
-Okay.
LAUNDRY ROOM
-Over here.
-Thank you. How kind of you.
-Don't worry about it. There you go.
-Thank you.
But all the machines are in use.
It's always busy at this time of the day.
-Is that so?
-Yeah.
What? Oh no! I've run out of detergent!
Laundry detergent?
There you go.
Wow! Thanks for your help, young man.
Why has he got that too?
Anyway, this hospital is so stingy.
The washing machine over there
has been broken
since I started staying here.
Our room's television
suddenly stopped functioning
the other day too.
That was three months ago, right?
It was fixed after I told a nurse
and it was re-plugged.
The heart-lung machine turned off
suddenly without warning.
Many things in this hospital
are so complicated.
Excuse me.
When did that happen?
What do you mean?
The television was broken,
but it was fixed
after you re-plugged it in, right?
Please tell me the date that it happened.
It was the day I was admitted,
so it was November 2.
November 2?
-That's--
-What time was it?
I went to my room at 11 a.m.
It was right before supper time,
so I think it was around 4 p.m.
Oh, it was raining like this
at that time too.
Thank you, ma'am!
Mr. Kurokawa?
Thank you, ma'am.
Mr. Kurokawa!
Just as I thought!
That's right. Sorry.
There you go.
Not this! Tell me what's going on!
AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL - OPERATING THEATER
This experiment's scale is large too.
Isn't it always?
-Good evening.
Here you go.
So, what did you find?
I checked the area
within a one-kilometer radius,
and it's what you expected.
Many residents there are elderly people.
Thank goodness they were helpful.
It's convenient to have someone
who works at a TV station.
They don't hesitate
to go to people's homes uninvited.
Do you have to be so sarcastic
about everything?
Would you like to see the equipment
before we do the experiment?
Is it okay, Mr. Akiu?
Don't let her touch anything.
-This way, please.
-Come on.
You want to ask something?
RADIO TOWER
I was told the other day that you were
Mr. Kurokawa's senior when he did
science and engineering here.
So?
Well…
I just thought there must be
another reason why Mr. Kurokawa
insists on doing experiments
for evidence and you helping him.
-Really…
-Over here. Over here.
He is an idiot.
Well, I won't deny it.
Kurokawa is cut out to be
a scientist, not a lawyer.
So he sticks to something unnecessarily
and worries over it.
What do you mean?
Someone died in this accident, right?
Well, yeah.
If the facts are revealed
after a scientific experiment…
will it make you happy?
I don't think I will be happy,
but it can prevent someone innocent
from being falsely charged.
-A scientist would be happy.
-Yes?
The experiment is done and it's over.
But that's not how a trial goes.
Even if you've done an experiment
to prove someone's innocence,
the dead can't be brought back to life.
The family they left behind
won't be delighted either.
Let's start the experiment.
-Stand back.
-Okay.
Don't touch the things!
RADIO TOWER
EVIDENCE REPORT
What you were worried about
won't happen in this case.
So, about Mr. Kurokawa's job here--
Well, I don't care whether
he can settle the case or not,
but can he win the trial with this?
We will see.
COURTHOUSE
Please have a look at the photo
of defense evidence number 52.
EXAMINATION OF DEFENSE'S EVIDENCE
This is a washing machine
in the laundry room at Aogashima Hospital
where the accident happened.
A witness told us that
on November 2 at around 4 p.m.,
that is, the same day
as the surgery was performed,
the machine was broken.
Next, please have a look at
defense evidence number 53,
a list of electrical devices.
They are the electrical devices
used in Aogashima Hospital
that were broken
on the same day at the same time.
Some of them were fixed
after they were re-plugged…
Why did this phenomenon occur
at the same time?
We have special permission
to play and use this as evidence.
Please watch defense evidence number 54,
the video of an experiment.
The phenomenon that caused
the accident to happen
was what we call
back-flow lightning surge.
RADIO TOWER - REVERSE LIGHTING
When lightning strikes a tall building,
the electric potential
on the ground rises rapidly.
INCREASE IN ELECTRICAL PRESSURE
Current flows from
higher electric potential
to lower electric potential,
so it flows through the earth wire
and back to the power cable.
EARTH
As a result,
it causes a malfunction
in electrical devices in the building
that are connected to the power cable.
HOSPITAL
Usually, in a hospital, to prevent
it from being struck by lightning,
there is a device called
a lightning arrester.
But the one at Aogashima Hospital
was not functioning,
so the lightning affected
the electrical system
at various places in the hospital…
LIGHTNING ARRESTER - OPERATING THEATER
RADIO TOWER
…and caused a power cut
in parts of the building.
As a result,
it caused the heart-lung machine
at the operating theater to stop.
In the statement given by the accused…
it stated that the machine
worked again after re-plugging.
It shows that the machine wasn't faulty
and it was the problem
of the electrical system.
That's all for the experiment.
As you have just seen,
the cause of this accident
was the lightning that struck
the radio tower one kilometer
to the southwest of the hospital
on the November 2 at 4:02 p.m.
This is how areas
within a one-kilometer radius
were affected by the lightning
at the same time.
We confirmed that many buildings
and houses were affected in the same way.
Your Honor,
both the video
and the defense lawyer's explanation
can't prove that the hospital
is negligent in dealing with lightning.
Defense lawyer,
can you prove that the hospital's
lightning arrester is defective?
Please have a look at
defense evidence number 55.
This is the document from
Komori Maintenance, the company
that manages
the hospital's electric devices.
The lightning arrester
in Aogashima Hospital
failed to function due to
a lightning strike in the past.
The company advised them to change it,
but they ignored that
because of the high cost
and did nothing about it.
The hospital's management system
caused the accident to happen.
To cover the fact,
they made the surgeon there
take full responsibility.
The deceased's parents
wanted to know the truth,
but the hospital
trampled on their feelings.
My client couldn't save the patient
and he feels responsible for it.
This time, the hospital's problem
became obvious,
and if this will improve the situation,
my client says he won't mind
the outcome of the trial.
But if my client has to take
the responsibility alone,
the day the hospital will improve
the situation will never come.
It won't do to say that you'll change it
sometime in the future.
Now, a problem has occurred,
you have to change it.
For the above reasons,
as the defense lawyer,
I insist that my client,
Kazuhiko Unzen, is innocent.
There aren't enough doctors.
By cutting entertainment expenses
and the directors' remuneration,
shortage of staff can be improved
without lowering the quality of personnel.
Paperwork for doctors is too much
and consultation time is shortened.
Improve work environment.
Set clear guidelines
for the work environment of doctors,
nurses, and hospital staff
to avoid irregular shifts
that make them work long hours.
NIGHT ENTRANCE
PRONOUNCEMENT OF JUDGMENT
I shall deliver the verdict.
Text.
The accused…
is sentenced to one year in prison.
-The sentence is suspended
-No way!
from the date of the final court decision
to three years after.
The following
is the reason for the verdict.
The defense lawyer claims that
the hospital's lightning arrester
was defective
and the electrical system was cut off,
causing the heart-lung machine
to stop working,
which caused the victim's death.
However, the claim is conjectural.
It cannot be proven that
the deficiency of the lightning arrester
caused the victim's death.
That's all.
Accused, if you disagree with the verdict,
you may make an appeal.
I won't make an appeal.
It is true that
I couldn't save the patient.
As the lawyer said…
no matter what the verdict is,
I believe that the accident
will teach the hospital a lesson
and they will make a change.
The chief judge didn't watch
the experiment properly, did he?
There's nothing we can do.
He has delivered the verdict.
Mr. Kurokawa.
In the end,
what caused our daughter's death?
Is it Dr. Unzen's fault?
Is it the hospital's fault?
Who should we hate?
Answer me! Please!
Answer me!
Let's go.
Didn't I tell you
not to think that you could win
a case that involves death easily?
What you did was uncalled for.
You shifted the target
of the parents' anger
and only made them sad again.
Everyone, Dr. Unzen was found guilty.
We have caused you a lot of trouble
in this case.
Also…
I think many of you have doubts
and are worried about
the hospital's future.
But we will not repeat the same mistake.
I'll change it,
so that it won't happen again.
Not just someday.
We'll start now.
When I was young…
I found a mistake made by a senior
and reported it to my superior.
He told me that if
I wanted to be a doctor…
I had to turn a blind eye to it.
At that time,
it didn't occur to me that I'd say
the same thing in the future.
I am very sorry.
SURGEON FOUND GUILTY
Some media have taken an interest
in Unzen's trial
and some people are starting
to blame the hospital.
It's annoying.
Is that so?
Well, Unzen has been found guilty.
If we just deny all knowledge of it,
the matter will be settled soon.
We cannot let you do that.
Because you have to handle
more annoying things in the future.
What do you mean?
Besides looking into
the hospital's problems,
Unzen also collected some information.
For example,
the bribe you accepted from…
pharmaceutical companies
and the affiliated companies.
PROPOSAL FOR IMPROVEMENTS
AT AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
Hey. Why did you do this out of the blue?
-Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
PROPOSAL FOR IMPROVEMENTS
AT AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL
To change the hospital,
it's time to squeeze the pus out.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
You'll go to a medically underserved area?
Yes, a friend wants me to go there.
I can't treat any patient for a while,
but I'll help the locals there for now.
Glad to hear that.
We weren't capable enough
and lost the case,
but you've found a new job.
It suits me more than
a cold, major hospital.
Miss Shirayama, will you go with him?
Yeah, I'll follow him there,
even if he says no.
You're a couple with a huge age gap.
Why not? It's passionate!
By the way,
I would like to say thank you
to Mr. Kurokawa too.
I am sorry, but today, Kurokawa…
Yes?
Mr. Kurokawa,
Dr. Unzen and Miss Shirayama have left.
They would like to thank you too.
FAULTY
I see.
I think you should've at least shown up.
I'm too ashamed to see them.
Dr. Akiu helped me,
so I have to say sorry.
Should I go there for you?
Sorry.
TAKU KUROKAWA'S HOME
AOGASHIMA HOSPITAL'S DOCTOR
SENTENCED TO ONE YEAR IN PRISON
LIGHTNING, LIGHTNING FLOW, EARTHING
How is Kurokawa?
He is obviously feeling down.
He's been reading the case's
judicial record again and again.
Lawyers sometimes lose a case too.
It's stupid to worry about it every time.
Whatever. There's nothing more
to talk about. Just leave.
Did something happen
when Mr. Kurokawa was a student?
Why do you think so?
He did science at first but changed
to study law to become a lawyer.
People don't usually do that.
So, there must be a reason.
I think I'd better know the reason
why Mr. Kurokawa went so far
to be a lawyer.
I have to help him in the future too.
Do you know about his father?
Yes.
He's the Supreme Public Prosecutors
Office's Deputy Prosecutor-General.
If you know, start from checking him out.
Dr. Akiu, you don't know the reason?
I do, but I don't want to talk.
Why?
Because it's troublesome.
LEGAL PAPERS
More…
If I had found a more indisputable proof…
SHIN KUROKAWA
THIS DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS
Kurokawa finally confronts
his father, a prosecutor.
Criminals lie and hide the facts.
A murder of a female office worker
happened on a beach.
The darkness of the murderer's heart
is revealed.
I just hate her so much!
Even if you hate her a lot,
you might not have actually killed her.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
Someone related?
Our positions are different,
but we share an unpleasant event.
I was the victim of a malicious stalker.
I insist that my client,
Nami Ogasawara, is innocent.