"Touo University…"
It is mine.
The case happened ten years ago,
didn't it?
You were still a student
at that time, right?
I was.
Is the case the reason
that you became a lawyer?
Why do you ask?
-Because I want to know about you.
-Yes?
No, I mean, we're colleagues,
so I think it's better if I know more.
Moreover, Dr. Akiu has told me
a little about it.
I know that something happened
when Mr. Kurokawa was a student.
It was why he aimed to be a lawyer
and isn't close to his father now.
Ask Kurokawa himself if you're curious.
I see.
Dr. Akiu said that.
-There you go.
-Why?
So, may I read it?
Well, I don't feel comfortable.
-Then you should refuse until the end--
-Oh no!
There are several related documents.
No, I'll only take this. Excuse me.
What… Wait, the fish…
Is it okay to read this?
What's the matter?
Oh, Miss Wakura?
-It's a scandal…
-Scandal?
It's the law firm you worked at before.
Miss Arima, I heard that you had
a fight with the director again.
I gave him the proposal of
a special news program about
the false charge cases Kurokawa handled,
but he rejected it.
He said it was dull and not eye-catching,
and that's why I'm useless.
I said I'd fix and submit it
as many times as he wants,
but he gave me a story
before I could do that.
Gossip magazines
have been exposing harassment
-in various industries lately, right?
-Yes.
But he wants me to do this topic
on TV after they've all done it.
JAPAN - THE KINGDOM OF HARASSMENT
I have no motivation to work.
I see.
Speaking of harassment,
I have a new story.
Someone at a law firm blew the whistle.
Huh?
Wait, this…
"Big law firm J. Y."
It's clearly James Yuri Law Office.
This is a huge scandal.
Are you curious about
what the voice recording is like?
-May we play it?
-Okay.
A VETERAN SOLICITOR'S
AGGRAVATED SEXUAL HARASSMENT
Please stop this! Mister…
I'm going to scream!
Shout if you want,
but your situation will get worse.
I am… with… and I am… as well.
Please stop… Stop… No!
Are you okay?
I am. It just disgusts me.
But I'm glad that the problem is exposed.
Yeah, true.
Isawa! I told you to do a summary
on investment law violation cases.
-Why are you chatting here?
-What?
But it's lunch break in five.
I don't care. I need it
right after lunch, so do it now.
Mr. Noboribetsu,
you're totally abusing your power.
Abusing my power? That's an exaggeration.
More people are seeking
advice on harassment
in your division too, right?
Maybe I'll get a voice recorder
and accuse you too.
Why do you all accuse me together?
I'm not abusing my power,
I'm educating him.
Only people who have
a twisted personality abuse their power.
Excuse me. I'm Takamatsu.
I'm here to talk to the lawyer.
We've been expecting you.
Please come with me.
You want to talk about an incident
at a high school?
Yes.
I'm the instructor of a club, and…
YOSUKE TAKAMATSU, SUSPECT
I'm suspected of abusing my power
and physically punishing students.
MAIN TITLE
Stop messing around!
My son still hasn't recovered emotionally.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
We have been suffering this
the whole time.
Even if you win the case,
the fencing teacher's life
won't be what it used to be.
It isn't a reason for you
to do something wrong!
The incident happened on
November 22, 2018, at 4 p.m.
In Kainan High School's gym,
the fencing club was practicing
under the teacher
Yosuke Takamatsu's supervision.
-Okay, enough.
-Wait.
-We'll spar next. Go to the piste.
-Wait…
-Tashiro, referee!
-Yes, sir.
Step forward. Don't step back!
I said, don't step back!
What are you doing? Get up!
Hey, what's the matter?
You don't want to practice?
-Fujisato!
-Fujisato?
Hey, Fujisato!
Sir, he isn't breathing!
During practice, the ace
and club president, second-year student,
Shun Fujisato, had a cardiac arrest
due to irregular heartbeat.
He passed out there
and was sent to hospital.
His life was saved,
but he lost consciousness temporarily
and is resting at home after
being discharged from the hospital.
A house arrest was made three days ago
for professional negligence
resulting in injury.
It's unusual that someone
is charged in a case like this.
The boy's parents were very angry
and sued him.
Some magazines exaggerated
various things in their articles too.
Physical punishment?
Kainan High School is famous
for having many interschool
fencing competition champions, right?
The previous Olympic Games
bronze medalist too.
Yes, he was my student.
I've brought various people trouble
after this happened.
Fujisato had a cardiac arrest.
Could it be because your thrust
was stronger than necessary?
It's impossible.
If it really was my fault,
I'd be a man and pay for what I did.
Mr. Takamatsu,
please let me verify two things with you.
First, was there anything wrong
with Fujisato during practice that day?
I don't think there was
anything wrong with him.
Okay, the second question.
Has there been any problem
or trouble between you and Fujisato?
I've been teaching Fujisato with
more enthusiasm than the other students.
He's a talented player who might
become Japan's leader in fencing,
and I think he understands
my thoughts very well too.
All right, then.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
Please leave.
I have nothing to talk to you about.
We would like to ask Fujisato
to tell us himself
what happened at that time.
My son still hasn't recovered emotionally.
I'm not going to let you see him.
Excuse me.
She didn't let us in.
We have to give up, then.
Let's go to the school next.
Mr. Kurokawa?
Hey, what are you doing?
It won't take long.
Would you let us talk to him for a bit?
Fujisato is the person involved.
His testimony can mean--
No! Mr. Kurokawa,
you shouldn't be too persistent.
But…
Huh?
I told you to leave!
I'll sue you if you still don't leave!
Didn't I tell you
not to be too persistent?
No, I… Sorry.
Was someone here?
He said he was a lawyer.
I kicked him out.
Go and rest in your room.
I will take care of everything.
His parents are overprotective.
Our school is trying our best
not to stir up any trouble.
The school thinks that
there is no problem
with the supervisor's teaching?
Yes, our fencing team gets good results
because of Mr. Takamatsu's help.
Then, when Mr. Takamatsu thrust,
Fujisato collapsed over there.
But there was
nothing different than usual,
and the situation wasn't unnatural, right?
Yeah, we were practicing like usual.
This weapon is for foil fencing, isn't it?
If it hits you,
will the number be shown here?
Yes.
The lame is made of metal
and it reacts if the weapon touches it.
What do you wear beneath it?
When we have a practice match,
we wear a protector on a T-shirt
and our uniform too.
We also wear the lame.
Wow, it looks very tough.
Actually…
If you don't mind,
will you let me give my testimony
during the hearing?
Testimony?
Other people say various things,
but as team members, we know how
Mr. Takamatsu teaches the best.
-That's reassuring.
-Yeah.
-Why are you here?
-Tashiro.
Are they the police?
We're lawyers. What's the matter?
-Lawyers.
-Moriyoshi,
if you want anything, talk to me later.
Is he your friend?
He's just a classmate.
This is the video taken
by the volleyball team
to check their postures.
It's at a distance, but…
Your legs.
Your legs!
What's the matter? Concentrate!
Don't step back.
Don't step back!
The noise is getting in the way.
I'll bring a copy that is easier to watch.
-Okay.
-But looking at this,
I know why people suspect that he
physically punishes students.
We can hear him shouting at this distance.
Fujisato!
He's well-known
for being strict in the first place.
He used to be one of Japan's
top five players in the past too.
CHAMPION
One of his lungs was removed
because of a disease.
After that, he has been putting
his efforts into training young players.
Daddy, dinner is ready.
But he gives too much attention
to the talented members,
which makes the others unhappy,
so many of them quit.
But he has gotten some results,
so the school tolerates it.
The deputy headmaster said so too.
His expectation for Fujisato
is especially high
and he even talks big
about him getting a gold medal.
However, this incident happened.
So, do you think you can win the case?
I think it probably isn't a problem.
You're unusually confident.
The medical expert's opinion
is that fencing's thrust
won't cause a wound shock
leading to cardiac arrest
due to irregular heartbeat.
A team member promised to give
his testimony as a witness too.
The parents seem to have gotten emotional,
but there seems to be no trouble
between the supervisor and Fujisato.
But we don't know yet, actually.
Why do you say we don't know?
We couldn't hear the story
from Fujisato himself.
The opinion of the victim
of bullying and harassment is important.
See you.
Guys, you didn't talk to the boy?
No, his mother splashed water at us.
REJECT CALL
VOICE MESSAGE
What is it? An interview request again?
Yeah…
Could it be about your last law firm?
A gossip magazine's reporter
wants to talk to me,
and he is very pushy.
I haven't replied to him yet.
Maybe you can talk to me
if you don't mind.
Please don't do that!
If you want to climb
the career ladder at our firm,
being my girlfriend won't hurt.
What this means…
You get it, right? Now, come here.
He was the law firm's senior member
and he was the head's friend.
In the end, his sexual harassment
was covered up,
but my punch was treated as a problem,
so I had to resign from the law firm.
The guy is more disgusting than I thought.
Because of this accusation,
even the law firm can't
turn a blind eye to it.
If I agree to be interviewed
and tell people everything,
will it make my heart feel lighter?
I think it's different for everyone.
I can't forgive my former boss, of course.
As a lawyer, I want him
to be punished too.
-But…
-If you are not sure,
I think you can reply later.
Indeed,
punishment and revealing
something are totally different.
Punishment and revealing something?
It's easy to reveal something,
but people are going to say
whatever they want about it too.
Like this.
-Die, old pervert!
-Identify the guy!
I'll post the list of
James Yuri Law Office's lawyers.
It's not funny that
lawyers sexually harass someone.
The guy is innocent if the woman is ugly.
Hold a press conference!
COURTHOUSE
Be quiet.
CROSS-EXAMINATION OF THE DEFENSE'S WITNESS
Witness, please say that again.
What did you just say?
Mr. Takamatsu is always
oppressive towards our team members.
He had physically punished us too.
Mr. Takamatsu is always
oppressive towards our team members.
He had physically punished us too.
I, other team members,
and Fujisato had been victims.
Tashiro, why are you lying?
Mr. Takamatsu, please calm down.
So…
Are you saying that this is
what caused this accident to happen?
Yes. On that day, Fujisato had been
looking very ill before practice.
I told Mr. Takamatsu and asked him
to let Fujisato have a rest,
but he didn't listen to me.
You mean Fujisato wasn't feeling well,
but he forced him to practice?
Yes.
Mr. Takamatsu has a special
practice menu for Fujisato
and the practice he makes
Fujisato do is like bullying.
That's why I've always thought that
this would happen someday.
Witness, when the school talked to you,
you did not mention
anything like that at all.
Why do you give such testimony now?
If this is a lie,
you could be accused of perjury.
Your Honor, the lawyer's remark
was intimidating.
Sustain.
Lawyer, please be careful of your remarks.
I am sorry.
Because of the results
Mr. Takamatsu has achieved,
I thought if I told the school
the truth, they might cover it up.
It's the reason
why I didn't tell the lawyer too.
Do you have anything solid to prove
what you have just said?
Yes, I do.
This is the video taken when
Fujisato was punished physically.
Don't be ridiculous!
It hurts.
What are you talking about?
-Wait!
-Witness,
-please don't play the video.
-Reporters!
Please reveal this to the public!
We have been suffering this
the whole time.
Be quiet!
The court will adjourn.
This is an unexpected turn of events.
He offered to be your witness, didn't he?
This is what he's been after
from the beginning.
Hello, Mr. Kurokawa.
Sorry for causing trouble.
High school students nowadays
are quite clever.
Who'd have thought he would
use the trial to accuse the teacher.
It must be extremely unexpected
to you as the defense lawyers.
We don't know
if his testimony is true or not.
Maybe you need to check the video,
but it must be true that
the supervisor slapped Fujisato.
I can't accept it if you deny
what the child had to
pluck up his courage to say.
TAKAMATSU
-Isn't it cruel to slap a boy?
-It is!
-Stop screwing around.
-This guy is horrible.
It was only once.
I had slapped Fujisato once.
The video was taken at that time.
When did it happen?
About two weeks before
the accident happened,
I thought Fujisato
had lost his motivation.
FENCING CLUB
So I wanted to talk to him
before the other members came.
Fujisato.
What are these?
I shoplifted at a convenience store.
-The cigarettes are my dad's.
-What?
I want to quit fencing.
Even if you stop me,
I'll be suspended from school
if I take them to see
the student counselor.
Be honest with me.
You must be at a loss for what to do.
As the ace, if I quit, it will
harm your reputation.
Don't be ridiculous!
-It hurts.
-What are you talking about?
Listen, I have high hopes for you.
If something is bothering you,
I'll support you as much as you want.
So don't be so stupid
and do something to ruin your future!
And then, Fujisato promised me
to continue practicing.
I apologized for slapping him too.
If that was the only time
that you punished him physically,
that means the testimony
given by Tashiro was false.
This is only an excuse,
but I was demanded to achieve results.
No matter how nicely you put it,
in sports,
you still need to be gifted.
In the midst of it,
treating all members fairly…
was what I couldn't do.
There they come.
Lawyers, please talk to us
about today's hearing!
Will you continue to defend
the supervisor?
-Sorry, no comment. Sorry.
-Please let us through.
-Sorry.
-Excuse me.
-Please tell us about Takamatsu!
-Let me through.
-A comment, please.
Go there! There!
-Mr. Takamatsu! Please talk to us!
-Mr. Takamatsu!
Mr. Takamatsu, what did you say
to the lawyers?
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
You finally messed it up.
CONFESSING TO PHYSICAL ABUSE
"Defense's witness acknowledged
physical punishment."
"The brave accusation
caused confusion in court."
You have damaged our office's
reputation tremendously.
-We are sorry, Mr. Beppu.
-Kurokawa.
Persuade the accused to admit
his mistake and put an end to this
at an early stage.
Professional negligence
resulting in injury
will surely be granted
a stay of execution.
But we haven't inspected
everything thoroughly.
I'm telling you to consider
the accused's benefit.
People will criticize him more.
It'll be more difficult for him
to return to his normal life.
It's my order as the office's head.
It's for the office's,
the accused's, and your own sake!
Stop this pointless fight.
I heard that Mr. Beppu
hates to do criminal case defense,
but he's totally abusing his power
if he goes this far!
Do you want to accuse him?
It'll only drag on, though.
When Mr. Beppu said
it was for Kurokawa's sake,
I think it was what he really thought.
This is you and…
Who's standing next to you?
That was my former partner,
Mr. Beppu's elder brother.
Mr. Beppu's brother?
Originally, my partner and I
opened this law firm.
He was an excellent lawyer who was
enthusiastic about criminal cases.
At that time, I was the one
who specialized in corporate law.
However…
when he lost a case defending a suspect,
people criticized him a lot too.
Because of that, he succumbed
to disease and passed away.
Mr. Beppu was working at another
law firm, but after that,
he took over this office.
A lawyer is the third party
that is the closest to a case.
Because of that,
we are very likely to be under
public scrutiny as well.
The useless lawyer
was betrayed by the witness.
He just wants attention. Serves you right!
The lawyer is guilty
for defending a guy like that too!
He isn't human.
Kurokawa is useless.
FAULTY
He's not coming out.
Give us your comment!
Let's go to his parents' home
for comments.
Miss Arima, we should go closer too.
He won't come out.
His daughter took a day off school too.
Well, I do feel sorry for him.
Yosuke Takamatsu, 51 years old.
He came from Miyagi Prefecture.
Champion of Asia foil fencing
tournament at 17 years old.
When he was 21,
a tumor was detected
and his right lung was removed.
His life as a sports player was over.
He married his junior in university
when he was 28 years old.
His only daughter is now nine years old.
Why say that out of the blue?
People who think that
they can ruin someone's life
because they did something bad
must have forgotten something.
That person is also human.
The law firm's sexual harassment case too.
Data of the guy's family
got exposed and it's tough for them.
The man's daughter,
a university student, attempted suicide.
DAUGHTER OF J. Y. LAW OFFICE'S LAWYER
ATTEMPTED SUICIDE
Yosuke?
Sorry.
How's Chika?
She shut herself in her room.
I see.
HIS DAUGHTER'S SCHOOL IS NERIMA
PUBLIC SCHOOL, THE NAME IS CHIKA
DIVORCE REGISTRATION FORM
I shouldn't bring you any more trouble.
For Chika's future too…
you had better cut ties with me.
FOIL FENCING MASK
8,990 YEN
IN YOUR CART, CONTINUE SHOPPING
THE FENCING CLUB
It's this place.
CERTAIN VICTORY
Who put the camera here?
NAKADA - YOSHIDA - KIMOTO
It's no use investigating anything now.
Our supervisor can't come back, anyway.
Hey, Tashiro!
Please don't worry about
what happened the other day.
By the way, please have this
with your fellow members.
It's a sports drink.
Fencing equipment are pretty expensive.
It costs about 150,000 yen
to get a full set.
But I went ahead and bought it.
I have to find new clues
before the next hearing too.
Well, good luck.
Did you really buy the fencing equipment?
Yes. I bought them at a second-hand
website and it cost 100,000 yen.
-So you really…
-Yes.
I think it has something to do with
why he had a cardiac arrest.
-Sorry to have kept you waiting.
-Thank you.
Well done, Moriyoshi.
-You want it for your club, right?
-Right?
Oh, it's the boy from before.
Are they the police?
Science club.
His name is Moriyoshi, right?
-What's the matter with him?
-Well…
REJECT CALL
VOICE MESSAGE
A call for an interview?
Yes.
It's tough to be someone
involved in a case.
Both the victim and the one responsible
have their wounds touched
by total strangers.
You can talk to me if you don't mind.
Mr. Kurokawa, are you worried about me?
What?
Yes. I am very worried about you.
Rather than me, worry about whether
we can win the case or not.
Come on. Hurry up.
THE MURDERER IS HOPELESS
HIS DAUGHTER'S PHOTO IS HORRIBLE
It's a storm of fierce criticism.
Public opinions like these
will work against us at trial too.
The police summoned Fujisato
as a witness for the next trial.
Mr. Kurokawa, what have you been doing?
I've been thinking.
Why did Fujisato have a cardiac arrest
at such a perfect timing?
-Perfect timing?
-Ouch!
Including the video taken without consent,
it obviously was a series of events
to set Mr. Takamatsu up.
But it's impossible to cause
a cardiac arrest intentionally.
Excuse me. Miss Arima
just sent us a new video.
Oh, please show us.
Don't step back.
Don't step back!
The noise is still there.
It seems that it's there
in the original data.
Maybe the camera was out of order?
What are you doing? Get up!
What's the matter?
You don't want to practice?
Do you know what it is?
That looks like folding chairs.
Maybe they forgot to put them back?
-Good afternoon.
-I'll put them here.
-Thank you.
That reminds me.
I bought one of these too.
Wait. Did you take our conversation
the other day seriously?
Well, I think I'd better have one
for self-defense.
It's high-performance
and is sensitive to sound.
I put it in my basement, but it
picks up sound on the ground floor.
Isawa, what did you just say?
Yes?
It's high-performance--
-Did you say basement?
-Yes.
Our house has three stories
above the ground and two under.
-I'll go to check something.
-Mr. Kurokawa?
Again… What? Again?
Come on!
Wait.
What do you want to check suddenly?
-Sorry.
-Wait…
The headmaster will shout at me
if he finds out!
I'm sorry!
Okay!
Mr. Kurokawa, tell me what's going on.
-Thank you.
-What?
The position should be somewhere here?
Just as I thought.
TOUO UNIVERSITY
I see.
-Indeed, it's possible in this case.
-Yes.
This can explain
the noise in the video too.
That means someone else set this up?
We think we know who it was.
Kainan High School's
science club is excellent too.
It had been the champion
of the Science Tournament.
The accomplice
is a high school student too?
Kurokawa, I'll check something with you.
Okay.
Even if you win the case,
the fencing teacher's life
won't be what it used to be.
On top of that, only more people will be
accused of a crime
and be stared at by curious eyes.
Do you still want to do
the experiment to verify this?
I am a lawyer.
All right, then. But on one condition.
SCIENCE CLUB
THE 28TH ROBOT CONTEST
Moriyoshi, these people
want to talk to you.
-Talk to me?
-About what happened in the fencing club.
Moriyoshi, will you tell us what you know?
You seem to be quite eager to study.
I look forward to your future.
This is Touo University Science
and Engineering Department's Dr. Akiu.
Touo University's
Science and Engineering Department.
I heard that you are very talented.
But don't forget this.
When you deal with science,
it always puts
your sense of ethics to the test.
COURTHOUSE
This is a Tesla coil, which can
generate electromagnetic waves.
ANTENNA ELECTROMAGNETIC WAVES
ELECTRIC FIELD MAGNETIC FIELD TESLA COIL
It changes electricity into
electromagnetic waves, sends it,
and the receiver changes the waves
back to electricity.
It can do the so-called
wireless power transmission.
This is a reel,
a piece of equipment used in fencing…
and it has been modified to be
an electromagnetic wave receiver.
In foil fencing,
when the thrust touches the body,
in other words,
when the tip of the foil
contacts the lame,
a weak current will flow,
causing the electronic scoreboard
to respond.
However, on the day of the incident,
the foil that the accused took
was connected to a reel
that was modified as a receiver.
The Tesla coil was placed
right beneath the stage,
where the incident happened.
PHOTOS OF THE RECONSTRUCTED SCENE
There is a noise in the video taken
when the incident happened
because it was affected
by the electromagnetic waves.
Electromagnetic waves
generated by the Tesla coil
turned into current at the receiver
and flew through the foil.
When it contacted the victim's body,
50 milliampere,
an amount of current
that can easily cause
a cardiac arrest, flew through.
If someone has some science knowledge,
he will surely expect the setup
to be able to take someone's life.
Depending on one's ethics,
science can easily become a weapon
that hurts people.
So I urge its maker
to deeply reflect on his fault.
That's the end of the experiment.
Mr. Naoya Moriyoshi.
You used this device to cause
Fujisato's cardiac arrest.
Is this true?
Yes.
On that day, I set up the device
and used the Tesla coil.
Why did you do so?
I'm bullied by Tashiro and his friends.
They ordered me to do so.
Fujisato might die if you use this.
Were you aware of that?
Yes.
That's why I tried to say no many times.
But…
he asked me to do it himself.
He?
Fujisato asked me himself.
-Fujisato? What do you mean?
-It is true.
This is what Fujisato said to me.
He said he wanted to kill himself
with this device.
Kill himself?
To make it easier for the current to flow,
it was necessary
to attach a cord to the lame
to pass the current to the body.
But…
without Fujisato's help…
this is impossible.
I wanted to save Fujisato.
CROSS-EXAMINATION OF PROSECUTOR'S WITNESS
The weight of Mr. Takamatsu's hopes
is too heavy.
I wasn't interested in participating
at the Olympic Games.
I only wanted to enjoy fencing as a sport.
But Mr. Takamatsu kept telling me
to work harder and aim higher.
Fujisato.
Your supervisor's expectation
was a burden.
Is that why you tried to kill yourself?
I was isolated in the club.
I do a special training course,
so Tashiro and the others hated me.
But Mr. Takamatsu and my parents
didn't let me quit the club.
Mr. Takamatsu said participating
in the Olympic Games wasn't a dream,
so my parents got carried away.
I couldn't talk to anyone,
so I thought dying was the only way.
Was it necessary to set up
a device like that for this?
It was Tashiro's idea.
Unlike me, Tashiro
was really dedicated to fencing.
Mr. Takamatsu didn't appreciate him,
so he couldn't forgive Mr. Takamatsu.
So he suggested a plan to take
fencing away from Mr. Takamatsu.
A plan that I would be killed
by Mr. Takamatsu's thrust.
Why?
Why did you have to go so far?
-I thought you…
-Mr. Takamatsu.
-If it's you…
Your expectations are annoying.
I have no motivation,
but you made me do it.
I was isolated by people around me.
I said I wanted to quit,
but you punched me.
In the end, I couldn't even quit.
Then…
What should I have done?
Mr. Lawyer, will you tell me?
I don't know.
-What?
-Even if I were you…
maybe I would be at a loss of what to do.
But…
it isn't a reason for you
to do something wrong!
There are only two things
that I can say for sure here.
One.
What you did was wrong.
Whatever your reason is,
making light of your life,
choosing death,
and using that as a way
to frame your teacher, is wrong.
What's the other one?
I'm glad that you didn't end up
killing yourself.
I am glad that you're still alive.
There's nothing to be happy about.
Everything is revealed,
reported,
and I'll be criticized on the Internet.
Either way, in the future…
I'm going to go through something
so bad that I'll want to die.
I know I deserve it, but…
Indeed, I think you deserve it.
So, even if it is tough…
you have to make up
for what you did yourself.
Live, make up for it…
and turn over a new leaf.
JOURNALIST SEATING
Reporters, please do me a favor.
If you will report this case,
don't write something
that fans the flames of criticism.
Please write what
the people involved think
and why an incident like this happened.
Please report it accurately as it is.
Unlike a hearing…
nothing can stop social sanction.
Please be considerate
and don't let everyone involved
in this case be cornered
by the third party's biased views
and speculations.
For the above reasons,
the defense lawyer insists that
the accused, Yosuke Takamatsu…
is innocent.
SEVERAL DAYS LATER
COURTHOUSE
Thank you for your help.
You won and proved
someone's innocence again.
It isn't about winning or losing.
We only revealed the truth.
This time, more people are hurt
as a result.
You warned the reporters,
but many articles
fanned the flames of criticism.
Mr. Kurokawa,
there's only one reason
why social sanction is so extreme.
All citizens think that the sentence
by law is too light.
They want severe punishment for evil.
But the severe punishment…
should only be given
if it isn't a false charge.
Reports about workplace bullying
and physical punishment
tend to go too far and this case
is said to have raised a question.
Well, this just happens to be the result.
The lawyer in charge of it
has a strong belief
and has proved the teacher's innocence.
To me, it's enough.
-I'll give him the documents.
-Thank you.
This is impressive.
Mr. Beppu is in a good mood.
He usually hates criminal cases,
but it's good advertisement.
Oh, Miss Wakura, I presume?
I have called you many times
for an interview.
I am sorry, but I will not be interviewed.
I heard that he did
something horrible to you.
It's important for the victim
to raise their voice.
I will sue the man myself
when I want to do so.
Moreover, I had already punched him once.
But…
You over there!
You don't want to listen to me anymore?
No, well…
Miss Wakura, you can go back to work.
Excuse me.
TOUO UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDER CASE
I'll give this back to you.
I'm just a third party
that isn't involved in this,
so I shouldn't read it.
I think it isn't a problem,
-if Dr. Akiu doesn't mind if you know.
-What?
Mr. Kurokawa, I smell something
burning in your room.
What? That's right!
I was cooking the fish! Oh no! Sorry…
Don't read it when you're having lunch.
Ms. Kinosaki,
you know about this case too?
I am just a third party.
Among those we know, Dr. Akiu
was the only person involved.
TOUO UNIVERSITY MURDER CASE
PRISONER COMMITTED SUICIDE
SENTENCED TO LIFE IMPRISONMENT
MURDERER DID NOT CONFESS TO THE CRIME
I WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH
VICTIM, AYAKA AKIU
"Akiu"?
His sister?
THE DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS
FENCING DOES NOT USUALLY CAUSE
ELECTRIC SHOCK
Someone was shot to death,
an infant was kidnapped.
Haruto.
I'll investigate thoroughly and fight.
That's what he is like!
Mr. Tarumae!
Can the lawyers save the little boy
with the power of science?
I claim his innocence.
Was Haru really kidnapped?
Haruto! Haruto!
Isn't it your job to find that someone?
The pain of losing a family member
isn't what you want to experience.
Even so, I can't say that
you aren't guilty.