Two murders are thought to be
committed by the same person.
The dead bodies have something in common
with the Touo University
Student Murder Case 11 years ago.
She was stabbed in the throat.
Don't you think it looks like
the wound on Ayaka Akiu's throat
in the murder 11 years ago?
The real murderer is another person
and they put the blame on someone.
This time, it was the man Fujita.
Eleven years ago, it was Daisuke Asama.
The Public Prosecutors Office
will set up a specialized agency
independent from the police
to conduct forensic investigation.
I was invited to join it.
By your own father.
Very soon,
maybe we can clear Senior Asama's
false charges and avenge Ayaka!
You don't know how cold a dead body is.
I don't mind that Asama ended up
being the murderer.
Instead of the truth,
having a ready answer can stop our agony.
Mr. Kurokawa!
Miss Wakura.
My nails.
What?
Clues.
Miss Wakura?
Miss Wakura!
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
You mean the lady was stabbed
to protect you?
Excuse me. Will you analyze this?
We are going to properly collect
evidence ourselves.
I've seen you on the news.
Well, I guess you don't trust the police.
How can they say something so mean?
You asked for it yourself,
didn't you, Kurokawa?
The reason you agreed to be
the case's defense lawyer is because
you suspect it's related to
the case 11 years ago, right?
But to the police and the prosecutors,
the case is closed.
You're doing this now
just to satisfy yourself, aren't you?
Mr. Beppu, please don't say anymore.
I killed all three of them.
He is the murderer!
How dare you treat me
like a murderer without evidence!
Everything was on your order, wasn't it?
FINALLY, THE TUMULTUOUS FINAL EPISODE!
FIGHTING AN EVIL SERIAL KILLER
A serial killer who killed three women.
I don't care! What's wrong with you?
-You were innocent 12 years ago.
-Shut up!
I will never accept it!
Miss Wakura?
Mr. Kurokawa.
Thank goodness, you've opened your eyes.
I had a horrible nightmare.
Your pile of books and files
kept falling onto my desk.
I had no idea I was unconsciously
stressed out by that.
I'm sorry.
And…
Why are you holding my hand?
I am really sorry.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
Miss Arima, it isn't your fault.
Kurokawa would've been stabbed
if you hadn't called.
He might have died in that case.
His power to survive
seems weaker than Miss Wakura's.
JUNPEI FUJITA
Among Mr. Fujita's
and Hanamaki's followers,
KooZ here is the only one
who follows both of them.
I'm impressed that you found them.
Let's say Kyoka Hanamaki
didn't die because
Junpei Fujita stalked and killed her.
In that case, the real culprit
clearly did something to deceive us.
If that's the case,
they must know the life of the victim
and the "murderer" to a certain extent.
Also, look at this.
They had been closed,
but they're Ayaka Akiu's
and Daisuke Asama's blogs.
ASAMA'S RUINS TOUR
KOOZ: I WILL GO THERE NEXT TIME.
AYAKA'S DIARY
2. KOOZ: I LIKE IT TOO.
Even 11 years ago…
KOOZ: TWEET: 3
FOLLOWING: 15, FOLLOWER: 11
The symbol.
So, what do you think?
What do I think of what?
I'm saying, do you think
this KooZ is the real culprit?
Look at the Magatama.
Doesn't it look like the wound
on the victims' necks?
Apostrophe.
Apostrophe?
You add it to a noun
to turn it into possessive form.
In other words, the wound on their necks
could be the murderer's claim that
the victims were his possessions.
But this alone can't even
be circumstantial evidence.
So you have never met KooZ?
No. He sent me a follow request,
so I accepted it. That's all.
Could the person be the murderer?
JUNPEI FUJITA, DEFENDANT
We have to investigate.
The person arrested
in the murder 11 years ago
killed himself
after he lost the case, didn't he?
Yes.
I know how he felt!
He was arrested
for something he didn't do,
so he would rather die in that case!
Mr. Fujita!
Please don't give up.
Until the very last moment…
I'm going to go all out
to investigate and defend you.
TODOROKI POLICE STATION
Excuse me.
Yes?
I'm here to turn myself in to the police.
Last night, I stabbed someone.
MIC GENERAL LEGAL OFFICES
KIYOSHI DOGO
Impressive.
The guy turned himself in
and he's here to negotiate already.
If the negotiation is successful,
it'll give him an advantage in the trial.
He said he was sorry about
what he did to Miss Wakura
and he regrets doing it.
He did not plan the assault,
he just did it on impulse.
In other words,
the victim could have been anyone?
Yes. He got frightened after that
and turned himself in to the police.
This is my client's personal details.
I have his permission.
"Kazunari Kozu."
NAME: KAZUNARI KOZU
Kozu?
OCCUPATION: EMPLOYEE
AT UNIVERSITY STUDENT AFFAIRS OFFICE
It says he works at
a university's student affairs office.
Which university is it?
I heard that it is Seiran Arts University.
Excuse me.
"Seiran Arts University."
Mr. Kurokawa.
Does the name Kozu ring a bell?
KOOZ: TOTAL NO. OF MURDERS IN 2017, 20,598
My client's father is now retired,
but he is a renowned pathologist.
He will pay more to settle this--
We'll talk to Wakura whether
we'll settle it out of court or not,
but on one condition.
Condition?
NAME: KAZUNARI KOZU
I am going to interview this man.
TODOROKI POLICE STATION
You were actually going to stab me,
weren't you?
KAZUNARI KOZU, SUSPECT
Well…
I saw you on the news.
You're a famous lawyer, right?
No.
Clearing someone of false charges
must be difficult.
The police
leaps at someone's self-confession
or simple circumstantial evidence.
You work at a university's
student affairs office?
My father got me the job.
I had been idling about at this age.
It's been half a year,
but I couldn't fit in at work.
Half a year?
I had been living abroad
for nearly ten years,
so my dad said it was time
for me to re-join society.
But I ended up working at
the student affairs office again.
You had worked at
the student affairs office before?
Yes, at Touo University.
It made me feel inferior.
All the students were gifted
and enjoying their youth.
It annoyed me so much at that time.
But you know,
no matter how gifted they are
and how much they enjoy their youth,
when people die,
they die in no time at all.
You…
Actually…
I killed all three of them.
In the case 11 years ago
and the two lately.
When I stabbed the knife into
their necks and twisted it,
it was so satisfying!
What's the matter?
The lawyer suddenly…
He is the murderer! He just confessed it.
I didn't say that.
The public didn't know
about the wound on their necks!
He knows that because he is
the murderer, without a doubt!
-What are you talking about?
-Calm down.
The interview is over.
You treat me like a murderer
without any evidence.
Are you a detective who forces people
to make a confession?
Mr. Kurokawa, how did the interview go?
Kurokawa.
Mr. Kurokawa, what's the matter?
Hey, don't ignore us!
Kurokawa.
He confessed it.
He said to me
that he killed all three of them.
Mr. Kurokawa. Breathe in.
Take a deep breath. Slowly.
I'm sorry.
But I have no evidence!
Evidence… None was found
in those two murders too.
It must be even harder
to get the evidence 11 years ago.
The investigator at that time.
Do you have any clue who it was?
When I produced the documentary,
one person was evasive.
He was still active at that time,
so he refused to be interviewed,
but he should be retired now.
Are you bringing up the murder
11 years ago again?
We heard that you participated in
the initial investigation,
so we hope you'll tell us about it.
At that time, in Kanagawa,
there was another major case, right?
A family in Hodogaya was murdered.
A man arrested by the police
wasn't charged
by Yokohama Prosecutors Office
due to lack of evidence.
The man committed the murder
right after that, right?
-It was…
-A family of five was brutally murdered.
The prosecutors' office's
stupid young prosecutor
caused the death of people
who didn't have to die.
The Touo University Student
Murder Case happened that instant.
To regain people's trust,
the police wanted to solve the case
at an early stage, right?
So they rushed it--
We made no mistake in our investigation.
We, the police,
arrested the most likely suspect
and collected evidence.
The method was the most proper one
in an investigation.
We want to pick up the pieces,
starting from that juncture.
If in the case 11 years ago,
something wasn't used as evidence,
another truth could be hidden in it.
Please tell us anything you know.
-Please help us.
A cigarette butt?
It was found at the crime scene,
but it wasn't even presented
as evidence at the trial at that time
because Senior Asama didn't smoke.
The prosecutor can choose
what they present as evidence, right?
That's why they didn't present
anything unfavorable to them.
If we analyze the cigarette butt,
maybe we can prove that Kozu was involved.
I'll file an appeal
in Yokohama District Court
for the retrial of the case 11 years ago
and request for the disclosure
of the cigarette butt collected.
In Kanagawa's Touo University
Student Murder Case 11 years ago,
there was a mistake of fact
in the evidence at that time,
so today, a law firm in Tokyo
filed an appeal
in Yokohama District Court for a retrial.
The convict, Daisuke Asama,
-Is this okay?
-stated that he is guilty…
The Public Prosecutors Office
warned us to report this with care.
It's all right.
I've prepared myself for the worst.
Miss Ayaka Akiu was stabbed
with a knife and her body was found.
The convict of the case had already died.
An appeal for a posthumous retrial
has been filed.
Mr. Taku Kurokawa, the representative
of the victim's family,
wants to reinvestigate the evidence
collected by
the investigation organization
at the crime scene
and he requests for the disclosure…
The press is making
too much noise about it.
The Prosecutor General is outraged.
We hope the prosecutors' office
will respond quickly.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
LIST OF EVIDENCE
CIGARETTE BUTT
Mr. Kurokawa!
Look! A cigarette butt was also left
at the scene of Kyoka Hanamaki's murder.
Later. We're in trouble.
Hey! Don't do whatever you please!
It's an unjustifiable search!
What's your reason for the search?
Mr. Tokunori Isawa
violated the Lawyers Act.
-Me?
-Twenty days ago,
when you had dinner with your friend,
you gave him legal advice
and accepted a fee, didn't you?
Oh. My friend is starting a business
and we talked a bit about it.
But I didn't charge him.
He only paid the bill.
Do you have to go so far
for something so trivial?
In other words, you're harassing us
because we brought up
the case from 11 years ago, right?
We're Tokyo's Public Prosecutors Office
and not related to Yokohama.
It's the Deputy Prosecutor General's
order?
Kurokawa, calm down!
That man worked at
Yokohama's office originally, so he…
Kurokawa. Don't.
Excuse me. It's a document for you.
Why now?
"Yokohama District Court"?
-Kurokawa.
-Let me have a look.
"Appeal for retrial of this case
is dismissed"?
DISMISSED
APPLICATION
CIGARETTE BUTT
NOT FOUND AMONG THE EVIDENCE
It isn't among the evidence?
They say there is no cigarette butt
among the evidence?
Excuse me.
POLICE DEPARTMENT
Miss Wakura?
I've been discharged from the hospital.
What is going on here?
Excuse me.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
TOUO UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDER CASE
CIGARETTE BUTT
NOT FOUND AMONG THE EVIDENCE
Welcome home, Shin.
Taku just came home.
You are too nasty.
The search in our office
and the concealment of evidence.
Everything was on your order, wasn't it?
Do you have to go so far to stop us
from finding out the truth?
Taku, your dad just came home--
Why is someone here now?
Anyway, both of you should calm down.
Yeah?
The real murderer was someone else.
The man himself confessed it
in front of me.
He laughed and said we had no evidence.
If only we have the evidence,
we could prove what he did!
But the prosecutors' office and you…
Are you going to turn a blind eye to it
just for your own dignity?
Miss Wakura is here too.
Sorry for coming so suddenly again.
It's okay. Anyway, your face is very pale.
I am fine.
Just wait a second.
Deputy Prosecutor General Kurokawa.
I am here for the same thing
as Mr. Kurokawa.
So far, Mr. Kurokawa has been
handling all the cases honestly.
He investigates what he doesn't know
until the last moment,
does experiments to prove it,
and it all started because of how
he feels about the case 11 years ago.
If you really think
the prosecutor's conclusion was right…
Miss Wakura.
I had no idea.
I didn't know about the cigarette.
That's my answer.
It was a waste of effort.
No matter what we ask him…
Was it really?
What?
Your father didn't say,
"There was no evidence."
He said he had no idea.
He had no idea.
If he was telling the truth…
The police didn't give it to him.
HOSHUNDO LAW OFFICE
You're back, Kurokawa.
What's the matter, everyone?
We talked about what we're going to do.
Our office is on the verge
of closing now because of you.
I am very sorry.
I'll take the responsibility
and quit my job here.
But please let me finish the case.
Can you take the responsibility
by resigning?
You inflicted such a big loss
on our office,
can you take the responsibility
by resigning from your job?
No, I think I can't.
But what should I do, then?
Show people that our office is correct.
In other words, prove that the defendants
of this case and the one 11 years ago
were falsely charged.
Don't yield to the oppressive prosecutors.
But the appeal for the retrial of the case
from 11 years ago was dismissed.
We will adopt a secret tactic.
In Mr. Fujita's trial,
we'll bring Kozu out as a witness.
Then we'll present the evidence
and prove the crimes he committed.
It's Mr. Beppu's idea.
Mr. Beppu!
Don't get me wrong, Kurokawa.
I hate criminal cases.
They don't earn me money.
But my brother defended the case
11 years ago.
If it'll settle the old score,
then it's a different matter.
Now, the whole Hoshundo Law Office
will work to exonerate Asama
in the Touo University Student Murder Case
and Fujita in the recent murders!
We have to be thorough!
Yes, sir!
SEIRAN ARTS UNIVERSITY
Mr. Kurokawa.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Hello.
-I'm Kurokawa, a lawyer.
-Yes?
I'd like to ask you about
student affairs office's Mr. Kozu.
Have you seen Nana with this man?
No idea.
Please have a closer look.
What?
-I've never seen him.
-No.
MURDER CASE UNDER THE TAKABASHI OVERPASS
STABBING OF WOMAN IN IBARAGI
We're gathering witness information
about this murder.
-Please tell us if You know anything.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
-Thank you very much.
We're seeking information about a murder!
MOUNTAIN PATH ENTRANCE
Not him.
All right. Yes.
Mr. Beppu.
Go to Narikawa Children's Park next.
KANAGAWA PREFECTURE
YOKOHAMA POLICE STATION
Is the cigarette butt from 11 years ago
really here?
I don't know.
Not knowing something
is important, isn't it?
That means we are going
to try very hard to find it out.
What a slave driver you are, Mr. Lawyer.
Thank you, sir.
But are you really sure?
What do you want?
TOUO UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDER CASE
CIGARETTE BUTT
The murderer was another man.
Senior Asama was falsely convicted,
so please help me do
scientific experiments to prove it.
Dr. Akiu, you are right.
I don't know how cold a dead body is.
And the pain it brought you.
The sadness too.
But…
I know the warmth that Senior Asama had
when he was alive.
We grew up together.
He had told me a lot.
About how much he loved Ayaka.
And how much he respected you
as a senior too.
The murderer was someone else.
Please help me this one last time.
I beg you.
Your son seems to have gotten
some new evidence.
I can't let him do something
that makes people criticize
the Prosecutors Office more!
My son…
He only wants to seek the truth.
Kurokawa!
Regarding the case 11 years ago…
IN CUSTODY. DAISUKE ASAMA
SHIN KUROKAWA
…I will settle it in my own way.
Not knowing something
is important, isn't it?
That means we are going
to try very hard to find out.
PERSONAL DETAILS
FAILED TOUO UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL DEPT. ENTER PREP SCHOOL
PASSED MEDICAL DEPT.
RESCISSION OF PASSING
ONE CRIMINAL RECORD
VIOLATED ANTI-NUISANCE ORDINANCE
The police
leaps at someone's self-confession
or simple circumstantial evidence.
You treat me like a murderer
without any evidence.
Are you a detective who forces people
to make a confession?
COURTHOUSE
DEFENDANT WITNESS EXAMINATION
This case, Kyoka Hanamaki's murder,
and Touo University Student Murder Case,
which happened 11 years ago,
have many things in common.
Like the wound left
on the victims' bodies…
SIMILAR WOUNDS FOUND ON VICTIMS
…evidence stained with the victim's blood
found near the body.
VICTIM - CLOTHES USED BY
MS. ASAMA FOR RESEARCH
Also, after 11 years, in this case,
we've found new, common evidence.
It shows that other than
this case's defendant, Mr. Junpei Fujita,
and Mr. Daisuke Asama, who was seen
as the culprit 11 years ago,
a third-party was possibly
involved in both cases.
He's saying that
the murderer is someone else?
Please have a look at
Defendant's Exhibit number 63.
The cigarette butt was found
at a riverbed in Ota City,
the scene of this murder.
The police found several cigarette butts
but did not treat them as evidence.
It is because the defendant
is a non-smoker.
Next, please have a look at
Defendant's Exhibit number 64.
This cigarette butt
was found at the ruin in Kanagawa,
the scene of the murder 11 years ago.
However, it wasn't even presented
to the public prosecutor
and was hidden in Kanagawa
Prefectural Police's evidence room.
It's also because,
like in this case,
Mr. Daisuke Asama was a non-smoker.
What? The police conducted investigation
under an assumption?
The two cigarette butts
have already been analyzed.
Now, with special permission,
Touo University Science
and Engineering Department's
Dr. Akiu will explain it.
The DNA on the evidence of this case
and the one of the case 11 years ago
have been analyzed using STR analysis.
A certain truth has been found after that.
The same person's DNA
was attached on both cigarette butts.
The same person?
It's a man being charged
for another crime.
The victim scratched the man
and his DNA was obtained
by taking the pieces of skin scraped off.
IDENTIFY DNA TYPE
MALE SKIN TAKEN FROM
A VICTIM IN ANOTHER INCIDENT
In other words, the evidence
shows that this murder is directly related
to the one 11 years ago
and we can identify the man who is
likely to be involved in both cases?
That's right.
Witness.
DEFENDANT WITNESS CROSS-EXAMINATION
In response
to the lawyer's claim just now,
I think there is another possibility.
For example--
A third party with ill intention
got a cigarette butt
and planted it at the crime scene.
It's a possibility.
Yes, you are right.
In that case,
that piece of evidence
makes no contribution as a clue.
I can say the same about
the prosecutor's evidence too.
The sketchbook stained with blood
found in this murder
and the blood-stained clothes and shoes
presented as evidence
in the murder 11 years ago
could also be planted to put the blame
on the two defendants.
But…
Relying on circumstantial evidence
to construct the image of the culprit
is the most risky and foolish act.
The investigation organizations
choose evidence intentionally
and even conceal it. This is outrageous!
People are falsely convicted,
not due to the lack of ability
to inspect or the lack of evidence.
It's caused by prejudice,
assumption, and useless dignity,
the weakness and ugliness
of people's hearts.
No matter how advanced
forensic science gets,
it's pointless if the people
who use it are corrupt.
What we need is
the simple and honest will-power
to seek the truth.
Without that,
the victim's resentment
and the agony
that the victim's family suffer
will never be able to be settled
in the real sense.
That was the case for the prosecution.
Thank you.
Please call the next witness.
I swear that…
the evidence I give shall be
the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.
Witness, Kazunari Kozu.
You'll be accused of perjury if you lie.
Please be aware of that.
Now, please begin.
First, please watch
Defense's Exhibit number 65, a video.
It's a video taken by
security cameras at a place
related to both murders.
CAMPUS OF SEIRAN ARTS UNIVERSITY
Mr. Kazunari Kozu,
at places near the victim, Kyoka Hanamaki,
near the defendant,
and the scene where
Nana Yamashiro's body was abandoned,
you were caught on the security cameras.
Also,
a witness testified that they saw you
with Nana Yamashiro.
From the result of the DNA analysis
and this evidence,
you're extremely likely
to be involved in these two murders
and the one 11 years ago.
If you can deny the accusation,
please explain yourself.
Well…
I cannot.
I've told you already, haven't I?
I was the one who killed Ayaka Akiu
11 years ago.
I was also the one who killed
Kyoka Hanamaki and Nana Yamashiro.
He admits to all the crimes?
Why did you do that?
If I must say, it was to reveal
the problem of Japan's police
and public prosecutors' office.
I came up with the idea 11 years ago.
If I plant evidence that points directly
to someone as the murderer
and go to kill someone,
what would you guys do?
I carefully selected the person
I would kill and the culprit.
Put the bait there.
I half-prepared myself for the worst.
I thought, they would find out
at once anyway.
But the result was
you guys simply took the bait.
So, I did it again,
using Kyoka Hanamaki
and the stalker there.
I stole Hanamaki's student ID card
and let the stalker find it.
I took the sketchbook
from the crime scene to the factory
and threw it away.
The only thing that went wrong
was someone saw me.
The kid, Nana Yamashiro.
She saw you,
so you killed her to shut her up?
No.
The idiot shamelessly showed up
in front of me
and told me to give her hush money.
That's why.
I did feel sorry for the stalker.
She was killed in the same way,
so they suspected that
you were a serial killer.
No wonder false convictions
still exist in this country.
I've been able to say everything
and I feel amazing now.
The press will make a fuss
and I'll become famous tomorrow.
"The vicious serial killer confessed
his crime in court," they'll say.
I'll be sentenced to death anyway.
If you like,
I'll tell you in detail
how I killed the women.
Mr. Akiu!
Good Lord, my work was amazing!
The useless police, prosecutors.
In your faces!
Kazunari Kozu, 35 years old.
Your father is a renowned pathologist.
You applied to Touo University's
Medical Department to do pathology
but failed four times.
What?
After the four years,
you finally passed the exam,
but just before your enrolment
on March 20, 2006,
you were suspected of molesting
a girl in high school on a train.
-You were arrested--
-Hey!
Stop it.
You kept denying the charges,
but you were charged,
put in custody for 58 days,
and found guilty.
As a result, you couldn't study
at the university you wanted to go to.
I said, stop talking about my past!
I went to meet the woman
who accused you of molestation.
She regretted it very much.
She lied and accused you of molestation
to get the money
for settling it out of court.
She said she falsely accused you.
She confessed to me that
she messed up your life.
This is ridiculous!
What's the point of doing this now?
Ridiculous!
Falsely charged of molestation.
This is the reason that
you committed the series of murder?
Mr. Kozu,
I cannot forgive you.
If you'll serve your sentence
without regretting what you did,
I will never accept it!
If you don't look properly
at what you had done,
the victims and those who lost
a family member won't get closure.
I don't care! What's wrong with you?
Because I didn't know.
I want to know everything about you.
-I want to understand you.
-Shut up!
Your Honor, I killed three people.
A serial killer who killed three women.
I don't want that to be
all I know about you.
Shut up!
Kazunari Kozu.
Shut up.
-You were innocent 12 years ago.
-Shut up!
Shut up!
-You were innocent.
-Stop…
That is exactly why…
I am very frustrated.
You should be the person…
who knows the agony
of being falsely accused most.
As a person…
Please face the pain in your heart
until the very last moment.
That was the case for the defense.
Prosecutor, any cross-examination?
No, Your Honor.
Come on. Stand up!
In that case, next--
Your Honor.
I would like to say something.
Just now,
the truth of a murder 11 years ago
and these two murders have been revealed.
I prosecuted Daisuke Asama
and claimed that he was guilty
and drove him to his death.
As a judicial professional,
a decision I made
took away a person's life.
I would like to apologize wholeheartedly.
I've finished.
People make mistakes.
That's why there are criminal cases.
People are falsely charged sometimes
and many people are hurt.
Even so, I don't want to lose hope
in the judiciary.
If we want to seek the truth,
admit our mistake if we made one,
and have the courage to correct it,
I believe
that we can surely
clear someone of false charges.
The defense lawyer…
insists that the defendant, Junpei Fujita,
and Daisuke Asama in
Touo University Student Murder Case
are innocent.
It's over.
Yes.
But I still don't feel relieved.
Because Ayaka and Senior Asama…
and the two victims this time…
will never come back.
True.
But at least I feel better now.
I can now…
mourn over the death of Ayaka and Asama,
the person she loved.
Yeah.
Why do you follow me?
What? You go for a drink
at a time like this.
But I'm telling you,
I'm going to have Oolong tea.
I want to file an appeal for the retrial
of the murder 11 years ago.
A public prosecutor has the right
to do so, indeed, but…
One needs to correct his mistake.
Good evening, dear.
UNREAD - CRIMINAL DEFENSE
REQUEST FOR MR. KUROKAWA
This is impressive!
It's packed with criminal case orders!
It isn't impressive and I am not happy!
We are short of staff
and they don't earn me money!
Calm down. A young man
who aims to be a lawyer
because he wants to handle
criminal cases has shown up.
Someone who is going to bring us
even more trouble than Kurokawa.
PASS
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Ms. Kinosaki, is it okay to be so relaxed
when the bar examination is coming up?
Ms. Kinosaki's result in the mock exam
was better than mine.
-Really?
-After I pass it,
I can help Mr. Kurokawa
on many, many more things.
I am going to work much, much harder too.
TAKU KUROKAWA'S HOME
What's the matter?
-Okay.
-Yes?
Interview!
My boss finally let me do
a special program on you!
I really don't know how to be interviewed.
You really won't
do the interview, Kurokawa?
I am sorry.
Oh, I have to work now. Sorry…
In that case,
I'll make it using the videos
I've filmed so far.
We've got loads of materials.
But in that case, you have to get
Dr. Akiu's permission too.
Speaking of whom,
Dr. Akiu is planning to set up
a private forensics science lab.
It'll be heartening to Kurokawa
if he sets up the lab.
Kurokawa will surely make Dr. Akiu
do large-scale experiments for him.
Excuse me.
Okay, where is the document?
Oh no!
I've learned my lesson.
It's useless asking you
to tidy up your desk,
and I know that now.
I'm impressed.
THIS DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS