-Is it really okay?
-Of course.
But won't it trouble you?
This is no trouble at all!
I'm going to save you!
Look! Isn't it nice? It's called Wasamyo.
Wasamyo?
A combination of wasabi
and myoga ginger. Wasamyo.
It comes with a pack
of instant fried noodles.
There are 38 variations,
so it's really hard to collect them all.
Would you like a pack, Miss Arima?
You would, right?
THE WEIRD WASAMYO FIGURES
38 IN TOTAL
You'd better not. It tastes super awful.
The wasabi myoga ginger mayonnaise
is especially gross.
It's offensive
to call it instant fried noodles.
It's another number four.
I heard that he felt down
after he lost the other day,
so I came to check on him.
He is actually more excited
than usual these few days.
CERTAIN VICTORY
Okay!
What are you doing, Noboribetsu?
Why are you wearing
the "victory" headband?
Marron Circle Company Limited?
It's involved in
a criminal case lately, right?
Case?
-Kurokawa!
-Yes?
I'll give you a job.
Defense of a murder case!
-These are the documents.
-Oh. Thanks.
-Hey!
-I'm sorry!
This is new.
You've brought him a defense job
for a criminal case, Mr. Beppu?
It's against my will too.
Noboribetsu's been doing it himself
secretly, without my permission.
Mr. Noboribetsu does criminal defense?
There's a good reason--
I don't care about your reason.
You usually only do corporate law cases,
so obviously, you'll lose.
But we don't know
if we can win or not either.
The press is interested in this case too.
Do it properly, Kurokawa.
Noboribetsu, your fee will be cut
as a penalty.
Also, depending on the result
of the trial,
you could be transferred to
the criminal division as punishment,
so be prepared for it!
No, Mr. Beppu! Wait a minute, Mr. Beppu!
Being transferred to
the criminal division is a punishment?
"The Amane Island
female employee murder case."
Yes! That's the case.
An employee of the company
that makes this toy was murdered.
Her colleague was arrested,
but she denies the charge completely.
She denies it completely?
That will make things pretty difficult.
A murder.
How could I kill her?
It's not possible.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
Criminals lie and hide facts.
I just hate her to the bone.
No matter how much you hated her,
we still don't know
if you really killed her or not.
The incident happened on October 21, 2018.
Eighty-two kilometers away from
Tokyo Bay's coast, on Amane Island,
a drowned female tourist's body
was found on the coast.
The deceased was
Marron Circle Company Limited's
contracted designer,
31-year-old Risa Himeshima.
Right before Himeshima went missing,
she was with her friend, Nami Ogasawara,
who traveled together with her.
We went snorkeling in the sea together,
then I couldn't find her halfway through.
I had no idea that she had an accident.
In the autopsy,
sea water and a large amount of sand
were found in her lungs.
The condition was clearly different
from usual drowned bodies,
so Ogasawara was arrested for murder.
What was the relationship
between you and Ms. Himeshima?
She was my junior at my company.
We were close friends too.
The statement states that
Ms. Himeshima was a contracted designer.
She planned to quit when
she got married three years ago,
but the company stopped her,
so she worked from home.
After all, she had designed
many popular pieces of merchandise.
Risa was blessed
with talent and friendship.
All our colleagues loved her.
I thought of her as my younger sister too.
How could I kill her?
It's totally impossible.
Definitely.
We don't know yet.
Pardon?
Even if you feel affection for someone,
it doesn't necessarily mean
that you wouldn't kill them.
Do you suspect me?
That's not what he means, he just…
Miss Ogasawara.
Please let me ask two questions.
Okay.
First.
Are you hiding anything?
It's a murder case and we have to win
by proving your innocence.
Will you tell us everything
without hiding anything from us?
I am not hiding anything.
I see.
Second question.
Did you really not kill the victim?
I did not kill her.
All right, then.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
I'm counting on you.
By the way, why did you ask
Noboribetsu to defend you?
Mr. Noboribetsu offered to defend me
when he learnt about the case.
He said I could count on him
to prove my innocence.
Did you know each other before this?
Yes, we met half a year ago.
-Matchmaking party?
-Yes.
One that was held
by the dating club I registered at.
We got along the first time we met
and we've already gone
on about four dates.
Have a look at this!
Even so, you shouldn't have said
something irresponsible,
like you'd definitely prove her innocence.
She isn't someone
who would commit a crime.
I'm confident
in my ability to judge a person.
That's not the point.
You offered to defend her to impress her,
but we have to do the job.
It isn't my fault! Mr. Beppu found out!
Anyway, our happiness
is in your hands, Kurokawa!
Miss Arima, about
Miss Ogasawara's information…
I gathered it right away.
Nami Ogasawara, 36 years old.
After she finished college,
she joined Marron Circle Company Limited
and worked at the Product Planning
and Development Division.
She has a 70-year-old mother
who needs to be cared for.
She lived with Ogasawara
before the incident,
but she stays with a relative now.
Her dad died two years ago and she'd been
caring for him for a few years too.
She's a serious person.
Everyone who knows her
can't believe that she killed someone.
You see?
I was right about her!
Kurokawa, do everything you can
to prove her innocence!
Anyway, I'll read the documents
thoroughly again tonight.
Mr. Kurokawa isn't like his usual self.
He just lost a case to prove
someone's innocence,
of course, he'd be nervous.
I've talked about Himeshima
and Ogasawara many times
to the police and the prosecutor.
We're wondering if you remember
or notice anything new.
I would've called the police if I had.
KEISUKE TSURUMI
I'm too busy to sleep because of the case.
We'll finish as quickly as we can.
Talk to our division's colleagues
if you want to.
I'm the only man in the team.
The two of them got along.
Miss Ogasawara was the one
who helped Risa become a designer.
Miss Ogasawara helped her?
Miss Ogasawara wanted to be
a designer too,
but she realized that Risa was gifted,
so she recommended Risa.
To Miss Ogasawara and Risa,
this is a token.
Kurimaru?
It's the first character Risa designed
under Miss Ogasawara's guidance.
It was rejected right before production
and wasn't commercialized in the end.
Risa felt down because of this,
so Miss Ogasawara used the design
to make pendants as a memento.
She made only three for themselves
and for the company's record.
We didn't gain any useful information.
We only confirmed again that
Miss Ogasawara is really nice.
Yeah, but frankly, she is so nice
that I find it fishy.
Why do you find it fishy?
She's a nice senior at work,
she looks after her parents.
On top of that, her junior became
a designer, which was her goal,
and even got married before her.
If I were her,
I'd get so stressed out, I'd explode!
I'm sure you would explode before that.
Mr. Kurokawa, where are you going?
-The scene of the crime.
-What? To Amane Island now?
Yeah, it takes two hours by fast ferry.
But it'll be dark when you come back.
You might have to spend a night there.
-You can't go too, right?
-I can't.
I have to pick up my son
from nursery school.
It's okay. I'll go alone.
But going there on your own…
I can't go, but how about you,
Miss Wakura?
This is where the two ladies
came for snorkeling.
Yeah, the police thinks that
this is where Himeshima was killed.
Her body was found on the beach
a bit further away, though.
The suspect pressed the victim's face
into shallow water
and drowned her.
The theory is based on
the large amount of sand in her lungs.
I can't imagine Miss Ogasawara
doing that at all.
Mr. Kurokawa?
Wait!
What?
Mr. Kurokawa, stop it!
What are you thinking?
It's the sea in mid-winter!
-Miss Wakura…
-What?
-I brought a change of clothes.
Gosh! This is horrible!
It's good!
Thanks for waiting.
That's great.
You could change your clothes.
The only haberdasher on the island
got it sent here.
I didn't expect to spend money on this.
Would you like some
golden eye snapper? It's tasty.
No, thanks.
Anyway, after doing so much,
what did you get?
I didn't get anything,
but Miss Wakura,
what do you think about the wound
on the victim's palm?
I keep thinking about it.
I don't think you should
look at it when you're eating.
Maybe her body hit a rock in the sea?
But if it had,
there should be wounds like that
on other parts of her body too.
But there are none at all.
I told you not to put them out here!
She was grabbing something tightly.
She must have grabbed it pretty tightly
or it wouldn't form a wound like this.
Are you more impatient than usual,
Mr. Kurokawa?
Why?
Mr. Yufuin said maybe the case
you lost the other day made you nervous.
During Miss Ogasawara's interview too.
Even if you feel affection for someone,
it doesn't necessarily mean
that you wouldn't kill them.
Are you hiding anything?
Somehow, I feel that you
were harsher than usual.
Did Miss Ogasawara say or do
something to make you doubt her?
That wasn't why. It's just…
Nobody knows
what another person really thinks.
Excuse me.
I don't understand how someone
can eat when looking at these.
What would you like, Mrs. Kurokawa?
We recommend our broiled snapper.
No, thanks. And I'm not his wife.
Is that so?
I don't have any kinky interest…
You're leaving the restaurant?
My golden eye snapper--
It's your fault that I can't stay there.
SET MEALS &amp; SPECIALS
Anyway, we have to leave now
or we'll miss the last ferry.
You're right. Let's go.
But will you go somewhere with me
before that?
Go somewhere?
Excuse me. This is…
My home.
KUROKAWA
You mean…
the Supreme Public Prosecutors Office's
Deputy Prosecutor-General
Mr. Kurokawa's home?
Yeah, he kept calling me
to tell me to show up at home.
-But why am I here with you?
-Because it'll be easier for me.
No. You don't make sense to me.
It's absurd to come so late anyway!
I didn't bring a souvenir either.
But you aren't here
to tell them we'll get married.
It's absurd even so!
-Let's go.
-No.
Here you go!
Miss Wakura, keep eating.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-Okay.
You said you missed your son,
so I told him to come.
Why don't you sit down?
But our son is home after so long
and brought such a lovely lady
with him too!
I'll have to cook a gorgeous feast.
The rack of lamb will be ready soon too.
-She hasn't changed, right?
-She hasn't changed.
Mrs. Kurokawa is lovely.
Thank you.
But it must be a disaster for you.
It's tough being his girlfriend, isn't it?
Yes?
As I've explained,
I am just his colleague.
Of course, I don't usually
dress like this at work.
Of course.
My son probably
caused you trouble, didn't he?
What?
He made you go to Amane Island
to do some absurd reconstruction
and you had to get changed
as a result. Am I right?
How do you know?
I heard that you will be defending
the case's suspect.
You got informed quickly
even though you aren't involved.
But it worries me
when I think that
my son might embarrass me again.
In the end, you lost the medical
error case the other day also.
Are you going to defend the suspect
according to her claim as usual?
Yes, I am planning to do so.
Criminals lie and hide facts.
Bear that in mind
or you'll be pushed around.
The police and prosecutors assume that,
that's why they still falsely charge
some people.
The rack of lamb will be ready
in three minutes.
-Do you have enough drinks?
-Yes, we do.
I haven't had your cooking
in a long time. It's tasty.
Is it?
Miss Wakura, do you enjoy the food?
Yes, ma'am.
I especially like the stewed seafood.
-The acqua pazza?
-Yes.
There's a simple trick to make it.
Your rack of lamb will burn.
That's right. I'll…
I will gather evidence in my own way.
Law enforcement agencies will conduct
an investigation with science.
It isn't a lawyer's job.
But the problem is
they don't do their job well.
If they had investigated
properly at that time…
That case still bothers you?
You haven't changed.
Taku, watch your manners.
It's ready!
This is the best one I've made in years!
They do look delicious.
I'm sorry, I just remembered that
I have to check some documents.
-Oh, but you can do that later--
-The case is urgent.
Miss Wakura, enjoy your dinner.
Well, I think there's something
that you should say to me.
Did you enjoy the food?
Not that.
I mean you suddenly dragged me
into your serious family gathering.
I'm sorry.
But my mom was happy because you came.
Somehow, I feel that she had
the wrong idea until the very end.
Wrong idea?
Forget it!
Anyway, you and your father…
We aren't on bad terms, we just…
think differently.
Many things happened when I was a student.
When you were a student?
We rarely see each other
after I left home,
but that's what happens
every time we meet.
Both of us haven't changed.
Let's hurry back to prepare for
the pre-trial conference procedure.
Defense lawyer, you'll debate
whether it's a murder or not?
Yes.
We don't see any trouble between
the suspect and the victim,
so my client has no motive
to kill the victim.
Mr. Kurokawa.
I had no idea that you would claim
the suspect's innocence this time.
That's what my client wants to do.
But in this case,
it's important to know if she really
has no motive for murder.
Do you know something?
Well, who knows? Excuse me.
NO MOTIVE
Hey.
You'll only defend her
based on the lack of motive
and circumstantial evidence?
Can you really win the case?
In the case of a lay judge trial,
letting them see the suspect's personality
works to a certain extent.
-Noboribetsu.
-Yes!
You want to be transferred
to the criminal case division now?
-No, I don't.
-Go to work, then.
-How is the MA case going?
-I'll do it right now!
Kurokawa, can you win this time?
I don't know yet.
If you insist that she's innocent
and lose the second time in a row,
your job will be at risk too.
Do you get it?
Yes.
I've always thought so,
but doesn't Mr. Beppu make it obvious
that he hates Mr. Kurokawa?
Because he wants to make this
a corporate law office someday.
Really?
Don't worry.
Even if he does, I won't let him
do so as long as I live.
Now, go and do the preparation.
Okay.
COURTHOUSE
As I have just said,
my client had a good relationship
with the victim.
There was no clear reason for her
to plan and execute a murder.
Therefore, we have enough reasons
to suspect the prosecutor's claim
is constructed on the basis
of circumstantial evidence only.
I've finished.
Next, we'll proceed with
the examination of a witness
-requested by the prosecutor.
-Yes.
Miss Ogasawara?
Please tell us your name
and the relationship between you
and the suspect or the victim.
EXAMINATION OF WITNESS
Keisuke Tsurumi.
I'm the victim Risa Himeshima's
and the suspect Nami Ogasawara's
supervisor.
You offered to testify
against the suspect in court
about an important fact.
What is it?
I was maliciously stalked
by the suspect there.
No way.
Why did she stalk you?
Because she didn't want to break up.
The suspect and I
had been in a relationship.
We had been dating on and off
for seven to eight years.
Your Honor, what the witness says
has nothing to do with the case.
If you listen until the end,
you will know why this is relevant.
Lawyer's objection is dismissed.
The reason we had trouble breaking up
was the victim, Risa Himeshima.
The suspect suspected that
I was in love with Himeshima.
In love? But the victim was married.
Yes, she got married three years ago.
That's why it is impossible.
You made a move on her.
So she began to stalk you?
It started when we broke up
half a year ago.
Half a year ago?
Her harassment got worse and worse.
She would come unannounced
in the middle of the night
and go to matchmaking parties
to try to get my attention.
In the end, she started saying that
she'd kill me, then kill herself.
This obviously is a threat.
She was too annoying,
so I said to her one day
that I envied Himeshima's husband
and that I wished I had dated
a lady like Himeshima.
Her harassment stopped completely
after that.
That means,
it's likely that she directed
her grudge towards the victim.
What did you think when you were informed
about Risa Himeshima's death?
I was sure that the suspect murdered her.
And part of it was my fault too.
Thank you.
My examination with Mr. Tsurumi is over.
Why didn't you tell us?
When we first met,
Mr. Kurokawa asked if you were
hiding anything. Why--
Why didn't I tell you?
Are you serious?
Why? How can I tell you?
You'd definitely think
that I killed her if I had!
Yes,
I hated Risa.
I couldn't get what I want and be happy,
but she got everything and I'm so jealous.
I just hate her to the bone.
I don't have the talent
to be a designer, but she had.
I'd been at the mercy of a man
who kept cheating on me for eight years,
but she was happily married.
While I cared for my mom
and work exhausted my energy,
she was enjoying
her wonderful life to the fullest.
How could I not be frustrated?
But she looked up to you, Miss Ogasawara.
-If you hate her so much--
-I should've bullied her?
We worked together in a small company.
I should've kept a distance?
That's totally impossible!
It'd only make me feel more miserable.
Risa was a really lovely girl.
There was nothing bad about her.
I only got jealous of her myself.
If she had really been a horrible person,
it would've been easier for me too.
I am sorry.
We'll lose the case anyway.
You don't have to do
anything for me anymore.
You hated Ms. Himeshima, didn't you?
Yes.
You wished she were gone--
-Didn't I tell you so?
-But…
You didn't kill her, right?
You've revealed
many of your real thoughts,
but you didn't say you killed her at all.
No matter how much you hated her,
even if you hated her so much
that you wanted to kill her…
we still don't know
if you really killed her or not.
You trust me?
So, please…
what happened at the beach that day?
Please tell us the truth.
I…
I realized that my relationship
with Tsurumi was beyond repair,
so I decided to resign from my job.
Also…
I decided not to see Risa again.
That's why I wanted to tell her
what I really thought.
Miss Nami, why did you wear it here?
I just wanted to.
I would've worn mine if you had told me.
But in the end, I couldn't tell her
what I really thought.
I wanted to pretend to be nice
until the very end.
I only told her that I would resign
and that I would never see her again.
Then, lastly,
I threw the necklace,
which was the token
of our friendship, into the sea.
Miss Nami! Why?
I told you that I'd never see you again.
So I don't need it anymore.
Get rid of your necklace too.
I don't want you to remember me anymore.
I am sorry.
And that was the last conversation
I had with Risa.
I see.
IMAGE OF THE VICTIM'S RIGHT HAND
Mr. Kurokawa?
NAMI OGASAWARA
"Murder out of unjustified grudge."
"Crime committed by a female stalker."
"The dark side
of a respectable career woman."
All the headlines are so harsh.
The content is even worse.
They all attack her personality.
The verdict isn't even declared!
It isn't. That's why they can
write what they want.
My boss told me to ask Tsurumi
to comment on this too.
Will you go, then?
I won't.
I mean, if Miss Ogasawara
didn't kill the victim,
it'll expose their trouble,
which has nothing to do with the case.
But he successfully gave the judges
the impression
that the suspect had a motive to kill.
And Kurokawa has come to a dead end too.
Sand…
Yes, he's come to a dead end.
That guy hasn't moved since he came back.
Mr. Noboribetsu, I know you're upset
about Miss Ogasawara,
but you have to go back to work.
She deceived me.
My romance failed. We lost the case.
I'll be transferred to
the criminal case division.
My life plummets to rock bottom,
like this.
How rude of you to say our division
is rock bottom.
Dr. Akiu!
Why did you come?
I had to do something near here
and Kurokawa's going to lose the case,
so I dropped by to see his funny face.
He came to check on him
because he got worried.
Amane Island?
I think golden eye snapper
is the specialty there.
Yes, I tried it when I went there
to investigate.
Golden eye snapper is a snapper,
but it lives in deep sea.
That's why its eyes are big.
Yes, and?
Something that doesn't happen
in a tank like this
happens sometimes.
What… Mr. Kurokawa!
I'm sorry.
Found it.
Are you trying to kill me?
What are you doing suddenly?
Maybe her body hit a rock?
I threw the necklace into the sea.
I see.
That's what happened.
I'll get the things ready.
Thank you.
-And I need…
-Wait, Mr. Kurokawa!
I say this every time,
but tell me what's going on!
CONTROL BRIGHTNESS
Dr. Akiu, thank you
for helping us this time too.
We brought the object
for your experiment too.
He seems unreliable as a guinea pig.
Here you are.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
Miss Arima, he'll check with
the fishery cooperative for us.
-Yeah?
-Yes.
I've just cast the net too.
The net?
Looking for something in the sea
is like finding one speck
of gold dust in a desert.
We have to increase the probability
as much as possible.
SATOKO ARIMA
PLEASE RETWEET
I'M LOOKING FOR A NECKLACE I LOST
ON AMANE ISLAND LAST OCTOBER
We're ready.
Okay, let's begin.
Please go into the swimming pool there.
Please tell me what's going on.
Mr. Noboribetsu, this is to prove
Miss Ogasawara's innocence.
Prove her innocence?
I've gotten over the nasty woman!
You're cold-hearted!
This is the job
that you took on yourself, right?
Just so you know, I might not look it,
but I'm good at swimming.
If you want to investigate
why the victim drowned,
I'm not the right man!
That isn't a problem.
Even a swimmer who can swim
in the Olympic Games
will certainly drown in this experiment.
-He might die in the worst case.
-What?
It's a big problem, then!
What?
Excuse me.
-I'm looking for something.
-Yes?
A necklace? I haven't seen it.
If it's so small, it's likely
to have washed up the shore.
Mr. Noboribetsu, are you okay?
How can I be okay? I almost died!
I want to repeat
the experiment at least twice.
But I don't think it's possible.
Should I do it for him?
No, it's fine.
I'll do it.
But…
I am a lawyer too.
I'll do anything to clear
someone of false charges.
You have some guts.
We'll resume five minutes later.
What?
Dr. Akiu.
I met Mr. Kurokawa's father the other day.
Mr. Kurokawa brought me to his home.
-Did he tell you anything?
-No.
But as I thought, something happened
when Mr. Kurokawa was a student.
It was the reason that
he aimed to be a lawyer
and their relationship got worse.
Ask Kurokawa himself if you're curious.
Is it okay to ask?
The matter seems serious.
If you can't ask Kurokawa,
you can ask Mr. Yufuin or Mr. Beppu.
Or you can ask Arima.
They are all involved.
Involved?
Our positions were different,
but we all share something
unpleasant together.
Does that include you, Dr. Akiu?
Kurokawa!
-I got it!
-Yes?
I got the information!
Wow!
This is bad.
Mr. Kurokawa is calling.
-Hello?
-Miss Wakura, I found it.
Really?
-Yes, a girl found it on the beach.
-Look at this!
It's pretty, right?
Glad to hear that! So…
How did the experiment go?
The experiment is done.
We are ready.
Okay. We'll be back at once.
COURTHOUSE
You threw the necklace
that was a token of the victim's
and your friendship into the sea
and left after that.
You didn't harm the victim at all.
Is that true?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
I still have questions for my client,
but please have a look at
defense evidence number 46, a video
that was granted special permission.
The coast of Amane Island,
that is, the scene of crime,
has the same shape
as I've reconstructed in this tank.
The distance between the beach
and shallow water is short
and it gets very deep suddenly.
Waves move in a special way
over a geographical feature like this.
The phenomenon is called a rip current.
RIP CURRENT
The rip currents formed here
go towards the bottom of the sea
at ten meters per second.
If a person is attacked
by rip currents like this,
what will happen?
As you see,
no matter how good a swimmer someone is,
he cannot fight against it.
The victim was dragged in by it,
which caused her death.
That's all.
In the autopsy,
blood was found
in the victim's paranasal sinuses.
It was because she was dragged
into the rip current
and pressure on her body
suddenly increased.
Your Honor, judges,
the video of the experiment
and the result of the autopsy
aren't enough to be the evidence
of this case and they mean nothing.
They mean nothing? Why do you say so?
This case is concluded as murder
because the amount of sand
found in the victim's lungs
was more than in usual drowning victims.
There was sand in the water.
When the victim went
to pick up this necklace.
This is the necklace that my client
threw away on the beach.
It was washed ashore
ten days after the accident
and a girl who lives nearby picked it up.
Next,
there are wounds
on the victim's right palm.
She injured herself
when she grabbed the pendant.
ANALYSED BY EXPERTS IN FORENSIC MEDICINE
This was verified
by a forensic pathologist.
In other words, the victim
tried to take back
the token of their friendship,
the necklace that my client threw away.
Everyone, the lawyer's claim
is no more than a theory.
How would you explain the wounds
on the victim's right palm, then?
It's simple.
When the accused tried to kill her,
the victim struggled and grabbed
the necklace the accused was wearing.
Would this be what you mean?
This chain and pendant have
the same shape the accused had.
This chain broke, right?
But Kurimaru's did not.
Also, if that was what happened,
Miss Ogasawara would've
taken the necklace back
to destroy evidence.
-But that's--
-Prosecutor.
The victim picked up the necklace
from the sea voluntarily.
Why did Risa do that?
Because she looked up to you.
She didn't want to lose you as a friend.
That's the only reason.
Then, at that time, a rip current
dragged her into the sea.
Then, in that case…
In that case…
it's my fault that Risa…
It was an accident.
It isn't murder.
Maybe you hated her…
and maybe you were the one
who caused the accident to happen,
but this is still an accident…
and you did not kill her.
Your Honor.
For the above reasons, the defense lawyer…
claims that the accused,
Nami Ogasawara, is innocent.
MURDER ON AMANE ISLAND
FOUND TO BE AN ACCIDENT
THE ACCUSED IS FOUND INNOCENT
Thank you very much for your help.
It's been reported excessively
by the press,
so life will be tough for you.
I've braced myself for it.
Though I didn't kill her,
it's still true that
I caused Risa's death.
I compared myself to Risa.
I got jealous and hated her
for unjustifiable reasons.
I totally realized how ugly I am.
Is it really okay
that I'm not found guilty?
Nobody can punish you for what you think.
No matter what you really thought,
you pretended to be
a good senior and a good friend.
So, in other words, as far as
Ms. Himeshima was concerned,
you were a really nice person.
I shouldn't have pretended, then.
If I hadn't,
maybe Risa would still be alive.
No need to blame yourself so much.
I did something very disrespectful
to you, Mr. Noboribetsu.
It doesn't bother me.
Just one thing.
If that wasn't why we met…
would you have… well…
considered marrying me?
It's okay.
Please tell him what you really think.
I am sorry.
I knew it.
Noboribetsu, the MA case--
I've gotten everything done.
There you go.
You have?
Mr. Beppu!
I'm more cut out
to do corporate law cases,
therefore…
What?
I will continue to do my best!
PROFIT
What's that headband? Profit?
Yes?
-Yes?
-Yes!
You said you'd treat me to lunch,
but not here, right?
It is. The broiled golden eye snapper
will be ready soon.
You didn't try it on Amane Island,
did you?
No, I didn't,
but if you're cooking me something,
you should tidy up the place a bit.
Oh. Sorry.
TOUO UNIVERSITY STUDENT MURDER CASE
Touo University…
TOUO UNIVERSITY MURDER CASE
PRISONER COMMITTED SUICIDE
THE DRAMA IS FICTITIOUS
Because I want to know about you.
The past of the lawyers is revealed.
A student at a prestigious
fencing team had a heart attack.
I'll investigate thoroughly
and defend you.
Is it because the teacher abused
his power when he taught?
-Or…
-There is no reason for you to do it!
When you do science,
it always puts
your moral sensibility to the test.
All the reporters here,
please reveal this to the public!
Punishing someone is totally
different from exposing secrets.
Live, make up for what you did,
and turn over a new leaf.