Hello?
Good morning.
The new school year starts today.
Yeah.
You're an upperclassman now.
Everyone else is your junior.
Nishikata-senpai!
Don't tease me.
So?
What?
Why did you call?
I was worried you might be bummed
since I'm not there.
I'm doing just fine.
I even did 100 push-ups this morning.
Even though I haven't teased you?
I guess so.
I see.
So you're totally fine without me.
Yeah well, that doesn't mean
I'm not lonely.
So, you are lonely.
But I still have my friends.
You must be the one who's lonely.
I am.
What?
So lonely that
I don't want to go to school today.
What?
Would you come see me if I said that?
Cut it out! I was being serious.
I feel much better after teasing you.
You feel better too, don't you?
No way.
Why would I?
Are you not going to be late?
It's fine. I still have time.
You?
Paris is seven hours behind,
so it must be around midnight there.
You even looked up the time difference?
No way! It's just…
It was in my homework the other day.
Is that so?
Nice timing.
By the way, Nishikata.
What is it?
I have something to tell you.
Something super embarrassing happened.
Embarrassing?
Yeah.
Oh! You should try and guess.
If you can get it in three tries,
I'll do anything you say.
Anything?
Yes. Anything.
Anything at all?
Yes. Anything at all.
I'll make whatever you want
the most come true.
"What I want the most"?
Oh, but… That might be the answer.
Oh, well.
Have a guess.
"Something embarrassing"?
Is that what you said?
Um…
You're not thinking something weird,
are you?
No way.
What could it be?
Hurry up.
Okay…
You were late on your first day of school.
I wouldn't do that.
I'm not like you.
I'm only late sometimes.
Two more tries.
Um…
Give me a hint.
Is it something
that I would be embarrassed by?
Yeah. Super embarrassed.
Really?
I have no idea.
Let's hear your second guess.
What?
Something I'd be embarrassed by?
Yes.
Well…
You got so nervous at your new school
that you farted in front of everyone?
I wouldn't do that!
Is that what you did?
No way.
Of course, she wouldn't do that!
I wasted a guess.
Hey, Nishikata.
Are you even trying?
I am.
What is it…
Give me a hint. This is too hard.
A hint?
Okay.
It's embarrassing
but also something happy.
What? Embarrassing but happy?
That's right.
Something happy for you?
Yeah.
But it might make you happy too.
Make me happy?
I have no idea.
Is there such a thing?
It's usually the opposite.
Embarrassing things are not happy.
How can I put it?
If you heard the answer,
you'd think it was
a pretty shocking confession.
You wouldn't believe it.
The most unlikely thing.
I think you'd be surprised.
The most unlikely thing?
A "shocking confession"?
Come on.
A shocking…
A confession?
What?
What's wrong Takagi-san?
Did you just say, a confession?
Yeah, I guess I did.
Wait a minute.
Did you think I called to confess
my feelings for you?
What?
What are you talking about?
You're confessing your feelings for me?
Well…
Is that your last guess?
Wait a second. Hold up.
What?
She's confessing her feelings for me?
There's no way.
Huh?!
She did say it was something unlikely.
And also…
it was embarrassing but happy.
What?
How do I answer?
Hello?
Hello.
Hey.
Is that your final answer?
That you think I'm confessing
my feelings for you?
Um…
Yes. That's my final answer.
Is that right?
I'll be so embarrassed if I'm wrong.
Wrong.
Not even close. You're hilarious.
-What were you thinking?
-Oh, no.
I don't know. I give up. I have no idea.
What was it?
What was the answer?
I see.
If I were to confess my feelings for you,
you'd be embarrassed…
but also happy.
It's not like that.
You said it was something unlikely.
You mean you'd be happy to go out with me?
Or, that if I confessed and you said yes,
I'd be the happy one.
Either way, are you saying you like me?
I didn't say that!
It feels so good teasing you.
Thanks.
"Thanks"? I didn't do anything.
So what was the right answer?
I'll tell you next time.
I have to know. Tell me.
Isn't it almost time to go to school?
You're right.
I got to go.
Okay.
Bye then. Talk to you soon.
You have to tell me next time.
Okay.
Next time.
Bye.
-Good morning.
Thank goodness I made it on time.
We're second-year students
and you haven't changed a bit.
That's not true.
I'm a senpai now.
Senpai?
I'm not in any club activities,
so I doubt anyone will call me that.
Nishikata-senpai.
What?
Is that what you'd like me to call you?
-Do you like it?
-No.
You sure look happy, Nishikata-senpai.
How is it?
How does it feel to be a senpai?
Cut it out.
A senpai…
There is that, but it's the class change
that really matters to me.
That's right.
It will determine our lives
for the next year.
Right.
I hope I'm in the same class as you.
What?
No, it's just…
If we're in the same class
I'll have more chances to beat you.
Oh?
So you want to be in the same class as me.
I said no!
That's not what I meant.
I hope we're in the same class again.
Yeah.
Oh?
Your face is turning red,
Nishikata-senpai.
Is something wrong?
Cut it out.
-I'm curious.
-Right, which class will we be in?
Yay! We're in the same class!
CONGRATULATIONS! 2014 CLASS LIST
-Oh, I'm in class three.
-Me too!
-You're right! I'm glad.
-Let's get along.
What about you?
NISHIKATA
So I'm in class three.
Same as Nakai.
All right.
I'm in class three too.
We're together again, Nishikata.
Oh, you're in my class too.
Let's get along.
What?
Takagi-san?
What are you doing here?
That's too big a reaction, Nishikata!
W-What about Paris?
Why? You went to Paris.
Let's get along again, Nishikata.
THIRD YEAR CLASS THREE
Good morning.
-Good morning.
-Takagi-san?
Huh? Good morning.
-Morning.
-What?
Didn't you go to Paris?
Good morning.
What are you doing here?
My dad's company
decided to postpone the move.
Really?
-Yeah.
-Let's make third year a good one.
-Thanks!
-Yes!
-Takagi-san, good morning.
-Good morning.
This is the embarrassing thing
you were talking about.
That's right.
The move got postponed.
Isn't that embarrassing?
After everything everyone did for me.
I'm so embarrassed.
We get to go to the same school again.
Yes. Just like I said.
Something embarrassing, but happy.
It makes me happy
and I thought you would be too.
Didn't you want this?
Well…
I did but…
In other words,
I get to keep on teasing you.
Isn't that great?
Not at all.
Takagi-san.
Yeah?
Thanks.
For what?
For calling me this morning.
I was actually going to call you too.
You were?
How come?
You wanted to hear my voice that bad?
No, it's not like that.
I just thought you might be lonely.
Is that so?
So you wanted to hear my voice.
It's kind of like…
we're a couple.
What?
It's not!
I was just worried.
Worried?
That sounds like we're a couple too.
You even looked up the time difference.
But that was just your homework right?
Seriously…
Just cut it out.
Once more for good measure,
let's get along again, Nishikata.
I look forward to it.
Why so formal?
Lay off.
Huh?
-It's so pretty.
-What is?
-It is pretty I guess.
-Yeah.
The sea is sparkling.
I wonder if we can see anything.
Far away.
"Far away, it is not"
became, "It is not far away"
as the language changed.
And so the negative form…
Takagi-san is next to me.
That alone makes me so happy.
Here.
Thanks.
That eraser.
Do you remember?
If you write your crush's name
and use it all up,
that person will like you back.
LOOK AT THE HALLWAY
This is the one you teased me with before.
When I told you before,
you said you didn't believe in it.
But some things really do come true.
What?
What do you mean?
Erasers…
have a front and back right?
What?
No way…
Could my name be on the back?
LOOK AT THE HALLWAY
It doesn't say anything.
Oh?
Did you think your name would be on it?
No way.
This isn't the same eraser as last time.
What do you mean?
I may have used that one all up.
What?
Nothing.
Three months later.
During summer vacation.
Takagi-san…
ended up moving after all.
It was postponed for a bit.
But because of her father's work
she ended up moving to Paris.
-Bye for now.
-Take care.
Takagi-san!
Goodbye!
Nishikata!
Let me tease you when I get back!
No way.
It will be my turn to get back at you.
Got it!
I can't wait!
-Takagi-san!
-Goodbye!
Bye-bye!
See you!
TAKAGI-SAN TAKE CARE!
See you next time!
Thank you!
Bye-bye.
Takagi-san!
Thank you, Nishikata!
Thank you!
Takagi-san!
Subtitle translation by: Tom Grathwol