Can you open it for me?
Yeah, I guess.
Whoa!
Keep it down, Nishikata!
Sorry!
You're making me laugh so much.
Give me a break!
That's my line!
I'm always getting teased by Takagi-san.
If you write your crush's name
on an eraser and you use it all up,
that person will like you back?
"Roukamiro"?
Here.
Thank you.
We've been staring and staring.
You and me.
Only because to draw we…
You ran all the way here
to send me a picture of the sunset.
It's not like that…
It's so red, isn't it?
Red? Am I blushing?
A beautiful red sunset!
So pretty!
Oh, the sunset!
Yeah, it sure is.
You'd better watch your back,
Takagi-san!
There's gotta be some way
to trick Takagi-san.
Some competition, I can beat her at…
Morning, Nishikata!
Morning.
Let's go together.
What about your bike?
My bike?
Well, today…
I wanted to go to school
while holding hands with you.
So, I left it at home.
Really?
-You think so?
-No!
Of course not!
Takagi-san, you always do this!
Oh!
That's it!
That will work!
-Actually, about my bike--
-Wait!
How about if I can guess the reason,
I'm the winner.
All of a sudden?
A competition?
Sure! Guess away.
Yes!
I didn't miss what you said, Takagi-san!
The words you casually spoke
on our way home yesterday…
I think something's wrong with the brakes.
To think I could win so easily!
-The answer is your br--
-Wait!
One more rule.
If you guess the wrong answer,
you immediately lose the game.
If I'm wrong, I lose?
Yes.
So? What's your guess?
Well, then…
Let me think about it some more.
Brakes?
Is it not the brakes?
Hey, Nishikata.
Want to go this way?
Yeah, I guess.
Stairs?
You can't take the stairs with a bike.
That's it! It's because
she wanted to go this way.
Takagi-san.
Yeah?
Hold on!
This might be one of her traps!
Nothing.
Without a bike,
we can take all sorts of new roads.
So, it must be the stairs.
No, think this through!
I'll lose if I'm wrong.
Wait a minute…
Takagi-san.
I don't think this competition is fair.
Why?
Even if I'm right, you could say
I'm wrong and I'd still lose.
Oh… don't worry about that!
I wouldn't lie to you.
Really?
Really.
I've never even once lied to you before.
What?
I saw this cat
the last time I came this way too.
Isn't it cute?
It's so cute.
It's not scared at all!
That's it!
Now, I've got it!
Takagi-san, can I guess now?
Oh, you figured it out?
Go ahead.
The reason you're walking to school today…
is because your brakes are busted!
Brakes?
Stairs, and now a cat…
You've tried to mislead me with
things you couldn't do on a bike,
but you've made a grave mistake!
You were trying to make me forget about
when you mentioned your brakes yesterday.
But I saw right through it!
Well, Takagi-san, am I right?
No! That's incorrect!
What?
The answer is…
I just wanted to see you
get flustered about it.
That's really the answer?
You didn't change it?
It sure is.
If that's true…
I lost the second
I proposed the competition.
I had two reasons,
and you still didn't get it.
Too bad.
Two? So what's the other reason?
I don't think you could guess
that one either.
What do you mean? Tell me.
You already lost,
so it doesn't matter, right?
I already told you the second answer
when I saw you this morning.
What?
Nothing!
Come on, tell me!
It's the brakes, right?
Yeah, sure, the brakes.
"Yeah, sure"? What does that mean?
-Secret.
-Huh?
What?
Ready? Okay?
You good? Look at each other.
Ready?
Go!
Oh, no!
The winner is Nakai!
He's too strong.
You didn't stand a chance.
Hamaguchi you should be able to take.
-Let's go. All right!
-You're going to regret this.
Ready, go!
Oh, not bad! Keep going!
Oh you're in trouble!
It's bad!
Hamaguchi wins!
What?!
I understand losing to Nakai,
but Takao and Hamaguchi too?
-Nice.
-He was actually pretty strong.
Hey! Let me try!
Who will you challenge, Takagi-san?
The weakest person, I guess.
So, Nishikata?
You can do it!
It's just Takagi-san.
-She's a girl.
-You got this! You can do it!
-What?
-Nothing.
Okay.
-Ready--
-Wait!
-What?
-I just…
It's nothing.
Sorry! Let's do it.
Okay, then…
Ready, go!
You can do it Takagi-san!
I totally got this.
Are girls really this weak?
Takagi-san, what were you about to say?
Say?
I was thinking about how Nishikata
and I are holding hands.
What?
The winner is, Takagi-san!
Yay!
Don't sweat it, Nishikata.
H-Huh?
Looks like I'm the winner.
No worries. Can't win them all.
Damn it.
How can I beat Takagi-san? How?
Nishikata!
What are you doing?
Don't scare me like that, Nakai.
I'm just going to the toilet.
Are you practicing cool poses
in the mirror?
-Of course not!
-Funny faces then?
Funny faces? That's it!
Hey, this is actually pretty funny!
Like this?
Or this?
You and Takagi-san are pretty close, huh?
You don't, like, you know…
Dodging the question like that,
you definitely do.
Nishikata? You definitely lik--
What did you say?
What kind of face is that?
Cut it out!
Perfect!
-This will do it!
-Do what?
Let's check the answers.
Today, we'll be covering the basics--
Laugh at my funny face and
feel the wrath of the teacher, Takagi-san!
I have to wait patiently
until she talks to me.
Playing soccer…
Hey, Nishikata.
Now! Take this!
What's up?
We can turn a verb into a noun.
This is called a gerund.
-Hey! Nishikata!
-Sorry!
I thought you'd do something,
but a funny face?
How boring!
Hey!
If you're making a funny face,
you need to do this with your eyebrows.
Like this?
And pinch your cheeks like this.
Yeah, that's great!
Way better than before.
-Why?
-And then…
The person I was trying to make laugh
is teaching me how to be funny.
How humiliating.
Make it more wrinkly.
It doesn't matter!
As long as she laughs and gets in trouble!
Is this pretty good?
It's great! Way better.
Then laugh.
I think it might be funnier from the side.
From the side, it will be hilarious.
It will?
Okay.
Take this side face!
-What the hell are you doing, Nishikata?
-Sorry!
Jeez!
That's enough, pipe down.
We're still in class.
Curse you, Takagi-san!
My tummy aches!
She's finally laughing,
but this is all wrong.
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
Hey, Nishikata.
What?
Hey!
I can't do it anymore.
If Mr. Tanabe gets angry again…
I've got to ignore
Takagi-san in class today.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
What?
What is it?
You finally looked.
Let's have a staring contest
The first to laugh loses
Here I go
What's with that face!
Hey! Nishikata!
Sorry!
Listen up.
You've been disruptive in class.
Get your act together.
Sorry.
As a punishment, you'll be cleaning
the science lab after school.
-What?
-Don't "what" me!
Got it?
Yes!
It's Takagi-san's fault I got in trouble.
Why do I have to do this by myself?
I'll just get it over with and go home.
What?
You're such a scaredy cat, Nishikata!
Takagi-san?!
That was so worth the wait!
Wait, you're being punished too?
-Okay! Let's quickly get this over with!
-What are you talking about?
Here.
Hey, Nishikata.
Open the window.
What?
Nishikata!
What are you two doing in there?
We have to clean as a punishment
for being loud in class.
That's rough!
How about you?
I'm just wandering around.
-You are?
-Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hi.
Hi!
Let's not get in the way.
Huh? In the way?
Oh, you mean these two.
You're right.
I'll be going then.
Okay. See you.
Oh! Nishikata.
Good luck!
What?
Sorry, Takagi-san!
It's okay! See you!
Let's go.
Nakai's not just wandering around.
I think they're headed to the roof.
From his reaction
I bet it was Mano who invited him.
The roof?
Yeah.
I bet they're up there now,
just the two of them.
You were thinking something naughty!
I was not!
-Let's clean!
-Right!
Right! Let's clean.
We have to get this over with.
How romantic.
Romantic?
Those two.
I wonder what it must be like.
What?
Young love.
Yeah.
Let's finish this up!
Takagi-san, did you learn your lesson?
Stop teasing me, okay?
Yes. I'll behave a bit more.
You haven't learned anything.
We're going to get stuck cleaning again.
Nobody told me I had to clean.
What? Really?
So why did you…
You were hiding just to tease me?
That's part of it, I guess.
So, why?
Because I also
want to experience young love.
What?
I know! To thank me for helping you clean,
buy me juice on the way home.
What? Why?
Thanks!
"Thanks"? You've got it backward.
I'm the one who deserves a juice.
I wonder what flavor I should get.
Subtitle translation by: Tom Grathwol