Let's have a staring contest
The first to laugh loses
Here I go
What's with that face!
Hey! Nishikata!
Sorry!
You're such a scaredy cat, Nishikata!
Damn it.
How can I beat Takagi-san? How?
I was thinking about how Nishikata
and I are holding hands.
What?
Looks like I'm the winner.
-No worries.
-H-Huh?
You'd better watch your back…
Takagi-san!
This concludes the morning announcements.
Now the teachers will…
You must have stayed up late watching
last weeks Hyaku Kata on repeat.
Did not.
Hyaku Kata…
that's 100% Unrequited Love, right?
You haven't seen it,
but you know its abbreviation?
Got it?
Nishikata and Takagi.
What?
Don't "what" me.
Starting today, Nishikata and Takagi
will be working reception in the library
every Thursday during the lunch break.
Got it?
Yes!
Pardon?
Don't "pardon" me!
Do you understand?
Yes.
LIBRARY
This book is so funny!
Hey!
We're losing a lunch break
a week for this.
It will go by in a flash if we read books.
Books…
Do you read a lot, Takagi-san?
Yeah.
You don't seem like you read much.
That feels like being told I'm stupid.
How about manga?
What do you read besides Hyaku Kata?
Why do you assume I read that?
Boys reading girly comic books
is totally fine by me.
I've read it but I don't really
know much about it.
We might as well grab some books.
I don't really read books.
I only joined the library committee
because it sounded easy.
DINOSAURS
Wow.
Did you find something, Nishikata?
Not yet.
Since we're here.
Why don't we choose a book for each other?
I guess we could.
Okay, so let's do it.
Three, two, one, go!
What?!
You looked interested in it.
You saw me?
I like encyclopedias too.
Here.
BRIAN BY TOMOKO MIZUKAMI
Huh… I've never read this one.
I wonder what it's about?
Have you read this?
No, but I thought it looked good.
I just grabbed it at random.
I hope it's good.
Takagi-san sure looks good with a book.
What's that?
Were you looking at me?
No, I wasn't.
Oh, I know.
You were thinking about
how to tease me since we're all alone.
Yeah, maybe I was.
PREHISTORIC TITANOSAURS
EVOLVED TITANOSAURS
I'm enamored.
What?
I'm in love.
With those honest eyes.
-Like the heart of a young boy.
-What?
What?
"When the young girl spoke those words,
Tanaka dropped his glass of orange juice.
Even the sight of the spill
was beautiful."
I see.
She was just reading aloud.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Oh! This is, um…
It's called an Argentinosaurus.
-It's a type of dinosaur.
-Yeah.
It's 36 meters in length.
-Really?
-It's long, right?
Super long.
We didn't get any visitors.
You're right.
Hopefully next week too.
So, we can be alone?
No! Because it's easy.
You should try reading a novel next week.
A novel? Do you have any recommendations?
Let's see…
Besides the one you brought me today,
anything is okay.
Huh? Was it really that bad?
Sorry, I chose it without checking.
No, it was good.
But I wouldn't recommend it to you.
What do you mean?
Because you'll realize I made up
the lines that I read to you.
What did you say?
Nothing.
What?
What did you say?
Forty-five…
Forty-six…
Forty-seven…
Including the walk home
I was teased twelve times today.
Fifty!
And twelve times five…
is sixty.
Fifty-three…
Five push-ups for each time
Takagi-san teases me that day.
Self-punishment
for always falling for her tricks.
Fifty-six…
To avoid going through this again,
I've got to keep my guard up,
starting tomorrow.
Fifty-nine…
Sixty!
Brace yourself, Takagi-san!
100% UNREQUITED LOVE
NOW A HIT ANIME SERIES
Oh, no! Hyaku Kata is about to start!
Huh?
Oh, here it is!
Okay.
100% Unrequited Love…
Yes!
Our eyes meet after school
And the usual teasing begins
Even though I act like I don't care…
There's a new intro!
You say that I'm clumsy
I know it may be true
I can't tell you the way I feel
Oh, no! A surprise attack! Gotcha!
Boom boom goes my beating heart
The love meter is about to blow
Welcome.
100% UNREQUITED LOVE
-This one please.
-Thank you.
That will be 463 yen.
Thank you.
Welcome.
That's exactly 463 yen.
Here's the special giveaway card.
-Thank you.
Boom boom goes my beating heart
Where is it now? Love's location
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
Boom boom!
-Nishikata!
-Whoa?!
Always so easily surprised.
Takagi-san? What are you doing here?
You bought it, didn't you? The new volume.
What?
It came out today, right?
And this one comes
with a special postcard.
Show me.
Oh, yeah, it did come with a card.
Is this it?
Lucky you!
Isn't she so cute?
Well…
I guess it's cute,
but I read it because it's funny.
Then can I have it?
No way.
The intro of the anime changed too.
You were singing it, right?
But in the chorus…
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
It's actually…
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
Right?
No, I was right.
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
That's not it.
I think it's…
Unrequited love, mutual love
That's it.
"Unrequited love, mutual love"
That's how it goes.
Why don't we listen
and get to the bottom of it?
What?
It's so pretty.
Yeah.
Let's sit there.
Okay.
I bought the song yesterday.
Really?
I'll buy it later.
Here, use this.
What?
Why don't you just play it?
We can hear better this way.
The waves are loud too.
We should have just gone somewhere else.
Are you getting embarrassed?
Not really.
Then, here.
I'll play the song now.
LOVE'S GETTING CLOSER!!
100% Unrequited Love
Our eyes meet after school
And the usual…
The beginning is so great.
Don't you think so?
Yeah, it sure is.
Takagi-san is sitting so close.
I can't pay attention to the song.
If it's "Unrequited love, mutual love,"
then you're right.
and if it's "Unrequited love, mutual love"
then I'm right.
Okay.
…I like you, I love you…
I've got to concentrate!
…If only I could tell you
Boom boom goes my beating heart
Where is it now? Love's…
Nishikata.
What?!
Nishikata, you're too concentrated!
Who cares if I'm concentrating?
Are you done? The chorus is next.
What?
Um…
I knew it!
It was "Unrequited love, mutual love."
Really?
I missed it. Play the chorus again.
What?
I'd rather listen again
from the beginning.
Huh!
All right, Takagi-san.
I bet you know I'm right
and you're going to tease me
so I can't hear the chorus.
Do you want to listen?
Okay, from the beginning.
I got you now, Takagi-san!
100% Unrequited Love
Our eyes meet after school
And the usual teasing begins
Even though I act like I don't care
I always lose my cool
You say that I'm clumsy
I know it may be true
I can't tell you the way I feel
Oh, no! A surprise…
Here comes the chorus.
You're right.
Boom boom goes my beating heart
The love meter is about to blow
Just try and tease me.
You won't get me this time.
Boom boom goes my beating heart
Where is it now? Love's location
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
What?
Unrequited, mutual love
Love's getting closer
Boom boom!
I knew it.
It's "Unrequited love, mutual love,"
right?
You're right.
Looks like I was right.
I was mistaken this whole time.
Let's listen again.
Okay.
What?
Is something wrong?
I was worried you'd try to tease me again.
How mean.
Have I teased you today?
What?
I just wanted to listen
to the song with you.
Really? If that's the case…
Come to think of it, she didn't
even mention a competition.
Maybe she didn't plan
on teasing me after all.
And when her face was close,
I was just embarrassed.
So, she really does
just want to listen with me again?
I'll play it now.
Wait.
Okay, ready.
100% Unrequited Love
Our eyes meet…
Huh?
…after school
And the usual teasing begins
What?
Huh? Did you want to
share headphones again?
Not really.
Why didn't you just say so?
I see.
You wanted to listen while sharing
a set of headphones with me.
No, not that.
It's just… You said it was
hard to hear with the waves.
That was so we could
figure out the rhythm.
Yeah, but something's not right.
Nishikata, put the earphone in.
It's fine.
Just play the song.
What? You want me
to put it on you that badly?
I didn't say that.
Let's listen without earphones.
Whatever you say.
Lend me your ear.
I said it's fine.
Here. Come back.
Here.
Hey!
-Don't you want to listen together?
-I don't.
I don't!
Almost!
Boom boom goes my beating heart
Where is it now? Love's location
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
Love's getting close
Boom boom!
Boom boom goes my beating heart
Where is it now? Love's location
Unrequited love, mutual love
Love's getting closer
Boom boom!
Subtitle translation by: Tom Grathwol