Merry Christmas.
Did you think I was sleeping, Takagi-san?
Oh!
You're up late.
I knew you were going to trick me
by sneakily putting a present
beside my pillow.
Too bad, you're busted.
Well, here.
It's for you.
Merry Christmas.
Do you admit defeat?
Yes. You can be the winner this time.
Yes!
I finally beat Takagi-san!
How does it feel?
To finally lose to me?
Is it so bad you can't even talk?
No.
This is only a dream anyway.
What?
Merry Christmas!
Damn it. She even got me in my dreams.
I'll return these.
Okay.
Third year class one. Number 24.
One, two.
Thank you.
LAST DAY TO BORROW BOOKS
Hey!
-Hey!
-Number 21, please.
-Number 21.
-Okay.
Today is the last day of second semester.
I've got to finish this year…
with a win.
You can crochet?
I just started recently.
Do you want to try?
Huh?
I have an extra needle.
No, that's okay. It looks difficult.
I'll pass.
First, you do this.
Wrap it around here.
Do this, and this.
I see.
Like this…
This…
Put it in through the bottom like this.
Like this?
It's tough to explain.
Right here.
Then you go like this…
and this.
One more time.
Wrap it around here…
I'm done. It's too hard.
Really?
Is that a scarf?
It's to keep out the cold.
I see.
Shall I make one for you too?
What? No that's okay.
This is actually a present.
A present?
Yes.
For a 15-year-old boy.
Really?
I hope he likes it.
15-year-old?
A boy?
-Hey, Nishikata.
-What?
That's Taro from the candy shop right?
Did something happen to him?
This is him.
Huh?
The 15-year-old boy.
His owner said she
wants to dress him up to keep warm
because he's very old for a dog.
So, I said I would make something for him.
I see.
What? What's the matter?
Nothing.
Dogs sure are cute.
So cute.
You're funny.
Who did you think it was?
Taro.
Really?
100 percent sure.
My last chance this year
to beat Takagi-san.
I've got to think of something.
I'll be going this way.
-Okay. See you.
-Yeah.
Takagi-san.
Yeah?
Shall we have a year-end competition?
Sure.
What kind?
Um…
In that case can I choose?
-What?
-No?
I guess that's fine.
What should it be?
I couldn't think of anything myself,
so I guess it's fine.
It feels like a disadvantage though.
Too late now.
I've got it!
How about whoever makes
the other happiest, wins?
What?
Starting from now, we'll think
of how to make each other happy
and in 30 minutes we compete.
How do we decide who wins or loses?
How about a point system?
That's so random.
What do you think?
Wait a minute.
I think I have a chance at this one.
Okay.
Great. It's decided.
All I have to do is pretend
not to be happy and I'll win.
You're ending the year with a big mistake…
Takagi-san!
Let's meet at Osaki Shrine in 30 minutes.
Okay. See you there.
Maybe I'll just grab a pinecone
and wait at the shrine.
I'm looking forward to it.
Maybe I should take this
a bit more seriously.
What would make Takagi-san happy?
When does she usually look happy?
TEASING TICKET
GOOD FOR ONE DAY OF TEASING
This is all wrong.
She'll tease me without this anyway.
Something that will make Nishikata happy…
This is harder than I thought.
CANDY SHOP
Hello.
Oh, Nishikata.
What?
Takagi-san?
What a coincidence.
You thought a present would make me happy
but you don't have much money.
So, you thought you could get me
juice or some candy here, right?
Bingo.
Me too.
-Wow.
-No peeking.
Did we have to come all the way here?
Those were the rules.
I'll go first.
-Merry Christmas!
-Huh?
That's what this is?
It's almost Christmas, right?
I guess.
Here.
Thanks.
I wasn't this embarrassed in my dream.
Okay, here's mine.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Wow!
You remembered my favorite juice.
You're always drinking it.
The vegetable Hanako snacks too!
I saw you eating that once.
Thanks.
Hey.
So, who's the winner?
Whoever makes the other happiest, wins?
In that case…
-Maybe I was…
-Takagi-san.
What?
How about we make it a tie?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I was happy too.
Getting a Christmas present from you.
Thank you.
Hmm?
It's nothing.
How do I open this thing?
Will it open?
Yeah.
-Wow.
-It looks so yummy.
You gave me so much.
I hope that Takagi-san
won't tease me this year.
-Nishikata.
-Woah!
Happy New Year.
-Did you come here alone?
-No. With my family.
They ran into someone they know.
Same here.
Let's walk around together.
-I guess.
-Hooray!
Let's get our fortunes.
What did you wish for Nishikata?
It's a secret.
How about whoever guesses is the winner?
The first competition of the year?
Yeah.
Let's see.
Maybe, "I hope
I don't get teased by Takagi-san"?
What?
I knew it.
Damn it. She got me already.
Now it's your turn. What's your guess?
I bet you hoped to tease me, right?
No way.
That will come true without wishing.
You're right.
"I'm right"?
Thank you.
Want to have a fortune competition?
The second competition of the year.
One, please.
This one is all luck.
A 50-50 chance of winning.
-One, please.
-Okay.
I'll get a good one and win!
Number four.
-Number 27.
-Okay.
Here you are.
Thank you.
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
-One, please.
-Yes.
Ready, go!
GOOD LUCK / EXCELLENT LUCK
-"Excellent luck"?
-Hooray!
I'm the winner.
Come on, even her luck beats mine?
Be careful, it's hot.
-Thank you.
-Here.
-One more for you.
-Thank you.
AMAZAKE
-It's delicious.
-It is.
It's so yummy.
What's wrong?
Thinking about something?
Was it, "I wish for good health"?
Oh, my wish.
You're still thinking about it?
Yeah. If I get it right it's a tie, right?
You didn't say how many guesses we get.
Wrong.
I don't think you'll get it.
Damn it.
I can't start the year on a losing streak.
I want to get this one right.
It seems like…
it's all families and couples here.
You're right.
I wonder if other people…
think we're a couple too?
It's my mom.
Hello?
I'm drinking amazake now.
Okay.
Sorry, I got to go.
Well…
What?
Don't you want me to go?
No! I just wanted
to have guessed your wish.
I'm only joking.
I even won the fortune competition.
I'm glad I saw you, Nishikata.
See you later.
Takagi-san.
My fortune will win next year.
Are you inviting me
to join you again next year?
No, only if we meet by chance.
I hope we can go together next year.
Okay. Next year.
I'm sure my parents will be busy chatting.
What?
It's nothing. I was just thinking
how it already came true.
My wish.
-Your wish?
-Yes.
The truth is…
I wished to be asked on a date by you.
That's not what it was!
You're lying!
You're just teasing me again.
A whole year from now…
I hope we can go together.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's make it a great year.
Subtitle translation by: Tom Grathwol