SHINSHINMARU 88
CAPTAIN: KYUSUKE TANAKA
[Hansuke] I've been here a month.
I make money by submitting reports
about the lives of the residents.
Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
[mimics train honking]
[Hansuke] The first time,
I was paid 10,000 yen.
-I thought this would be a breeze.
-Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
[beeps]
[indistinct chatter]
EPISODE 3
HANSUKE AND THE CAT
But it didn't continue.
I had nothing to write.
I could only write lies.
[fly buzzing]
[camera shutter clicks]
[Hansuke] Is Hatsutaro actually
Shuzo Matsuoka's brother?
Tanba-san, you've got rice on your back.
-Get it off.
-[camera shutter clicks]
[Hansuke] Does Tanba-san have
a shogi board tattoo on his back?
MESSAGE SENT
But this is what I get paid.
Things are getting bad, Tora.
You can live this way,
but I can't survive on cucumbers!
[Tora] Why not write about yourself?
[soft chuckle]
I couldn't do that. That's so conceited.
[Tora] It's good enough
for one episode of a third-rate drama.
[Hansuke sucks teeth]
[collar bell jingling]
Sorry.
[Hansuke] When I open my laptop,
-that's the sign for Tora to leave.
-[collar bell jingling]
It's like he's saying, "I don't want
to interfere in master's work."
He's so well-behaved.
[meowing]
[lively music]
He's fat and tubby,
and his head's big and round,
like a soccer ball.
Wherever Tora goes,
he struts around like he's the boss.
He's completely different
when he's outside than when he's at home.
His territory grows every day.
He grew it all through his own effort.
[dog snarls]
-[screaming]
-[dog whines]
[whining]
[lively music]
[Roku-chan mimics train honking]
[mimics brakes squealing]
Hey! Hansuke's thieving cat.
You're on the tracks. Get off!
[Hansuke] Maybe he does it out of spite.
But it's more like he's daring you
to try something with him.
You're hopeless.
[Roku-chan mimics train chugging]
[Hansuke] He's always taking life head-on,
and powering through it and winning.
-That's how Tora lives life.
-[keyboard clacking]
KUNIKO'S WHIMSY DISH
HAM CUTLET ROLL
And Tora has a weakness for fried foods.
His recent favorite is the ham cutlet roll
at Wanpaku Delica.
[screaming in delight]
[Hansuke]
Reporting about Tora won't do me any good.
[sighs]
[Roku-chan mimics train chugging
in distance]
[Okabe] Sorry.
Things have gotten stricter lately.
Mm-mm.
[Okabe] All the boxed lunches
and sandwiches we toss out
have to be recorded and reported.
Thank you. That's a big help.
How's work? Going well?
What are you writing about now?
I actually read a lot myself,
like Risa Wataya.
[Hansuke slurping]
Today, the radio said
that since the temperatures are mild,
it'll be a nice day.
-Pollen levels are high too.
-Hmm.
That's right.
[Okabe] Hmm?
The boat banner, right?
It's the same as the one outside.
That's why
you suddenly got all awkward, right?
I'm not being awkward. Am I?
[awkward chuckle]
[Hansuke]
My family was an offshore fishermen.
Dad, Grandpa and my brother
were washed away on the boat in the thing.
But their boat banner
must have been found somewhere.
Do you mean The What?
The What or whatever it is.
Seeing it made me really happy.
That banner was
a symbol of the Tanaka family.
[somber music]
And only you survived?
Mm.
[Hansuke] And Tora.
[wind gusting]
[Hansuke] You feeling better now?
[Tatsuya] No, I'm not.
That's why I'm drinking.
I've finally learned.
To a parent, the bad kid is more adorable.
You're drinking
to get your mom to worry about you?
Then this place is a real bargain.
Man-to-man discount stew, 90 yen.
"Man-to-man discount"?
The stew's only 90 yen?
[Masuo] Better not ask what's in the stew.
[Hatsutaro] Have you watered this down
so we can't even tell it's shochu?
-[Hatsutaro yells]
-[head thumps]
Hatsu.
[chuckles]
That's called "oyuwari."
[Hatsutaro] Oh, my mistake.
No wonder you graduated from high school.
[Masuo] Hey, kid.
If you need money, we'll get you a job.
-It's manual labor.
-Seriously?
[Masuo] Seriously. If you've got a seal
and have gloves,
you'll get paid 10,000 a day.
Don't do it, Hansuke.
You can't do physical labor.
You'll just get hurt.
Assemble scaffolding.
Tear down scaffolding
and assemble it again.
It's scaffolding hell
of eternal assembling and tearing down.
If you need ideas for a novel,
I'll think of some.
What about that homeless father and son?
Homeless?
[Okabe] Here.
Sorry, but I can't give you bread
or boxed lunches anymore.
Hold on a sec.
[quirky music]
[son]
Maybe I will travel to Miyashita Ginza.
[father] I cannot allow you
to travel that far all alone.
I'll be fine.
Several restaurants there provide food.
It's almost their closing time,
so you go on home.
Are you sure?
If you insist, then I'll let you go.
Mostly, the boy gathers food for them.
He may not look it, but the father
is apparently
a privileged university grad...
-[shushes, chuckles]
-What? What?
[Tatsuya] Here. Here.
[footsteps approaching]
[Hansuke]
I decided to call him "Rich Man."
They don't have to live there.
There are empty prefabs here.
They should move in.
It's rent-free, after all.
You can live here if you lost your home,
but you can't
if you didn't have a home to begin with.
[collar bell jingling]
[jazz music]
[Hansuke] Tora walks through
the night-life district.
INFORMATION
It's the same as always.
Everything that humans do
is so dull and superficial.
Oh?
Tempura...
TEMPURA
Thank you.
-[customer] Thanks for the meal.
-Thank you.
-It's ready.
-Yes, sir.
What's that?
[chef] A stray cat?
[hisses]
[whispers]
Hey! Shoo! You're scaring people off.
-[screams]
-Ah!
Darn you! Don't do that here! Shoo!
Shoo!
[sizzling]
[whispers]
There's no need to cook it for him.
There's leftovers he can have.
When a cat gets like that,
they're bigger connoisseurs
than most people.
[server] Oi. Oi.
Eat this and go away.
[tired groan]
[snarls]
[comical music]
[blowing air]
[crunches]
-[Tora exhales in delight]
-[Hansuke] This is so delicious!
-[sniffing]
-Such a refined oil flavor and aroma.
This is miles better
from the fried food at Roku-chan's place.
The breading is crisp
and the inside is tender.
This texture,
if I could describe it in a word...
[screaming]
[soft chuckle]
-[collar bell jingling]
-[Tora grunts, snarls]
[Tora screeches]
[Hansuke] He could have scared him off
by attacking with his claws.
But the serious determination
in the boy's eyes said
he wouldn't be scared off.
[suspenseful rock music]
[music stops]
Oh, exalted cat. I beg of you, please.
You may have the mushrooms,
but please allow me to have
the two pieces of shrimp.
Please.
[son] Shrimp is Father's favorite. Please.
[collar bell jingling]
FRIED FOODS
RICE
[server] Ah!
-That tempura--
-[chef] Stop!
Come wait here next time.
[both] Thank you for this food.
-[camera shutter clicks]
-[son] Do you want this?
[father] You have it.
[camera shutter clicks]
[Hansuke] I sent a report to Mikki
along with the photos.
[kids chattering]
[kid 1] See you later.
[kid 2] Bye.
What?
MIKKI SENT YOU 50,000 YEN
[Hansuke] Oh. Sorry.
[mimics engine hissing]
[mimics train chugging]
RICE COOKER
COMPLETE PURCHASE
[soft gasp]
I bought it!
[Hansuke] Look, Tora.
It's the kind that reduces carbohydrates.
-[Kuniko] Here.
-[Hansuke] Look!
-[Kuniko] Why won't you eat this?
-[Hansuke chuckling]
[Tora] I'm used to high-class tempura now.
What's wrong, Tora?
Has your stomach shrunk?
You silly cat.
[Tora] Cut that out!
Quit touching my weenie!
[vehicle approaching]
[Kuniko] You want a corndog instead?
[resident 1] What's going on?
[resident 2]
They're tearing the whole place down.
[loud clattering]
[yells]
Can't you be gentler?
-[garbage truck engine whirring]
-[Masuo groans]
[son] Stop!
[resident] Those bastards.
Here's some emergency rations.
And this is a map to a soup kitchen.
[loud clattering]
Dang, it sure is a cold world.
It sure is.
I wonder who reported them.
It wasn't me.
I may not look it, but I'm compassionate.
-[resident 1] Huh?
-[resident 2] I wouldn't be so sure.
-[resident 3] He says he's compassionate.
-[resident 4] Not the way I see it.
[Mikki] What's wrong? I paid you.
[Hansuke over phone] That sure was a lot.
You did good work.
That's what I want more of.
Mikki, did you send me here
to be like some kind of spy?
[Mikki over phone] What if I did?
I knew it.
I wish you'd told me from the start.
[Mikki] Then you wouldn't have done it.
I totally would have. In fact,
it would have been easier if I'd known.
Besides, why me?
No family ties.
If anything happens to you,
it only affects your cat.
SHINSHINMARU 88
[Ryu] Hey, Hansuke.
[Hansuke] Oh.
Going to the bath?
-Yeah.
-Yep.
[Hansuke] Enjoy.
[Ryu] Will do.
Oh, right. Hansuke.
[sucks teeth]
-Let me read your novel sometime.
-[Hansuke] Uh, sure.
[Mikki] I'll tell you more later.
Check, please. Sorry I didn't finish.
-[customer] We're going?
-Yeah.
I'm still eating.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-It was very good.
[Hansuke]
But the boy never showed up again.
-[Tora shouting]
-[cat meowing]
[Hansuke] Since his rival was gone,
Tora became even more brazen.
He was in the heyday of his life.
Eventually, he went into heat.
[meows]
[screams]
[clattering]
[screeching]
[Hatsutaro] Shut up!
[Tanba-san inhales sharply]
It's no fun playing for nothing.
Let's wager something.
Let's see.
How about if the loser reveals a secret?
Okay.
-[Tanba-san] Hmm...
-[bottle cap clicks]
Tanba-san, what's your occupation?
I'm an influencer.
Just kidding. I'm a cabinet maker.
What's an "influencer"?
You don't need to know, Tanba-san.
[Tanba-san] What about you?
You always been a writer?
Actually...
[inhales deeply]
...I'm not sure what I should write.
I didn't want to be a fisherman.
I defied my parents,
and while I was in Tokyo
for entrance exams,
my home got wiped out.
So I didn't have to become a fisherman.
[Hansuke] If I'd been a fisherman,
I'd have died too.
So, I survived,
but everything I write sounds so fake.
Are you listening?
[Tanba-san] Yeah.
When people hear this,
they usually say, "That was really rough."
You're not the only one who had it rough.
And it's not in the past.
Things are rough even now.
-That's for sure.
-Hmm...
You're absolutely right.
You know,
people are always trying to pigeonhole us.
"It was 12 years ago,
and we need to learn from the tragedy."
I get all that.
But that's not what we're living for.
Not for the past or for learning.
We can't be satisfied with their pity.
-Things are always rough!
-[grunts]
[in raised voice]
We can't start over unless we get out!
Their pity becomes meaningless over time.
It's always rough for everyone.
Local and national governments
can't take care of the homeless.
It's your turn now!
-I give up.
-[in normal voice] No, I'm sorry.
I wasn't saying it to you, Tanba-san.
I'll be honest with you.
Actually, I'm--
[Tanba-san] Done.
Done?
Oh, well. Come with me.
-I'll show you my secret.
-What? Really?
I won?
[Tanba-san] It's in here.
Promise you won't tell anyone.
-[Hansuke] Eh? Eh...
-[keys jangling]
[Hansuke] What's in there?
Wait.
[Tanba-san] I saw them
picking up empty cans in the rain.
Thank goodness.
You're alive. Rich Man's alive.
I'll tell the council president.
I'd appreciate it
if you told the Young Men's Club.
No problem.
Are you hungry?
[uplifting music]
[rice cooker beeping]
-[Tora meows]
-Welcome home, Tora.
[Hansuke] Look. Tanba-san gave me this.
You can have rice and bonito flakes.
[chuckling]
[Hansuke] That's so good!
[Masuo] Hey, kid.
[laughter]
-[Tatsuya] That's so not you.
-[chuckling]
-Got your seal?
-[Hansuke] Yeah.
Get in.
Ooh!
[laughs]
Watch after Hansuke.
[Hatsutaro] What are you? His parents?
Let's meet
under the boat banner at 6:00 p. m.
If I make it back alive.
[Tatsuya and Okabe laugh]
[Tatsuya] See ya later!
[Okabe laughs]
[cell phone chimes, vibrates]
ANYTHING INTERESTING HAPPEN?
NOPE
[indistinct chatter]
[Masuo] Hatsu and I have been pals
for 12 years now.
-Oh.
-All of Japan knows what The What was.
Pop idols used to come pay their respects.
-Those were the days, right?
-Oh.
[Masuo]
Episode four is "The Bucolic Life."
-You'll like it. Right, Hatsu?
-Oh.
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey