[Hansuke] I email reports
to my employer, Mikki,
about everything I hear
and see in this town.
Then he pays me a maximum of 10,000 yen.
At least that was the plan.
[delivery man] Is Mr. Tanaka in?
[delivery man grunts]
Delivery from Mr. Mikimoto.
Oh, sorry.
[muttering]
A TOWN WITHOUT SEASONS
If I paid you 10,000 yen each time,
I'd go broke, moron.
[Hansuke] At least send me food
I can eat raw. I can't cook.
Enough whining.
Give me gritty human drama.
The gritty life in temporary housing.
EPISODE 2
FOR MOTHER
[Tanba-san] That's useless.
I've moved my knight.
Oh, right.
Then…
-[Tatsuya sucks teeth]
-[piece clanks]
-The bishop can get you.
-Oh, right.
Then…
-[piece clanks]
-The rook can get you.
[clattering]
[playful music]
[object clattering]
Tanaka here.
From building three.
Would you like one of these?
Good timing. Take over for me.
I've got a doctor's appointment.
But I don't play shogi.
My darn brother came back.
Long time no see, Tatsuya.
Before The What, he lived with us.
We were a family of four.
[Tatsuya sighs]
We were happiest then.
Dad died in The What.
[Tatsuya sniffles]
There was nobody we could turn to.
We had no choice but to come here.
[Tatsuya] Akio of the Young Men's Club
was a really great guy.
Mrs. Yoda. Mrs. Yoda.
Don't just stand there.
You must be hungry.
I'll show you around.
Come on. Let's go.
-[Akio] Let's go.
-[Mrs. Yoda] Thank you.
[Akio] Everyone!
This is Mrs. Yoda.
She's moved into building five.
Nice to meet you.
-[all] Nice to meet you.
-Okay, let's get you in line.
[Tatsuya] Ultimately, my brother
didn't fit in here and ran away.
Mom ended up marrying Akio.
-They soon had a daughter.
-Let's go, Akane.
-[Tatsuya] But Akio…
-See you later.
-…treated me nice and cared about me.
[Tatsuya chuckles]
He was like a real dad.
You should try to get
into college, Tatsuya.
-I'd never get in.
-Why?
Mom's pregnant again and we can't live
in temporary housing forever.
But that's no reason
to put your own future on hold.
Dad…
I'll work my tail off,
so don't put your future on hold.
Check.
-[Roku-chan] Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
-Oh! Whoa.
Let's get you a suit.
-What?
-You'll look great in one.
-Let's go.
-[gasps]
We'll get you one
for your entrance ceremony.
-Really?
-Yeah.
He actually had a suit made for me.
We were happiest then.
THEY WERE HAPPIEST THEN
[Hansuke] Happiness isn't any good.
-Huh?
-Hm?
[Tatsuya] Mom had a baby boy,
and I had entrance exams.
Akio worked day and night
so he wasn't home often.
That's when my brother, Shingo, showed up.
[upbeat music]
He looked like
a parody of a debt collector.
My sister was so scared,
she didn't stop crying.
-But Mom…
-[Mrs. Yoda] Shingo?
Mom.
[Mrs. Yoda] Shingo.
Sorry. I've put you through so much.
[Shingo's friends] Nice to meet you.
My…
[Tatsuya] We had sukiyaki that night.
I didn't eat any,
but Mom was in high spirits.
Tatsuya and Akane,
come on in and have some.
It won't be long before you can get out
of this rundown place,
and we can all live together.
Right, Tatsuya?
Thank you. You're so kind, Shingo.
[chuckles]
Me and these guys, we'll start a company.
-An IT-related company.
-Really?
-[friend 1] We'll work hard.
-[friend 2] You can count on us.
[Mrs. Yoda] Congratulations!
I think I'll drink tonight.
[all cheer]
[Tatsuya] The next morning,
when I woke up…
[baby babbles]
-[Tatsuya] What are you doing?
-Morning.
-Sorry it's not in an envelope…
-Thanks.
Take care of Mom, Tatsuya.
Hold on! That's my suit.
And that's the money for my college.
Give that back!
[Tatsuya panting]
Got a problem with it?
[Mrs. Yoda] Tatsuya.
-[Shingo] Yo.
-[friend 3] You look great in that, man.
[Tatsuya] That's when…
I don't know how to say this.
[inhales deeply]
I lost sight of what my life had been for
and what I was living for.
I was…
-In despair?
-Yeah, despair. Despair.
-Sorry.
-Huh?
Things were tougher for you,
so I shouldn't complain.
It's been tough for everyone.
You can't go around
comparing who's worse off.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[chuckles]
-Then?
-Uh…
I gave up on college and got a job.
But that bothered Akio,
and he worked even harder.
[Tatsuya] One day,
he coughed up blood and collapsed.
Mom was pretty desperate then.
She went to Akio's co-workers
and borrowed money from them.
The other residents raised money too.
-Everyone else helped make this.
-Thank you.
I know things are rough. Here, have this.
[gasps]
[Tatsuya] I got an advance on my pay
and worked night shifts.
We eventually got
two million yen together.
I swear I'll pay you back.
[Tatsuya] But the whole time,
my brother kept pestering Mom for money.
[tense music]
-Sorry it's not in an envelope…
-It's okay.
-Are you eating?
-Yeah.
-Are you sleeping?
-Yes, I am.
Are you getting a good bath, too?
Yes, I am.
[Shingo chuckles]
It cost 400,000 yen
for the operation and hospitalization.
When Akio asked for the money
that was left over, Mom just…
I lent the rest to my son.
[Tatsuya] The look on Akio's face then,
I'll never forget it.
He wasn't angry.
He wasn't sad.
It was like he was seeing someone
he'd never met before.
Instead of criticizing Mom,
Akio stopped talking to her…
and eventually left her.
That finally got Mom's attention.
Now she works days at a supermarket
and nights as a janitor.
She even works at home.
She packages those non-woven masks.
And I've got three jobs.
It took six years to pay off our debts.
I thought we were finally getting
into the black.
I've put you through a lot, Tatsuya.
Sorry I'm so useless.
-I'm sorry.
-Shingo, can we talk somewhere else?
-It's been so long.
-The house is a mess.
-[doorbell dings]
-[inhales sharply]
She must be at work.
You must be busy.
-I'll let her know you came.
-I was in the slammer.
-The slammer?
-Don't tell Mom.
I covered for my buddies for three years.
But I've totally changed. Believe me.
A guy I met on the inside got me a job.
You know Ryuji Asakura
of the Citizens Party?
He's been looking after me.
We're gonna go hear him speak today.
[Mrs. Yoda] Shingo?
Mom?
Shingo!
[panting]
You're alive, Shingo!
[uplifting music]
Sorry I made you worry.
I couldn't contact you
these last three years.
But you were always with me, Mom.
After all, I'm your son.
♪ I wanna give you a proper life ♪
♪ But I just can't
Not with minimum wage so low ♪
♪ And nobody wants
to take responsibility ♪
♪ We're worse off than foreign laborers ♪
♪ We grin and bear it
with Japanese pride ♪
♪ From this town of prefab homes ♪
♪ Let's get outta here, Mom, come on ♪
-Shingo.
-Yes?
-[Shingo] Yeah?
-[Mrs. Yoda] Shingo.
-[Shingo] Yes?
[Mrs. Yoda sobbing]
-[Mrs. Yoda] Welcome home, Shingo.
-[Shingo] Yes!
That's pretty brutal.
You bet it's brutal.
I bet it was brutal for Mom, too.
All she could say was his name.
Is he a rapper?
Oh, welcome back.
It's okay. Keep playing.
He's in with some politician,
but he spouts lots of hate speech.
Either way,
we don't have any cash at home.
[laughs]
What are you laughing about?
Tanba-san.
I've actually been saving up money
without telling Mom.
[Tanba-san exclaims]
Money to move house.
If we're gonna move,
I wanna surprise Mom
with a luxury condo
that has a self-locking door.
[chuckles]
He always shows up out of the blue.
[clicks tongue]
I forgot to take my bankbook with me.
[Hansuke] It's at your place?
[Tatsuya whines]
It's okay.
It's well-hidden.
It's safer there than if I had it.
If I had it, he'd threaten me and take it.
-You're probably worrying too much.
-Huh?
-He may not have come for money.
-No, he did.
He definitely wants money.
Money, money, money!
-You sure are certain.
-[scoffs]
What else would he want?
He's hopeless.
His life's not going anywhere.
Have you ever heard
the rakugo story of Kogoto Kobe?
[Tanba-san] Kobe was a landlord
and he always complained
about every little thing.
How long are you gonna wash
your face, Masuda?
-That water is for everyone.
-Yeah, yeah.
Keep scrubbing
and you'll scrub your skin off.
It smells like smoke.
-Your rice cakes are burning.
-Huh?
Wear your shoes right.
Abandoned bicycle.
Your kid's crying, Misao.
Do something to shut it up.
Abandoned bicycle.
[yelps]
You peeing on this again, you darn cat?
Abandoned bicycle.
Abandoned bicycle. Oh, that's mine.
How long are you gonna wash your face?
You've scrubbed your skin clear off.
It sure is lousy weather again today.
[Tanba-san] He complained so darn much
everywhere he went
that everybody he knew grew sick
and tired of him.
Phew, I sure am beat.
[Kobe] What a hard bench.
So, what about it?
I just happened to remember it.
Let me see. What was your move?
Are you saying that I'm like
that grumbling old guy?
Though nobody asked me to,
I worry about things I don't need to
and save money.
That's not what he's saying.
You don't know a thing
about my brother, Tanba-san!
[sighs]
He's a total lost cause.
But to him,
your one of his few family members.
No way! I ain't givin' him that money.
That's money we're gonna use
to move the four of us outta here.
Are you sure that's what
would make your mother happy?
[Hansuke] What Tanba-san said
really struck a nerve with Tatsuya.
"What would really make Mom happy?
Is it living in a luxury condo?
I called my brother selfish
because he ran away from here.
But now I'm secretly saving money
and trying to get just ourselves
out of this miserable town.
I'm doing the same thing he did."
-No, no…
-[Kobe exclaims]
Watch where you're walking, young man.
You'll step on that dog poop.
He didn't step on it.
[Hansuke] "When we ended up here,
everybody treated us well."
That's right.
[Hansuke] "And most of those people
can't get out of here.
But I want us to escape alone.
I'm even more selfish."
[Tatsuya] That's right.
[Hansuke] "Even though he's like that,
he's still Mom's adorable son.
When he's in trouble,
she wants to help him.
Try to understand that."
[Tatsuya] That's right!
Tatsuya?
[Hansuke] "I can save money again.
I'll give that money to Shingo."
That's what I'll do.
[soft music]
[steel rasping]
-I'm home.
-Welcome home.
Shingo left.
-He said he's busy.
-I see.
What'd he come for?
Probably begging for money again.
When I told him I didn't have any money,
he said he'd come back again.
-Do that in your own room.
-Oh, buzz off.
How was Shingo?
He was in a good mood.
[thudding]
That's him.
Are you Tatsuya Yoda?
Yeah.
This wouldn't happen to be
about my brother, would it?
[police] The station called us about this,
so I don't have any details.
[sighs]
What did my brother do?
[politician] Give me your support.
[police] He was stabbed.
[mellow music]
[people clamoring]
[Mrs. Yoda] Tatsuya?
I need your bicycle.
[panting]
Tatsuya?
[Mrs. Yoda whimpering]
Darn it!
[panting]
[doctor] He's in shock from bleeding.
It went in his back through his liver.
But he told you
my name and address, right?
[doctor] No.
He was in a comatose state
when he was brought in.
Huh?
[doctor] Those are his things.
TATSUYA YODA
MITSUBA BANK
[Tatsuya] I get it now.
This is how the police knew
what my name and address were.
Shingo!
[doctor] Ma'am, you shouldn't see this.
Tatsuya…
-Mom.
-[Mrs. Yoda] Wake up.
Shingo, it's your mother.
Wake up.
Mom.
My savings account bankbook is here.
Why…
did Shingo have it?
I know this isn't the time for this.
[Mrs. Yoda] You're so mean.
Huh?
I gave your bankbook to Shingo!
Why bring this up now?
I can't help it. I'm his mother.
You never listen to him and just leave.
He said he'd get his act together.
He said needed money to do that.
-I couldn't ignore him.
-Maybe we should talk outside.
[Mrs. Yoda] But you were secretly
saving up money.
I've seen you open up that bankbook
at night and grin at it a hundred times.
But when Shingo's in trouble,
you won't help.
Your savings
is more important than family.
[Hansuke] "You're wrong, Mom."
Tatsuya silently pleaded with her.
-[monitor beeping]
-[nurse] BP is falling.
[doctor] Get back, ma'am.
-Raise the vasopressor to 10 cc.
-[nurse] Okay.
Thank God your bankbook wasn't hurt!
Even with your brother in this condition,
you're just happy your bankbook is okay!
-[doctor] Give him norepinephrine.
-You're so cold and cruel!
Shingo!
[Hansuke] "You're wrong!
I wasn't saving money just for me.
It was to move our family
to someplace better.
In fact, I reconsidered.
I came back home
to give Shingo this money.
That's the truth. Believe me!"
Shingo was always kind.
He always cared for his mother,
not like you.
He was always considerate
to me, and said, "You cut your hair,"
and "You must be tired. Don't overdo it."
But did you ever say that? No, never!
When you were saving that money,
did you ever think of your mother,
of Shingo, of Akane, or Ryu?
No, I bet you didn't.
You only thought of yourself.
When I said, "I'm tired,"
you'd selfishly answer, "I'm tired, too."
That doesn't help!
That's not what I want to hear!
-[nurse] BP still falling.
-[doctor] Give him a transfusion.
[nurse] Okay.
[Mrs. Yoda] Please, listen to me Shingo.
[sobbing]
Shingo, no. Don't die.
-Don't you dare die, Shingo!
-[nurse] Pulse is infrequent.
-[doctor] Give him a shot of atropine.
-[nurse] Okay.
[Mrs. Yoda murmuring and sobbing]
Oh, that's right.
[Okabe] Tatsuya?
[sighs]
When the knight moved…
When the knight moved,
that's when I blew it.
I should have moved
the silver general back to 4-8,
and then I should have attacked
with the knight.
-[Okabe] Shogi?
-Now I get it.
[sobbing]
Darn it.
[sighs heavily]
Now I get it.
[breathes heavily]
[Hansuke] Let's see. If I go like this…
-Then like this…
-[Tanba-san] You can't jump like that.
-This isn't a racing game.
-[Hansuke] Then here.
[Tanba-san] Besides, you left the board.
Don't be so stupid.
What was the point of that story
about the landlord Kobe?
I'm not sure what the point was.
[Hansuke] It seems to me
that what he's doing only hurts him.
He complains out of kindness,
but nobody pays him any attention.
[Tanba-san] That's his character.
He'll eventually realize
that the world still revolves
whether he's around or not.
Welcome home, Tatsuya. Where's Mom?
-She'll stay at the hospital tonight.
-Really?
Welcome home.
What're you up to?
I searched for ways
to get rid of tons of napa cabbage.
-[Okabe] Here we go!
-Wow!
It shrunk. This'll be easy.
You're too optimistic.
Look how much is left.
[Tatsuya] We can do it!
-There's no way.
-Yes, we can.
-No way.
-If we all eat it, we can.
-We can eat it!
-There's no way!
Let's eat!
-[keyboard clacking]
-[Hansuke] Four days later,
Tatsuya's brother woke up.
He didn't die,
but since he didn't have insurance,
they'll use Tatsuya's savings
to pay for his treatment.
[laughter]
[Hansuke] His brother will come around
asking for money in the future,
and his mother will probably dote on him.
Nobody listens to Tatsuya's complaints.
-[Okabe] Here.
-But it's not midnight yet.
It's okay. They won't sell, anyway.
-Thank you. Bye.
-[Okabe] Bye.
Hansuke.
Again?
Delivery from Mr. Mikimoto.
[grunts]
[shouting]
It's fresh.
[Tora] Meow! I'm Hansuke's cat, Tora.
Hansuke thinks that he owns me,
but I'm the one who owns him.
Episode three is "Hansuke and Tora."
To me, it's "Tora and Hansuke."
[meows]
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey