What a nice day it is, Hansuke.
Are you listening?
[Hansuke] I started doing day labor
at a job that Masuo got me.
After work, we drink cheap beer
at Okabe's convenience store.
I can't drink. I've got work tonight.
Darn that Yoshie.
She's being crabby again.
What's she say?
I can't read it. You read it.
The neighbors are gonna complain,
so could you guys keep it down?
I think it says, "Come straight home."
Fine, I will!
I'll go home after this last one.
[Hansuke] That wasn't his last one.
Setsuko Karasuma is the greatest!
Setsuko Karasuma in 1980 was
the greatest seductress in human history.
-Seductress?
-I should really be going.
What's the damage?
-1,800 yen.
-That's expensive!
Don't worry.
-I'll cover it.
-No, you won't.
I can't let you do that.
What's wrong? Did you lose it?
-A pickpocket!
-I was robbed!
Let's look for it.
Where'd you put it after you bought beer?
I found it.
That's your name, Masuo.
Oh, this is yours, Hatsu.
[both laugh]
Oh!
What's wrong now?
This is missing. Where'd mine go?
-A pickpocket!
-I was robbed!
Look for it. You haven't even tried.
Let's see. I'll call you.
What happened to your phone?
[groaning]
You come straight home
without spending your pay!
Fine! Every day, it's the same.
Ketta-kusowarui shrew.
Hatsu!
Coming!
-Morning.
I'll lock the door at 8 p. m.
Cut that out!
Don't be so disgraceful in front of Masuo.
-Let's go.
[both laugh]
[Masuo's wife] What time did yours
come home last night?
-After 1:00 a. m.
-No way!
Sorry for the racket.
Same here.
Men are so stupid.
Why do they go out drinking?
Yeah, especially
with such hot wives waiting at home.
EPISODE 4
THE BUCOLIC LIFE
Why do wives always gotta put
their husbands in a bad mood?
You say that stuff nowadays,
you'll get criticized
for gender discrimination.
You mean SDCheese?
You're so smart, Hatsu.
How about a drink at Man-to-Man tonight?
Sorry, today's a no-liquor day.
-Good morning.
-Hi, Hansuke.
Listen. If I try to have
a drink today, say this,
"You can't, Hatsu.
Today's a no-liquor day."
-You said that yesterday.
-Who cares?
I'm going home sober today,
no matter what!
[both singing]
MAN-TO-MAN
[singing continues]
Thank you.
This is Hansuke.
You know him, right? He's Tora's owner.
I'm sorry I kept
your husband out drinking.
I can see right through you.
Did you think I'd forgive you
if you brought home a young man?
-[banging on door]
-[Masuo] It's me, Hatsu! Open up!
-It's open!
-[door slides open]
-[thuds]
-[indistinct chatter]
What's the matter, Masuo?
It's all ketta-kusowarui, that's what.
My old lady's such a hag.
Did you fight with Mitsuyo?
Yup.
[Hatsutaro laughs]
We had a tussle.
[Yoshie] Really?
-Yoshie.
-Yeah?
I got a question.
Are fried eggs a breakfast dish
or a dinner dish?
That's ridiculous.
When I got home,
I was dying to have fried eggs.
You ever felt that way?
-Never.
-I have.
-Sometimes I have.
-Never.
You know what my hag of a wife said?
"I don't wanna make
breakfast food at night!"
She didn't!
So I told her, "Then what about
a fried egg on a hamburger steak?"
She said, "That's dinner food."
But I don't want no dang hamburger steak.
I get you.
I only craved hamburger steak until I was
in my second year of high school.
You're always right, Masuo.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
-What?
-[thumps]
-[Masuo] I tried to see it her way.
I said if she put a sausage with the eggs,
then I might eat it.
[oil sizzling]
Then she said, "That's breakfast food!"
[Hatsutaro chuckles]
You were arguing in circles.
But I stuck to my guns.
"Then forget the fried eggs!
Cook me up five or six sausages!"
-That's all topsy-turvy now.
-Huh?
What do you think my wife said, then?
-What?
-Huh?
"That's lunch food!"
[laughter]
What a joke!
She's such a ketta-kusowarui shrew.
A husband's got a right
to his own opinions.
That's right.
You're always right, Masuo.
Are you listening?
Why's she always gotta nag me?
That ketta-kusowarui shrew.
Quit shouting.
What exactly is "ketta-kusowarui," anyway?
Sorry.
I've just been wondering what
the "ketta" in "ketta-kusowarui" means.
You don't even know what that is?
Sorry.
Then?
"Us women got our own troubles."
"Like what?"
"There isn't any law that says
a woman can't nag."
[Hatsutaro] Are you kidding?
That's when I lost
my temper and stormed out.
I'm still all tight in the chest over it.
[Hatsutaro] She's got too much time
on her hands.
She's just having fun nagging.
and makin' things worse than they are.
I know. I'll go and tell her off.
Not at this hour. Isn't that right...
That's right.
Don't you dare. You're drunk.
How dare you!
I know better than anyone
whether I'm drunk or not.
Who do you think I am?
[wheezes]
I'm me!
Who are you? Me?
[Hansuke laughing]
He's stinking drunk.
You'll never do
any good in that condition.
Ma'am...
[Hansuke] Wait, Hatsu.
Hatsu.
-[Masuo groaning]
-[door slides shut]
[erotic music]
Huh?
Well, if it isn't Hatsu's wife, Yoshie.
Can I share a drink with you?
I was about to have one myself.
Here ya go.
[Yoshie chuckles]
[Yoshie laughs]
It'll overflow.
This sure is a surprise.
You still feeling tight?
No, it's totally gone.
Has my heart stopped?
Here, let me feel for it.
Oh.
Oh, it's beating properly.
[Yoshie] Hear it? Thump, thump.
[laughs]
Amazing.
It's practically knocking my hand away.
That's so amazing.
That's amazing, huh?
How's your heart?
Why don't you feel it with your own hand?
Something wrong?
No.
Hatsu fell asleep
the moment he got to Masuo's place.
[Yoshie] You want a fried egg, too?
No. Thanks, anyway.
[Yoshie] Okay. Good night.
[Masuo groans]
I forgot.
About that "ketta-kusowarui,"
the "ketta" part comes from "kettai."
It means "weird."
In Kansai dialect,
they say, "You're so kettai."
Adding "kusowarui" makes it more intense,
so it means "the weirdest of the weird."
[Masuo snoring]
That's all. Good night.
Wait.
Is this okay?
Yeah, it's okay.
It'll be fine.
[Hansuke] Masuo, the truck's here.
Masuo!
-Morning.
-Huh?
You come straight home
without drinking a drop!
Fine!
-Yo, Hansuke.
-Huh?
Looks like it's gonna rain, Masuo.
You're in for it
if you don't come straight home.
Fine, you witch.
-Let's go.
-Right.
Hopefully, it won't rain
until the afternoon.
[both laugh]
-We drank way too much last night.
-[Masuo] Yep.
-Hansuke!
-Coming.
You know, Mitsuyo, men are just
like children when they're drunk.
-That's for sure, Yoshie.
-[both laugh]
[Hansuke] From that day on,
Masuo and Hatsutaro mistakenly took
each other's home and wife.
A double affair?
Actually, it's not as sordid as that.
[both singing]
[singing continues]
Thank you.
[Hansuke] That day, they had fun
and drank like usual after work.
-Later, Hatsu.
-[Hatsutaro] See ya tomorrow.
But then Masuo went to Hatsu's place,
and Hatsu went to Masuo's place.
They're just so... calm about it.
They're not the least bit concerned.
It's just so bucolic.
But they're married couples.
Does this kind of thing even happen?
[Tatsuya] It ain't the same
as taking the wrong pay envelope.
When we were kids,
we sometimes accidentally took home
another kid's textbooks or PE clothes.
What about their clothes?
They seem to have
the same taste in clothes.
But the size is a little off.
-Yo, Masuo.
-Nice day, isn't it?
They've changed places.
They've changed places!
Any other changes?
Neither of them complains
about their wives anymore.
That makes sense.
[laughs]
And the wives have
stopped complaining about their husbands.
Those vegetables sure are expensive.
Don't you think, Mitsuyo?
Yeah, yeah. Thank you!
Fish is expensive, too.
Plain saury is a luxury.
Chinese people have learned
how tasty sauries are.
That's what Akira Ikegami on TV says.
-[Mitsuyo] I hate that Miyane guy.
-[both laugh]
[Yoshie] I hate him, too.
[Mitsuyo and Yoshie laughing]
Can you believe those couples?
It's disgusting. They deserve each other.
They're going to hell.
God will punish them.
My own kids said
they want to switch papas, too.
[all laughing]
[Hansuke] I'm not sure what to do.
Leave them be.
Around here, it's not so unusual.
Goodbye.
Shiro!
You're wearing Tsutomu's shoes again.
I am Tsutomu.
-Oh.
-See you later.
What do you want for dinner?
Anything is fine.
[Tatsuya] That's Ryotaro Sawagami.
His wife, Misao, is pregnant.
What's their story?
Each kid's father is a different man.
What's more, they're all in this town.
[Tatsuya] Father of the oldest daughter,
Mariko, is Kuma, the thug.
Father of the oldest son, Tsutomu,
is the delivery man, Yokokawa.
Father of the second daughter, Rika,
is Man-to-Man's owner.
Father of the second son, Shiro,
is the greengrocer, Hasegawa.
Mama...
[Tatsuya] Father of the third daughter,
Ryoko, is the Indian laborer, Rajini.
They're here.
[Hansuke] They're all in this town.
[Hansuke mumbles]
Are you sure it's okay? Do they all know?
The wife does remember doing it with them.
But the husband and kids don't know.
In other words, everyone knows
except for the husband and kids.
Really?
How incredible.
That's nothing, Hansuke.
What's really incredible
is how they fell in love.
Neither of them were originally residents
of this town.
SHINSHINMARU 88
Veggie Girls!
Where'd the Veggie Girls go?
Give me your autograph!
[people clamoring]
Hot pot coming through!
[Tatsuya] Ryotaro was
a soup kitchen volunteer.
Misao was a member of the Veggie Girls,
a local pop idol group
who came to entertain us.
Wow, they're real?
-No, thank you.
-I love vegetables.
This is great! I'm a fan!
-I don't want sprouts.
-Hey!
♪ Feeling crispy like lettuce ♪
[crowd] Lettuce!
♪ Lingering like a juicy tomato ♪
[crowd] Tomato!
♪ The fickle salad missed the train ♪
♪ While I cry in the triangle corner ♪
Sprouts!
[cheers]
[whooping]
♪ I'm no herbivore, that's a rumor ♪
♪ A rumor, a rumor, a rumor ♪
♪ Crush the vegan, steal the virgin ♪
Sprouts is the best!
♪ Veggie, veggie, veggie, veggie
No more! ♪
[wailing]
Don't tell anyone!
[Ryotaro] Sprouts.
Please! If the management finds out,
I'll be fired.
We're about to get our debut.
This is an important time.
They've left already.
Seriously?
Sprouts!
-[Ryotaro] Sprouts!
-[containers clatter]
[Ryotaro] Sprouts!
[Misao] Wait! Wait!
Sprouts isn't on the bus!
[panting]
[Okabe] So she ended up staying here,
and eventually got with Ryotaro.
-That's hilarious!
-[laughter]
[shushes]
Ryotaro's a skilled brush maker.
He turned his place into a workshop
and makes quality brushes.
-Here?
-Yeah.
[Tatsuya] For Ryotaro,
who was a fan of Sprouts,
it's like his dream came true,
like he's living his dream.
Even though she sleeps
with all the guys in town
and has a baby every year,
he's still living the dream.
Sprouts!
[kids] I'm home.
Welcome home.
Dinner's almost ready, so wash up.
Okay.
[Okabe] In other words,
happiness is different for each person.
[sighs]
[Ryotaro] Careful, it's hot.
[kids] Let's eat!
[Ryotaro] Eat up.
-I'll eat tons.
-Good.
-I got a sausage.
-[sobbing]
Dinner's so yummy!
Tsutomu, stop crying.
You'll make Rika worry.
What's wrong, Tsutomu?
Dad, is it true
that none of us are your children?
Who says that?
Everyone.
Who's everyone?
Everyone. Everyone at school
and in the town.
Hmm...
What do you think, Tsutomu?
I know that I'm the father of all of you.
That's why I adore you
and treat you all with love.
But if you didn't love me
or didn't believe you're my child,
then I wouldn't be your father.
Isn't that right?
Okay, let's eat.
It's not just me!
Shiro and Mariko have heard it, too.
Our father is somebody else,
and we're the only ones who don't know.
They say a DNN test will prove it!
Huh? DN what?
A DNN test!
[door slides open]
[Misao] I'm home.
-[Ryotaro] Welcome home.
-[door slides shut]
[kids] Welcome home.
People say all kinds of things.
But nobody knows the real truth.
If they say that again, tell them this,
"What about your father?"
I'd like to see the person
who can answer that question.
In other words, either you trust me,
or trust someone else.
If you don't like me,
then go believe that DNN or whatever.
So, who do you believe?
Dad!
Dad.
I believe Mariko.
Her, huh?
-Guess I'm no match for her.
-[all laughing]
Oh, please.
[soft music]
What?
I've gotta eat for the baby, too.
Got a problem with it?
[kids laugh]
That's right. Mom's gotta eat for two.
Okay. Let's eat, too.
[kids] Let's eat!
[Hansuke] Happiness is different
for everyone.
We've got no right
to define it for others.
Isn't that right, Tora?
I'm going straight home today.
You never have.
Then make sure you stop me from drinking.
I have been.
[grunts]
Hey, what's that? Cut that out, Hatsu.
I can't open my eyes.
[Hatsutaro] Hey, that tickles, Masuo.
That tickles, Hatsu. What's your problem?
Cut that out! That tickles.
Stop it, Masuo.
Enough, dang it!
What's your darn problem?
Jerk.
I've had it!
[both singing]
[bar owner] Thank you.
[Hansuke] Okay. Tomorrow,
I'll come get you at 7:00 a. m.
-Good night.
-Yeah.
We drank a little too much today, Hatsu.
I sure hope it's sunny again tomorrow.
Okay, let's go home.
-Yeah, let's.
-Yeah.
I gotta pee first.
[groans]
Don't look at me like that!
Got a problem?
What time do you think it is? Huh?
Darn it. Look at yourself.
What a smell!
I'm home!
Good timing. Give me a hand.
Well, if it isn't Masuo.
Weren't you together?
[Hatsutaro] I'm not sure.
Okay.
Pull yourself together, Masuo. Let's go.
Well, if it isn't Hatsu.
Don't be like that. He helped you inside.
Wow. That's a big surprise.
[laughs, snores]
He's out cold.
Thanks.
Bye.
Yeah. Good night.
Hey, tell Yoshie hi.
-Yo.
-Good morning.
Hatsu!
It's sunny.
-Weather's great today.
-Morning, Masuo.
Dang, it sure is bright.
-Make sure you come straight home.
-I know. It's a no-liquor day.
-Right, Hansuke?
-Hey!
-You forgot your lunch.
-Thanks.
Let's go, Hansuke.
[both laugh]
-See you later.
This weather is unbelievably good.
We'll get sunburned.
Yes, it is. It really is.
[passerby] Good morning.
[Masuo laughs]
-[passerby] Good morning.
-Morning.
[grunting]
[snorts]
Good morning.
[Shima] Hello, everyone. I am Shima.
When do you sense spring has arrived?
When cherry blossom buds are growing?
When spring cabbage arrives?
Sorry, I forgot. This town has no seasons.
Episode five is "My Wife."
What is your wife like?
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey