A TOWN WITHOUT SEASONS
[Hansuke] Tanba-san's place is
at the far end of the town.
TANBA
His door is never locked.
His place is pure Japanese style.
It's small,
but there's even an elevated alcove.
[playful music]
EPISODE 9
TANBA-SAN
Welcome.
[Hansuke]
All the residents rely on Tanba-san.
You're first.
Lately, Hatsu's been kinda distant.
[sighs]
You think he and my wife…
[Hansuke] When faced with problems.
I accidentally dropped
Masuo's favorite sunglasses in the toilet.
-[chuckles]
-[Hansuke] At happy times.
Roku-chan's found something
he likes more than trains.
-Power shovels.
-[Hansuke] At sad times.
My filling fell out again.
[Hansuke] When irritated.
I love her so much, I can't sleep.
I want to see her so badly, I tremble.
Have you felt like that?
-[Hansuke] Or when they just want to talk.
-Are you okay?
I've been council president for 13 years,
and now I've finally found love.
You're single?
Everyone calls me "council president".
I bet they don't even know my name.
Do you know my name, Tanba-san?
Council president.
She called me by my name from the start.
[council president]
She was a news anchor in Saga or Oita,
-and is Miss Dekopon.
-[wailing in distance]
She led a sheltered life,
so she had to use a dating app--
-Shush!
-[rattling in distance]
[council president]
What is it? What happened?
[resident 1] Same as always.
Kuma's gotten drunk
and is going on a rampage.
-[Kuma groans]
-[Hansuke] He's got a sword!
It's the great Muramasa sword,
a memento of his grandpa.
-[resident 2] Watch out!
-[residents screaming]
[resident 3] What's happening?
What's going on?
[resident 4] Watch out!
It ain't no lie!
I killed a guy with this
and went to prison for it!
-Why'd he get like this?
-His hamster died.
His hamster? Hamsters die all the time!
It was suicide.
-[Hansuke] The hamster killed itself?
-Mm. Mm.
It was so stressed out
that it jumped into Kuniko's frying oil.
-Kuma!
-[residents yelp, whimper]
I know it's difficult,
but you must give it a proper burial.
-[resident 1] What's that?
-Ham Cutlet.
"Ham Cutlet"?
-[screams]
-[resident 2] Watch out, Tanba-san!
[resident 3] Watch out, Tanba-san!
Outta my way, gramps!
Outta my way or I'll slice you up!
Want me to take over?
[breathing heavily]
Huh? What?
I'll take over for you.
It's too much for you to handle alone.
[Kuma breathing heavily]
[Tanba-san] It's all right now.
It's all over.
[residents murmuring]
[Yoshie]
Oh, so that's what it was all about.
I thought Tanba-san
had struck a nerve or something.
When he said he'd take over…
[sniffles]
It wasn't like I was pounding mochi.
I couldn't just say,
"Go ahead. Thank you."
I mean,
I lost my temper and flew into a rage.
To be honest,
I didn't know how to control my feelings.
It felt like he understood
what I was going through.
[Kuma] I was so ashamed.
-[resident 1] It's Tanba-san.
-[resident 2] Hello.
[resident 3] Who is Tanba-san anyway?
Rumor is he was handsome
when he was young.
One of those flashy street dancers
in Harajuku.
[resident 4] Wasn't he a Tokyo Olympic
torch bearer in the '64 Olympics?
How old is Tanba-san anyway?
62?
Or is it 63?
It says you were born in Showa Era 24.
Is that right? So, how old am I?
Your blood pressure is normal.
How are you feeling?
Pretty good.
I'm glad you come every month, Hattori.
It must be hard to get comfortable
living in temporary housing.
No. I'm just killing time until I die now.
What'll you do about your coffin?
You can't lay one down in here.
If I can't lie down in it, I'll sit in it.
I'll grasp my knees like this.
[chuckles]
This is the Recovery Public Housing.
The elderly get priority for moving in.
No, thanks. I'm still only 62.
[dog barking in distance]
[footsteps approaching]
[ominous music]
[ominous music continues]
[Tanba-san] It's not in there.
Those are my work tools and porn videos.
[rattling]
If you want money, it's over here.
This is all I've got now.
My pension arrives
at the end of the month.
Come back then. Oh.
You can have these too.
Come in the front next time.
That way is much less suspicious.
[playful music]
Take care.
[Roku-chan] Hey! You thieving cat!
[Roku-chan groaning]
[gibbers]
[imitates engine rumbling]
You're hard at work, Roku-chan.
Yeah.
It's the end of the fiscal year.
Construction jobs are backed up.
[imitates engine whirring]
Liquor Shop Okabe…
Okabe here!
I'm ready.
[Okabe chuckles softly, squeals]
Oh, my. I like it. Is that your twin look?
It's called coordinated outfits, Auntie.
-[Taeko] I ain't your auntie.
-[awkward chuckle]
See you later.
See you.
[calm music]
You're first.
Everything in my life sucks.
I can't take it.
My life is totally over.
[sighs]
I want to start all over again.
I haven't seen your mom lately.
She left.
Huh?
When she heard Shingo was getting out
of the hospital, she got restless.
She took my little brother and sister
and left.
I'm living alone
in that three-room prefab.
Is that right?
Sorry that I didn't notice.
Everyone's got
their own troubles to deal with.
Shima-san's been good to me,
so I might become a full-time employee.
I had a suit made,
but when I came home to show it to Mom,
the place was empty.
I'll never be able to wear a suit.
The one my second dad had made,
Shingo took it from me.
Shingo takes everything I love
just when things are looking up.
But you're a sensible man.
It's enough to destroy my confidence.
I worked hard.
I wanted the four of us
to move out of here
and live in a three-bedroom place
that's not a prefab.
I guess…
that's not what Mom wanted.
[indistinct chatter]
[employee] Please think about it.
[Mrs. Yoda] Excuse me.
Are there wheelchair-accessible rooms
in this apartment?
[employee] Yes. Please look at this.
-Here you go.
-[Shingo] Wow.
-See? Look how huge it is.
-[somber music]
[employee] Here.
[Shingo] Yeah. Akane, you'll be in charge.
-We'll come by and check it out.
-Great.
-[employee] I look forward to seeing you.
-[Ryu] Thank you.
[Shingo] This is good news.
[Mrs. Yoda] Let's go, Akane.
Let's go. I can hardly wait to see it.
-[Mrs. Yoda] How about Sunday?
-[Shingo] Sounds good.
-[Mrs. Yoda] Wanna see it?
-[Shingo] Yeah. Looks good.
She wanted to live
with everyone else except me.
[inhales deeply]
Mom hated me.
[sighs]
She should have told me.
I would have gotten out of her life.
You shouldn't think like that.
You're about to become
a full-time employee.
[Tanba-san] What's wrong?
[Hamaguchi]
Illegal occupation, subletting,
and malicious use has run rampant,
causing trouble for local authorities.
So final discussions
to clear out the place are going to begin.
There are 15 households still remaining.
Our goal is to clear them out by March.
Get serious.
[Hamaguchi] It's not a goal.
It's imperative.
Isn't that right, Shima-san?
Well, the government originally offered
to provide the housing for two years,
but it's been 13 years now.
-Right.
-[Tatsuya] Before I knew it,
I was in charge of the project
to clear people out.
OCCUPIED TEMPORARY HOUSING
[Tatsuya] We'll be holding discussions
with each household to get out by March.
[somber music]
[Tanba-san]
I guess our time really is up now.
They never intended to build
a café in the first place.
I could never kick people out.
I love everyone here.
Roku-chan and Hatsu and Masuo
and Katsuko and Kuma
and of course you, Tanba-san.
I know nobody has anywhere to go.
Wait…
I don't have anywhere to go either!
[breathes heavily]
I even went and saved all that money
to move into a condo.
[voice breaking]
I'm such a loser.
[sniffles]
[in normal voice]
Therefore, I came here today…
to tell you goodbye.
Dying here would only cause
everyone here trouble,
so tonight,
I will jump in front of a train.
[breathes deeply]
Thank you for all your help.
[Tanba-san] Hold on a minute.
[rustling]
Wolfsbane.
[Tanba-san]
You know it, right? It's deadly poisonous.
If you eat a gram of its root,
you'll die for sure.
If you're serious about dying,
then this is the best way to do it.
Don't you dare go dying
where nobody can see you.
You're not a cat.
Everyone should be made aware of…
why a fine young man like yourself
decided to die.
If they don't, there'd be no point.
How long before I die?
It's quick.
You won't even suffer.
Should I take it all?
Yes, that would guarantee…
[gasps]
What?
-[groans]
-How do you feel?
How do I put this?
There's a kind of earthy smell.
[retches]
If there's anyone you want to see,
you should see them.
Huh? What?
There's time for that?
[breathes heavily]
-You should lie down.
-Huh?
Wait. What?
SHINSHINMARU 88
[Tanba-san] How are you feeling?
Well…
Hansuke.
[Tanba-san] Hansuke?
I can't believe
I forgot to mention their names earlier.
Hansuke and Okabe.
-Want me to get them?
-It's okay.
I don't want them to watch me die.
[Tatsuya exhales slowly]
Now I can see Dad.
The one who made your suit?
Not that one. The first one.
My real dad who died in The What.
-For some reason, lately…
-[indistinct chatter]
-…he's been in my dreams.
-[soft music]
[Tatsuya] Only Dad…
You did great! This is amazing!
…ever said, "You're doing good.
You're amazing."
It's kind of weird,
but, like we're friends,
we drink,
and we talk…
in my dreams.
That's only possible while you're alive.
Huh?
Your father exists in your mind.
Therefore, your father only lives
while you're alive.
And if I die?
[Tanba-san] He'll disappear.
When you go, he goes too.
[gasps]
[sharp gasp]
How long has it been?
Only about five minutes have passed.
What's wrong?
[retches, coughs]
-That's a vase.
-Don't you have something?
-Like what?
-Don't you have something for this?
You mean an antidote?
Are you sure? You won't be able to die.
I don't want to die!
I don't want to die! Hurry!
-[Tanba-san] Uh, just a minute.
-[grunting]
[retches, groans]
-[breathes heavily, retches]
-[clattering]
HELP!
[Tatsuya] What are you doing?
-Take some Seirogan.
-What?
Are you insane, you geezer!
You wanna kill me?
[Hansuke] Tatsuya! What's wrong?
-Did you eat vinegared mackerel?
-[Tatsuya breathing heavily]
Don't touch me! Why did you come?
You called for me!
That's no reason to come!
[breathing heavily]
Hansuke, what's the antidote
for wolfsbane?
Wolfsbane? Wolfsbane?
-It's too late.
-There isn't one.
-[screams]
-I typed in "wolfsbane antidote",
but it said "none".
-We have to pump his stomach.
-Pump his stomach?
Oh, no. When I typed in "pump stomach",
it says "hell".
-[retching]
-Pull yourself together, Tatsuya!
What's wrong? Vinegared mackerel?
Wolfsbane.
Thank goodness.
I thought he got a parasite.
[both] It's not okay!
Why'd you eat wolfsbane?
-Leave me be!
-Huh?
Hurry up and tell them!
Tell them someone's gonna die!
[breathing heavily]
[Tatsuya]
This is a list of all the residents left
in temporary housing.
In the "reported by" column,
that's your name, isn't it?
Shinsuke Tanaka!
[Okabe] What do you mean?
[Tatsuya] He's a spy.
He's been reporting everything
he learns about us to them for money.
What? Hansuke was?
Is that true?
When I told him about the homeless,
the next day, those workers came in
and tore down their cardboard house.
Right around then,
this guy bought a rice cooker.
[Tatsuya] How do you feel about that?
What do you mean?
Don't you feel guilty?
[Tatsuya] With the money you made
from destroying someone's home,
you made some nice rice
and ate it with your cat!
I didn't think about
the consequences then.
I just reported what I was told to.
In fact, the guy who hired me didn't care.
And the guy who hired him is Shima-san.
What do you mean?
[Hansuke]
Mikki and Shima-san are in cahoots.
Look!
[Okabe] The dolphin mark.
The dolphin mark is on the bags
of masks you carry every day, Katsuko.
They're all subsidiaries of No Season.
-What?
-Report to them.
Now!
Tatsuya Yoda was abandoned
by his family and drank poison.
One more place is empty!
-I will not!
-Why not?
Because your story doesn't make money.
I reported it, but I didn't make a dime.
Your story got me five napa cabbages.
But you're still my precious friend.
-Tatsuya!
Katsuko, get some water.
[Tatsuya] Oh, no. I'm blacking out.
[breathes heavily]
No, I don't want to die.
That's right. It'd be stupid to die!
Selling out my friend
for five napa cabbages wasn't worth it,
so I quit doing it.
That's why Shima-san came here himself.
You've gotta be kidding!
That's a pretty lame friendship!
-I'm sorry!
-That won't cut it!
You're short on brains, Hansuke!
It's your fault that I was put in charge
of clearing people out!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
-Tatsuya, don't die!
-Ow! Ow! Ow!
[Hansuke] Throw up!
[Tatsuya] I can't take anymore!
[Okabe] Katsuko,
this isn't the time for that.
I don't wanna die!
[sobs]
-I don't wanna die!
-[Hansuke] Throw up, Tatsuya!
-What's that about hyacinth?
-[Tatsuya whimpering]
Hyacinth?
Hyacinth.
Hyacinth…
[Katsuko] This is hyacinth.
[Tanba-san] Hyacinth?
It's not wolfsbane?
-[Katsuko] It's hyacinth.
-Hyacinth.
Hyacinth root?
Tanba-san!
[Tanba-san] Huh?
[comical music]
[Hansuke] Tatsuya's suicide attempt…
failed.
Did you have a fun date?
[soft chuckle]
Sorry.
SHINSHINMARU 88
[Hansuke] For a while after that,
their peaceful
yet boring daily lives continued.
It was only this big.
-[whistle blowing]
-That scared me.
Good morning, water-faucet ladies.
This is my sweet wife,
the council president's wife, Harumi.
It's nice to meet you.
Excuse me, please.
[exclaims, chuckles]
She is Miss Dekopon, after all.
Be kind to her.
She's my sheltered wife,
so I won't be letting her out much.
[hisses]
-Then leave her inside.
-[chuckles]
-[resident] That's right.
-[whistle blows]
[robber] I came inside here,
then opened that up.
But then he said
there's nothing there and got up
and gave me his wallet.
Did you hear that?
[Tanba-san] Nobody's that nice.
That's for sure.
He doesn't look rich either.
Hey, hold on here.
Try to remember what happened, mister.
You gave me the porn videos from there.
-[Tanba-san] Are you insane?
-[knocking on door]
[Hattori]
Hattori here from the Support Center.
TANBA
[employee] It's been a long time.
[grunts]
Lowering the arm.
It's the power shovel nut!
-[Shiro] It's the power shovel nut!
-[imitates engine whirring]
[Shima] We've met before,
but I'm Shima from No Season.
This March marks 13 years since The What.
[Shima] This is
the only temporary housing remaining.
[Hattori] The Recovery Public Housing
is right near here.
If everyone moves there together,
you won't be lonely.
Of course, wounds don't always heal
with the passing of time.
However, by having the courage
to look toward the future
and make a new start,
older people like you, Tanba-san,
can be an example to others.
[Shima] Then even if people can't forget
their pain, they can at least overcome it.
[Tanba-san] Silver is in trouble.
Excuse me?
[Tanba-san] That's Sankichi Sakata.
It's past the point of no return.
But you'll move it out of the way.
This might just change
how my life goes now.
Thank you.
[wheezes, sneezes]
Sorry.
All right.
I'll leave.
KAZUO TANBA
-[imitates engine whirring, beeping]
-[marching drum music]
[engine rumbling in distance]
[soft gasp]
[unsettling music]
[children shouting]
-[Kuniko] No, Roku-chan!
-[Roku-chan exclaims]
-Watch out!
[Roku-chan] That's so cool!
That's so cool! Wow!
-Hansuke…
-[Roku-chan] It's huge!
[whirring]
-[ominous music]
-[loud thud]
[Hansuke] Tanaka from Building Three here.
You've come this far, so I'm sure
you'll watch the final episode.
But here are the highlights.
Hansuke goes wild. Roku-chan goes wild.
Katsuko laughs like wild. That's all.
I'll miss this place.
There's no better place, right, Tora?
What? There is? A cat café? No way.
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey