[Rich Man]
The best place would be on top of a hill.
[Rich Man's son]
Yes. I think you're right.
A TOWN WITHOUT SEASONS
[Rich Man] Since ancient times,
the Japanese have always wanted
to build homes in low places,
such as at the foot of mountains
or in valleys.
[Rich Man's son]
Yes, you're right about that.
There is a good reason for that.
There are a lot of earthquakes
and typhoons in Japan, right?
Selecting low places,
where disasters are rare,
is a necessity, in a way.
Yes.
It's a necessity,
so it has to be that way.
[Kuniko] There.
Oh, what good timing.
[soft chuckle]
There are exactly two left over.
Here you go.
Thank you.
[light music]
[Hansuke] Rich Man and his son live
in the garbage dump.
When it's your own home,
you can't be worrying
about ethnic characteristics.
I don't think…
[Hansuke] They talk with each other about
the house that they'll build someday.
The boy doesn't go to school.
He is a little small
to be in middle school,
-but he speaks like a grown-up.
-[children chattering in distance]
Okay!
Question! What's for dinner today?
[Tora] Cat rice, obviously.
It's cat rice!
-[Hansuke singing]
-[Tora] How can you always get so excited?
It's called "cat rice,"
but cats only eat it because we feel
obliged to since it's named after us.
But I've never met a cat
who liked cat rice.
Taco-flavored rice is way more popular.
Now for the seasoning!
Yay! Cat rice!
-[Tora] Dang it! I can't stop eating it!
-[singing continues]
Cat rice! Cat-cat-cat-cat rice!
[Hansuke] Huh?
[Tatsuya] Cat rice! Cat rice!
Cat rice! Cat…
[panting]
Happy about something?
-[Hansuke] No.
-Really?
Even so, you're really upbeat. Amazing!
Cat rice. Cat rice. Cat-cat-cat…
-I make a presentation tomorrow.
-Yeah?
If it goes well,
we just might get a café here!
-That's great.
-Yes!
You know, Shima-san is really amazing.
Without him,
it may have ended as just a dream.
[Tatsuya] Welcome!
[elder 1]
When I watch TV all day like this,
I get the feeling that I can say
funnier things than they do on TV.
-[indistinct chatter on TV]
-"Of course!
You couldn't hold it if it was crunchy
in the middle and creamy on the outside."
[laughing]
Katsuko, I'm pretty funny, right?
[elder 2] I'm checking into the hospital.
Huh?
[Okabe] Liquor Shop Okabe here.
I've got a delivery.
They need to run tests.
The lump in my breast
seems to be getting bigger.
You'd better get that checked
from a medical point of view.
Are you tired?
Just as you ordered,
a case of Strong Shochu Highballs
and a two-liter bottle of shochu.
This is a free calendar.
Who needs that?
Give me an extra can of Strong.
Sorry, but this comes free
with the shochu.
-[elder 1] Then give me a free bottle.
-[elder 2] Sorry.
He's drunk.
It's 3,240 yen.
[whispering]
You can have this.
[Hansuke]
Rich Man and his son get up early.
[slow-paced music]
They collect the empty cans
before the trash truck comes.
-That's their morning routine.
-[cans clattering]
[Rich Man] When you build a house,
first you must decide on the front gate.
The front gate is like
the face of the house.
[Rich Man's son] You're right.
You can tell what a person is like
from their face.
Actually, that is not always true.
You're right.
They say you can't judge a book
by its cover.
Actually, they're often
just what they appear to be.
-Which is it?
-Huh?
At any rate, we must first decide on
the front gate, the doorway, the entrance.
[Tatsuya] The entrance is designed
to resemble a Hawaiian bungalow.
And it's accessible for everyone.
[Shima] It looks nice and cool.
[chuckles]
What about that boat banner?
-It's the town symbol.
-[Shima] I like it.
But there's no sign.
[Tatsuya] Sorry, but I haven't come up
with a name for the café.
[soft chuckle]
Let's think of one, together.
[staff] Something easy to remember.
-[rain pattering]
-The gate should be European style.
How about Rococo style?
Yes, I like it.
Spanish is nice too.
English style is okay too.
But something more casual, more familiar
would be nice.
Oh, I've got it!
How about Station?
[all] "Station"?
It's a French word that means "station."
-Is this about Roku-chan?
-Right.
Dodes'ka-den.
[Shima] A train runs through that town.
If you're boarding, please hurry.
[Shima] But nobody rides it.
-I've often wondered why that is.
-All aboard.
-I think it's because there is no station.
-[imitates train chuffing]
If there's a station,
Roku-chan can take a break.
Right, Yoda?
I'll rework it
based on this station concept.
-Oui! Café de Station, très bien.
-[soft chuckle]
[Rich Man] Next are the outer walls.
Since the color of the walls determines
the building's overall character,
we must be prudent.
[Rich Man's son]
There are certainly many types of houses.
How about that one?
[sucks teeth]
Salmon pink, huh?
It makes me doubt their character.
[Rich Man's son] You're right.
It's rather unpleasant.
[Rich Man] And walls made of concrete
are no good. They have a pretentious air.
[Rich Man's son] Total nouveau riche.
How revolting.
[Rich Man] Harmony with the surroundings
is also vital.
[Rich Man's son] Yes.
[Rich Man]
However, beige is too unrefined.
[Rich Man's son]
It shows a total lack of thought.
[elder] Excuse me…
Little boy, buy some sweets with this.
[children chattering in distance]
[Rich Man's son] I'm sorry,
but we don't accept that kind of thing.
[Hansuke]
They never accept handouts of cash.
And they never ask for food themselves.
[elder] Then…
Thank you.
[Hansuke] They have
their own kind of pride and principles
they strictly adhere to.
I think there is a modern-style house
built with wood in the next town.
Let's go see it.
I would really love to go,
but I should be going to Miyashita Ginza.
The tempura restaurant is about to open.
[Rich Man] I see.
There's no need
to decide on the walls right now.
I'm sorry.
[Hansuke]
It was the boy's job to gather food.
[chef] Tonight, there is a banquet.
Come back around 9:00 p.m.
-Heat it up before you eat it.
-[Rich Man's son] Thank you!
[Hansuke]
Naturally, he wasn't welcome everywhere.
[restaurant owner sighs, speaks in Korean]
We still have customers.
-Sorry.
-[door closes]
[Hansuke speaks in Japanese]
Competition is fierce in the back alleys.
[dog growling]
[plate clanks]
-[in Italian] It comes with dessert today.
-[Rich Man's son] Grazie.
[Hansuke speaks in Japanese]
He isn't picky,
and never forgets
to show his appreciation.
[Indian chef shouts]
Namaste.
[Indian chef] Namaste.
-[chefs exclaiming]
-[Italian chef] Hey, that's my pizza.
-[Taiyaki restaurant owner] Wow.
-[Indian chef] Curry goes with anything.
[soft music]
I'm home.
Actually,
I've settled on a double-door gate
made of cypress.
OTHER FOOD, FRIED FOOD, MEAT
[Rich Man] There will be two buildings,
one European, one Japanese.
The land between will be a garden.
Yes. We have
2,000 square meters of land, after all.
The big issue is the kitchen.
Should it be a simple Japanese style,
or a modern-style European kitchen?
[crows cawing]
Oh, sorry. I wasn't listening.
[Rich Man] It's okay.
There is no need to decide quickly.
[cawing continues]
SHINSHINMARU 88
[sizzling]
[Rich Man's son] It's ready.
Then let's eat.
Thank you for this food.
It's about time
to decide on the furniture.
[Hansuke]
The father never stopped talking about it.
As for the European home…
[Hansuke] It was as if…
he was dulling
his sense of smell and taste
so he wouldn't focus on the food
that he was eating.
However, very occasionally…
[chuckles]
Goodness me. If it isn't roast beef.
Yes. The fancy restaurant chef
gave it to me.
It's been ages.
It's been cooked perfectly rare.
[chuckles]
You can have mine too.
[Rich Man] What? Why?
I don't like undercooked meat.
Beef, my boy, is eaten raw in the West.
If I'm not mistaken,
in the Bavarian region of Germany…
[Hansuke] The father knew much
about a wide variety of topics.
-[melancholy piano music]
-His son was his very best listener.
…adding spice…
[Rich Man] Now for the drawing room.
Of course, there must be
central heating and cooling.
You must want to go to sleep.
I'm not sleepy. It's okay.
We'll do it tomorrow.
The drawing room is
the biggest test of one's taste.
[Rich Man's son] Yes.
Good night.
[Hansuke] What?
Tomorrow is the community meeting.
-For… What is it? Café de…
-[Tatsuya] Station.
At one in the afternoon.
Come if you can.
[footsteps receding]
[Hansuke] Well,
I'm sure the father was distressed by it,
but about when they'd settled on
placement of the furniture,
his son…
HIS SON…
[keyboard clacking]
[ignition knob rattling]
-[Rich Man] What are you doing?
-[Rich Man's son] It won't light.
[Rich Man] Oh.
-That's vinegared mackerel.
-[cat meows]
The sushi chef told me
that I must cook it before eating.
[soft chuckle]
He is clearly mistaken.
It is preserved with vinegar and salt
so it can be eaten without cooking.
But the sushi chef said…
[Hansuke] It didn't happen often,
but the son disagreed with him.
Yes. It's thick and delicious.
You try it as well.
[screeching, panting]
If you don't hurry, the cat will eat it.
[whimpering]
[screeching]
You're right. It's delicious.
[Hansuke] That night,
both the father and son had a stomachache.
This isn't the vinegared mackerel.
[in strained voice]
Yes, you're right.
[both groan]
If it were the vinegared mackerel,
we would first get hives.
Then we would vomit.
Then what is it?
[Hansuke] The father's symptoms
subsided after three days.
However, the son grew
more emaciated with every day.
-[stomach rumbling]
-At times like this, we must fast.
But one can only take so much.
[in weak voice]
If only… I could walk.
That's not what I mean.
I'm not asking you
to go to Miyashita Ginza.
Humans can do fine without food
for a week to ten days.
[Rich Man's son groaning]
-[groaning continues]
-[clattering]
[Hansuke] Tora noticed right away
that something was wrong
with the father and son.
[Tora] Take him to a doctor! Now!
Or else it'll be too late!
About the drawing room,
I think all the furniture
should be Scandinavian.
[Tora] Forget about the darn drawing room!
Get someone here now!
[Hansuke] Unfortunately,
he couldn't hear Tora's cries.
-[Rich Man's son] Uhm…
-Yes? What is it?
I forgot about one thing.
Let's build a pool.
A pool, huh?
You're right. Yes, let's do that.
We'll build it any way you like.
[Rich Man] Well then,
it looks like it's about complete.
[cigarette sizzling]
[puffs]
LIQUOR SHOP OKABE
Uh, where's your son today?
This is his favorite. I saved it for him.
Huh?
SHINSHINMARU 88
-[Tora meowing]
-[Hansuke] Tora!
-[rain pattering]
-Tora!
What's wrong, Tora? You'll catch a cold.
It's time for dinner.
-[Tora growling]
-[Hansuke] Huh?
Rich Man's there?
Huh?
[knocks on car window]
Hey. You okay?
[Hansuke knocking on car window]
Hey. Hey!
Open up! Hey! Where's your dad?
FRIED FOOD
[inaudible chatter]
-[knocking on car window]
-It's locked.
We'll have to break a window.
Here's a wrench.
No, thanks. I'll go get something.
Roku-chan, go get Tanba-san.
[breathing heavily]
[Tatsuya knocking on car window]
Hey!
-What are you doing?
-Calling an ambulance.
-Don't you dare!
-Why?
-They'll get kicked out again!
-But…
If you call an ambulance,
they'll call the cops
and local government too.
-But…
-Those people are merciless!
You saw what happened.
There's no time to worry about that!
We've gotta…
[shouting]
You're the one who reported them, right?
-[loud rumble]
-[inaudible chatter]
They've got nowhere else to go!
That's why they came back!
Leave them be, dang it!
[shouting]
But… But if he dies, what's the point?
[Tanba-san] I called a doctor.
Don't you worry.
I'm sure they don't have insurance,
but he'll still check him.
[door clicks]
What did you say?
Pool…
A pool?
There's… a pool.
Thank you.
[tranquil music]
[tranquil music continues]
[Hansuke] The doctor came.
But it was too late.
[music fades]
COMMUNITY MEETING FOR CONSTRUCTION
OF CAFÉ DE STATION
The meeting where Tatsuya explained
to the community about his café was held.
Ain't nobody else comin'.
Hurry up and get started!
[Hansuke] Only three people showed up.
Thank you, everyone,
for gathering here today.
[resident]
There are only three people here.
Uhm…
Uh, excuse me…
[staff 1] That was hard to sit through.
[staff 2] I'll call a taxi.
[crows cawing]
[rattling]
[Hansuke] Ultimately, Tatsuya's café
and the house with the pool
ended only as dreams.
[somber music]
Rich Man left the town
and started living under a bridge.
Oh, Katsuko.
[soft chuckle]
What's wrong? Are you not feeling well?
[somber music continues]
[Okabe] Did you lose a coin?
[Rich Man] I'd agree…
that having a pool with white tiles
in the middle of the garden would be nice.
However, there can be problems
with water supply and drainage systems.
But don't worry. I'm sure we can build it.
I promise.
You see,
the only thing you asked me for…
-was to build a pool.
-[water lapping]
You should have…
asked for all the things that you wanted.
[Okabe] Okabe of Liquor Shop Okabe here.
I talked to Katsuko
when making deliveries again today.
Actually, I did all the talking.
I wondered if she was bored,
and when I looked, she was asleep.
She must be tired.
Episode seven is, "Ganmodoki."
Ganmodoki?
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey