A TOWN WITHOUT SEASONS
[singing "Happy Happy Birthday"]
["Happy Happy Birthday" ends]
EPISODE 8
GANMODOKI: PART 2 OF 2
"Café de Station"?
What language is "station"?
[resident] It means "station" in French.
-[residents] Really?
-[Yoshie] Do we need a cafe here?
-There's not even a dollar store.
-We need a dollar store more than a cafe.
-Or a Donki.
-Or a net cafe.
TENYA. I'd go there every day.
Not a TENYA. They're my competitor.
Yamada Udon.
With a net cafe on the second floor.
KUSHIKATSU TANAKA.
Like I said, not fried food.
Something besides fried food.
What's the point of a fancy cafe
when we don't even have Yamada Udon.
Who needs fancy?
To hear these unreserved opinions of yours
is why we're having
a community meeting next month.
Please attend this time.
[residents] Huh? A community meeting?
What's that all about?
What's that for?
[Yoshie] Oh, don't!
[resident 1] Don't bother them.
-[resident 2] Get back over here.
-[Mitsuyo] Don't go.
[Tatsuya] Oh, Hansuke.
Wanna drink?
-[resident 1] Oh my!
-[Mitsuyo] She came out.
[Tatsuya] Huh?
Hello.
So, that's what's up, Hansuke?
No, it's not like that.
[Mitsuyo] "Like that"? Like what?
[Hansuke] Our relationship
isn't what you all think it is.
Really? But your prefab
sure was doin' a lot of shakin'!
[residents cackling]
[Hansuke] Cut out that vulgar laugh.
But you were really gettin' it on
in the middle of the day.
[residents laugh]
Okay, I think I'll be going.
-[Hansuke] No, it's--
-Bye.
[Hansuke] Sorry.
Wanna come inside?
[Tatsuya] No, I'll go home.
How come?
You finished work, so let's drink.
Mom's getting dinner ready for me.
-[Hansuke] I see.
-Maybe another time.
The community meeting, right? Got it.
Bye.
[resident 1] Hurry up and go after her.
-[resident 2] What're you waitin' for?
-[resident 3] Get goin'!
[residents cheer]
[clock ticking]
[Okabe sings "Tapestry"
by Miyuki Nakajima]
Naw, that's kinda creepy.
[indistinct chatter]
[receptionist] Number nine, please.
[uneasy music]
[Taeko] Katsuko.
[receptionist] Here is the bill
for today's visit.
It comes to 8,060 yen.
You've gotta be kidding.
Week nine? That was two months ago
when I was in the hospital.
That bastard of a husband. How disgusting!
I hope the scumbag goes to hell.
Katsuko!
[Taeko breathes heavily]
[sighs]
There's no point in getting mad at you.
[pants]
We made it.
We made it, Beyonce.
Beyonce, you sure have grown.
[meows]
Tora, you've gotten even fatter.
Tora.
You know what? I think it's time to go.
[Tora] No, it's not!
-You tryin' to get rid of me?
-Feel that nice breeze, Tora?
[quirky music]
Tora, the weather's really great.
[Tora] Huh? What's with that?
You want me outta here?
No way!
-Why don't you people leave?
-Go, go, go, go.
Go, Tora.
[Misao] That shop clerk's back.
That's his ex-girlfriend.
The embers have caught fire again.
-Huh? What's that mean?
-A flame lit once burns again easily.
Look. They kicked out the cats.
[resident] Poor things.
[residents] Poor things.
[Kuniko] They even kicked out the cats.
[Yoshie] Why can't they leave them be?
They told us to get out.
[residents] Those poor things.
Those two are so naughty.
By the way, did he give her
that present? The white cardigan.
Okabe?
I'm not sure.
My manager's such an a-hole.
Where I work now.
Is that so?
Yeah. A total a-hole.
I blocked them on LINE,
so they cleared out my locker.
What?
What an a-hole.
I know, right?
A-hole.
[Hansuke] She's always had a foul mouth.
So she comes over and spills
all her complaints.
Then goes home once she feels better.
I'll bring you a coffee maker next time.
[Hansuke] I've been accumulating
lots of appliances lately.
So it's not like
the gossiping housewives think?
No.
We both hate the same things.
The food we dislike,
and TV shows we dislike,
and people we dislike,
are almost all the same.
We started dating
because we had such fun complaining.
That's rare.
Isn't it usually that way?
It's a lot more fun
to talk about the stuff you dislike
than the stuff you like.
We can build trust too.
[Mikki] You should get back together.
No.
[chuckles]
I bet she wants to.
No, she doesn't.
I was awful to her.
FOUR YEARS EARLIER
Guess who is pregnant.
[Hansuke] We lived together,
so I thought it might happen eventually.
But when it did,
I so totally lost my cool.
It's only at times like that when things
like The What and my dead family
-go through my mind.
-[mumbles]
-I need to do things right.
-Wait. Hold on.
-I need to do right by you.
-Beyonce.
-And do right by Beyonce too.
-It's the cat.
-The cat?
-She's pregnant.
[Tora meows]
Sorry.
-[Tora laughing and meowing]
-[Beyonce meowing]
[Tora mumbles]
[Tora and Beyonce mumbling, meowing]
-Sorry.
-[wheezing laugh]
The cat? The cat?
[laughs]
I totally thought…
[cackles]
After that, it was awkward being together.
And that's why you escaped here.
Please don't tell Tatsuya and Okabe.
[doorbell rings]
Liquor Shop Okabe.
Okabe here.
[Okabe] I'm here for the empty bottles.
[Taeko] Okay.
[Kyota] You don't have to announce it.
Katsuko.
Sorry, but can you go to the market
in Nakamachi and buy leeks?
And a Sasagawa yokan.
[Kyota] Yokan?
I wonder why women always want
to eat all that extra sugar.
[door slides open]
[door slides close]
[Taeko] Katsuko is pregnant.
What'll we do?
Let her have it, or abort it?
Oh!
[chuckles]
Working remotely again today?
Sorry, but my brother is so noisy,
I can't concentrate at home.
I don't mind. Take it easy.
-I'll use your restroom.
-Sure.
[door slides open]
Welcome.
[Okabe exclaims]
[Okabe] Katsuko! I just went
up there to deliver…
[silence]
[knees thud]
[body thuds]
Huh?
I bet you suspect me,
but I swear I didn't do it.
What I want to know is
what we'll do with it. That's all.
Of course.
We'll figure out who did it later.
That's exactly why I'm denying it.
I swear it wasn't me.
[crunching]
Though we're not blood relatives,
she's still my niece…
"Munch munch"?
An uncle and niece would never…
Enough of your munching!
-Should we let her have it?
-There's no way we can.
She's still a child.
-Ethically, in fact, forensically, it's--
-Talk in a way I can understand.
Abort it, right?
How can you be so vulgar?
That's right! If you want to
say it like those supermarket tabloids do.
We don't have the money.
[scoffs]
Now it's a financial problem?
We'll have to borrow from my sister.
You'd better believe it.
She's Katsuko's real mother, after all.
[loud thud]
Katsuko?
[heavy panting]
Someone's been injured.
Katsuko is…
in really bad shape.
Please come with me to the liquor shop.
Welcome.
[exclaims]
Katsuko!
-[Okabe] I just went up there to deliver…
-[knife stabs]
[somber music]
[thuds]
[groans softly]
[knees thud]
[body thuds]
[Katsuko breathes shakily]
[Hansuke] That night,
when her aunt Taeko came home,
her uncle Kyota had been drinking.
What's the situation?
Did Katsuko really stab
the boy from the liquor shop?
You went to the hospital, right?
How's the boy?
I'll tell you in a sec.
I've been thinking about it.
If Katsuko really did stab that boy,
there's only one reason why.
I bet you agree.
There's only one reason.
-That boy--
-Okabe.
That Okabe,
he's the one who did that to Katsuko.
Right?
[Taeko slurping]
Amazing.
Your own niece
went and stabbed someone, but still,
you want to satisfy your hunger.
Before a woman worries
about psychological matters,
she's always thinking
about physical needs.
Okabe says he didn't do it.
[Taeko slurping]
He can talk?
I love Katsuko.
So it made me sad.
She works so hard that she looks like
she could collapse any second,
but still, people call her a rotten--
"Crushed."
Ganmodoki.
So I gave her eclairs and ice cream bars,
and ate them with her,
while I asked her riddles
or we played word games.
She must have hated that.
Well, you were awfully zealous,
but not enough to make her stab him.
-That's right. Ow!
-Sorry.
She must have thought I'd done something
that someone else had done to her.
Even if it was a mistake,
a crime is still a crime.
[Hansuke] Will she go to prison?
The punishment won't be light.
[detective] It's different though
if you don't press charges, Mr. Okabe.
I won't press charges.
I mean, I know she didn't mean it.
[Hansuke] The police detective told
Katsuko's aunt exactly what Okabe said.
See? He's only saying that
because he's guilty.
Isn't that right?
[snickers]
That boy's digging his own grave.
They say the man who did it
can be charged with assault
and forced intercourse.
That's for sure.
He's the victim before the perpetrator.
The police told me
that you should turn yourself in.
Apparently,
Katsuko has something she wants to
tell the police with you there.
If you don't turn yourself in,
they say they'll come and take you in.
You've gotta be kidding!
Why me?
What proof do they have that I…
How should I know?
When she heard that Okabe didn't die,
she said she had something to say
and wanted you to come.
It's a lie.
It sounded like
the police had already heard
what she had to say.
Lies! Lies! All lies!
Taken in by the police?
That's absurd!
I swear I'll fight this!
[Taeko] What's the matter?
Are you saying Katsuko's lying?
Then quit getting so worked up.
Just go to the police and talk to them.
I'm not the least bit afraid of
the darn police.
[Kyota] Darn that filthy hussy!
How dare she bite the hand that feeds her!
They can't prove it.
You know why?
Because it's a lie.
[Hansuke] Her uncle Kyota gulped down
the last of the liquor,
dashed out of the house, and disappeared.
A few days later, they caught up to him
when he tried to sell the masks for money.
[door slams]
LIQUOR SHOP OKABE
Two weeks later, Okabe was back at work.
Welcome.
[Hansuke] He said
that he wouldn't press charges,
but Katsuko was held
in custody for two months,
and got an abortion
at the police hospital.
[indistinct chatter]
The rumors about
what happened spread in an instant,
and then they were forgotten
in an instant.
[indistinct chatter]
-[resident 1] You only got two?
-[laughter]
That's hardly any.
-That's a little scary.
-It's a little wrinkled.
They often say that.
[residents exclaim]
Go ahead.
I'm done, so go ahead.
-Go ahead.
We're just talking, but run the water
to make it look like we're busy.
-[laughter]
-I can't believe you do that.
[Misao] Say, Katsuko, which do you like
better, dollar stores or Donki?
[resident 2] That's a hard question.
[resident 3] Why a dollar store?
[Misao] 'Cause everything's a dollar.
[resident 4]
Walmart's got too much stuff.
[resident 5] That's right. It's crazy.
[resident 6] That's what's good about it.
Sorry about complaining all the time.
It's okay.
Shinsuke…
[Hansuke] Mm?
…isn't there anything that gets you mad?
You can tell me.
I'll listen.
Right?
There's nothing really.
That can't be true,
especially living here.
Isn't there someone you dislike?
No, there isn't.
Since I came here,
most everything is funny, so I don't mind.
Does it mean you've become optimistic?
When I became pessimistic about
how pessimistic I am,
I must have ended up becoming optimistic.
I'm glad to hear it.
Yeah.
Bye.
[Hansuke] After that,
she stopped showing up.
[Okabe] Katsuko!
You're back.
Why didn't you come and see me?
I don't really get it.
Why did you do that?
[Katsuko] I'm sorry.
[Okabe] No, I'm not angry.
I just want to know why.
I intended to die.
Huh?
You did?
Huh? That makes no sense.
If you wanted to die,
what's the point of stabbing me?
I don't know how to put it.
I don't understand it myself.
But…
I was afraid.
Afraid?
When I thought I would die…
I was afraid
that you would forget about me.
After I died,
I was sure you'd soon forget me.
That scared me.
Being forgotten by you…
frightened me so badly,
I couldn't stand it.
I still don't really understand.
By the way,
I've started playing the guitar.
I'm not any good yet though.
[grunts]
♪ Born in a town without seasons ♪
♪ Raised on a hill with no wind ♪
♪ I left a home with no dreams ♪
♪ And met a person with no love ♪
♪ I did things for the sake of others ♪
♪ And got tossed all around ♪
♪ When I finally found some kindness ♪
♪ It withered away so easily ♪
♪ Everything will come to an end today ♪
♪ Everything will be different today ♪
♪ Everything will pay off today ♪
♪ Everything will get started today ♪
♪ Everything will come to an end today ♪
♪ Everything will be different today ♪
♪ Everything will pay off today ♪
♪ Everything will get started today ♪
Sorry, but don't harmonize, please.
I'm sorry.
Eat this. It's good.
I don't want to.
Take it home and eat it later.
I don't like chocolate.
What?
It gives me pimples.
Huh?
[exclaims]
You gotta be kidding me.
Why… Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I'm sorry.
[gentle music]
Katsuko!
Happy birthday.
[gentle music]
[Tatsuya] Shima-san, that proposal I sent…
Shima-san?
Your proposal?
Ah…
I'll read it later.
[Tatsuya mumbles]
"Recovery Public Housing…"
"Now accepting residents…"
TEMPORARY HOUSING WILL BE EMPTIED
AND REMOVED BY MARCH 2024
Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
[Roku-chan imitates train chugging]
Morning. Roku-chan here.
Next time,
something is happening to Roku-chan.
Only Tanba-san and Mom know why.
Episode nine of "A Town Without Seasons"
is "Tanba-san." Enjoy.
[Roku-chan imitating train chugging]
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey