[quirky music]
[Hansuke] You've gotten fatter.
[Tora] Hansuke, that's cat harassment.
[Hansuke] Get some exercise.
I'll leave this open.
Go on.
Wonderful weather, isn't it?
Tanaka, do you have the day off today?
A TOWN WITHOUT SEASONS
[Shima] Oh, I'm sorry.
I saw you at the entrance yesterday,
so I took liberties just now.
EPISODE 5
MY WIFE
I just moved in next door.
My name is Shima.
There's so much I don't know,
so please help me out.
[chuckles]
Okay.
-Now?
-Yes.
-[Shima] I'm Shima.
-[Hatsutaro] Shima-san?
Hello.
Sorry, but I'm fresh
out of business cards. I'm Shima.
SHIMA
Yes.
These are the public water faucets.
There's water in the houses,
but since I don't cook,
this here is enough for me.
-[Shima] I see.
-[Hansuke] And--
[Shima] Hello. I'm Shima.
I'm the council--
The laundromat is there, and for Wi-Fi...
[Shima grunting]
[Hansuke] For Wi...
-For Wi...
-[Shima snorts, sniffles]
Sorry.
For Wi-Fi, everyone uses the router
at Tatsuya's place.
Magnificent.
[chuckles]
What does everyone do for a bath?
The baths here are tiny.
There's a public bath five minutes away.
And that flag is the symbol of this--
[Shima grunting]
[Hansuke] It starts suddenly,
and even Shima-san can't control it.
It's his...
What is it?
Habit? Routine?
He suddenly freezes up,
and one eyebrow raises.
Then he blinks really fast.
Next, each of his eyes
and his mouth go
into separate spasms of their own.
Simultaneously, something seems
to surge up his throat...
[snorts]
...and comes out his nose.
Sorry. Please continue.
Uh, where was I?
[chuckles awkwardly]
Sorry I can't help you.
[sighs]
[comical music]
When I was in university,
I was injured playing rugby.
-It must make you curious.
-No, no.
[Hansuke] I'm way more curious
about the noise he makes than his leg.
I am a real estate broker.
My business also helps
with the reconstruction.
I was suddenly transferred here
but couldn't find a place.
My sweet wife wanted to live in a hotel.
But the neighborhood
by the station is bad.
-The neighborhood here is way worse.
-[laughs]
This place is really great.
It's so nice and open
and everyone's so kind.
[grunts]
-[Hansuke] Is it happening?
-And the view is nice.
[Hansuke] Guess not.
My sweet wife really loves it here.
[Tatsuya] I'm skeptical...
You too?
Anyone who comes here
and blabs about themself
is most likely lying about their past.
Right?
I'm not sure about Shima-san.
-But his wife…
-You saw his "sweet" wife?
[eerie music]
[Tatsuya] Ma'am, what are you doing?
They're rotten.
[Tatsuya] Huh?
Oh, dear.
Weigh this.
Ma'am, I don't sell cabbage by weight.
The price is per head.
[murmurs]
Unbelievable.
Are you nuts?
You're including
all these rotten leaves in the price?
-[camera shutter clicks]
-Hey. Hey, what're you doing now?
[Shima's wife] I'm posting this.
#RottenCabbageRip-off.
Fine. Just take it. It's free.
-Now you've done it!
-[Tatsuya] Huh?
Why, you! Who said I wanted it for free?
I told you I would pay, you scumbag!
She's really mad.
-What happened?
-All of a sudden she...
Why, you! How dare you treat me
like I'm a problem customer!
Now you're really ticking me off!
[whimpers]
-She's scary!
-Okay, I'll weigh it!
[Tatsuya] But the real surprise
was when she put the leaves she tore off
into her shopping bag and walked off.
This town's full of freaks,
but she's a new type.
"New type"?
[laughing]
Even the ladies at the water said,
"Shima's a nice guy,
but I can't stand spasm-man's noise
and his beastly wife!"
[thudding]
[Shima's wife] Odore!
-Okabe.
-You left the bathroom light on, odore!
[whispers]
It's your fault, Okabe.
[Shima's wife] Darn it, odore!
What's your problem, odore?
She's saying, "dancing dunce!"
"Dancing dunce"?
This is bad. The walls are so thin here.
You should probably go over and apologize.
-[banging on door]
-[all grunting]
[banging continues]
Dinkin'?
"Dinkin'"? Oh, are we drinking? Yes.
-Want to join us?
-Hey!
Magnificent!
Wait. I'll be right back.
Then Shima-san brought over
expensive wine, caviar, and hard bread.
It was like a fancy party.
In temporary housing?
This guy's getting more mysterious.
[Shima] So, do you guys know
of a legal way to make good money
with a single magic marker?
-A magic marker?
-That's right.
Buy one at a convenience store
and go to Shinagawa Station.
Or Shin-Osaka Station in Osaka.
If you spend all day at the ticket gate,
baseball players,
and TV stars will pass through for sure.
"I'm your fan. Can I have your autograph?"
Then you sell it on the web.
-[Hansuke] No, no.
-[Okabe] No way.
I mean it.
For Emiko Kaminuma,
you can get up to 20,000 yen.
-No, no.
-No way.
[chuckling]
But then we figured something out.
For just an autograph,
it doesn't have to be the real thing.
We studied handwriting
and copied autographs all night long.
[chuckles]
For a while there,
my sweet wife did more Kaminuma autographs
than Kaminuma herself.
Understand?
-[Hansuke and Okabe chuckle]
-Do you understand?
If you abandon your pride,
you can make money in a million ways.
What a scumbag.
To be honest, I was disgusted.
[Hansuke] But Tatsuya,
the most suspicious, wanted to know more.
This has faded a lot,
but it's the autograph
of some pop idol when they visited.
-50,000.
-Seriously?
I've got a ball
autographed by Shinjo at home.
Do you need money, Yoda?
-His brother's in the hospital.
-Hey!
Why don't you come down to our office?
I can get you work.
But...
[laughs]
Now, we've branched out a lot.
We utilize open innovation, for example,
to start cafes in underpopulated towns.
-Cafes? Did you hear that?
-Cafes? Cafes?
Actually, our Young Men's Club
has a plan to open a cafe here.
Magnificent!
Let's do something together.
My business card.
Where's my business cards?
[grunts]
[Hansuke] And now,
Tatsuya is working at Shima's company.
But I don't get it.
It's not underpopulated,
because there's no cafe.
It's the other way around.
What about you?
About what?
Isn't it obvious?
You haven't sent me
any reports at all lately.
-Quit blowing me off.
-[thuds]
Who reads those things anyway?
I do.
But someone asked you for them
so you had me do them, right?
That town's gonna be torn down.
Don't make that face.
It's temporary housing, after all.
But... you said it so casually.
None of them will leave easily
so we need dirt on them.
[softly]
I see.
The homeless and foreigners move in
all the time.
That Shima guy will just sublet his place.
Whoever lived there before
just might be dead anyway.
Thanks.
I'll look into him.
[somber music]
-No, no. It's okay.
-Take it.
Keep an eye on them.
I didn't finish again.
[purring]
Shrimp.
-Shrimp.
-[Hansuke] Tora.
Isn't that you, Tora?
What're you doing here, Tora?
Tora!
[shouts]
[cries]
[Hansuke] Tora didn't
come back home that day.
Tora!
It's open seating,
so sit anywhere you like.
-Okay.
-There.
[Hansuke] Shima-san seems to like Tatsuya,
so he's working pretty hard.
-Good morning.
-[employees] Good morning.
[Shima] Doing well?
[Hansuke] Tora?
Tora?
-Welcome home.
-[screams]
Are you kidding?
The window was open.
The front door was too!
The window is for Tora to come in.
I got this. It's really good.
It's a new product.
Thank you.
I delivered liquor next door.
To Shima's place?
They're having guests tonight.
Hey!
What? Is something up?
There's... a girl I like.
-Katsuko?
-What?
How did you know?
You're not trying to hide it.
[shushes]
[Okabe] That poor girl.
Her uncle's a drunkard.
[presenter] Now for the weather.
It better be sunny tomorrow.
The laundry is really piling up.
You're always complaining
about the weather.
Are you a meteorologist or something?
Or maybe an astronomer?
My shoulders are so stiff.
-[snickers]
-[groans]
[scoffs]
That's not pain caused by illness,
but pain caused by movement.
A little harder.
That's the way.
[sighs]
So sometimes I'd give her snacks
and chat with her.
Fine. Next time, I'll do it in secret.
Don't do that. Be out in the open with it.
[distant laughter]
That really was fun.
I realized and learned a lot
from today's discussion.
[Shima] This is it.
Hello! I'm home!
Actually, we should probably be going.
It's all right.
She's looking forward to this too.
[Shima] Hey!
Maybe she's at bath.
Is it okay?
Come in.
This place is nothing to be afraid of.
Come on in.
There. Have a seat.
[groans]
Take a load off.
Okay.
[Shima exhales loudly]
[sniffles]
[exclaims]
There aren't any glasses.
I'll get them.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
[employees murmuring]
[gasps]
[eerie music]
[employee 1] I realized and learned a lot
from today's discussion.
[employee 2] I bet you did.
[employee 1] For innovation to work,
you need to respect the local residents.
[clattering]
You're here?
Get out here and greet everyone.
They are promising members of our team.
Come out. I'll introduce you.
[Shima's wife groans]
The signal here sucks.
Darn this cell phone signal.
This ticks me off.
It's all the fault of jerks showing up
in the middle of the night to mooch.
You know, Hamaguchi,
those Yakult Swallows sure aren't winning.
-Huh?
-[Shima chuckles]
[clears throat]
Uhm, this is my sweet wife.
[Shima] This is Igawa and Hamaguchi.
You've met Yoda, right?
No, we haven't met properly.
Sorry to drop in at night.
[Hansuke] "This would be the right time
for one of my spasms."
That's probably what Shima-san thought.
But it's always at times like this
that it doesn't turn up.
[exhales sharply]
I'm going to the bath. There's barazushi.
[door slams]
Okay, let's drink.
Daiginjo sake.
[chuckles]
Let's start over.
Igawa got this first.
You just had a son, didn't you?
That's me.
Oh, that's right. We need to celebrate.
There.
There. Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy.
There we go.
Once more.
Cheers!
[all] Cheers.
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
We should drink it warm.
It's cold tonight.
It's okay. I'll do it.
Thanks.
[Hansuke] All three of them
were moved to tears in their hearts.
Shima-san has a disability
and a health issue,
yet he's cheerful, happy, and polite.
But as he bustled
about to serve his guests,
all they could do was watch.
[Shima grunts]
Barazushi is a specialty in our home.
You can't get started without eating it.
[chuckles]
Oh, right.
Do you know of a legal way
to make good money with a magic--
[Igawa] Selling autographs, right?
[Tatsuya] Sorry. I told them.
You did?
Forgery is a crime,
so you should be careful.
That was a long time ago.
I don't do that stuff now.
[awkward chuckle]
Shima-san...
-You know how to get soup kitchen food--
-Shima-san.
Yes?
Tonight, we're, like,
uninvited guests, right?
Why do you think that?
Isn't it obvious?
[grunts]
Did I say something to offend you?
No, no. You're a nice guy, Shima-san.
A really nice guy.
But... In fact, that's why I wonder...
about what happened earlier.
Earlier?
You introduced us
to your "sweet" wife, right?
That's why Igawa
and Hamaguchi greeted her.
But her attitude...
Now, now, Yoda. That's enough.
Sorry about that.
You shouldn't apologize, Shima-san.
That's right.
I'm not criticizing you, Shima-san.
In fact, I respect you.
How do I put this?
You feel righteous indignation?
I don't really get it, but sorry.
Like I said, you shouldn't be apologizing.
No, no, Igawa.
That's the kind of woman she is.
She's bad at expressing emotion.
It's way more than that!
Like I said, I'm sorry.
He's not mad at you.
Are you mad?
If he is, he's mad at you
for not getting mad.
That's right.
Forget how she treated us.
It was pretty bad though.
But what I won't stand for
is her attitude toward you, her husband.
She sure didn't show any respect.
She didn't even say "welcome home."
She complained about the signal,
threw the food on the table,
tossed the potato chips and seethed.
"Going to the bath." Slam!
What's with that?
I'm ticked off.
-What's with that?
-I said I'm sorry.
Like I said,
you should have gotten mad at her.
Your wife's treating us with contempt.
Even in this town...
In fact, because we live in this town,
we greet each other properly
and treat each other with respect!
Even Kuma and Roku-chan
and the homeless guys do!
I'm apologizing in her stead.
Quit apologizing!
Why do it for that woman?
It's pathetic!
Instead of apologizing to us,
kick that woman out of this house!
[grumbles]
Whoa! Stop it!
[Tatsuya] Shima-san!
Hey, how dare you say that? How dare you?
[yells]
[Hamaguchi] Shima-san!
[panting]
Kick her out?
I wouldn't kick her out
even if she had hurt you,
but she hasn't done a thing to you!
[Hamaguchi] Cut this out, you two.
It's okay.
Let's listen to what he has to say.
She is...
She is my sweet wife.
To you guys, she may seem like
she's not worth dime.
But no matter what anyone says,
she is my sweet wife!
She's suffered through a lot.
She suffered for my sake.
She waited for famous people
at Shinagawa Station.
She lined up
at the soup kitchens countless times.
She put up with poverty so bad
that she had to do
those humiliating things.
So how dare you!
What right do you have
to tell me to kick her out?
What the heck do you know
about me and her?
[Hamaguchi] That's enough, Shima-san.
Let go of him.
[Shima] Quit your laughing!
-[objects clattering]
-[Shima panting]
We had to come.
I heard a loud noise. Is everything okay?
[Igawa] Fine.
I get it.
That was inappropriate of me.
Shima-san,
please forgive me.
No, it was me who started it.
I'm sorry.
[grunts]
[sneezes]
Okay, let's get back to drinking.
Okay?
[Igawa] I'm not in the mood.
Let's wind things up.
[Shima grunts]
But we've only just started.
We haven't had the barazushi.
Yoda, get the barazushi from in there.
Okay.
You, Young Men's Club,
have some barazushi.
-Good night.
Don't leave. Please.
Where are you, Yoda?
We don't have the right to eat this.
Incredible.
[soft music]
Didn't I tell you?
My sweet wife was looking forward to
to you guys coming over.
I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
-[camera shutter clicks]
[door slides open]
[Shima] Come again sometime.
Don't let this put you off. Come again.
Good night.
[Shima] See you tomorrow.
The bath was closed today.
I heard.
"My sweet wife," huh?
[scoffs]
You say I'm your sweet wife?
Don't make me laugh.
[grunting]
[soft music continues]
[Tora meows]
Tora!
Where have you been, Tora?
I was so worried.
Tora.
Sorry I called you fat.
Huh? You lost weight?
[Tora] No, I didn't.
You didn't? No, you didn't.
But you're not fat either. You're not fat.
Want some?
Want the barazushi
made by his "sweet" wife?
[Hansuke] Thanks to Shima-san,
Tatsuya's dream
gradually came closer to reality.
We'll make a wood deck
that looks like this.
What do you think?
It looks cheap.
-Hey.
-"Cheap," he says.
I was gonna put
your boat banner around here.
Someone's over there.
[Okabe] Open it. Go ahead, open it.
[Tatsuya] Quit hiding!
That's even more noticeable.
[Hansuke] One day, not long after that…
Oh, it's Mikki.
[door slides close]
[foreboding music]
What's going on?
[Tanba-san]
Tanba from building seven here.
Everyone thinks old folks know everything,
but there's stuff I don't know.
Like taking medicine.
When do you take it
if it's "before or during meals"?
And nobody has any idea
when that homeless father and son arrived.
But that's normal.
Episode six is "A Home with a Pool."
[closing theme music]
Translated by Brian Athey