[grunts]
[elder] You've seen these
temporary housing places on TV, right?
[newcomer]
Where the disaster victims live?
[elder snickers]
Not just victims now.
-[newcomer] Really?
-[elder] There are all kinds here.
[newcomer] Tora!
-[resident 1] Get out!
-[groans]
Don't you ever come back!
-Back off, woman!
-You're drunk!
I know better than anyone,
whether I'm drunk or not!
-Beat it, loser!
-[door slams]
How dare you say that to me!
Who do you think...
[clicks tongue]
[newcomer] Tora.
[lively music]
You'll work remotely.
I'll pay you in digital cash.
What's my job?
Report to me.
About what?
What you hear.
All right.
[resident 2] You're all better, huh?
That's great. See you around.
That's the laundromat
and public water faucets.
[elder] If you pay,
you can get water in your home.
Don't look at them.
As for Wi-Fi,
for some reason,
you can only connect to it around there.
See you.
Oh, right.
If anyone asks you what you're doing,
just ignore them.
They can't find out.
[lively music]
SHINSHINMARU 88
CAPTAIN: KYUSUKE TANAKA
A TOWN WITHOUT SEASONS
It has been 12 years
since that sinister event.
[reporter 1] The victims of The What
who lost their families and homes
still live in this temporary housing.
[light music]
[reporter 2] Now, 12 years after The What,
13 families still live their lives
in this temporary housing.
[newcomer] Twelve years, huh?
[reporter 3] Twelve years after The What,
the government has canceled
some funding for reconstruction.
[sighs]
I'm starving.
-Some want funding to continue--
-Sorry.
We're picking up train noise.
Can you do it again?
Mister, what is "The What"?
-[distant rumbling]
-Huh?
-Does a train run by here?
-No.
Before you were born,
around here, there was a large...
[train driver] Clickety-clack.
Clickety-clack.
Huh?
[train driver] Clickety-clack.
[reporter 3] Some people's homes
were washed away.
"Dodes'ka-den"?
[train driver] Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
-Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
-[newcomer] Huh? What?
[train driver shouting]
[playful music]
[crew] What the heck?
Excuse me. May I ask you--
Out of the way!
-Dodes'ka-den.
-[train honking]
-[meows]
-That was dangerous!
I'm sorry!
You'd sure better be!
What're you letting it on the tracks for?
Tracks?
You don't even know what tracks are?
You country bumpkin!
What's your name?
I'm Tanaka. Shinsuke Tanaka.
Shinsuke? What a joke.
You in your shorts.
You're more like Hansuke! Shorts Hansuke!
We just made an emergency stop,
because an obstruction was detected.
Be more careful, you fool!
[clanks]
[engine hisses]
Train now departing.
[train driver] This is a local train
bound for Asahimachi Station.
That's Roku-chan.
Huh? Who's that?
He's famous here.
Roku-chan the train nut.
-Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den...
-[kids chatter]
Shut up, you train nut!
By the way, who are you?
Now, now, Hansuke.
Don't be so unfriendly.
ANYTHING STRANGE HAPPEN?
I'm Tatsuya Yoda.
This is my place.
Wi-Fi's good here, right?
A TRAIN RUNS THROUGH HERE.
THAT'S INSANE. LOL
I know it's sudden,
but wanna join our Young Men's Club?
[Tatsuya] It's so dull here.
There's nothing but old folks.
Before, volunteers served up food
and celebs would come to visit.
Look at this.
It's the autograph of...
some pop idol.
[wheezing]
Rent's free here.
-Seriously?
-You didn't know that?
MIKKI SENT YOU 10,000 YEN
[Tatsuya] But if you make
over 120,000 yen a month,
you have to move out.
So foreigners and ex-cons move in here.
Are you listening?
No.
Wait. Tora! Tora!
-[clatters]
-[tap water running]
[resident 3] Hey! Get out!
Ahh.
I'm sorry.
-I'll pay for those.
-Is that your cat?
-Do you take digital cash?
-No chance!
How much is it?
[Roku-chan] Clickety-clack.
Clickety-clack. Skree!
What happened, Mom?
You again?
How dare you, Hansuke!
-Forget it. Just go away.
-I'm sorry.
Don't say that, Mom!
This train is going to the garage.
No riders are allowed.
Entering the garage.
Wait, Mom!
Hands off!
Mom!
-[oil sizzling]
-Mom!
What's the matter, Mom?
Nothing.
Then why are you making that face?
Are you crying?
No, I'm not.
It's just that the oil's hot.
[sniffles]
Why are you so darn worried?
Things will be fine.
You've got me, you know.
[Hansuke] Roku-chan is the driver
of the local train.
REPORT
[keyboard clacking]
However, there are no tracks
or overhead lines.
There isn't even an actual train.
-[oil sizzling]
-Ah.
My hat.
Huh?
-My hat.
-Oh.
My hat.
[Hansuke] In other words,
besides the driver, Roku-chan, his gloves,
and a few other items,
the train is a complete fantasy.
See you later.
Have one before you go.
[steel clinking]
[resident 3 giggles]
Yum.
Don't you dare leave the town.
Okay?
Promise me.
[Hansuke] The other residents
-pay Roku-chan no attention at all.
-[Roku-chan mimics train honking]
-[residents laugh]
-[Hansuke] They're totally indifferent.
To them, he's part of the scenery.
In fact, I'm not sure
if they can even see him.
-It's all limp.
-It even bends.
It was picked just yesterday!
[Roku-chan mimics train honking, chugging]
Hatsu, want a sausage?
-You bet!
-[Roku-chan mimics train chugging]
[indistinct chatter]
[Hansuke] Roku-chan
doesn't see them, either.
Except for a very select few.
[engine hisses, stops]
[Roku-chan] Tanba-san.
Hi, Roku-chan.
How's your mom?
She prays morning and night
at the family altar.
Sorry to hear that. Sorry for Kuniko, too.
Not to worry. She's got me, after all.
You're right.
You're a train conductor, after all.
I'm a train driver!
[Tanba-san] Right.
[clanks]
[Hansuke] In other words,
anyone who can't see Roku-chan
can't be seen by him, either.
SEND
MESSAGE SENT
[groaning]
I'm starving.
[doorbell dings]
[delivery man] Excuse me.
Liquor Shop Okabe here.
I have a delivery of food and liquor
from someone named Mikki.
Seriously?
That'll be 4,126 yen.
Cash on delivery?
-I've only got digital cash.
-Hello there!
[snickers]
-Like I thought, this place is empty.
-Hey. Stop!
What's going on? Get out!
I got you a fridge. It still works.
He's Okabe from the Club.
Hi. We take digital cash.
[Hansuke] Hey, take off your shoes!
My shoes, my shoes.
-What's going on here?
-Okabe, help out!
Get that cat box.
There we go. Okay. Okay.
Good kitty.
-Here.
-Okay.
[panting]
Huh? Where's the cat?
When I start working, it leaves.
Work? Are you a writer? An author?
[Hansuke] Something like that.
Amazing.
[Tatsuya] Nobody amazing would live here.
MIKKI SENT YOU 10,000 YEN
Where'd you live?
Before here? All over.
Like Tokyo?
I was in Tokyo for about three years.
Amazing.
Okabe, you're too fast
with your admiration.
Sorry.
I want to keep him talking and dig deeper.
You're so dense.
You can dig, but you won't find anything.
So, why come here now?
"Why"?
Only disaster victims can live here.
Understand?
It's not like we doubt you. Right?
Tatsuya's the Club leader.
He did the same the other day.
A criminal group took up residence
in the next place over.
It was a hideout for a phone scam gang.
I passed the screening.
My house was destroyed,
my mom died, and my dad
and grandad and brother are missing.
[somber music]
[whispers]
He's just like us.
Amazing.
[chanting]
[both chanting]
Father, I know I always pray for this,
but please make Mom's head better.
Please.
[somber music]
Dad.
While I'm away,
I want you to watch over Mom.
[both chanting]
Do it like me.
Okay, time to get to work.
RIBBON CITRON
[Roku-chan] Pliers, wrench, oilcan. Check!
Commence morning inspection.
[rustling]
[clanking]
[clinking]
Check!
What?
[screw squeaks]
Darn that maintenance guy.
He's always cutting corners.
-[screw creaks]
-[groans]
-[clinking]
-Check!
-[glass squeaking]
-This guy's getting pretty old.
But there's no point
in complaining about it.
[sighs]
-[clinking]
-Check!
[clinking]
What do you want?
Give me a ride.
My bicycle tire's got a hole.
You can't do it?
No, I can.
[kid] What's the matter?
I'm not supposed to leave town alone.
Mom says so.
You're not alone.
All aboard.
Be careful of the doors.
Closing doors now.
[clanks]
[engine hisses]
[mimics train honking]
[epic music]
[mimics train chugging]
[train honking]
[Roku-chan] Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
[mimics train accelerating]
[uplifting music]
Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
Dodes'ka-den.
[mimics brake screeching]
Dodes'ka-den. Dodes'ka-den.
[kid] Train crossing!
[alarm blaring]
This is far enough.
[mimics engine hissing]
Here it comes!
Thank you. That was a big help.
[distant droning]
[brakes squealing]
Hm?
Yeah, I saw the trains.
What did I think?
No big deal.
The brakes were really loud.
They gotta oil those.
Welcome home. You're early.
No trains today. It happens sometimes.
[Hansuke] Tora! There you go again.
That's stealing! You're a thief cat!
Cut that out!
I don't wanna owe anybody anything here.
[cop 1] Stop!
-[siren blaring]
-[cop 1 pants]
Stop!
[whimpering]
-What happened? What did Roku-chan do?
-Kidnapping.
And possible forcible indecency.
[cop 2] Will you come with us, ma'am?
A missing person's report was filed
for a young girl missing since yesterday.
Hey, you gotta be mistaken.
My wife said she heard his train
this morning, same as always.
He was caught on this dashcam.
[cop 3] He's carrying the girl
on his back.
-What time was that?
-What time?
[cop 1] Around 8 or 9 a. m.
[resident 4] This morning at eight,
I heard Roku-chan's train. Right, Mitsuyo?
That's right. His "clickety-clack"
wakes up my husband every morning.
Like an alarm clock.
But he's on this dashcam.
He passed me by
at 9 a. m. near the water faucets.
I saw him, too,
doing his "dodo-sukosukosuko."
No, it's "dodes'kaden."
So obviously, you've got the wrong guy.
But this dashcam shows...
Who are you gonna believe?
Some dashcam or my pal here?
The dashcam.
Why, you!
[resident 5] Tanba-san, what good timing.
You saw Roku-chan today, right?
You bet I did.
We played shogi at my place.
Right, Roku-chan?
[Tanba-san] It was a good game.
Your cat was there, too, so ask him.
You live here, too?
Huh?
So, did you see him?
I bet you didn't, did you?
Uh, just a sec.
[muttering]
Can you hold this?
It's fried fish.
[Hansuke] The 7:28 a. m. train
passed by my place at 7:40 a. m.
Then it looped back at 8:10 a. m.
Then it looped back at 8:40 a. m.
and again at 9:10 a. m.
It looped my place every 30 minutes.
Then after an hour's lunch break,
the afternoon train departed at 1:12 p. m.
southbound and 1:50 p. m. northbound.
You a mystery writer?
What's with you?
How come you know so much?
Well, I'm his fan.
[distant panting]
Sorry to interrupt, officer!
My daughter came back home.
[residents gasp]
She skipped cram school yesterday
and spent the night here last night.
[kid] That boy gave me a rice ball.
That man gave me a ride to the station.
Roku-chan...
I'm sorry, Mom.
See? I told you he was on the dashcam!
[resident 6] Who cares?
Case solved.
Let's get us a drink, Hatsu.
Yeah! I'm coming!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for causing so much trouble.
[Roku-chan] Sorry about that.
[Kuniko] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
-[resident 7] A daily occurrence here!
-[resident 8] Are they gone?
[resident 8] That was close.
Did they ask about me?
Did they?
You sure as hell
better not have told them anything!
Thank you, Mr. Train Driver.
I just went along with everyone.
Thank you so much. I mean it.
Don't thank this guy!
Roku-chan!
Keep an eye on him from now on, too.
Keep an eye on Roku-chan, please.
Sorry about Tora.
[door closes]
I'm indebted to people again.
Okay, now it's time
for the Young Men's Club
to welcome Hansuke to the Club.
Hey, Katsuko!
[grumbles]
Where are you going, Katsuko? The bath?
Aren't you cold? You'll catch a chill.
You've lost weight again.
Are you getting enough food and sleep?
Let's do a staring contest. Ready, go.
-Boo!
-[sobbing]
[whimpers]
Never mind! I'm sorry!
I heard laughing builds
your immune system.
Have this fried chicken stick. It's good.
Have this boiled egg, too.
-Okabe.
-[bicycle bell rings]
I gotta go.
See you later.
Enjoy the bath. Take it easy.
Is the Young Men's Club just you two?
No. With you, it's three.
[whooping]
[snickering]
After what you did today,
everybody accepts you here.
Hold on. What is this club supposed to do?
This is temporary housing.
We're all gonna move out sometime.
The government's stopping funding, too.
Why don't we tell him your plan, Tatsuya?
We, of the Young Men's Club,
will build a cafe here!
A cafe?
He's mocking us.
Seriously? Do you need a cafe here?
Would any of these people use it?
Not really a cafe, but a salon.
A hangout spot for young people.
A cafe? A salon?
More like a studio,
with paintings and sculptures.
Like a memorial park--
-Just as long as I can play darts.
-No.
What do you want to build?
It doesn't matter. Anything is fine.
I wanna make what we don't have here.
Something besides our everyday stuff.
A place where people naturally gather
and laugh and cry together.
No, not for me.
Best of luck.
[lively music]
SHINSHINMARU 88
Father.
I know you must be sick of hearing this,
but please make Mom's head better.
-Tanba-san is worried about her, too.
-[snorts]
I pray that Mom becomes normal.
[Kuniko] What's the matter, Roku-chan?
[Roku-chan] It's nothing.
[singing bowl chimes]
You don't need to worry about it, Mom.
Worrying about things
is bad for your head.
[birds chirping]
Long time no see, Tatsuya.
Shingo.
[Tatsuya] They say the bad kid
gets spoiled, but you can go too far.
When my bad brother returns,
it makes me look goody-goody and lame.
Then things get bad.
Watch A Town Without Seasons,
episode two, "For Mother."
This has been Tatsuya Yoda.
Get Wi-Fi here!
Translated by Brian Athey