AROUND THE SAME TIME
ROHAN AND TONIO
MAKE THEIR WAY TO HYOGARA ROCKS
I feel terrible
that I get you entangled in my mess.
Don't you worry.
I should be the one apologizing
that the most I can do
is sip tea with you.
I appreciate your company.
What a sweet aroma.
It's tasty.
Speaking of scent,
Tonio's cooking
is not only very delicious,
but it also smells wonderful.
It's not that it smells special
or anything,
but more that it makes me feel calm
and a little nostalgic.
Just one whiff
and I can't help but reach for my fork.
Izumi.
Can you recall the moment you were born?
What?
You mean, when I was a baby?
Sorry,
that's a little too far back for me.
I remember
the day I was born.
Wow.
To be specific,
I remember the scent of it.
The scent of your birth?
I was born in an old hospital
over a century old
tucked in the mountains
of the Shikoku region.
It was a November morning
when the doctor scooped me up
and I felt the fresh breeze.
I remember being surrounded
by the sweet scent of raspberries.
It's a sweet, tart,
and a little nostalgic scent.
Isn't it silly,
a newborn thinking a scent is nostalgic?
That scent stimulated my appetite,
and I clutched on to my mother's breast.
My grandmother saw this
and laughed and said…
"Oh dear. This one is fond of eating.
She might grow up to love cooking."
Wow.
You remember it that clearly?
You must think I'm spouting nonsense.
No, I believe you.
I've had nothing but strange encounters
since I became Mr. Rohan's editor.
Just as my grandma thought,
I grew up to love cooking food.
That's why I became a patisserie.
Then, two years ago, I met Tonio.
Back then,
I was suffering from hay fever
and had a terribly stuffy nose.
It's a serious problem for any chef.
That's when Tonio
made a lasagna to console me.
I still remember
the jolt that ran through me
when I first saw his cooking.
Though I couldn't smell,
I definitely smelled
that scent from his lasagna.
That scent?
Right.
That irresistible scent that stirs hunger
but also calms you down at the same time.
The same scent as the day I was born.
That warm and gentle smell.
Like that feeling
of sipping
your mother's homemade miso soup at home?
He said, in Italy, lasagna
is the taste of the mother's cooking.
Wow, is it really?
Tonio's lasagna healed my allergies.
There's something really magical
about Tonio's cooking.
But to me,
it's the smell from his cooking
that's truly precious and endearing.
You know,
I bet he pours his kind personality
and all the affection he feels
for his family and loved ones
into his dishes.
When I stand next to him in the kitchen,
I forget the flow of time.
My dream is to bake treats
that smell just as sweet and tart
as Tonio's cooking.
I love that.
All this talk worked up my appetite.
My appetite really is twice the size
of anyone else's.
I can cook something easy
if you'd like.
Oh, but--
Right.
Snacking at night is bad for beauty.
Let's not.
When Tonio and Mr. Rohan get back,
it might be time for breakfast.
I just want them to come back unharmed.
They don't even need
to bring back any abalone.
Before my grandmother passed away,
I was overcome with sadness
and anxiously asked her this:
"Grandma,
will you become a star after you die?"
My grandmother smiled and replied…
"Some become stars,
some become butterflies.
And others even become raspberries.
No matter what they become,
they stay close to their loved ones
and watch over them.
Even after I die, you won't be alone.
I'll always be by your side, Hatsune."
Even now.
They say there's one fate
that's inevitable as much as inescapable.
One day, we will die.
But if it's as my grandma says,
then I don't fear death.
Every day, I try to live my life
to the fullest
so that when my time comes…
I won't have any regrets.
I met Tonio.
I tasted his dishes.
I even cooked alongside him.
Just with these moments of joy,
I've lived the happiest life.
Even after I pass on,
as long as Tonio is alive and well…
I can stay by his side and watch over him.
I prattled on.
I'm sorry.
Ms. Hatsune.
Recently, my schedule has been so hectic
that I haven't had time for proper meals.
That's when I had Tonio's cooking,
and it deeply touched me.
Then this thought came to me.
Earlier, you said
that death is inevitable.
One thing that's for certain
is that we'll all die one day.
Yes.
But I believe something else
is equally important in life.
Something else?
Enjoying food.
I think that living a life
you don't regret
has to mean that
you thoroughly enjoy delicious food.
I think that's really important.
The dish doesn't have to be elaborate.
It's important
to enjoy food made with love every day,
whether it's for yourself or someone else.
Izumi.
Sorry to sound like a know-it-all.
I haven't touched a pan in a while,
and I don't have
a wide repertoire of recipes.
Who cares,
as long as you pour your heart into it?
Exactly.
Now I'm really hungry.
They'll be back soon.
Mr. Rohan might come off
as lofty and full of confidence,
but for some reason, he's very reliable.
And he never fails to deliver.
So we can entrust it to him.
Wow, now…
I'm starting to smell breakfast.
Café au lait and sugary biscuits.
Tonio's brioche is exceptional too.
I can't wait to try!
Brioche is one of my favorites.
I just got a whiff of wild strawberries.
Me too.