FISHING PROHIBITED AREA
What a bust.
That was some tight security.
I knew it.
Reaching the other side of Hyogara Rocks
is nearly impossible.
There were more security cameras
than I could count.
I would've loved to get my hands on
just one abalone.
Though it won't be that hard
to scam that foreigner.
I agree.
He easily believed me when I said we have
hookups in the fishing union.
It looked like he would hand over
a million yen for one abalone.
All that money for abalone?
Must be a real dimwit.
I know.
Let's find some other ones
at another spot close by.
That man doesn't know a thing
about this area.
If we pull a poker face and say
it came from Hyogara Rocks,
he won't be any wiser.
That's smart!
Boss, I swear you're a genius!
Oh stop it, I'm no genius--
You there! Pipe down, will you?
I thought I'd finally get to see them.
Now they're hiding.
Just unbelievable.
-Excuse me?
-What?
Is that Kishibe Rohan?
What do you mean?
I was hard at work.
I came to do a live drawing
of the rare Japanese mitten crabs
said to inhabit this area.
These creatures are delicate
and only come out for a short span of time
in the early hours of the day.
I quietly camped all night to see them.
They were finally beginning to emerge…
-when you came along.
-Right.
Live drawing? Well, pardon our intrusion.
Here's an idea though.
What if instead of going through
all that trouble, you Google them?
Boss, he's the famous manga artist,
Kishibe Rohan.
-He's a well-known celebrity!
-Wait, manga?
Manga, though?
Then what's the issue here?
More reason for a quick Google search.
What are they called again?
I'll pull it up on my phone.
-It's for manga--
-You honestly think the Kishibe Rohan…
would be satisfied referencing
some stock photo on the Internet?
Come again?
My vocation is creating manga art.
Reality is the most important thing
in a work of manga.
That's why I dedicate myself
to finding authentic material
in the name of pursuing realism.
That goes for a critter
that appears on a single panel too.
Its color, shape, scent, and…
taste.
The entire manga would be a lie
if I don't express the realism
I experience with my own body and senses.
A manga approached
with half-baked research…
is nothing but an offense to the readers.
Well, we'll get going.
Hold it.
You two.
You're interesting.
Let me use you two as my reference.
Perhaps one day,
you'll make good material for manga.
I'm interested
in what you were about to do.
Weren't you…
going to poach?
I don't have the faintest idea
of what you mean.
Ridiculous.
-Our cover's blown.
-Time to go.
Heaven's Door.
Let the door to your mind now open.
What's happening to me?
This is an ability of mine.
I can read people's memories and thoughts
in the form of books.
The human body remembers everything
that has ever happened to it.
Even if a person forgets,
the body does not.
These are 100% real memories
that can't be found in any interview.
This reality is what breathes life
into my work,
providing only the finest entertainment.
I CAN DO IT
WITH MY DIVING SKILLS
I can't have thieves like you
get in my way ever again.
The orders I write down
can never be disobeyed.
SURVEIL THE SEA FOR ROHAN
Surveil the sea for Rohan.
I can only see this as a gift from heaven,
but it's not as important as my talent
that uses them as material for manga.
AUG 14 MAN MISSING
SWEPT OUT TO SEA
AUG 19, 2019
SUSPENDED SEARCH FOR MAN
WHO WENT MISSING WHILE DIVING
AUG 10, 2006 - WENT MISSING
WHILE SWIMMING WITH PEERS
AUG 14, 1954 TWO MEN MISSING
LAST SEEN ENTERING SEA
YESTERDAY MORNING
Mr. Rohan!
Sorry I'm lagging behind.
I spaced out
and went all the way to your house.
Work's been crazy busy in prep
for the Bon holiday next week.
Things have been so hectic.
I've barely slept all week.
And my tooth has to start hurting now.
I don't even have time
to go see a dentist.
-For you, Miss?
-Milk tea.
Certainly.
Oh, man, it stings.
So, do you always get
deliveries and takeouts?
I've got no time to cook.
By the time I'm home, I'm wiped.
It's too much hassle.
Embrace food as medicine.
What's that?
Prevention starts with
a conscious effort to eat a balanced diet.
Your body will naturally
learn to fend off diseases.
Since you already
don't eat a balanced diet,
a few hectic days
are enough to wreck your health.
What am I supposed to do
working in this industry?
Let's get on the same page.
You wanted me to come out here,
me, who is in the midst of
a popular serialization,
because you had a favor to ask?
Was it, "Can I schedule in
your next one-off?
How about a mystery horror
themed around food? Ha ha!"
Does that sound right?
Someone with your atrocious eating habits
is unfit to supervise such a story.
You nailed it.
So why don't we go grab a delicious bite?
-What?
-Let's say, an early lunch.
Hey, hey, hey.
We haven't even started our meeting.
No formal offer either, I was--
I spotted a sign on the way to your house.
It wasn't there last week.
This restaurant must have recently opened!
It's rare to see an Italian restaurant
in a place like this.
Italian restaurant?
Italian cuisine is known
for its health benefits.
Doesn't it go along with
"Embrace food as medicine"?
We'll continue our meeting there.
Not sure when you found this sign,
but this was your plan all along,
wasn't it?
-Over there!
-Listen, you.
500M AHEAD
I admit it.
This place wasn't here before.
There aren't many
residential houses out this way.
An Italian restaurant in a secluded area.
Rather surprising, don't you think?
It must be one of those trendy
hole-in-the-wall places!
I have high hopes for this one!
AN ITALIAN MAN
APPROACHED US ABOUT ABALONE
"An Italian man who relocated
to an old mansion.
An Italian restaurant.
A strange Italian man.
He's seeking the legendary abalone,
willing to pay any price.
Whimper of a dog from the kitchen.
Questionable experiments."
Here we are.
What a large mansion.
I don't see how this can go wrong.
Now close it.
Yes, sir.
Strange.
The sign said it's open, but…
Maybe they're in the back?
Great interior design.
This is weird.
There's only one table.
But there's so much room.
That's because I do everything by myself.
Welcome to my Trattoria.
Please take a seat.
So, are you from Italy?
Yes, ma'am. I'm Tonio Trussardi.
I'm from Napoli.
Tonio, where's the menu?
Menu?
You're talking about la lista.
-Yes.
-There's none.
What?
The dish will vary
depending on the customer.
It's because I examine each guest
and decide on their courses.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
It seems…
you only slept three hours last night.
Additionally…
you have a cavity.
It's on the right side,
the second molar from the back.
How can you tell?
I can tell everything about your body
simply by examining both of your hands.
Your turn now.
Your intestinal lining is irritated.
There's more.
Your shoulder is stiff.
It's the right shoulder.
Is that right?
Yes.
That's impressive.
Could you be the famous Kishibe Rohan?
-Yes I am.
-No!
Your work, Pink Dark Boy,
is cherished in Italy too.
I'm a lifelong fan myself.
-World-famous, Mr. Rohan.
-Zip it.
Oh, pardon my rudeness.
There's no time to chitchat.
I should be flipping pans in the kitchen.
You two are my very first customers.
Let me give you special treatment.
I've never been to a restaurant
without a menu.
What a strange restaurant.
I wonder what dishes he'll make.
Mr. Rohan?
What is it? Is it the toothache?
This water…
I've never had such delicious water
in my entire life!
It's refined, yet refreshing
all at the same time!
If I must say, it's befitting of
a princess plucking a harp in the Alps.
Or the first sip of water after wandering
in the desert for three whole days.
You're right.
Just exquisite!
Wait…
It's so delicious, I'm tearing up.
I can't hold them back,
they keep pouring out.
Izumi?
What's happening to you?
My tears!
-My tears!
-One moment, please.
Please calm down.
This reaction is only temporary.
This water is 50,000-year old
melted snow from Mt. Kilimanjaro.
It cleanses out your eyes
and treats sleep deprivation.
This didn't happen to you, Mr. Rohan,
because you got
a full night's rest last night.
What do you mean?
Mr. Rohan.
I feel refreshed.
It's like I slept on the most
comfortable bed for 10 hours straight.
I feel revitalized.
For you.
Why did I gush out like that?
I feel great though.
Mr. Rohan, do you really have
a sour stomach and a stiff shoulder?
Yes. I've been playing too much
with the frisbee you got for Bakin
without my knowledge.
As for the indigestion,
I blame the greasy Chinese food I had
with your bosses last night.
Wow, even you have bouts of malaise.
The antipasto is
mozzarella and tomato caprese salad.
Italians were the first to incorporate
tomatoes in their cuisine.
No one can compete
when it comes to using tomatoes in a dish.
This isn't a lousy boast.
I take pride in it.
I serve the kind of recipes that
are passed down from mother to child.
Dishes that have accompanied
the ebb and flow of Italian history.
Pride, right.
Sorry to insist after
you've poured your heart out to us,
but will you take the first bite,
right this minute, right here?
Yes, sir. My pleasure.
Well then. Enjoy.
Absolutely fantastic.
This dish…
As simple as it seems,
its flavor is rich and deep.
The cheese and tomato
complement each other perfectly.
It's a Simon and Garfunkel duo.
Tetsuya Chiba's manga
of author Ikki Kajiwara's Ashita no Joe!
Precisely so.
The flavors work in harmony
to reach new heights.
Thank you. I'm honored
you regard my dish so highly.
My shoulders…
Mr. Rohan?
What just came off?
That's your dead skin.
Dead skin?
All that peeling just means that
the increased metabolism
is improving your blood circulation.
It itches!
Mr. Rohan!
It won't stop!
You're almost there.
Mr. Rohan!
It feels light.
It's as if a balloon is
lifting up my shoulder.
The stiffness…
It's gone!
I'm ever so glad.
It's amazing, but…
also frightening.
The Primo Piatto is
spaghetti alla puttanesca.
Is something the matter?
-Tonio.
-Yes?
I've never had water and caprese
quite like yours,
but…
I'm getting full.
I think I'm ready for the check.
I don't really like spicy peppers.
Don't worry,
even people who can't handle spicy
can still enjoy my pasta.
I'm so sorry.
I understand.
I'm sorry my cooking didn't satisfy you.
Don't bother with the payment,
it's on the house.
Izumi, could you…
wait here for a minute?
Sorry.
I couldn't hold myself back.
It's good. It's too good.
I don't even like peppers.
What can I say, it's addicting.
It's like I'm drawn to it,
and my appetite gets all worked up.
The more I eat, the hungrier I get.
This must be…
your cavity.
Izumi.
-Jaw! My jaw!
-Hey!
A new tooth grew in!
Impossible.
How can this even happen?
What's happening to me?
What's this?
I know it.
They are found only by the Sea of Okhotsk
in the Kamchatka Peninsula.
Poisonous whelk.
It's highly poisonous,
and the locals don't eat it.
Its ingestion is prohibited.
It's a banned shell.
Poisonous?
Did we just ingest food made with poison?
That's what it seems like.
The water and even the caprese?
I knew it was irresistible.
Is your tooth all better now?
Tonio…
Is this some sort of
sick human experiment?
Please tell me--
you don't plan on killing us.
Now, I brought the main dish,
stewed lamb and mushroom.
These mushrooms…
Devil's porcini.
These are sourced
from the Czech-Polish border.
-Are they poisonous?
-Of course.
You're kidding!
The poison in the mushroom…
Muscarine, anatoxin, trichothecene…
It's an exhibition of poison.
Ingestion causes indigestion,
seizure, vomiting,
and in some cases…
death.
It's as you say, Mr. Rohan.
You sure are knowledgeable.
Mr. Rohan?
You can't, Mr. Rohan. Don't!
Mr. Rohan!
Mr. Rohan?
Are you okay, Mr. Rohan?
Talk to me. Are you okay?
I've never felt better.
What?
I feel full, but also--
light and refreshed all at once!
I'm glad to hear.
How the…
But, the poison…
At times,
poison acts as medicine.
Poison acts as medicine?
Nitroglycerin, the main ingredient
in bombs, is used to treat angina.
Morphine, used to make illegal drugs,
is used in anesthesia and pain relief.
In other words…
even deadly poison
can become life-saving medicine
if used correctly in the right dosage.
Tonio must be an expert
in all sorts of toxins from animals
and plants around the world.
He uses just the right amount
to heal sicknesses.
Embracing food as medicine.
He is really
a master of medicinal cuisine.
He's trained in all schools of herbology,
from Eastern medicine,
Africa's wildflowers and plants, and
the art of medicine men in the Amazons.
So you've figured out
my secret ingredient.
It didn't come all at once.
Though, I had a gut feeling
it's something like this.
The final dish was completely up to luck.
The Sicilian basil on the caprese is fake.
This herb is highly poisonous,
but when paired
with olive oil from the Rhodes,
the toxin is neutralized as one's
metabolism is drastically increased.
The chemical reaction between tetramine,
the whelk's deadly poison,
and the capsaicin in Nicaraguan peppers
form a compound with mind-blowing
antibacterial properties.
As for the main dish, by serving
devil's porcini with lamb from Normandy,
the dish releases digestive enzymes
that get rid of harmful gut bacteria.
It's the best defense against
stomach irritation.
I didn't get any of that,
but it sure sounds awesome.
Did your dog have an upset stomach too?
How did you guess?
You see, my Angelo scarfed down
too much food
and upset his tummy.
For two whole days, I fed him
the same lamb dish you're eating now.
Thanks to that,
he's back to being a happy puppy.
Tell me,
how did you know what was wrong with us?
It's all because of…
a miracle I experienced.
A miracle?
It was five years ago.
I had accidentally drank
a dangerous amount
of scorpion venom in Mexico.
I lost consciousness
and suffered from high fever.
But miraculously,
the fever suddenly subsided
after a week of bed rest.
When I woke up,
I had somehow gotten this strange ability.
Now, I can tell a person's ailments
just by examining their hands.
This ability has greatly
enhanced my cooking too.
Wow.
Strange things like that really happen.
It was what you'd call
blessings from heaven.
With this newfound ability,
I plunged myself into research
and came up with a variety of recipes.
All so that my dishes
can help people feel better…
and live a comfortable life.
Thank you. See you again.
I don't mean to stick my nose
where it doesn't belong,
but what is a talented chef like you
doing in Japan?
With your skill set,
I'm sure you'll succeed in Italy.
Why would you--
open a restaurant in a foreign country,
let alone all the way out here?
He's right.
Does it have to do with abalone?
Abalone?
How did you know?
Should you be up?
Yes. I feel a little better now.
I'm Hatsune Morishima.
I'm a patisserie,
but I'm currently on medical leave.
My disease is the reason Tonio opened
his restaurant in a place like this.
Your disease?
You must be wondering,
"Why can't you use your cooking
to heal what's wrong with her?"
Well…
There's a tumor
the size of a grapefruit inside my head.
Two years ago,
Tonio came to Japan
to study medicinal cuisine.
That was when we first met.
We found out about my tumor
shortly afterwards.
Tonio poured his knowledge,
experience, and everything he can
and made me one of his special dishes.
But it didn't work.
That's when I recalled
a strange rumor I heard
while visiting Taiwan.
It was about a mythical Japanese abalone
with the power to heal any sickness.
Then, last month,
I finally found a clue
near the fishing village in this area.
Hyogara…
Yes, I've heard of 'em.
The Hyogara black abalone.
Young man, that's what you're lookin' for?
Those precious mollusks only live
in Hyogara Rocks' southern inlet.
They are as rare as they come.
Not a single soul can access that place.
You can even call them
legendary abalone for what it's worth.
Geez!
Legendary abalone?
I pleaded with him
and told him that I have to find it,
no matter the cost.
I know. Rumor goes that
there's one day out of the year
when you have the chance
to harvest the precious thing.
On this day,
the abalone get "drunk", if you will,
and leave the Hyogara Rocks.
This story has
been passed down for centuries,
so the details are lost.
If I could just buy one, I would.
My hearing's shot.
Eatin' one of those abalone
may just take care of it.
I searched for someone who could
tell me more about the prized abalone,
but there was no one like that.
I'm content with
how hard Tonio tried to help me.
Even his cooking can't cure me,
so I've accepted that I'm fated to die.
Hatsune, you can't give up hope.
Funny enough,
I was also digging
into this abalone's legend
for a different reason.
I found this 17th-century document
at an antique bookstore.
It's a collection of food-related
legends and myths from this region.
It includes an anecdote about
the prized all-curing mollusks
and how to catch them.
What?
Is there really?
In August, on the full moon nearest
to Bon festival at the witching hour,
all the abalone lose sense of up and down
due to the moon's pull on the current
and they get "drunk."
They then wander out of the Hyogara Rocks.
It was true!
It corroborates the fisherman's story.
The next full moon is…
in two days!
Mr. Rohan, you have my thanks.
With this, I know I can cure
Hatsune's tumor.
Although…
In Japan, it's illegal to harvest
abalone without a permit.
Don't do this, Tonio.
You can't break the law for me…
Hatsune!
Are you okay, Hatsune?
Is she all right?
Yes. I gave her
some medication to stabilize.
She's fast asleep now.
Mr. Rohan,
will you go harvest abalone with me?
You seem to be an expert
on these mollusks.
Give me a break.
Did anything I said get through to you?
You're asking me to break the law.
I'll harvest the abalone.
All you have to do is take me there.
Come on now.
That's it? I'm just gonna be your guide?
I'm a manga artist
for wholesome boys and girls.
You see, I happen to be a little famous.
I've heard that abalone larvae take
five full years to reach maturity
after they are released into the ocean.
Not to mention, this variety of abalone
is especially rare and protected.
Imagine the repercussions
if we got caught.
I accept the risks.
Danger accompanies the night sea.
I've read articles that multiple people
have gone missing in that bay.
You may lose your life.
I'm going to poach.
That's why I like you.
Good.
I'll help you.
Mr. Rohan!
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
This is for my curiosity.
Hyogara Rocks lies
on the other side of that cape.
The sacred inlet where
the legendary abalone nest.
According to the ancient document,
just for tonight,
the abalone lose sense of direction
due to the full moon's effect
on the current.
They detach from the rocks
and get washed ashore here.
That means we won't have to go underwater,
and we don't need knives or other tools.
We'll catch them with our bare hands
and toss them into this basket.
This method has no risks
and we won't leave any trace.
Quite thought-out for a poaching method.
A little too thought-out.
Whether in Japan or Italy,
we can rely on our forefathers' wisdom.
Abalone are nocturnal.
They spend the day sticking to cliffsides
and feasting on seaweed such as kelp.
Once they feel threatened,
they cling onto rocks.
Hit them with a hammer or run them over
with a car, they won't crack open.
The shell has a little opening
they use for breathing
as well as releasing waste and sperm.
Its natural predator is…
Something just moved!
Something rubbed against me too.
What…
is this?
They're actually swimming.
There are so many of them.
They're swarming us!
They're huge.
It's heavy.
So this is the legendary abalone.
Tonio.
Let's grab some and go.
Tonio?
Tonio!
Tonio Trussardi!
I don't believe this.
He couldn't have drowned
in this shallow water.
This is bad.
Really bad.
Darn it.
If I don't pry it off, he'll asphyxiate!
Abalone's shell won't crack open,
even if you hit them with a hammer
or run them over with a car.
The more they feel under threat,
the stronger they cling on.
This is bad.
I have to do something. And fast!
There's no way to fight back.
I'm going to drown.
This place…
is a graveyard.
TWO MISSING
ENTERED SEA YESTERDAY MORNING
MISSING
The abalone clings
onto anyone who comes here to poach.
They drift ashore onto this island…
and get carried here.
Abalone have long been
sacred offerings for Gods
since they are said to grant longevity.
Out of all the abalone, the Hyogara Rocks'
black abalone are the most prized.
Poaching these sacred abalone
is an offense punishable by death.
It's a trap.
The poachers who read the document
are lured to this island,
where they meet their end.
It was all a trap!
This is bad.
At this rate…
At this rate, I'll…
That's it.
Don't underestimate Kishibe Rohan.
Heaven's Door.
Enjoy your plate.
Who knew octopus could be so decadent?
It's a perfect medley of sweet and sour,
along with the octopus's unique flavor.
Abalone's natural predator is…
ATTACK THE ABALONE NOW!
IMMEDIATELY!
Octopus.
Say,
how's Hatsune doing?
She's getting better.
This octopus's healing properties are
just as potent as the black abalone's.
I served her the same dish earlier.
She's sound asleep right now.
Is that so?
I'm optimistic about this time.
It devoured copious amounts
of Hyogara black abalone.
Without a doubt, this octopus
has absorbed their healing properties.
Turns out the legend of the abalone
under a full moon was just that, a legend.
It's an old tale.
From the moment I read this,
I was hung up on why the poaching method
was written in great detail
in a book meant for the general public.
The ultimate way to fend off poachers.
That's how I make sense of it.
The legend of the abalone
under a full moon itself is
a carefully laid trap
meant to finish off poachers.
A beautiful work of art that leaves
no evidence or bodies behind.
Here lies our forefathers' wisdom,
and their pride.
I've got to tell you,
I would've liked to try
these Zogara black abalone.
Try again.
-The Zogara--
-Hyogara.
-Ms. Hatsune!
-Hatsune!
Beautiful.
I baked the dessert.
Why don't we enjoy it together?
Will you, Tonio?
This is the same recipe my mama made
when I was a little boy.
Crossed tarta.
I've traveled all around the world
and tried all sorts of cuisine.
To this day, I haven't found anything
that tastes more delicious
than my mama's crossed tarta.
Tonio and I promised that
one of these days,
we'll bake his mom's
crossed tarta recipe together.
And today was that day.
It's mouth-watering.
It smells wonderful.
Now, let's dig in.
Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Thank you.
Yum!
I'm so happy for them.
What a graceful couple.
They got a happily ever after.
I'm calling it now,
people will stand in line for his dish.
I'm gonna tell all my friends about it.
Although a part of me
wants to keep it to myself too.
Oh, about that mystery horror one-off
themed around food.
It has to take place in Italy,
the country of cuisine!
It'll be perfect.
We have our
next business trip destination!
Mr. Rohan?
-Mr. Rohan?
-Don't speak.
Mutsukabe blue frogs.
They're mating.
Come again?
You're dismissed. Go.
Where?
Can't see them.
I said go.
Leave now.
Lame.
Oh well.