Mr. Rohan?
Can you hear me?
Come back!
How was it, Mr. Rohan?
Wonderful realism, isn't it?
This VR is so real, it's hard to believe
you're not actually underwater.
The manufacturer has absolute confidence
in its realism.
Not only has it attracted various media
outlets, we, as an advertisement agency
will launch a large-scale
advertisement campaign.
And this is where you come in.
Mr. Kishibe Rohan, you are very popular
among all generations.
Success is in our hands
if we have your endorsement.
That's why we visited you today.
Of course, we understand you're busy.
We have a few ideas of our own already.
For example--
Highly recommended by the Kishibe Rohan!
Rohan-approved!
Everyone from Pink Dark Boy shed tears!
They all cried!
We are very fortunate that
you showed interest in this product,
and that you were able to try it
for yourself.
We'd love to hear your honest opinion.
What did you think? No need to be polite.
It's interesting.
The picture quality is much better
than it used to be.
I'm very interested in its possibilities
for entertainment purposes.
-Mr. Rohan, how perceptive!
-But--
-I expected no less!
-But…
I was able to breathe just fine,
and I didn't die.
Well, we don't want to cause any deaths.
Is it realistic when I can breathe
and don't drown underwater?
No, no.
This device isn't for inducing fear.
It's a lighthearted way
to experience the world.
You can easily write a manga
using this device as material.
You honestly think the Kishibe Rohan
would write manga
based on such arbitrary material?
What?
No matter how bizarre the story--
no, because it's bizarre--
it needs reality at its core,
or the readers will stop reading
right away.
That's why I always aim
for the real thing.
I seek out material seriously.
But…
death,
and the pain leading up to death--
This is one realism
I haven't been able to pursue.
I don't mind experiencing death.
But if I died, how could I write about it?
So I'll read about it instead.
I can experience the writer's reality
secondhand.
Fantastic.
Thank you for your comment.
Now, excuse us.
We'll cook up a comment
and apologize later.
Hold it.
Are you trying to deceive my readers?
That's not our intention.
Excuse us.
Heaven's Door.
Let the door to your mind now open.
What is this?
What in the…
This is a talent
that I have been gifted with.
I can change a person's memories and soul
into a book for me to read.
The human body remembers everything
that has ever happened to it.
Even if a person forgets,
the body does not.
These are 100% real memories
that can't be found in any interview.
I HEAR HE'S DIFFICULT
This reality is what breathes life
into my work,
providing only the finest entertainment.
WE'LL COOK UP
HIS COMMENTS LATER!
"Use Rohan's comments as they are."
The orders I write down
can never be disobeyed.
I can only see this as a gift from heaven,
but it's not as important
as my talent that uses them
as material for manga.
ROHAN
Yes, I've been cooped up for days.
I can't believe
we aren't allowed to cover stories
in person.
SIX MONTHS LATER
JULY 7, WEDNESDAY
What?
No way.
I can't feel out the interviewee
on an online meeting.
Don't drink, Bakin.
I'll get you new water.
There.
What?
No, not "Dokin," "Bakin."
Right. Little Bakin.
I never thought you were
the kind of person to get a dog.
Did my snacks arrive?
Yeah, though Bakin didn't like them.
Really?
He might be a puppy,
but he's a picky eater.
Oh, Mr. Rohan,
can we switch to video call?
Sure.
So, about the issue
I brought up the other day…
The new character for Pink Dark Boy:
Hot Summer Martha.
I thought hard about it again.
You say my design is plagiarism.
No.
They say there's an issue
with the three-circle design.
It may lead to copyright problems
down the road.
Getting complaints may be just
an urban legend,
but there is a possibility.
If it leads to problems,
you'd get lots of hate and slander online.
-Slander…
-So, I'm telling you,
we ought to change its design.
Izumi.
You've become a bit boring.
What?
When did you learn to tread so carefully?
Listen. If there's anyone on earth
who accuses me of plagiarizing designs,
tell them this:
Three circles is a design
that ancient Celts
would have doodled
on their bathhouse walls
without batting an eye,
monkey brain!
Mr. Rohan,
we're discussing a manga character here.
Two big, round ears aren't allowed.
Not to mention its black color.
They're practically identical!
Izumi,
those circles you called ears…
they're eyes.
What?
Mr. Rohan!
-I'm crazy about you!
-Thank you. How kind.
You're in my--
You're in my yard.
You can't just walk over.
-Mr. Rohan, I'm your biggest fan.
-That's very sweet.
My babies love you too.
Thanks, but I gave them my autograph
the other day, remember?
Anyway, please don't trespass
on my property.
I got scolded…
Will do.
Mr. Rohan, how did one of your fans
get a hold of your address?
I ran into her at the vet clinic.
Wow. You have to be on guard.
I'll come over now and tell her off.
It's not that serious.
Nowadays, it can lead to serious trouble.
Let's change your locks
and install cameras.
I'll arrange it now.
I said it's fine!
Argh!
Mr. Rohan?
It's all because of this mask.
How much longer
do we have to keep this up?
Oxygen isn't getting to my brain.
Mr. Rohan, are you okay?
The recent events
have taught me that I'm the kind of man
who does his own research.
Visit the land,
touch the soil and feel the breeze,
join the crowd, and at times,
even lick rotten foods.
That's my manga.
Mr. Rohan, I understand.
Once the mandate lifts,
let's go anywhere, even overseas,
for material.
Mr. Rohan, where are you going?
Taking Bakin out on a walk.
He hasn't been himself lately.
I get he's under a lot of stress, but…
But I have to do something about this.
We're in trouble
if Pink Dark Boy gets canceled.
Oh, and order the locks.
BEWARE OF MUDSLIDE
Everything is stagnant.
The gears just don't mesh.
They don't turn well.
It's as if I'm walking through
a dark tunnel.
Am I despairing?
Maybe this is what
the others call depression.
It's as if I'm suffocating.
I can't go anywhere.
It's not that I'm refusing to move.
I'm just…
completely paralyzed.
What's wrong?
You become restless
whenever we come to this path.
Is something bothering you?
You're okay.
We'll steer clear of that path.
We'll go this way instead.
Is there something over that way?
How did we…
This shrine--
Has it always been here?
Incredible.
There was a different sacred tree
on the grounds,
but this one looks more dignified.
Is this one sacred also?
Strange.
It's cared for.
Rather,
it's sealed.
A mirror.
But why is it…
here?
Hey.
Do you feel it too, Bakin?
They're working for the first time
in a long time.
The wheels are finally turning.
What was that?
Are you okay, Bakin?
We'll set out
for a full-out research tomorrow.
Story materials are to be found outside.
That's for certain.
I HAVE NEWS!
Hot Summer Martha's first appearance
is tremendously popular.
I'll drop off your manuscript
around 3:00 p.m. today.
My manuscript?
THURSDAY, OCTOBER 7
Give me a break.
Look at this mess, Bakin.
Hold on.
I don't believe this.
Did you grow fangs already?
Of course not.
Don't cause too much trouble.
Mr. Rohan!
The latest volume of Pink Dark Boy
is selling like hotcakes!
The Hot Summer Martha arc
is a massive success.
Izumi, have you made any changes
to my manuscript?
I scanned it in.
That's not what I mean.
How did you get a hold of it--
No, who finished my manuscript?
Did you come in and grab my manuscript?
Also, this!
See that?
You had a designer do it, huh?
Well, yes.
I got a designer's help.
Is there a problem?
Yes, there's a problem!
This Hot Summer Martha design!
You changed the design to four circles!
You have no right to do this
just because of potential complaints!
Why are there four circles?
Wait a minute.
We discussed this design change.
I gave the manuscript back to you
after the printing process.
This happened…
about two weeks ago.
Are you okay, Mr. Rohan?
-Mr. Rohan?
-No!
I said no biting!
Hey, Mu-chan, stop.
What in the--
How did you get in?
Who are you?
Mr. Rohan.
What are you doing in my house?
Is that our next toy?
You're so dirty. Who will be the pitcher?
Mr. Rohan, you naughty man.
You're-- You were in my yard earlier.
What are you doing here?
-Pee time.
-What…
What on earth is going on?
This must be a dream.
"October"?
This manuscript…
I spilled ink on it today.
But the page has been completed.
The story, characters' lines, the layout…
Everything is my work,
save Hot Summer Martha's design.
I'm sure of it.
But…
I swear I didn't write this.
Then…
who did?
I borrowed your shirt.
Heaven's Door.
SEPTEMBER 23
I LOVE YOU, MR. ROHAN
SEPTEMBER 25
What in the world?
SEPTEMBER 29
Heaven's Door does not tell lies.
Meaning,
those days she spent with me are real.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH, MR. ROHAN
This can't be true.
And…
These dates…
OCTOBER 7, THURSDAY
Thank you for stopping by.
But we're closed for the day.
We open at 6:00 a.m. tomorrow.
I'm only passing through.
It's just more shrine grounds in the back.
This entire area belongs to the shrine.
I'm in a rush. Excuse me.
Is something the matter?
Is there something troubling you?
You are Kishibe Rohan, the manga artist.
Mr. Rohan, who lives nearby.
-Is something wrong?
Tell me what you know
about the big tree behind the shrine.
I believe it's sacred.
-The divine tree?
Well, to be precise, no.
But there's a shrine at its base.
It's enshrined and in good condition.
What? You don't mean you took a peek?
Or that you went inside?
-Did you?
-Go inside?
I see.
So it was yours.
Was that August? No, July?
Yes, three months ago.
You came out of the back,
passed through the shrine grounds,
and walked off like a ghost.
I watched you walking off.
Looking back, that was Yabubako-Hoshi.
It must have been.
Hold on.
I don't understand a thing.
Mr. Rohan?
Are you in trouble?
Mr. Rohan, are you…
in big trouble?
Yes, I'm in trouble!
Three months flew by,
but I don't recall any of it!
No, no.
I would not say that time has flown.
It was all done by Yabubako-Hoshi,
who lives in the tree.
What are you saying?
-Shall we go, then?
-Do you wish to go?
This tree is 800 years old.
The shrine was built about 500 years ago.
Indeed, it's been about 500 years
since our ancestors enshrined this tree.
I believe you saw the mirror inside.
An old mirror on a pedestal.
I did.
The reflection you saw of yourself
was actually Yabubako-Hoshi.
It came out the moment
you were reflected in the mirror.
It took your place.
Took my place?
That's not right.
Yabubako-Hoshi took your place
and lived as you.
According to the legend,
Yabubako-Hoshi returns to the mirror
in three moon cycles.
Three cycles of the moon, or three months.
It was a blink of an eye for me.
Time is not constant.
There's no difference between
a split second and three months.
Just like the tale of Rip Van Winkle…
Who turned into an old man
at the end of the story.
But…
I can't accept this.
This makes no sense.
We may look the same, but he isn't me.
But he is you, Mr. Rohan.
Yabubako-Hoshi reflects
the yin to the yang.
He is your shadow.
Yin and yang.
They are the two sides of the same coin.
You did whatever you wanted
for the last three months.
That's what this means.
But in reality,
it messes up most people's lives,
just like yours.
This is why our ancestors blocked
the entrance and sealed the shrine.
I see.
I've stepped into a sacred territory
no one is allowed to enter.
I see what I've done.
I am…
truly sorry.
Now,
tell me how to undo this mess.
Undo this mess?
By "undo," do you mean
you want to go back in time,
from October to July?
You want to travel back in time?
That's right.
Yes, that's exactly it.
Yabubako-Hoshi is ruining my life!
Mr. Rohan.
The line between good and evil
is very blurry.
What is considered good, and what is evil?
It all depends on how you see it.
Yabubako-Hoshi is your shadow.
It may have relieved some of your stress.
What if you think of it as a dream
and embrace the yin and yang?
Good and evil.
Listen closely.
That was never my issue to begin with.
Four circles!
Something I didn't draw is circulating
under my name.
This is unforgivable.
That's the only thing I can't tolerate.
I couldn't care less about
the good and evil of society.
Is there a way to undo this or not?
Hurry up and tell me.
It's impossible to rewind the clock
back to July.
You cannot travel back in time to July.
I told you, didn't I?
Let's just cut this tree down.
Father, the head priest
ought not say such things.
What brought you here in the first place?
There's an intersection I usually walk by.
But on that day, I took a turn.
You need to proceed with caution.
Since ancient times,
it's dangerous when roads cross like this.
A little chance is all it takes
to run into those not of this world.
For example, a Tsujigami yokai.
It may be revered as a god, but Tsujigami
brings bad luck to intersections.
It has always been bad--
the four-way crossroad.
No use crying about it now.
From what you told us,
it's not so much about the time you lost,
it's about your manga, correct?
That's right.
Then we know of one way.
The enshrined mirror.
Rotate the mirror so that your reflection
does not cast upon it.
The mirror sits on a pedestal,
so I suggest you rotate the entire thing.
Rotate it 360 degrees to the left…
three times.
All of Yabubako-Hoshi's actions
will be undone.
Undone?
That means--
You won't get back the lost months.
Only the results of Yabubako-Hoshi's
actions will be severed from this world.
The actions will be sealed.
Yabubako-Hoshi's actions will disappear
if you rotate the mirror
counterclockwise three times.
But why…
three times?
We don't know.
But so it is conveyed.
Throughout the world, the number three
is considered a lucky
and harmonious number.
It's a balanced number,
known for stability.
Three is a good number.
Three.
Not four.
You mustn't forget.
Do not cast your reflection
onto the mirror.
Enter the shrine from behind.
Make three counterclockwise turns
with the mirror
and watch that Yabubako-Hoshi
does not see you.
This will undo everything it did.
-The caller is unable to answer…
-Strange.
Lately, Mr. Rohan hasn't been
answering my calls at all.
The Hot Summer Martha
figurine sample is ready.
I'll bring it to you now.
Is it…
finally over?
Good evening. It's me, Izumi.
Oh, right.
Mr. Rohan?
Your entrance is a complete mess!
Are you here?
Fantastic.
Still,
something feels a bit off.
Izumi installed this.
When did she get it done?
Bakin?
It's okay.
Bakin!
That mirror…
I rotated it three times
without casting my reflection!
But…
It's happening again.
FRIDAY, JANUARY 7
How?
Three months have passed!
Did I fail?
My image was reflected on something else,
which was then reflected onto the mirror.
JANUARY 7, FRIDAY
This can't be happening.
It's now a figurine!
Four circles…
Mr. Rohan.
Catch!
Is he Yabubako-Hoshi,
the one that took my place?
Izumi…
Are you all right?
Get a hold of yourself!
This is bad.
How…
You injected something…
No, someone else did this.
Who did this to you?
Was it…
me?
Mr. Rohan?
Tell me, Mr. Rohan.
This woman--
somehow she got a hold
of a spare key to the house.
How did she get it?
Hey.
Stop!
This sly thief
sticks her neck
in other people's business.
She sat at your work desk
like she owned the place.
She put her fingerprints
all over the beautiful
Hot Summer Martha figurine
without disinfecting or wearing a mask!
Why?
Tell me, Mr. Rohan.
What gives her the right to do
whatever she wants in this room?
Izumi…
She has nothing to do with this.
We need…
to call the ambulance right this minute.
She's already…
Mr. Rohan, there's no way
I'm raising this baby by myself.
It can't be true!
Okay?
No…
I'm going to be with you for ten years,
20 years, 50 years,
and forever and ever.
Nope.
Three more minutes.
Or will it be five more minutes
before she dies?
We've got a few minutes to kill.
I know.
Your magical talent.
Wanna try it?
You know, I have an idea what it does.
I know you can read people's minds,
Mr. Rohan.
You do this motion…
with your hand.
I've had a near-death experience before.
I was in a car accident.
Hypnosis?
Mind reading?
Hey. Do you want to read my mind?
It's full of love and adulation for you.
I love you.
Never mind.
Not very fair only you get to read
other people's minds, is it?
I love you.
Please.
She only stopped by…
for… work.
Please.
Let her live.
Why should I?
Mr. Rohan,
I'm the only one you need.
That's why you loved me.
Isn't that right?
No.
We're going to sit here until she's dead.
You and I,
we'll be accomplices.
And we'll spend the rest of our lives
sharing our little secret together.
I love you.
Our baby,
you…
and me.
It'll just be our happy little family.
Okay?
Do you… see this?
This is…
my gift.
I call it Heaven's Door.
There's only…
truth…
written…
on here.
Aren't you curious?
Don't you want to confirm my love for you…
or the lack of it?
Know whether I've betrayed you…
or… trust you?
You just might
learn…
the truth for yourself.
But promise me…
that once you're done…
you obey my orders.
Turn Yabubako-Hoshi's mirror
counterclockwise three times.
This will undo…
all of Yabubako-Hoshi's actions.
I don't know
what kind of a shadow she released.
Even so,
it was my responsibility to see
that she didn't cause any trouble.
DON'T COMMIT ANY CRIMES - I WILL
KILL ANYONE WHO GETS IN MY WAY
Though he was…
just a shadow,
that Yabubako-Hoshi…
He is my dark side.
Why am I sleeping here?
Sorry, Mr. Rohan. Looks like I dozed off.
Oh, no. I have submissions today.
Mr. Rohan, I'm leaving your sample here.
Don't forget to check it out.
I'll be off.
Bakin!
Let's go to the dog park
with my Maron sometime.
See you.
Four circles…
It didn't change.
Hot Summer Martha's design…
had nothing to do with Yabubako-Hoshi?
This means…
Izumi Kyoka…
That woman…
Hurry up and show me!
-Hurry up!
-Yeah, hurry it up!
What a sick enemy!
Hot Summer Martha!
There's no way it can be defeated.
There!
It's awesome!
Let me read the next page!
-Hurry up!
-Turn the page!
Hurry!