The new character for Pink Dark Boy:
Hot Summer Martha.
They say there's an issue
with the three-circle design.
This Hot Summer Martha design!
You changed the design to four circles!
Why are there four circles?
It was all done by Yabubako-Hoshi,
who lives in the tree.
It came out the moment
you were reflected in the mirror.
It took your place.
Yabubako-Hoshi took your place
and lived as you.
Make three counterclockwise turns
with the mirror.
This will undo everything it did.
Four circles?
It didn't change.
Hot Summer Martha's design
had nothing to do with Yabubako-Hoshi?
Izumi Kyoka…
that woman…
Are you… Mr. Kishibe Rohan's editor?
Yes?
At the café…
You always have the Pink Dark Boy meetings
at the café down the hill, right?
Thanks for reading it.
Sorry. I can't get his autograph now.
I'm on my way to work.
Why does Hot Summer Martha have
four circles instead of three?
Because it looks stronger, I guess.
Bye.
You're still here?
I've already submitted
this week's manuscript,
and the meeting for the one-shot
is tomorrow.
Mr. Rohan, are you still mad
about Hot Summer Martha?
You told me it was okay
to leave it up to the designer.
No.
It's not your fault, Izumi.
I thought it was weird when you said okay
after being so against it.
Back then, you were acting differently,
and we couldn't meet due to remote work.
Thinking about it now,
I should've talked to you in person
about it.
Why don't you create a new character
with three circles?
Hot Summer Martha's brother,
Hot Summer Brother!
As long as the color isn't black,
the team might approve it.
Izumi.
Oh, yeah. Earlier…
I want to speak with Kishibe Rohan.
Sorry, but this is where I work.
I don't like surprise visits.
Why doesn't Hot Summer Martha
have three circles?
You're that kid!
PINK DARK BOY 95
Aren't these eyes?
Considering Hot Summer Martha's
abilities and body,
I can't find a reason for having
another eye here.
In other words, it's not necessary.
And there's no beauty
in having four circles.
Look at it. Doesn't it look messy?
Having three makes it
simple and beautiful.
Hot Summer Martha would've been perfect
with three circles.
Make it three.
It's still not too late.
Everything works if it was three.
It should be three. Three.
Thanks for your thoughts.
I'll take it into consideration.
Mr. Rohan,
you should install a security camera.
Huh? Wasn't there one before?
He must have followed you.
But what a strange kid.
So opinionated and logical.
What he said was… right.
I guess.
He has to be a huge fan of mine.
He's read Pink Dark Boy multiple times.
If he didn't perfectly understand
my preferences and style,
he couldn't have analyzed it like that.
But is three such a perfect number?
Which one is more stable?
Huh?
Well, out of the two, the triangle.
The center of gravity looks more stable.
Exactly.
Three is the simplest and most stable.
It's a special number
that has symbolized harmony and strength
since ancient times.
Amaterasu bestowed
the Three Sacred Treasures.
Christianity has the Trinity.
There's also "The third time's the charm."
Anyway,
he understands my original intentions.
Mr. Rohan, why don't you reconsider having
a Hot Summer Martha with three circles?
You think it's that easy to change
what I've already approved and published?
That's why you should make it her brother.
What about a sister?
With cute colors like pink and yellow.
Enough!
-Put it down.
-Yes.
-Open it.
What's in here?
-Isn't it cute?
-Go do your job.
Geez!
But it looks like he's back to himself.
The meeting for the one-shot is tomorrow!
Three is perfect.
Three is perfection.
Kishibe Rohan.
I won't forgive you.
Ever.
DANGER
It should be three.
Three, three, three--
Three.
Rock.
Scissors.
Paper.
It's perfect.
Mr. Rohan, let's play rock paper scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors.
The three moves makes it the perfect duel.
Rock, paper…
Hold wrists at a perfect 90-degree angle.
Keep all fingers straight and unbent.
Place palms forward.
While maintaining wrist placement,
bend each finger, one at a time.
One, two,
three, four, five.
And now open them again, one at a time.
Look at the time already.
Hey, taxi!
Hey, you!
Why are you cutting in?
What? Are you half asleep?
I'm the one who got the taxi.
What did you say?
Got a problem with that?
Then…
let's decide who'll take this taxi…
with rock paper scissors.
Rock paper scissors!
You lose if you're too slow.
Ready? Rock, paper--
Heaven's Door.
Sorry. Can you wait about 30 seconds?
There's something strange about this kid.
"Oyanagi Ken.
Eleven years old. Sixth grade.
Likes math and writing.
Enjoys pointing out his teacher's math
and spelling mistakes.
Favorite manga: Pink Dark Boy.
Has all the volumes.
Considers volumes 28 and 40
as masterpieces.
Has read them at least 20 times.
Dislikes bell peppers and red bean buns.
Favorite food: fatty meat.
Has never pooped at school."
Well, he's a little pushy,
but naive like a kid.
Was it my imagination?
I don't see any problems.
"Likes rock paper scissors.
Has strong urges to play
rock paper scissors.
Starts the game with scissors."
This kid
really just wants to play
rock paper scissors.
Let's start.
You lose instantly if you're too slow.
If we tie, we play until someone wins.
-Are you ready?
-Yeah, let's do it.
I just need to play, right?
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Satisfied? See ya.
I lost.
Huh?
What are you doing? That's my seat.
What? Your seat?
You haven't sat down yet.
Besides, have you ordered?
No, you haven't.
Which means this isn't your seat.
-It's mine.
-What's with you?
You've been getting in my way.
Didn't I say I'd consider your opinions?
Let's decide whose seat this is
with rock paper scissors.
Rock paper scissors.
Welcome. Excuse me.
-Orange juice.
-All right.
Sir, we don't have any tables available.
Wait a minute.
I'm the one who got his seat taken.
He's the one in the wrong.
No!
-I sat here first!
-This kid!
-This is my seat!
-Can't you just give him your seat?
He's just a child.
Aren't you acting childish?
Shut up!
You've got me mad now.
Fine. I'll play rock paper scissors.
I just have to play, right?
Rock paper scissors!
That's more like it.
You lose if you're too slow.
If we tie, we play till there's a winner.
-I know. Stop repeating it.
-Here we go!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Yes! I won, I won! Take that!
This is the first time I'm this happy
to win rock paper scissors.
Now get out of the way, kid.
Mr. Rohan…
You think I'm acting childish?
Everyone?
Nope!
It's the best feeling to beat a kid.
Cancel the orange juice. Make it iced tea.
Izumi, let's start the meeting.
I found my inspiration just now.
What?
Leave.
Leave!
Mr. Rohan, you're really tough on kids.
He's only in elementary school!
You never know how and when
rumors will spread in this age.
You'll be in trouble if
"popular manga artist makes children cry"
spreads all over the Internet.
I don't believe kids are pure
and innocent.
They are the embodiment of evil
and think they'll be forgiven
just because they're kids.
That part of you is really stubborn.
Isn't that kid a fan of yours?
Well, he is a weird kid.
You…
Our meeting is done.
Why don't you go home?
You've got other manga artists to see.
-But--
-Rock, paper, scissors.
You played paper. It's my win. Bye.
Geez.
BOTANICAL ENCYCLOPEDIA
These plant illustrations can be used
as reference material.
This bookstore isn't bad.
7,500 yen.
Did I bring enough?
Excuse me. I'd like to buy this book!
Stop. You!
Should we decide with rock paper scissors?
Fine.
You lose if you're slow.
If it's a tie, we keep playing, right?
Here I go.
-Rock, paper, scissors!
-Rock!
Quit messing around.
Don't come near me again!
I won.
Look! It's paper.
I finally won!
This makes one win, two losses.
What's with this kid?
What's going on?
This is…
Does he…
have the same kind of gift I do?
But why?
This is amazing!
I feel a beautiful and amazing power
pouring into me.
This is bad.
I'm getting more and more powerful!
Heaven's Door.
Why…
does this kid have such power?
"I can't attack Kishibe Rohan."
"I got Pink Dark Boy volume 95
after waiting in line since morning.
So lucky.
So excited for the first appearance of
the strongest enemy, Hot Summer Martha.
It finally appears!"
What's this?
"Something's wrong.
Did Kishibe Rohan really draw
this character?
I can't believe this.
Four circles isn't beautiful at all.
It would've been perfect if it was three.
It took all my courage
to ask him directly,
but he just turned me away.
I had so much respect for him,
but this is the end for Kishibe Rohan.
What a disappointment.
Kishibe Rohan has no right
to draw Pink Dark Boy."
"Three.
The perfect number. Three.
Rock. Scissors. Paper.
I want to play rock paper scissors
with Kishibe Rohan.
I really want to.
I'll beat Rohan with rock scissors paper
and make him unable to draw manga."
I'll never forgive you for drawing
such a character.
You should never draw manga again.
That's why I'm going to win.
I'll beat you with rock scissors paper.
Rock scissors paper…
Rock paper scissors
isn't a game of chance.
It's about your will to win.
Winning rock paper scissors is
winning with the power of your heart!
If I defeat you at rock paper scissors,
it means my spirit is stronger than yours.
What… are you talking about?
I will overcome you.
I CAN'T ATTACK KISHIBE ROHAN
I CAN ATTACK KISHIBE ROHAN
He changed Heaven's Door.
First to win three duels wins.
So if I win two more times,
all your powers will be mine.
Then…
you will never draw manga.
This…
little brat!
A third of your power is now mine.
That won't work on me anymore.
What exactly is…
An X.
"Ten" in Chinese writing.
Don't tell me that's…
You need to proceed with caution.
Since ancient times,
it's dangerous when roads cross like this.
It has always been bad--
the four-way crossroad.
Tsujigami.
Mr. Rohan.
Looks like if I don't play
rock paper scissors,
you'll do whatever you want with me.
You finally understand.
Fine.
I'll play rock scissors paper.
Good!
Good?
What are you laughing at?
I just…
wonder if you understand your situation.
You're the one with one win, two losses.
You can't afford to lose again.
Do you understand
you're standing on the edge?
If you lose the next match,
it's over for you.
Of course I know that.
But I will still overcome you.
All right. Do your best.
But I'll say it again:
I have the luxury of two more chances.
The one standing on the cliff is you.
Are you putting pressure on me?
Maybe.
Now, shall we play?
No, not yet.
Actually, I'm thinking about
what move to make.
Didn't I just win with paper?
It's human nature
to want to use something else,
but maybe that's a childish strategy.
But it doesn't look like
you have a naive personality,
so I was thinking it's also a good idea
to be sly and play paper twice in a row.
Okay, I've decided.
Let's go!
Rock, scissors, paper, shoot!
What?
I did it! I won with paper!
I beat your spirit once again!
With this, it's now two wins, two losses!
Looks like you can't stand up.
Should we take a break?
No.
There's no need.
When I win…
I should be looking…
down at you like this as you lose.
That's good.
We're now even,
with two wins and two losses.
That means you and I are both
standing on the edge.
But, you know, Mr. Rohan,
it doesn't feel like I'll lose at all.
You see, think about it.
Even if we both have two wins and losses,
I've won twice in a row after two losses.
It's the opposite for you.
You've lost twice in a row.
You are now…
in a slump in this duel.
Mr. Rohan.
I'll say it again.
You're now…
in a slump!
You've gotten better…
at pressuring your opponent.
No.
It's the truth.
It's true that you've lost twice in a row.
That's just the truth.
But if you're saying that,
I'll tell you another truth.
In the next round…
you won't be able to…
use paper.
Well, I wonder.
Come on.
Hey, now. Wait a minute.
You just said I was in a slump.
I've used rock twice and lost.
Rock is now an unlucky move to me.
Am I wrong?
Do you think I'll use the unlucky rock
in this important, last round?
Use the unlucky rock three times in a row?
Since you said I was in a slump,
you can't use paper.
Because if you did,
then you'll be admitting
that I'm not in a slump.
I'll stick with it.
No, you won't.
Let's go, Kishibe Rohan.
Rock paper scissors…
shoot!
What?
It's a tie.
After all that I said,
he still has the guts to use paper!
What strong spirit!
I won't lose.
I'm on a winning streak.
Not good. I can't predict what he'll do.
I'll use paper again.
Four in a row! I'll stick with paper!
Argh! Use my instincts. Rock!
I'll make the unlucky rock lucky.
Paper!
There's only rock!
Let's go! Shoot!
My knee's losing strength.
What? He's moving differently.
He's going to use scissors!
I can't go with paper!
Looks like
this is no longer my unlucky rock.
The one losing his luck…
Kid!
Don't you think…
it's you?
Hey, Miss!
Hey, Mr. Rohan. Let's test our luck.
Since she knows you,
she should come if we call her.
But if luck is still on my side,
she won't come over.
What?
Hey, Miss!
Come play rock paper scissors
with me and Mr. Rohan!
Why are you--
You should call her over too.
Those two are still together!
Come quickly!
Let's play rock paper scissors!
Rock paper scissors?
Are they still fighting?
Mr. Rohan is really so childish.
But I can't be doing this.
I have to pick up Mr. Jugo's manuscript.
Sorry!
Be nice to him, Mr. Rohan!
And you should go home soon!
Yes!
Looks like my luck is still better.
I'd be invincible
even at Russian roulette
with five bullets in six chambers.
Look! Even if I do this!
Now, let's have our final round.
What are you doing?
Let's get started already.
I've already started.
Just like this.
I'll be using this.
-What do you mean?
-It's exactly what you see.
I've already decided.
This is what I'll use.
It's you who needs to start.
Stop joking.
This isn't a joke.
You've got luck that will help you win.
Hurry up and choose your winning move,
so we can duel.
You'll change to rock at the last second.
All your plans are useless.
I'll tell you one thing.
You said you'll overcome me,
but I've lived longer,
so I'll give you some advice:
Beating someone isn't hard.
It's harder to--
You ready?
It's harder to…
overcome yourself.
I will overcome my own luck.
No matter what you say,
I will not be losing.
Let's go! Let's play!
Rock, scissors, paper…
shoot!
But I should've played scissors.
With this, I have three wins, two losses.
Your rock is the unlucky rock.
Why?
You hate this Hot Summer Martha.
You have a strong hatred
for the four-circle design.
When you see it,
you always turn red,
clenching your right fist.
In other words, when you get angry…
you unconsciously make a fist.
Don't look down on a manga artist's
power of observation.
You relied only on your luck.
I changed my luck with my own strength.
That's what it means to overcome yourself.
Shut up!
That was a battle of words!
You won by cheating!
You coward!
Let's play another round!
Sure.
I'll play.
All right!
I'll overcome you!
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Shoot! Shoot!
I can't win.
Not yet.
Not yet!
I haven't lost yet!
My spirit will not lose to you!
I'll win.
I'll definitely win!
I won't lose!
Rock, paper…
Wow! I like you, kid!
I have a weakness for drama
and courage like yours.
I lost.
I've been utterly defeated.
SHISHI JUGO
Mr. Jugo!
He's not in! Again!
And he tells me to come on time!
He's too carefree!
Aren't you a smart boy?
Lately, you only visit
when it's time to walk Bakin.
That's not true. It's just a coincidence.
Right, little Bakin?
Oh, sure. I believe you.
Oh, Mr. Rohan, was everything okay
with the rock-paper-scissors boy?
He seemed very stubborn.
Yes. No problem.
That's good.
Did you give him something? An autograph?
Kind of.
Good boy!
That was really…
due to the Tsujigami?
A demon that lives in a four-way
intersection and plays tricks on humans.
It should have been sealed,
but if something caused it to appear
and resonated with the strong emotions
of a human
and played a prank
that amplified those emotions…
Have you heard of
tsuji-ura street fortune-telling?
Tsuji-ura fortune?
Not backstreet?
Tsuji-ura is an ancient Japanese form
of fortune-telling.
A four-way intersection is also
an intersection with the spirit world.
So conversations from people walking by
have a strange power.
For example, when you want to know
your love fortune
and you hear "My shoelaces are undone,"
your love life isn't good.
If you hear "There's gum on my shoe,"
your love life will be good.
Wow.
But it sounds like a stretch.
It relies too much on coincidences.
Most fortune-telling is
deciphering coincidences.
It's bad luck
if a black cat crosses your path
and good if the tea stalk is
floating upright.
That is true.
But where is that special intersection?
It doesn't have to a particular one.
Then let's tell our fortunes here!
I want to travel overseas.
Impossible! That's impossible!
Why? You promised!
Going to a haunted house!
Never!
Why not?
Didn't you say it wasn't scary?
Let's go.
Even so, Japanese people
came up with a lot of things.
It's not just Japan.
Strange and mysterious things are found
all over the world.
The stories of the curse of King Tut
and the ghosts of London Tower
are still talked about today.
There's an association of vampires
in Italy
with 2,000 registered vampires.
There could be something hiding
behind the things we take for granted.
There are stories all over the world.
All over? Sounds good.
Let's go abroad for the next one.
It's been so long since I visited Taiwan
or Hong Kong.
Bangkok is good too.
Kuala Lumpur is also--
Mr. Rohan!
The new chapters will be
about intersections.
I want to start on it right away,
so please leave.
Geez!
It's good he's feeling better now.
Hold wrists at a perfect 90-degree angle.
Keep all fingers straight and unbent.
Place palms forward.
While maintaining wrist placement,
bend each finger, one at a time.
One, two, three, four, five.
And now open them again, one at a time.
One, two, three, four…
Stories are found all over the world.
Paris!
The Louvre Museum.