Sorry.
What are you doing?
Is this your first day or something?
Sorry. I'm new here.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Rena-san. Rena-san.
We're out of damp towels. Are you all right?
Whoa, whoa. Are you okay?
You're soaking wet.
Sorry. Excuse me.
Hey, wait.
That guy's a regular,
but he loves new people.
Rena, are you okay?
I'm totally fine. I'm just
struggling to get used to it.
You can take it one step
at a time. Take it slow.
The cast are our treasure. Our idols.
Oh, right. Apparently Imai-san is
a hardcore idol fan, despite how he seems.
The other day, he even went to a photo event.
Wow, you must really love Mystery Kiss.
Well, yeah. Actually...
I'm a huge Rui-tan fan.
Wow.
I've been a fan longer than anyone else.
Really?
Rena-san. Rena-san.
Someone's asking for you.
What?
Already, huh? You gotta get more fans.
Okay.
You've got this.
I'll do my best.
Go get 'em.
What?
I'm not cut out for this.
If you know that, then
what are you doing there?
Why? I got a job right away.
I thought you were looking for your junior.
I am. A huge Mystery Kiss fan works there.
I thought I could get some
information out of him.
Besides, I have to pay all my own expenses.
I guess so.
If you don't like it, then stop helping me.
But if you do, then leave me alone.
Why would you say something
so extreme and sad?
Because the police, the yakuza, our boss,
and a big-name entertainer
are involved in this mess.
What do you expect?
Are you worried about my safety?
If you're not careful, you could end up dead.
It's not even your job anymore.
It's not like I can quit now, either.
Anyway, I can't believe
he fired you out of nowhere.
The boss is probably in a tight spot, too.
That's why he set me free.
Anyway, are you doing okay at work?
I'm fine for now.
Actually, I just blew half
my first paycheck on that.
That place is way too expensive.
Then you can pay me the other half directly.
I'll go get you a refill.
Hey, wait.
Anyway, I tried coming up with a theory.
You don't need to try so hard
to act like a detective.
Just listen.
On October 4th, the day
Mitsuya-san went missing,
she definitely got into Odokawa's taxi.
That taxi headed to Harada Building 3.
So you still only know where
she was until the convenience store—
Anyway, Mystery Kiss' agency
is inside that building.
The building is currently
owned by the yakuza.
Based on these facts, I think
these three groups are suspicious.
The question is, which of them found
Yuki's existence a nuisance, and why.
Yes. What did Mitsuya-san witness
and learn that day?
If we still haven't found
any evidence, that means
we're not dealing with a crime of passion
or repeat offender, but a premeditated crime.
Someone with a grudge against
Yuki herself or Donraku-san,
or someone involved with the criminal
organization the boss met with.
You think it's Odokawa?
What? Have you been listening?
That doesn't make sense.
I think we can limit ourselves to either
the agency or the criminal organization.
We should look into Odokawa more.
Sounds like you want it to be Odokawa.
Are you sure Dobu didn't do anything to you?
No? I mean, Odokawa's suspicious, right?
Why did Rena-san join this agency?
Oh, you haven't heard?
Well, she doesn't talk about herself much.
Despite how she seems,
she's actually been through a lot.
She's probably reluctant to open up about it.
True.
She's quick-witted. I bet she
studied really hard in school.
She must've been way above average.
She dropped out of high school.
What? Why?
Ask her yourself.
Oh, come on. Don't tease me
with partial information.
Oh, right. You wanna try
getting someone together?
What does that mean?
You really don't listen, do you?
I told you about it when you started.
I'm talking about romantic engineering.
Getting people to meet
or couples back together.
Making couples break up, reuniting them.
All as if it's a coincidence.
Romantic engineering?
That's something we do?
A long time ago, I once helped a big name
entertainer get together with someone.
That's kind of scary, like you're
manipulating people's lives.
In our world, every encounter
and parting of ways is inevitable.
Someone might be controlling you, too.
Come on. Let's go.
You almost had me for a second there.
Imai-san, good morning!
Good morning.
You're looking handsome again today!
Thanks. You're looking cute, too!
Let's do this, huh? Let's do this.
Hello.
So, how was your trial
employment experience?
Feel like continuing to work here?
Honestly, it's not often that we get
people who could start right away.
Personally, I think it'd be
great if you could stay.
Maybe if you told us about
the billion yen you won.
What? Kanon-chan, how
do you know about that?
Imai-san.
Everyone knows.
Imai-san, I'm looking forward
to another day with you.
Same.
Don't you think it was risky
to post about it online?
People figured out where you work.
Is that why everyone's
been so nice to me recently?!
Wait, is that why you guys
started working here? For the cash?
What are you going to spend the money on?
I'm going to invest all of it
into Mystery Kiss.
What? All of it?!
I wonder if Rui-tan saw
my post. It went viral.
One of the other members
liked my post. Ichi-something...
Ichimura?
Yeah. I just want Rui-tan to notice me.
I'm just a regular guy,
but I thought I finally had
a chance to get her attention.
Morning, Imai-san.
Looking forward to another day.
Same.
Why did you win?
Why? Is there a reason other than luck?
Wow!
You're meant for the entertainment business.
But maybe it wasn't just luck.
The driver of the taxi
I happened to get in that day—
Don't you want to see the person
who made you lucky?
Hold on.
You're scaring me, Rena-chan.
How do you know how to find him?
This girl is amazing. She's a detective.
And we're childhood friends.
She left the boonies in Saitama
and went right to being a detective.
Kanon, careful what you say.
What's the problem? Imai-kun
doesn't seem like a bad guy.
Imai-kun, you say?
Wait, hold on. A detective?
Are you investigating me?
Oh, no. But I do know about that taxi driver.
His name is Odokawa.
I've been wanting to thank him,
but I took that taxi on a whim,
so I'd given up on the idea.
I know how you can see him.
But in exchange, could you
tell me about Mystery Kiss?
Of course! Ask me anything.
So, how can I see that Odokawa-san again?
Rena-san, hello.
Sato, can you check the computer for me?
Yes.
Where is Odokawa's taxi now?
Around this time, he's either driving
around the intersection at 3-chome
or waiting for passengers
around the Sansan Building.
Oh, yup. He's in front of the Sansan Building.
Got it.
Wait. Where are you right now, Rena-san?
Hello? Huh?
Apparently Imai-kun has been watching
Mystery Kiss since their first concert.
Yeah. It's fate. I just happened
to attend their concert.
I think it was a year ago.
Rui-tan was already
on another level back then.
Huh.
There were five of us
in the audience, and Rui-tan...
So, what was Mitsuya Yuki like?
She was especially good at dancing.
She seemed athletic.
Rui-tan's good at dancing,
and she's a good singer, too—
Do you have any video or
photos of her from back then?
Oh, I wanna see!
I sure do.
She's so cute!
Cute!
Yeah, super cute.
Look at this one. Ah, she's so cute!
Next, next, next.
This one is so cute.
Hey, you take too many pictures!
Where's Mitsuya Yuki?
Oh, I've only ever taken
Polaroids with Rui-tan.
Do you know any Mitsuya Yuki fans?
I'm clearly the only one who's
been following them forever,
and they only recently started
getting media attention
because they're making their major debut.
I doubt there's any photos of her.
Is that even possible?
There must at least be selfies or something.
Oh, right. Come to think of it,
they did a stream.
The members chatted
and answered fan questions.
Starting around 9 PM, Rui-tan—
Then has Mitsuya Yuki been
acting strange recently?
I have no idea.
Aside from Rui-tan, I feel like their
dancing's not as good as it used to be.
I mean, I can see why
they'd feel discouraged.
They have to wear masks
when they're finally debuting.
Right?
Is it possible Mitsuya Yuki
was replaced at some point?
Honestly, I really only
pay attention to Rui-tan.
Too much attention.
Oh, right. There's
an open audition coming up.
Mystery Kiss will be attending as guests.
Really? We should audition.
Why would we do that?
It's kind of frustrating, don't you think?
I'm definitely cuter than them.
I'd support you. You'd
totally make it to the final.
Right?
Yeah.
You're really here.
Hey, you're the idol fan.
Mystery Kiss.
You remember me?!
More importantly,
I'm glad I got to see you again.
Why?
I wanted to thank you.
What did I do?
I actually won the lottery using
those numbers you gave me.
Really? That's amazing.
That's not much of a reaction!
I mean, I picked those numbers at random.
You just haven't heard how much I won.
I won one billion yen!
Really?
Really!
I haven't claimed my winnings yet,
but I've checked it about a hundred times.
If that's true, you shouldn't
be spreading that around.
It's my first time telling
someone in real life.
I had to tell you.
What do you mean, in real life?
I told people online, but that's online.
I had to tell someone.
Now you can buy Mystery Kiss CDs.
That's right. I've been keeping
my winning ticket on me
so I can claim my winnings right
when their CD comes out.
You'd better not lose that.
Anyway, Odokawa-sama,
I wanted to thank you.
You don't need to do that.
No, no way! I've gotta do something!
Isn't there anything you need money for?
Not particularly.
Then, maybe your family or someone
you care about is in trouble?
Nope.
Do you just not feel desire?!
In that case, Odokawa-sama,
are you free right now?
As you can see, I'm right
in the middle of work.
I'll pay you whatever you'd make today.
Come with me.
Nice to meet you.
This is VIP Odokawa-sama.
Everything is already paid for,
so order whatever you'd like.
Really? Wow.
So cool!
Odokawa-san, what would you like to drink?
Actually, I've got to drive...
Is it okay if we drink?
Uh...
Sure, go ahead.
All right! Can we get
something bubbly, then?
Yeah, sure.
Yay!
Have you ever driven any famous people?
That's personal information.
I can't share that.
Aw, you're no fun.
What about girls our age?
Do you drive them a lot?
No, rarely.
I do frequently get requests for pick ups
and drop offs in this area, though.
Do you remember all your passengers?
I can't tell them apart.
Girls your age all look the same to me.
What? But we're totally different.
What?
I've never given you a ride, have I?
Ah, well, I work nights around here.
I might've gotten a ride
with you before. Why?
Rabbits aren't uncommon,
but you're a Polish rabbit.
What are you talking about, Odo-chan?
Are you the type of guy who
uses avant-garde pickup lines?
No, sorry. I don't belong here.
What about this girl?
A black cat.
What? No, I mean, have you
given her a ride before?
You, too?
She's my friend.
Sorry to ask out of nowhere.
No. I gave a black cat a ride,
but it wasn't her.
So, uh, why don't we have a toast?
If you've got something to say, then say it.
I looked into Rena-san's background.
She's in the company's database.
Hey, don't use that for personal matters.
I thoughtlessly looked out of pure
curiosity, and now I regret it.
That database gets used
for all kinds of credit checks.
People with criminal records,
people who have caused accidents.
Anyone who's experienced
twists and turns in life.
Those kinds of people
are more likely to end up on it.
Her parents died when she was young.
She went through a lot as a kid.
I wouldn't call it the silver lining,
but she was too young to remember.
She grew up in orphanages after that.
Is that why she became a detective?
No, she was just looking
for someplace to work.
Someone introduced her to me.
Don't worry. I'm also happy to hire people
like you who casually get into the business.
Is that right?
Since starting this job, I've learned
the world can be pretty unfair.
Rena said the same thing.
She said that made her glad
she became a private eye.
Despite how she seems,
she's got a strong sense of justice.
That's exactly how she seems.
Kakihana-san.
We know you're in there, Kakihana-san.
Hey, Kakihana. You need to
pay back what you borrowed.
Didn't your parents teach you that?!
He's not here.
Let's go.
Sorry, I know you're busy with work.
I'll wait forever, so don't
strain yourself.
Sorry, I just finished. Where are you?
Yeah.
What the hell did you do to our girl?
No, wait. This is a misunderstanding.
I promise I'll pay off my debt soon.
Debt? Misunderstanding?
What are you talking about?
Did you think you could screw around
with her and get away with it?
You've got it all wrong.
Shiho-chan and I have
a serious platonic relationship.
She's a girl with a future.
I think you owe us compensation for damages.
You make twenty million a year, don't you?
N-No, I boosted my numbers a bit.
Don't lie to me.
That's a pretty nice suit you're wearing.
I took out a loan to buy this.
What? Loan this, debt that.
I thought you were rich.
I'm in the cleaning business.
The cleaning business? So what?
Don't use your job as an excuse!
I'm sorry!
Your profile is full of lies.
What is this?
No, wait. Anything but that.
It's for Shiho-chan—
An engagement ring?
What is this?
An open audition.
Yeah, I can see that.
We made it to the final round.
What? Who did?
Me and Kanon.
What?!
Keep your voice down.
When?
I submitted a karaoke recording
and video the other day.
Do you have a group name?
I can't tell you.
Wow, that's lame! I mean, uh...
Do you have any songs?
No, they gave us a song to sing.
Kanon and I are practicing like crazy.
I don't get it. Why are you
auditioning to become idols?
I'm going to join this agency
and investigate them.
It's too late for honest methods.
I've been stuck at an impasse for a while.
My only clue is the calls from Nikaido.
I'm running out of time.
Yeah, but...
You could've asked me for advice.
About working at the cabaret club, too.
What? That's your problem?
You know, it's been
bothering me for a while,
but you talk and act
like you're my boyfriend.
What?
No, not my boyfriend.
Something worse than that.
The preachy old men who come to the agency
to ask if I should be doing this job.
If that's how they feel,
they shouldn't be there.
What? That's... It's not on purpose.
Maybe you're just too self-conscious.
Well, it's not like I'm your
girlfriend or anything,
so why do you criticize what I do?
I'm just acting on my own judgment.
Rena-san, are you sure you're not
trying to reclaim your lost youth?
Just because you didn't graduate
from high school or college...
And now you're discriminating
based on my academic history.
That's not what I meant.
Thanks for the meal.
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
Home.
Oh, there's something else
that's been bothering me.
What is it?
Have you told anyone about Odokawa?
What? No. Of course not.
This is your last chance.
Taeko-san told me.
She said you repeatedly said how sorry
you were for what you did to Odokawa.
Oh, Taeko-san.
The truth is, Dobu-san threatened me,
and said something bad might
happen to you if I defied him.
I just wanted to protect you, so...
Listen, it sounds like you're trying to
spin this like you did something heroic,
but this only happened because you went
off to find Dobu's hideout on your own!
It was going well up until that point.
So, he told you to frame
an innocent man. Am I wrong?
Actually, when I told Dobu-san—I mean, Dobu—
that we were investigating Odokawa-san,
he told me to keep him informed
and keep an eye on him.
I did all of this for you, Rena-san.
Why'd you have to strike that jackpot?
Oh, well...
I suspected it before, but you really suck.
You always act like nothing's your fault.
It's written all over your face
that you grew up pampered.
That's— You don't know that, Rena-san!
I'm not taking that from someone
who never had a proper adolescence!
Not that you'd understand,
since you don't have parents.
Who told you that?
Is Mitsuya a stage name?
Next Time
Why?
They're only trying to promote Nikaido-san.
I'm gonna rob a bank.
Did you kidnap her?
Who are you?
Shiho-chan!
I'll sell it to you.
How much?
One billion yen.
This show is a work of fiction.
We have a problem.