Cut!
Okay, cut. That was good.
We'll do the parking lot scene next.
We'll resume in 20 minutes.
Also, everyone, Nikaido-sama brought
us some sweet buns. Thank you!
Thank you!
You were fantastic, Rui-chan.
That felt really real.
Keep up the good work.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Director.
Sure thing.
You were great.
Why do I have to do this?
What?
Hello.
Come on, don't do this now.
You're the one who said you couldn't
make it on singing and dancing alone.
You're gonna get cast in bit parts to start.
No, I mean why does it have to be this role?
There weren't any other options.
We couldn't say no after
they made a role just for you.
Well, thank you very much.
What's wrong with you? Don't get so upset.
You're judging that audition tonight.
Be friendly. I'm counting on you, okay?
Hello.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you two in Mystery Kiss?
Nice to meet you.
This actually isn't the first time.
We've met before.
Oh, you were at the release event.
Oh, is that why?
It's not like we have any other female fans.
I'm so happy to be
standing onstage with you.
Wow, I'm impressed you
made it to the final ten.
It's just a coincidence.
How was your audition?
I think there were about a hundred people.
A hundred?
And the three of you were chosen?
Yeah. The three of us were chosen.
I guess people who survive
are a different breed.
Right?
How?
What?
They make us wear masks.
They're only trying to promote Nikaido-san.
Why?
Why? Because... I don't know.
It's probably the agency's strategy, right?
Are you two okay with that?
Sorry. Good morning,
good morning, good morning.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
What is this? We're all
sharing a greenroom?
We've got a lot of people. We can't help it.
I want my own room.
But it's full of equipment and costumes.
Then install a partition here. Now.
Hold on.
Hey. Nikaido, hey.
She's got a cute face, but...
Mitsuya-san, what is Nikaido-san like?
Like you just saw.
Strong-willed and hates to lose.
I wish I could talk to her.
I get it. Not even I feel like
I can casually talk to her.
She's been even more on edge since it was
decided we'd make our major debut.
Mystery Kiss is kind of impressive, though.
You only had five fans to start, right?
Huh?
Oh, yeah. There was a time like that.
It was tough.
Is Mitsuya a stage name?
Why?
We have this high school junior we haven't
been able to get in touch with recently.
We're looking for her.
Her name is Mitsuya Yuki.
Hey, Kanon.
What?
What a coincidence.
Is your junior an idol, too?
I see. You must be worried.
Yeah, so could you let me know
if you know anything?
Sure. I'll let you know
if anything comes up.
Thanks. Do you mind?
Look. Look at this.
I'm looking, I'm looking.
Don't I look amazing?
Hold on.
I could totally debut.
Can you be quiet for a second?
Hello? We have a problem.
Rena, I think you're wearing that backwards.
Oh, you're right.
Pull yourself together. This isn't like you.
Sorry.
I'm heading back out there.
Okay.
Do you know where Mitsuya Yuki is?
No. Probably still in the green room.
The real one.
Greenroom?
May I see your ticket?
Where's the greenroom?
The greenroom isn't open to the public.
I'm asking you where the greenroom is.
Um, if I could see some ID...
What? You're useless.
She suddenly disappeared.
I can't find her anywhere.
Sometimes girls cancel last minute.
We can't wait any longer, so you're
disqualified due to an absence.
You're on next, Mystery Kiss.
Seriously?
Where have you been?
I was worried about you.
We failed the audition, y'know!
Get out of there. Go somewhere safe.
Not your home. Somewhere around people.
I'll call you later.
Who is that?
Crap, crap, crap.
Watch out.
Hey! Whoa!
Rui-tan! Rui-tan!
Thanks for waiting, everyone! Here we go!
Ready, and...
Who the hell are you?
What were you doing there?
Why didn't you audition?
Thanks again, Odokawa-san.
Could you take us
to Shibaura Wharf in a hurry?
Thanks.
By the way, have you considered my request
to hand over your dash cam data?
Yeah, sure.
Really?
I'll sell it to you.
For one billion yen.
That's the kind of price
a child would come up with.
Doesn't this seem like not enough profit?
Is this all we make from concerts?
They weren't the only ones performing today.
Why's she here?
She doesn't want to run
badger games anymore,
so she's here to talk to Yano-san.
He's busy right now.
More importantly, I've got some bad news.
Could I talk to him for a few minutes?
Bad news?
Shiho-chan.
It's about the dash cam.
Is that you, Shiho-chan?
That's not you, is it?
Who are you?
Shiho-chan!
You're being tricked, right?
I'll protect you from these guys!
I'm actually pretty strong.
I've mastered every martial art there is,
from sumo for kids to whatever-jiujitsu.
Don't get the wrong idea, mister.
Seriously, I can't even.
Didn't we have fun together?
We ate lots of good food together.
Spending time with you was painful.
That's why I want to quit
running badger games.
You're not the kind of girl who says that!
Shiho-chan, you're a liar!
You're the liar, you bum! You're broke!
Ichimura.
Why?! Why would you say that?!
What, what, what?
I don't believe you! You're lying!
So, what's your bad news?
It's about the dash cam data.
Someone else offered to buy it.
We need to get that dash cam data soon.
I haven't been able to sleep since then.
I keep expecting my doorbell to ring.
Can't you do something about this?!
Quit your whining!
Mystery Kiss is doing great right now!
They're about to make their major debut!
You guys are doin' pretty good these days?
Then ain't it about time my favor was repaid?
What should we do with him?
What should we do? What should we do?!
You're just like him, too.
Lacking in caution.
Quit asking about our next move.
So, how was Yamamoto?
He seemed flustered.
He wanted to know who was trying to buy it.
Want some?
So, what are you going to do next?
I haven't heard from Kakihana-san in a week.
Do you know where he is?
I'm gonna rob a bank.
What? Sorry, I wasn't listening.
I'm going to rob a bank.
Are you stupid? How, in this day and age?
To be precise, I'm going to rob someone
who's at the bank to make a withdrawal.
I want you to help me.
I told you, I'm not helping you.
Just listen.
It takes a week or two to get
enough cash for a large withdrawal.
They're supposed to contact me
when that happens.
They'll let me know who's receiving
how much cash on what day at what time.
How do you know that?
Lottery tickets can only be redeemed
at an exchange bank.
Anyone who wins a large amount
has to visit that branch,
and I've bribed one of their bank employees.
It's basically like I won the lottery.
That's an awfully roundabout
way of doing things.
Why not just have the bank
employee withdraw the cash?
You don't get it.
That would make the employee a victim.
If I make them an accomplice, then no matter
what happens, it'll work out for me.
As the day of the withdrawal approaches,
guys like me will swarm around
that bank employee.
And we'll beat 'em all and take the cash.
You won't be in any danger.
All you have to do is put the cash in
your car once I've taken it to a safe place.
We'll ditch the main car then.
You and I will disappear with the cash.
Don't think about it too hard.
We're asking for donations.
Thank you.
You're drinking again,
aren't you? You gotta quit.
Thank you.
Children eat for free.
Here.
We're asking for donations, please.
Thank you!
It's warm.
Here.
I thought I told you not to come here.
Why are you doing this?
They didn't have enough staff.
I'm not talking about the pork broth.
I want to retire and focus on this.
I won't forget everything you've done for me.
You're awfully hasty, aren't you?
So, about that dirty-as-sin heaping
pile of cash you can't spend...
You don't have to put it like that.
The billion yen Dobu-san's got his eye on.
I already found it.
The police are watching me.
I can't do anything.
That's why this is an opportunity.
I can't let you do this.
I'm gonna bring you some
sparkling clean money.
You idiot!
I'm doing this for the world!
For the people!
I didn't found an NPO just to launder money!
Doesn't matter to me either way.
If you're determined to retire,
then you'll definitely need money.
You need money to help people, too.
So you're gonna steal some
from an honest man?
No, I'm gonna protect an honest citizen.
He's been yapping about it on social media.
Even if we left him alone,
someone worse would prey on him.
I haven't finished cleaning up
your mess, you know.
There was a time when I thought
about making you an executive.
I must be going senile.
Did you kidnap Don-chan's daughter?
The girl my friend met through a dating site,
and the girl who was with a talent agency
guy named Yamamoto are the same person.
My spring's finally on the horizon, though.
So? Why do I have to be your bodyguard?
You're the one who proposed
I transport a billion yen.
Those are hardly equal.
So, where's your friend?
At the wharf.
Hold on. You don't mean
Yano's place, do you?
If it is, there's nothing I can do.
Isn't Yano your junior?
You're the one obsessed with hierarchies
and pledges made over sake cups.
You should be able to
resolve this by talking.
There's an unspoken rule that we don't
interfere with each other's business.
If I can't save Kakihana,
I'm not helping you rob a bank.
Wouldn't that mean Yano
is interfering with your job?
You think you're so witty, don't you?
Hey.
Well, if it isn't Dobu-san.
What do you think you're doing?
It's cold out here. Let me inside.
Who is he?
A taxi driver.
That's your underling?
You've fallen far, Dobu.
And you're out here runnin' badger games,
so I could say the same of you.
Hey, taxi driver. I'm gonna
chuck this guy into the sea.
Take your friend and get
outta here in the meantime.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Odokawa...
I get to go home?
Yeah, let's go home.
I'm so pathetic.
And you know what he said?
That I've always been pathetic.
Suddenly, I felt better.
He's my hero.
So, where is this Odokawa person now?
He said he still had something to do.
Kakihana-san, do you know
where you were being held captive?
Not sure. Seemed like
some kind of warehouse.
Did you see any young girls
around Ichimura Shiho's age?
Who was holding you captive?
This big bear of a man wearing glasses.
He was wearing a black track suit.
Do you remember anything else?
Did they say anything?
They were talking about some dash cam data.
They said they really needed
to get their hands on it.
Kakihana-san, should we call the police?
Nah, it's kind of embarrassing.
Besides, I'm tired.
Around 8:30AM on the 24th,
Live
Breaking From Location of Found Body
Abandoned? Police Rush to Identify Body
Minato City, Shibaura Wharf
the body of a woman wrapped in a blue tarp
was found at 3-chome Shibaura
Wharf in Minato City, Tokyo.
The Tokyo Bay Police Station
is working to confirm her identity
while investigating this
as a case of an abandoned body.
I promise I'll catch whoever did it.
Next Time
It must be Mitsuya.
Mitsuya's back for revenge.
Bet you wish you were
getting a cut now, huh?
I want to see the pictures you took
on your first day of work.
None of your damn business, you bastards!
How would you know how I feel?
Why are you doing all this for my daughter?
This show is a work of fiction.