Digging Deeper
Largest Ever Carry-Over
of 1 Billion Yen
Incredible!
Soon we'll be announcing
the winning numbers.
Digging Deeper
Carry-Over Finally Hits
1 Billion Yen!
We're all looking forward
to the end of the year.
It doesn't feel real, does it?
But somebody is going to win all of this.
I keep thinking, "What if I win?"
I'd like to add a sauna to my bathroom.
What about you, sir?
If we're giving it to him, we should
offer that N-1 prize money instead.
Why's everyone so desperate for money?
Digging Deeper
Largest Ever Carry-Over of 1 Billion Yen
Is it really that important? How disgraceful.
There are more important things in life.
Hey, you watching TV. Yeah, you.
Make sure you're filming me, cameraman.
That's right. You right there.
First, hug the people next to you. Love them.
You shouldn't be wasting your time
watching dumb crap like this.
I'm telling you idiots to look
at the people right next to you.
Digging Deeper
Largest Ever Carry-Over of 1 Billion Yen
Next up, the weather. Sakurai-san, save us.
I'll go get the car.
Sure.
Excuse me, Donraku-san.
Thanks for looking out for Yuki.
Of course. I'm just worried
about where she is.
I'm worried, too.
I'm actually a private eye.
What?
You hired my boss Ibusuki, didn't you?
No, I asked an old acquaintance for help.
We can't seem to get rid
of each other, y'know?
Maybe it reached your agency through him.
I see.
Did you receive any threatening
phone calls or ransom demands?
I already told the police this,
but no, nothing like that.
At first, I thought that might be it, too.
Maybe someone found out
that she's my daughter.
I've got a lot of enemies, you see.
I'm sure there are people
who hate me all over.
So, what about Yuki?
Apparently she ran away from home
and said not to look for her.
Then my wife canceled the search.
I'm not convinced, though.
I won't believe it until I see her face.
Is that how kids are these days?
I don't think Yuki's that kind of girl.
Another celebrity was caught cheating.
What do you think, sir?
You know what I think? Who cares?
You'd better not be slacking off again.
Sorry.
Another bill for you.
Thanks.
I sure did everything I could
for my first job.
It made me realize everyone's got a history.
A life. Even ordinary taxi drivers.
What do we do with this information?
What about the illegal stuff?
Should we retrieve it?
Odokawa could be involved
in a criminal case.
We can't leave things the way they are.
We already looked into that.
He was just a regular middle-aged guy.
Besides, he drives dozens
of passengers a day.
It's not that odd if one of them
went missing.
That one passenger was
my junior in high school,
and she might've gotten
mixed up in something.
Well, I don't know your high school junior.
Oh, yeah?
At this agency, you're my junior.
Guess I shouldn't care about you, either.
You can do the rest of this yourself.
Ibu, one of your young 'uns
went to see Don-chan.
I told her not to.
You didn't put her up to it?
The girl's her junior from back home.
Once she gets into something,
she acts indiscriminately.
Yeah?
That's no good.
Please just leave her alone.
If anything happens to her,
then I'll be forced to act.
Why hasn't the girl been found yet, anyway?
Doesn't make sense.
This shouldn't be that difficult.
Well...
So, actually...
After aggressively haggling over his fare,
that chatty passenger said he was
going to buy lottery tickets
so he could buy up some idol group's CDs.
I made up a random number on the spot,
and he rushed right over to buy a ticket.
I was like, "Seriously? You still had money?"
Hey, are you listening?
Love is both a painful and beautiful thing.
Dude, don't. Did something happen to you?
She's just a little girl.
She's still only 18.
So far we've only exchanged messages,
but we get along great.
We're supposed to meet up soon.
But she's too busy to meet, right?
I know what you're trying to say.
You think she doesn't exist, don't you?
She's really real.
Kakihana-san!!
Good luck at work
Are you sure you're not being tricked?
Here you are.
Are you jealous?
Of course not.
Think about it. You said so yourself.
There's no demand for us
in the marriage marketplace.
I'm telling you, it's the feeling—
You've never even met her.
How can there be any feeling?
Look.
Let me see your profile.
No.
Give it.
Quit it.
That's my personal information.
Give it.
Kakihana Eiji
Occupation: IT Worker
Annual Income: 20,000,000 yen
Education: College
These specs you lied about
way outshine any kind of feeling.
I know.
But still, I wanna dream.
Ibusuki?
The guy who used to help us out
runs a detective agency now.
Come to think of it, some youngster
was sniffing around your territory.
Was he one of Ibusuki's guys?
Dunno, but I gave him a beating.
I'm telling you, you've gotta
learn to use your head.
If this is true, I'll have
to offer compensation.
Don-chan will be dragged into this, too.
What do you say, Dobu?
Could you clean up my mess again?
I'm begging you.
You want me to protect Yano?
Not protect him.
I'm asking you to let me settle this.
I'm doing this for your sake, too.
Kabasawa-sama?
Hey. Rena-chan?
Yes.
Wow.
I bought this car and condo, too.
But now that I have them,
I'm kind of disappointed.
Maybe I spent too much.
No way. You're trying to make
the world a better place.
You deserve this level of luxury.
Thank you for waiting.
Oh, I can't drink.
You're 19, right?
Yeah.
Oh, right. Right, of course.
I'm supposed to be a model citizen.
I shouldn't be acting like this.
Since the police are no help at all, we all
have high hopes for you, Kabasawa-sama.
You can count on me.
That's why I'm hoping
you'll get my laptop back.
I've got lots of important data saved on it.
Where does Dobu normally hang out?
Apparently you picked up
the missing high school girl from Nerima.
I handed over my dash cam data
to the police a while ago.
I have a request.
What's that?
I need you to keep your mouth shut.
Daimon already told me
to keep my mouth shut.
Not just the police. Don't tell anybody.
Don't tell anybody? Like who?
Everybody.
Tell 'em you lost your dash cam data.
So, what do you want help with?
If anyone shows up looking
for your dash cam data,
I want you to let me know.
And if I refuse?
I'll kill you.
Let me handle the laptop.
I promise I'll get it back once I catch Dobu.
Anyway, what do you want to do after this?
Wanna come to my place?
You piece of shit.
Huh? What was that?
I don't know...
Sometimes I want to be spoiled by
someone who sees me as Kabasawa Taichi.
Everyone calls me a hero, but
men who fight need breaks, too.
Today let's forget about everything
and have fun, Rena-chan.
So, when do you think you'll take down Dobu?
I said let's forget about Dobu today.
Hurry up and become a real hero.
Did you know you're
getting more haters recently?
"Kabasawa isn't a hero.
He's just desperate for recognition."
"He's scared of Dobu. Just a one-hit wonder."
"He's sleeping with his female followers."
Wait, that last one might be true.
I was frustrated that I couldn't
tell them they're wrong.
But after seeing how
you've been acting recently...
Shut up.
What?
You don't know anything about me.
I stirred up a sensation
and put myself in harm's way.
I didn't ask to be deified, okay?
You don't know what the pressure is like.
It's terrifying.
Don't project your fantasies onto me.
You got to dream, too, didn't you?
Who do you have to thank for that, huh?
Crap.
Hello, Rena-san?
Where are you?
And what happened to Taeko-san's
report? It's weirdly dry.
What have you been doing with Kabasawa?
Are you slacking off again?
Dobu was in Odokawa's car.
What? Why?
Not only that, but Dobu demanded Odokawa's
cooperation and threatened to kill him.
Wait, wait. The dash cam caught all of that?
We should call the police.
What are we going to tell the police?
We're filming him without his knowledge.
Hold on. Did you use my computer
without my permission?
But you left it open.
I hope Dobu hits you again.
Gimme a break, here!
Anyway, I'm going to follow Dobu.
What?
I'm going to get my data back
and solve this mystery.
With my photos, we might be able to
find your high school junior.
We'll be able to give the banker's
wife her evidence, too!
How?
I'll steal my laptop
back while he's sleeping.
Are you stupid?
There's no way you'll make it out
unscathed if you go alone.
You told me to handle it myself, though.
That's not what I meant!
Because of you, I'm eating
yakiniku by myself.
Why are you having yakiniku?
Because I'm in the middle of following him.
Please don't make any decisions by yourself.
Don't try to solve anything, either.
Limit yourself to just watching him.
Got it. But you know, I had
more than two choices this time.
I chose from out of at least ten. Bye!
Ten...? Hey, wait!
I've snuck into Dobu's hideout!
Ow, ow, ow!
Let go!
Mercy! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
What?
Listen, my boss is trying to
construct a building here.
I know all his henchmen.
Naturally, all the construction
workers are his guys, too.
You know what that means, don't you?
Um, there's joy in creating
something with your friends?
Ow, ow, ow!
I don't know.
You need to be direct with me. I'm not
good at reading between the lines.
Scream all you want.
No one's coming to help you.
I've got the solvents I need to
dissolve your corpse right here.
If I bury you, they'll never find anything.
No, wait. I've only lived 24 years.
You think your life's just
getting started, huh?
I do. I finally got a job recently.
It's boring right now, but
I'm hoping things will pick up.
So for now, I'm being patient
and working really hard.
Why did you follow me?
It was a coincidence.
Who put you up to it?
This happens to me all the time.
I run into my teachers from school
when I go traveling.
Really. I'm serious.
Uh-huh. I've got one question for you.
Okay.
It's a simple, two-choice question.
Two choices...
Do you prefer your right finger
or your left finger?
But I've got ten.
I can't answer the phone right now—
I can't answer the phone right now.
Please call again later.
I see. A background check on Odokawa, huh?
Then you should be following him.
I happened to see you while watching him
and wondered how you were doing.
Terribly, obviously.
Right.
Hold on. What do you mean, you saw me?
Well, uh...
Oh, the camera. It's the camera
in Odokawa's car, isn't it?
It's called a dash cam.
I don't give a shit.
So, how come you can see what's on that?
Ow, ow, ow!
Don't invoke your duty of
confidentiality when it suits you.
Are you working with Odokawa, too?
What do you mean, working with him?!
Aren't you working with him?!
All right, fine. Then you're
gonna help me, too.
What?
What is this?
Anything but that, please!
She's your girl, huh?
Oh, well... I'm not sure
what she thinks, but...
Personally, I don't think
it's out of the question...
She's not gonna go to the cops
if she doesn't hear from you,
and you don't have a GPS up your ass, right?
Nope, she doesn't care
about me at all. Sadly.
And yet, her name's in your
contacts without honorifics.
Yes.
I'm going to tell you everything
I know about Odokawa.
I've already investigated that thoroughly.
What?
I already know plenty.
Ow!
What do you want help with?
What is it, Driver?
I feel like I've seen her before.
Whatever. Let's get moving.
She keeps her face hidden.
If you recognize her face, you must've
come to her concert before she debuted.
Is she a singer or something?
That's not it, then.
I've never been to a concert.
Are you okay? Are you tired?
Is Nikaido-san coming?
Later.
Did she do something?
I can't keep up with her ambition.
You can work at your own pace, Ichimura.
She's incredible. I bet she'd
kill someone just to get ahead.
She probably already has, honestly.
What are you talking about?
Maybe I'm not suited to this job.
Mitsuya's already inside.
I don't like her.
I liked things better before.
What are you looking at?
Head towards the Kamimeguro
intersection next.
There's a building nearby.
Kamimeguro?
Yeah.
I was just thinking about how I once drove
a girl around that other girl's age there.
What? When?
About two weeks ago, I think.
She must've been from your agency.
I'm surprised you remember,
but it must've been someone else.
She was a young girl taking a pretty
long trip in the middle of the night.
Not only that, but she
called herself an idol.
Are you sure it wasn't
the girl we just dropped off?
But she's a calico cat.
What does that mean?
You're sure you dropped off
that girl at this office?
Yeah.
Listen, Driver.
Does this car have a recording device?
Why?
Sometimes you see them in the news.
You know, in stories about robberies.
Yeah, I've got one.
Any chance I could get your data?
What? You finally picked up.
Where'd you wander off to?
You weren't answering your phone.
Sorry.
The boss is hiding something.
He was with some shady people yesterday.
I see.
You're awfully low-energy today.
I'm at the hospital right now.
What? Why? Did Dobu do something to you?
Oh, no. Actually, I lost him
while I was tailing him.
Then why?
I fell down the stairs and broke my pinkie.
Liar.
I might've found the taxi
Mitsuya took that day.
And?
Apparently the driver remembers her.
What should we do?
Where is Yuki now?
Next Time
Do you think Donraku-san
is hiding something?
We're partners, Rena. Buddies!
Something definitely happened to you.
You tell me the truth, got it?
This is where they practice.
Shiho-chan, do you actually
want to get married?
This show is a work of fiction.