What?
What? Seriously?
Sato.
Ow!
Rena-san.
What are you doing hanging around here?
I won two bonus drinks
in a row for four total.
Why are you buying so many when we
won't be able to use the bathroom?
Oh, I couldn't drink this many regardless.
Wait, there's no bathroom?
Not even a convenience store?
Nothing. It's just bars and love hotels.
Come on. What are you doing?
Hot!
That's hot.
Anyway, I'm surprised a big-time banker
would visit an out-of-the-way place like this.
This whole area's got a shady history.
A few people even turned up dead
since the trouble with land sharks.
What?
According to his wife, he frequently
meets a woman around here
because he works at the branch nearby.
We're going to film evidence
of them entering the love hotel,
spending the night, and coming
out together in the morning.
But isn't it possible that
they'll arrive separately?
Well, yeah. We'll need to keep the camera
recording for at least an hour for insurance.
What? Why?
If their stay is short, they might
not have gotten intimate.
That's not gonna happen.
In any case, we have two
options in situations like these.
We can keep filming from the car,
or we can wait for them in the lounge.
Well, you can.
I've never been in one of
those establishments before.
Yeah, that's not my problem.
Look this way.
Cut it out.
What are you doing here?
Nothing in particular.
You can't be doing "nothing."
A couple like you must be up to something.
Is this a deal or something?
You're not hiding syringes
or anything like that, are you?
Where'd this come from?
We'll leave, okay?
Hey, wait. You in the back.
What is that? Is that a camera?
You're not secretly
photographing people, are you?
No, we're just capturing memories.
Then show me what you've got on there.
Actually, uh… we're bound by confidentiality.
If you can't show me,
that means you're guilty!
You, out of the car.
Come on!
Ow!
Show me.
I can't.
If you're just capturing memories,
there's no problem.
I can't show you.
Show me, dammit.
Just show me the damn pictures.
Rena-san, help me.
Show me.
I really can't.
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you filming an authoritarian cop
so you can post the video online, huh?
Hey.
Come on, man. It's your first day.
Are you even trying? Depending
on how your training period goes…
While I was practicing taking pictures...
The only thing around here is stray cats.
Actually, I managed to get
a proper private eye kind of photo.
A young woman entering a sketchy multi-use
building wearing a hat and sunglasses.
She's gotta be a celebrity.
That's the purview of paparazzi,
not private eyes.
They're definitely asleep.
Even though it's a weekday,
they're staying overnight.
We missed our best shot because of you.
You'd better at least get
a picture of them leaving.
I didn't think I'd be questioned
by the police on my first day.
Why don't we call it quits for today?
Why did you interview with our agency?
Because it's cool.
I grew up watching anime.
You know, Detective What's-His-Name.
That's all?
No. I thought it'd make me
popular with the ladies, too.
Honestly, I didn't think
this job would be so drab.
I thought detectives did cool stuff.
Aren't detectives—
Wait, what?
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Back up, backup, back up.
You know it's not like that.
When can I see you next?
Crap. They're leaving.
Next?
I'm going after them!
Crap!
We did it. We got them.
I can't tell if you're lucky or not.
Here.
Let's go. We got the evidence.
I'll write up a report
as soon as I get home.
No. You can't take that out of the office,
so you'll have to write it there.
This is huge for my first day.
I can't sit still!
Let's have a toast. Would you like
coffee or soda? I'll go buy some.
Why are those my options?
Hello, this is Ibusuki. Please respond.
Sorry, boss. Were you asleep?
Oh. It's you, Rena.
We just finished.
Did you get the pictures?
Yes, just now.
How's he doing?
Sato, was it?
His instincts are miserable,
but he seems lucky.
I see. That's a relief.
What?
Seriously? Lucky me.
Hey.
Oh, I'm sorry. I keep
winning free drinks today.
I don't recognize you.
What?
That's a pretty nice camera
you've got there.
Oh, yes.
Who are you a reporter for?
Actually, I don't work for a magazine.
I'm a private eye.
Then what are you investigating?
I have a duty to confidentiality.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Actually, I doubt it has
anything to do with you.
I was asked to investigate a banker's affair.
Yeah? That's great!
No, stop! There isn't anything on here.
Oh, yeah?
Yes.
In fact, why should I give you
my camera, anyway?
Did the banker hire you?
If you have a legitimate
reason, let's hear it—
I was never doing this
for a legitimate reason.
The pictures are on this.
What? They're on this thing?
Our generation is physical, you know?
My agency just provided me
with that. Hey, wait.
You haven't made any copies
or sent these anywhere, have you?
I wish I had.
You know what'll happen
if I find out you have later, right?
Yamabiko
Ow, ow, ow. It's definitely not broken.
It's broken.
amabiko
mabiko
biko
ko
Not broken.
Excuse us.
Here you are.
Can I get you a beer—no, an oolong tea?
Yes, please.
Thank you. There weren't any other
shops around, so we had to come here.
I'm really sorry about this.
He doesn't have a shred of tact.
We appreciate you opening your shop for us.
Oh, right. You can't drink.
I'm surprised you can.
How do you know my age, anyway?
You're 19, right? The boss told me.
Even kids as young as you
work as private eyes, huh?
It's so exciting, isn't it?
To be suddenly attacked by a thug.
I love that sort of thing.
He's a rookie who just started today.
I wouldn't call him a private eye yet.
And don't give personal information
out to people you just met.
You're not an amateur.
Why do you think you were hired?
Probably my interview.
I'm pretty confident about what I said.
Thank you.
There was a written test, right?
Yeah, the 50 two-choice questions?
You got all of them wrong.
You were hired because the boss said
he'd never seen anything like it.
Have some self-awareness.
Well, Mr. Unreliable Detective,
have you ever been hired
to investigate anything really crazy?
Like a murder, or something
else you'd see in a movie.
We have a duty of confidentiality.
Well, shucks. I thought I'd get
to hear some juicy gossip.
You don't have any stories like that?
Why are you asking, too?
U-Um...
Ma'am, is there anything
you're curious about?
Like someone or something
you'd like to have investigated.
Call me Taeko.
I'm not sure if I should say this, but a few
of my regulars are curious people.
Your regulars?
You mean this place is surprisingly popular?
If it weren't, I would've
closed shop a long time ago.
Oh, right.
All the shops around here have been closing.
The neighborhood keeps shrinking.
But some people just keep coming.
So, which regular are you most curious about?
I'm not sure how to describe him.
I'd like to know what he spends his
time doing. How does he see the world?
He's just such an odd person.
If he's a regular, why not ask him yourself?
That's the thing. I wish I could, but I can't.
Just between us, I feel like
there's a hidden side to him.
He never wants to talk about his past.
Like we said, we're private eyes.
If you tell us more about him,
we'll investigate whatever you want.
Odokawa-san. His given name is Hiroshi.
Born year of the tiger, so I think he's 41.
Odokawa Hiroshi.
Year of the tiger, 41 years old.
You don't need to repeat it.
Here.
Thank you.
Odokawa Hiroshi
41, Single
Taxi Driver
Idiot!
Just forget it.
Ibusuki Detective Agency
Confidential   Free Consultations
If you'd just look at these…
No, wait—
Call us if anything else comes up!
What?
I'm really sorry. I screwed up.
I guess you weren't ready to lead.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
I promise I'll make up for it
on the next job.
Well, that background check into
what's-his-name sounds perfect for training.
Then we'll call it even.
Yes, sir.
Here he comes.
At a glance, he seems like your typical
slightly creepy but ordinary middle-aged guy.
You're contradicting yourself, but yeah.
He lives a totally boring, ordinary life.
Well, yeah. But the client
might still find it remarkable.
We're back.
Good work out there.
Welcome back.
The job's going smoothly.
Huh? Are you still mad, boss?
No. A new job came in.
Rather, an acquaintance's daughter
hasn't been home in two days.
He can't get in touch with her, either.
What? A runaway?
She said she'd be back home soon.
She's just a high school student.
Something might've happened to her.
What? Then we should start
looking for her right away,
instead of wasting time on
this taxi driver's biography.
Do your own job.
That's right. I'm still single.
Not even a girlfriend.
Oh, shut up.
So you're looking for one.
Sir, how's your relationship
with your daughter?
What happened out there today?
You weren't your usual straightforward self.
The producer said they'd never
seen you so quiet before.
They said they'd come to check on—
I mean, say hello later.
What's wrong? How about something sweet?
Here. What were those idols called?
Those young girls brought you a gift.
What's wrong with you?
You're in a terrible mood.
Goriki Clinic
Does he have a chronic illness?
Go check it out.
Is this really an investigation?
Why are you alone?
It's simple.
If you've got nothing to hide,
open your door.
This dash cam allows you to film
the inside of your vehicle, doesn't it?
That's right.
How long do you store your recordings?
About two weeks.
She'll be on here, then.
What?
That missing high school
girl got in your car.
My car?
I'm taking your data. This is a seizure.
If anything comes up,
I expect your cooperation again.
Don't go to the police, though.
Hello, ma'am.
Hello.
Taeko-san was right. He doesn't
seem like an ordinary taxi driver.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Any developments in the missing
high school girl case?
It's all over the news.
Yeah, because her life's in danger.
The media started
receiving information today.
Just after 1 AM two days ago on the 4th,
after doing some shopping at a
convenience store, she got in a taxi.
Have they identified the taxi?
Apparently the clerk remembered the number.
Huh? After seeing it only once and briefly?
It happened to be their birthday, 1022.
What?
Wow.
A high school girl has gone missing
in Nerima City, Tokyo.
She has been unreachable
since she left her home late at night
two days ago on the 4th of this month.
The next morning, her family…
We, the Homosapiens, just received
the results of Round 1 of the N-1.
And would you believe it? We passed!
Of course we did.
Even amateurs could make it past Round 1.
Where do you think the finish line is?
Equator Sauna
But last year, we failed in Round 2.
After ten years in the business...
Equator Sauna
Who is it?
We work for Ibusuki.
Hello.
You look young. Have a seat.
Excuse us.
So?
We need a remote monitoring
dash cam and GPS installed.
What? Hold on. That's totally illegal.
Where?
His car. This is the dash cam.
It's a common model.
You'll install it, won't you?
If you pay for it.
You'll be paid tomorrow.
No can do. Equator operates 24 hours
a day, but that's just the sauna.
How long will it take?
I'm busy. Give me three days.
Make it one.
1.5 days, or pay a rush late night surcharge.
How much?
550,000. And I'll need your help, too.
Pretty old car.
Didn't need all these tools.
How long will it take?
About seven or eight minutes.
Seven or eight minutes?
Yeah.
What is it?
Are you hungry?
Hold on.
Okay, all good.
That should do it.
Fine. I'll go buy you something.
Stay put and be good.
Crap, crap, crap.
Odokawa's coming, Odokawa's
coming, Odokawa's coming!
Crap, crap, crap!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Was he really talking to someone?
Yeah. He even ominously told them
to “stay put and be good.”
Anyway, I could imagine him kidnapping
and holding someone as cute as her
if she happened to get in his taxi.
He may be involved, but kidnapping
and false imprisonment?
No, you're right. I guess not.
Did you call her cute?
Did I say that?
Yeah, didn't you just say that?
No, you definitely did.
What?
Her photo hasn't appeared on the news yet.
Why'd you say that?
I didn't say that.
No, you did.
What? Really?
Yeah.
I caught a glimpse of the boss' documents.
I knew it.
They were out in the open on his desk.
Hold on.
Hey.
Where'd they go?
Don't go through his stuff.
This is it.
Don't.
Wait, wait, wait.
Look at this Buddha.
Tada! A Buddha.
Wait a minute.
Mitsuya?
This is Yuki.
Mitsuya-san.
Next Time
Have we met?
Why'd you end the investigation?
Rumor is he's done a lot of gray work.
He's probably never paid
for his mistakes before.
You should stay away from them.
You're cute, too, Rena-san.
This show is a work of fiction.
What?
I told you, I won't work for you.