We're screwed.
Calm down.
We're still the only ones
who know what happened.
We'll be fine.
You call this fine?
Then why are the cops here?
It must be Mitsuya.
Mitsuya's back for revenge.
Keep your voice down.
I should've reported it then.
Nikaido.
Hello, Mitsuya-san?
Why didn't you audition the other day?
I was looking forward to your performance.
I suddenly felt ill. Maybe I was nervous.
I actually wanted your advice on something.
My advice?
My manager told me to go
make some money tonight.
He said Ichimura-san's doing it, too.
What do you mean?
Apparently she gets paid
to eat with old men.
Does your agency make you do
that kind of thing?
I'm not with an agency, but if mine
told me to do that, I'd quit right away.
Right? After all, I joined
this agency to become an idol.
Yeah. No one wants to do that.
It's weird, though. Nikaido-san's
the only who doesn't have to do it.
Anyway, what happened with
your junior you mentioned after that?
Not much.
I told Nikaido-san about her.
What?
Her reaction was obviously strange.
Strange how?
I guess you could say she seemed flustered.
In any case, it was weird.
Weird?
And lately our agency's
been acting weird, too.
They told us not to talk to anyone.
Why are you telling me this?
I just came to Tokyo.
I don't have anyone to turn to.
I see. That must be disheartening.
What do you do for work, Rena-chan?
You're not part of an agency, right?
I'm working another job right now.
Part-time at a cabaret club.
Huh. Really?
Around 8:30AM on the 24th, the body
of a woman wrapped in a tarp
was found at Shibaura Wharf
in Tokyo's Minato City, Kaigan 3-chome.
The Tokyo Bay Police Station
is working to confirm her identity
while investigating this
as a case of an abandoned body.
The body was discovered near
the Shibaura Wharf station, and—
...while investigating this
as a case of an abandoned body.
The body was discovered near
the Shibaura Wharf station,
and the area was temporarily in an uproar.
Rena-san.
Mitsuya-san called me this morning.
What? Mitsuya? Wait, what?
Of Mystery Kiss.
Oh, right.
She said Nikaido-san and
her agency were acting weird.
Sounds like they're starting to slip up.
Yuki had all those incoming
calls from Nikaido Rui.
Yeah.
I want to see the pictures you
took on your first day of work.
Dobu has those.
There's no way to get them now.
Who wants those pictures?
We do.
No, the guy who cheated.
And what does he do for work?
Niji Bank Staff Entrance
Nijiiro Bank
What?
Please return my laptop
with the affair photos already.
You're one persistent bastard, aren't you?
Your laptop broke.
What?
Just kidding.
I don't have time for that right now.
Again.
I'll blow up your phone.
You're a real pain in the ass.
I'm done with that laptop.
I'll return it to the banker later.
You can negotiate with him.
Return it? But it's my—
I mean, my company's laptop.
And later? When and where is that?
Shut up. I'm busy!
I'll kill you!
What? Hey, wait! Dobu-san—
You suck at this. See?
Do you mind?
Congratulations on winning the lottery.
Congratulations.
Niji Bank
Good work.
You did well. Now hurry up.
I was worried they'd check
the fake notes. Right?
Are we going to be all right? They're not
going to retaliate later, are they?
You'll be fine. Once they lose the
contest, they'll leave this town.
Now, hurry up.
Got it.
Um, what about the pictures?
You'll get paid once I check the contents.
I'll send you the location later.
Okay.
Looks like it went well.
For now, yeah.
Wow.
Bet you wish you were
getting a cut now, huh?
No, I don't need that. But you're
gonna pay your taxi fare.
Niji Bank
Hey, Sato! Sato!
Rena-san.
What'd they say?
That banker just left.
Really? Then—
Then he can't have gone far.
Hey, wait!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Sorry. Wrong person.
Hello? I'll be right there.
The tire... the tire...
Hey, what are you doing?!
Who are you?! The police?!
We don't care about your affair!
Someone might've been killed!
Be grateful your wife
won't find out you're cheating!
What? She won't? Really?!
That depends on you.
What? Who are you guys?
I don't understand.
The suspect in another case might be
in the photographic evidence of your affair.
What does that have to do with me?
How do you weigh a person's life,
an affair, and one billion yen
against each other on your scales?
What? But you can't weigh three things
against each other on a pair of scales.
This guy's joking around.
I'm being serious.
You think you're worth that much, huh?!
Don't get the wrong idea!
I'm not getting paid one billion yen.
I'm sure they'll get arrested, anyway.
So will you for doing this.
Did you just come here to threaten me?
You're just like Dobu.
Just like Dobu?! We're not like Dobu!
Maybe we are.
In the end, maybe
we all commit a little evil.
But you regret your actions. So do I.
And trying to make up for it
can't be a bad thing.
Sorry. I'm really sorry.
It's on! Nice.
This is it! Found it. I found it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Nikaido Rui.
I knew she came to the office
the night of the incident.
Where was Mitsuya Yuki-san at this time?
Based on her call history, Nikaido invited
her to the agency, so she was there, too?
She saw something here and
got caught up in some trouble.
Which means Odokawa gave Yuki-san a ride
and dropped her off at the office?
I'm going to go see Nikaido.
I'm going to go talk to Odokawa.
Studio
Do you need something?
You're that girl from the other day.
I'm here about Yuki—Mitsuya Yuki.
Where is she now?
She just left.
I'm talking about the real Mitsuya Yuki.
The real Yuki?
I don't know. She suddenly disappeared.
Our manager doesn't know what to do,
so he replaced her with another girl.
Didn't her mother submit
a missing persons report?
She rescinded it right away.
I heard she contacted them.
Oh, yeah?
She asked them not to look for her.
Maybe she realized her father
had yakuza connections.
She couldn't have kept working
as an idol after that.
You think her dad would've accepted that?
I don't know. But it's her father who feels
guilty about what he's done, right?
He hasn't.
What?
He hasn't accepted it, so he hired
a detective to find his daughter,
but she's still missing.
You're a detective, aren't you?
Formerly. Not anymore.
Then why are you doing this?
Because she was my junior in high school.
That's all?
How can you be so calm
when someone is missing?
She might've gotten caught up in a crime.
Fine. I'll cooperate.
I'm already cooperating with the police.
So, what?
Plenty of girls go missing
due to poor mental health.
If anything, it's weird that
you're so fired up about it
just because you went
to the same high school.
She's holding me back and
causing huge problems for me.
All kinds of people are under
suspicion because of this.
Uh-huh. Well, you go on
holding other people back.
I used to be the same way.
I understand what it's like to
wish someone would just go away.
She could do everything, including track.
Not only was I less talented than her,
but she even worked hard in secret.
Watching Yuki threw my own
failures back in my face.
How would you know how I feel?
On the night of October 4th,
you were at Mystery Kiss' agency office.
What proof do you have?
The last call Yuki received was from you.
Also, I have this photo.
Okay? So what if I was at my own agency?
You came up with some pretext
to invite Mitsuya Yuki to the agency
in the middle of the night.
And?
You killed her.
That's a huge leap. Are you stupid?
Besides, it's not that easy to kill someone.
No, it must've been on impulse.
You suspected your agency was
backed by someone shady, didn't you?
The yakuza disposed of the body.
That's why Yuki hasn't been found.
If you were truly smart and calm,
you wouldn't have killed her.
And if you were smarter and calmer,
then you wouldn't have done this.
This pretending to be a detective
or pretending to be an idol.
Damn it. That bastard.
Take me to a doctor, Odokawa.
There's an unlicensed doctor
I'm well-acquainted with.
Hurry up. Put me in your taxi.
You should go to a normal hospital.
Receive proper treatment.
Wait. The car. What are you
going to do with it?
I'm going to return the money to its owner.
It finally caught up to you.
This is what they call retribution.
This is goodbye for you and me.
Don't screw with me, Odokawa.
Hey! Dobu-san, hang in there! Hey!
What are you doing here?
Why'd you have to go and get shot?
A lot of people have it out for me.
This is what they call retribution.
Did Odokawa do this to you?
He's just a taxi driver who
gave a passenger a ride.
Hurry up and call the cops.
Otherwise, there's no telling
what Yano will do to him.
Huh? What?
No. Stay with me!
Hey! Hey, Dobu-san! Dobu-san!
Nice shot.
You're on the green.
Nice one.
Nice.
Excuse me.
Right.
Huh? Are you okay?
What happened? Hey.
Before dawn on the 25th, three male
members of an anti-social organization
nearly stole roughly one billion yen
in lottery winnings.
Representative Kuroda Shigeru was transported
by emergency services to the hospital,
This morning before dawn,
the police arrested a 27-year-old
where he is receiving treatment for...
and 33-year-old unemployed man
fleeing from the scene of the crime.
According to the MPD, suspect Kyohei
was shot with a firearm in a parking lot.
Illegally acquired funds were
being supplied to the NPO...
Due to severe blood loss, a 39-year-old man
thought be to connected to the same case...
The police have been waiting
for Kuroda to recover to...
Until now, he's supported
over 5,000 children
orphaned by traffic accidents
or without living relatives...
In the case of the unidentified body
found near Shibaura Wharf,
the MPD is investigating a connection
to the missing Nerima high school girl
due to similarities
in appearance and clothes—
Well?
The day she disappeared,
Yuki-san received a bunch of calls
from another girl in her group
in the middle of the night.
That's right. She said her friend
invited her out before she left.
Where was she invited to?
I don't know.
That girl is the leader
of the group Yuki was in.
I see.
Yes.
And that night, that leader...
Nikaido entered the agency's office.
This is Nikaido Rui. Do you recognize her?
Did Yuki do something
to make this girl hate her?
Even if she did, what happened
to her is unforgivable.
I promise I'll catch whoever did it.
Why are you doing all this for my daughter?
A man named Yano has been telling me
to keep quiet about this.
"Don't look for your daughter. If you tell
the police, I'll expose your husband's past."
At first, he promised
to tell me where Yuki was
if I rescinded the missing person's report.
Yano?
A potential executive
of a criminal organization.
Why didn't he want you to talk?
My husband Donraku was
going to be named a tomena.
Tomena?
Rena-san, you don't know what that is?
It means no one else will take his name.
It's the highest rank someone can achieve.
Yuki was overjoyed by the news, too.
So at first, we thought Yuki ran away
because she was shocked
to learn about Donraku's past.
Did Yano tell you that?
Was there anything else
unusual about that day?
It was the same as always.
On weekdays, she came home
around eight at night.
Donraku was home for once, so
the three of us had dinner at home.
We talked about trivial things,
like the trouble Yuki caused when
she was little by bringing frogs home.
Hello?
I'll be right there.
Huh? Ma'am?
The body found at Shibaura Wharf
has been identified.
The deceased is Nerima City resident
Mitsuya Yuki-san,18 years old.
I'm sorry for all the trouble we've caused.
Nikaido Rui
Yamamoto Fuyuki
Sergio Takagi
We've been unable to conceal our shock
Ichimura
since we learned that
Yuki Mitsuya was found dead.
Nikaido Rui
Yamamoto Fuyuki
Sergio Takagi
In October, Mitsuya Yuki's
mother contacted us
to tell us that her daughter
hadn't returned home.
Nikaido Rui
We did everything we could to help look
for her, but failed to locate her.
Ichim
Then who's this Mitsuya Yuki
sitting up there?
Nikaido Rui
Yamamoto Fuyuki
Sergio Takagi
We had another girl stand in for
Mitsuya Yuki so the group could debut.
I've heard the police are
investigating this case as a murder.
Do you have any idea what happened to her?
Well, she was underpaid
before the group debuted.
I believe she promoted herself
on social media
and may have been close with fans as well.
You mean she was killed by a fan?
No, I'm just saying that's a possibility.
We take responsibility for failing to protect
her privacy and provide adequate security.
We cannot regret what happened
more than we already do.
We also can't bear to face
Shofutei Donraku-san
who entrusted his daughter to our agency.
Has Donraku-san said anything about this?
How do the other members feel?
Does Donraku-san know
Mitsuya Yuki was replaced?
The body found at Shibaura Wharf
has been identified.
Mystery Kiss Member
Mitsuya Yuki-san (18 years old)
The deceased is Nerima City resident
Mitsuya Yuki-san, 18 years old.
Mitsuya Yuki-san was a member
of idol group Mystery Kiss.
I'm so sorry. Donraku
is currently out right now.
Fans have been shocked by
the sudden news of her death.
Could I please ask you to
leave for today? Excuse me.
Donraku-san! Donraku-san!
Could we get a comment?
Honestly...
Honestly, I know
I'm an irresponsible parent.
But honestly, I wish I could kill her killer.
Is this related to your
past criminal associations?
Will this affect your tomena naming?
Is that all you have to say
when your daughter was killed?
None of your damn business, you bastards!
What the hell are you doing?!
Go on! Get out of here, bastards!
Rena-san, everyone's worried about you.
We brought you those
salmon roe rice balls you like.
Are you okay?
Rena-chan.
Excuse us.
Sorry the place is a mess.
It's fine.
I'm glad you're okay, but...
It's dark in here.
Give us a second.
Have some.
That's good.
Yeah?
So, Rena-san, when are you
coming back to work?
Don't ask her that right now.
But if the boss were here...
Yeah.
We'd be like a family, you know?
What does that mean? Oh, please.
Imagine the boss were here.
The four of us would be a family.
I guess that's not so bad.
Is it good?
It's so good. What's with this salmon roe?
Yuki's working hard, too.
I couldn't say that to her.
Next Time
What? Yuki? Are you okay?!
Hey! Are you okay?
Please.
I don't want anything to do
with this stuff anymore.
I really didn't do it!
Mitsuya called me.
What? What is this?
We're doing this without
the higher ups' knowledge.
This show is a work of fiction.
We're screwed if they find out.