Shofutei Donraku
There have always been
shady rumors about him.
They're mostly true, too.
At first he only asked them for favors
to protect his daughter and me,
but the more involved he got
with them, the weirder things got.
Weird how?
I'm sure he felt pressured
to do it for his art,
but he'd get drunk and wild all the time
and end up hurting regular people.
They'd settle matters like that for him.
They killed a tabloid article about
him having a child with his mistress.
Then there's all the stuff I don't know.
For a period of time, he relied
on them for everything.
That's why you and Yuki-san
moved back in with your parents?
I was running away. For Yuki's sake, too.
Where is Yuki now?
Have you heard from her since then?
Well, Donraku told me not to tell anyone.
Do you think he's hiding something?
I don't know.
Could I take a look around Yuki-san's room?
I may be able to find some clues.
The police took a bunch of things
when this all started.
Nothing's been returned yet.
I won't tell Ibusuki-san about this.
In exchange, please don't tell
Donraku that I talked to you.
That's Yuki's number.
If you're her friend, they
might not find you suspicious.
What? That's all?!
Are you sure you're a detective?
I'm watching him, just like you told me to.
He hasn't done anything
out of the ordinary yet.
A high school girl has been missing
for roughly ten days.
Since this morning, the MPD
has been speaking to a taxi driver
who may know something about the situation.
The missing person is an 18-year-old high
school girl from Nerima Ward in Tokyo.
It's unsettling, isn't it?
According to the investigation, the high
school girl was last seen ten days ago,
entering a taxi in Nerima Ward
before she went missing...
You think they're talking about Odokawa?
Calm down.
Until recently, you were acting like
you'd done everything you possibly could.
What's with the attitude?
It's not like you weren't furious, too.
Fine. Does that mean you're
okay with helping me?
What are you talking about?
We're partners, Rena. Buddies! Best buds!
There, there. Good boy.
So, Dobu kidnapped a famous
high school girl to ransom her,
colluded with police to hide the evidence,
and stole a taxi driver's dash cam.
The taxi driver got dragged into it
because he knows something,
and now he's being threatened.
Uh, what?
Or else Odokawa and Dobu are actually
working together, and it's the police who—
Can we stop talking about Dobu-san?
Well, that's quite the change in attitude.
Something definitely happened to you.
Nobody falls down the stairs
and breaks just one finger.
Yes?
Um, I'm here about the missing person.
I called the office.
Ah, we've been waiting for you!
Please, come in.
Rena-chan.
Got it!
Right this way.
Thank you for waiting.
Kobayashi Tome
Why didn't you tell me sooner
that we have a database like this?
I told you just now.
We have access to it
through the boss' old job.
Huh.
The major offices have their own,
but we have to use whatever we can.
There she is. Kobayashi Tome, 84 years old.
She lives right by the client.
You're right.
It's always hardest to see
what's right under your nose.
I hope we can find everyone this easily.
And we get paid to do this? Easy money.
I wish class reunions were
the only thing we worked on.
You want me to end your
training period right now?
Finding people is a real job, okay?
Can I see something?
There's a lot of people
you won't find in there.
Mitsuya
What's her name? Mitsuya something.
Yuki. Only other people show up
when you search for her.
Come to think of it,
did she answer her phone?
Nope. I've just been getting voicemail.
Oh, you're right. Mitsuya Yuki.
81 years old, 51 years old...
Huh? It's ringing.
I knew it. I thought now would be—
Yuki?
Who is this?
This information will cost you.
It took a lot of time to restore it, too.
The contents?
It's all on here.
If I were you, I wouldn't
go snooping through phones.
Can you show me who Yuki called
the day she went missing?
Of course.
Nikaido Rui
She got a bunch of calls
from the same person.
In the middle of the night, too. Who is she?
Oh! She's an idol from that website
we looked at the other day.
What were they called?
Mystery Kiss?
Yeah.
Hey, this is that girl
you got really excited about.
Nikaido Rui.
First of all, tell me how right I was.
What? Does that mean their member
Mitsuya Yuki is our Yuki?
But you met her, right? And it wasn't her.
Something's fishy.
It's been a while since this
phone's owner went missing, right?
Yeah, which means there's no way she's okay.
Hey! Pay up.
C'mon. You gotta trust me.
Fine. I'm sorry for doubting you.
But you tell me the truth, got it?
I'm telling you, I don't know.
I've never said a word about your business.
If something happened,
"I don't know" isn't gonna cut it.
My own guys are looking everywhere for
that girl right now, but we can't find her.
She's about to debut, y'know?
We ain't happy about this, either.
Why are you suddenly so
interested in her, anyway?
Little girl idol groups aren't for us.
We shouldn't be involved in business
that's likely to cause trouble.
I'm worried about her because
she's my friend's daughter.
Boss, um, about the girl—
Sekiguchi, did I ask you a question?
Yano, even if you're not involved, try doing
anything that makes you look suspicious.
You'll be tripped up by the cops
and other groups.
I know. I'll be careful.
Meanwhile, Dobu still thinks
he can rely on brawn
and is talking about some crackpot
job that'll make him a billion yen.
We used to do so well back then.
What happened to us?
A billion?
Be careful what you say
about other people's work, boss.
Why are you suddenly so
interested in Odokawa?
We can't rule it out as a possibility.
But there's no evidence of that.
It's a false accusation.
We don't even know if it's Odokawa
the police are questioning.
So, where are we going?
Here. This is where they practice.
Seriously? This stinks of overtime.
You said you'd help me.
Sorry! Thanks for waiting!
Ready for overtime.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kanon.
I'm Sato.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
You, too.
What?
I'm Sato. Nice to meet you.
Quit it.
Cool, huh?
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Try touching it.
Why?
It's hard.
You're right. It's so hard.
I wrapped it myself.
Uh-huh.
Rena-san, how'd you figure this out?
I just looked for someplace a small
agency's three-woman idol group
could practice together.
Uh-huh.
They haven't made their mainstream
debut yet, so privacy isn't that important.
Also, they probably still need
to come up with choreography
and will need to use the space frequently,
so it has to offer either discounts
or reasonable prices.
Also, it should be either along their
agency's transit line, or easy to reach by taxi.
You're totally a detective.
Totally a detective.
Ew, no.
Good work, everyone.
Thank you.
When are we meeting next week?
Can you see them?
Yeah, totally.
The other two are surprisingly cute, too.
You're on Shimura. I've got Mitsuya.
You're on Nikaido.
You'll make your train, right?
Yes.
Okay, good night.
They're leaving, right?
Yeah, let's go.
I'm counting on you.
Roger that.
One, please.
Any seat you prefer?
911.
I might be able to get her
real name at reception.
911. Got it.
I might be able to get her
real name at reception.
Nikaido Rui lives in a luxury high-rise apartment!
Here you are.
Thank you.
Nikaido Rui lives in a luxury high-rise apartment!
She entered a restaurant with a middle-aged man.
Can I help you?
Bet he's her sugar daddy.
What?
If you could fill in this form—
Oh, I'm good. Sorry.
I'm good. Excuse me.
Are you meeting someone?
Yes.
Sorry.
It's fine. I wasn't expecting
to get to eat at a place like this.
So, how's it look?
Like I said, that's her sugar daddy.
Look at how unenthusiastic she is.
Excuse me.
Could I get another glass, please?
Yes, sir.
So, uh, I got you something.
I hope you like it.
Huh. Thanks.
Shiho-chan, when are you the happiest?
When I'm in the bath.
Is the bath at your house
as amazing as I think it is?
Can you stretch your legs out?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
Its got jets and stuff. Of course it does.
Really?
Can you watch TV from the bath, too?
Of course.
Does the water come out of a lion's head?
A lion?
Shiho. So that's Ichimura Shiho.
I can't figure out what she's after.
Just money, right?
But isn't it risky for an idol
to use her real name?
I'm sure they've all got side gigs.
I bet only a handful of girls
make enough just off performing.
Some girls who play in bands
at my place also work as entertainers.
She could at least use a fake name.
Are they making her do it on purpose?
To create something to blackmail her with.
The question is, who's making her do it?
Is it a man?
Or her agency.
Her agency?
Shiho-chan, do you actually
want to get married?
Yeah. It's always been
my dream to get married.
I think the sooner I can, the better.
Being surprised with an
engagement ring would be amazing.
A ring.
Yeah.
In that case, would you—
Hey, look at this.
It says he won one billion yen.
Do you think it's true?
One billion yen, huh? Wow.
Not even I have that much.
He's a Nikaido Rui fan, huh?
Are you getting married or engaged?
Actually, uh...
Would you like to see the back?
Taeko-san wants to see you, Rena-san.
How much have you been drinking on your own?
You just don't understand
how I feel, Rena-san.
Sorry I'm not more considerate.
I feel sick.
Here.
Pull yourself together.
Why is Ichimura Shiho
meeting Odokawa's friend?
Kakihana-san? He was there yesterday, too.
And?
So he was there yesterday.
He's a regular there.
He was complaining about
how expensive rings are.
That's it? Why do you
even bother going there?
Then share more of your information with—
Ow!
I'll be back.
See you later.
See you later!
Hey, why do you think an active
idol would have a sugar daddy?
Is it possible that she needs the money?
Kanon said the same thing. It's possible...
But that Ichimura girl
seemed unhappy to be there.
Someone must be making her do it.
I definitely don't think
Yuki would allow it to happen.
So Mitsuya Yuki found out about it
and was killed when she tried to quit?
Killed? Don't say stuff like that.
Sorry.
It could be that she just wanted to
be alone and left the country.
Has she always been that kind of person?
Or else someone is keeping her quiet,
or she's being held captive somewhere.
No way. A lot of time has passed
already. That can't be...
She's alive. She's definitely alive.
Wanna stop by Taeko's place tonight?
Nah. I'm working tonight.
Hey, don't.
Why not? Taeko said she
misses seeing your face.
Are you listening, Kakihana?
I had fun the other day! Good luck at work
Hey.
Hey, good to see you again.
How're you doing?
Yeah, great.
Hey.
Good to see you.
Is 50 enough?
Yup.
You good?
It's cold tonight.
My wallet's feeling a bit drafty, too.
Give 'em a kick in the ass.
My girls are working hard, you know.
Why can't I win the lottery or something?
Just kidding.
What?
Haven't you heard?
Everyone's talking about it online.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Apparently one of our oldest fans
won a billion yen in the lottery.
Tell me more about that.
I think I'm going crazy
from looking at too many cats.
Enough. These definitely
aren't the right cat.
But I think I'm starting to see it.
Rena, you got a second?
Good morning.
Morning!
What is it?
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
What are you talking about?
You'll never survive unless you
work on your shadowing skills.
I understand how you feel after all
you've seen over the past few days.
Why don't you take a little vacation?
Why?
If you don't, I'm firing you.
Is that your decision, boss?
Yes.
Then I quit.
What?
Sato and I are quitting.
Not Sato.
What?
Fine.
As of today, I no longer work for you.
You have nothing to do
with my future investigations.
But until I find my footing,
I'm going to keep using my desk,
computer, and other equipment.
I'll pay whatever it costs.
What do you mean? I don't understand.
Fine.
Well, you understood.
You can do whatever you want,
but in exchange, I can't protect you.
You got that?
Yes.
He's actually real.
So, this is Imai-kun's place?
Yeah.
Detectives are amazing.
They know everything.
More like he made everything public,
including the fact that he won a billion yen.
He might just be an idiot.
Okay, let's check it out.
What are we trying to find out about Imai?
I thought he might know
something about Yuki.
He's one of Mystery Kiss' oldest fans.
Also, the driver I was investigating
frequently looks for passengers around here,
so he's probably given him a ride.
Here?
Is this it?
What's this? You two are really cute.
You interested in our place?
A little, I guess?
Oh, I know. You need money, don't you?
Is there an Imai-san here?
Yeah. He's working today.
You wanna see him?
Can we?
Show them inside.
Watch your step.
Okay.
Next Time
What did Mitsuya-san learn that day?
I won one billion yen!
My only clues are the calls from Nikaido.
Every encounter and parting
of ways is inevitable.
I'm a huge Rui-tan fan.
This show is a work of fiction.
I've never given you a ride, have I?