Sorry I'm late today.
You're still homeless, huh?
This nation really will fall
due to incompetent politicians.
Those damn nepo-baby Diet members—
Mom, I've been wondering.
Why do you turn off the TV?
Because we're gonna eat.
Come on, sit up straight.
You always turn off the TV
when Donraku comes on.
We promised not to talk about that anymore.
We used to have tons of pictures of him up.
How long are you gonna hide it?
I might see him in Tokyo.
I'm saying this for your sake.
Once you grow up, someday you'll
understand, whether you like it or not.
Um, excuse me. Is the
audition in this building?
I dunno. Look it up yourself, why don't you?
Are you auditioning today?
Huh? Uh, yes.
Then let's go together.
Thank you for earlier.
It's totally fine. That map
was impossible to understand.
Yeah. I just came to Tokyo yesterday.
What? Wow.
That must've made it
even harder to understand.
Where are you from?
Oita.
Is that why your backpack's so big?
I even packed everything I need.
What? Really?
You didn't bring anything?
Oh, right. I didn't notice.
You seem so calm. You're not nervous at all.
I actually just noticed
since you mentioned it,
but I seem to have forgotten my bag
at home because I was so nervous.
What? Seriously?
I'm Mitsuya Yuki. Nice to meet you.
I thought if I became an idol
I'd be able to meet my dad.
That's a nice dream.
I'm sure it'll come true.
Why did you audition, Mitsuya-san?
I think my reason's a bit like yours.
Like my father, I wanted to
make people laugh and cry.
I wanted to get a job in entertainment
that would let me move people's hearts.
That's amazing! Your dad's an entertainer?
Oh, but I didn't tell him I'm auditioning.
My father said he'd introduce me
to some people in the business he knows,
but then I wouldn't be
doing it myself, you know?
That sounds like a wasted opportunity.
Not at all.
I don't want people to say I only
got the job because of my father.
He honed his art all on his own.
Huh.
I'm kind of jealous.
Oh, sorry. I shouldn't have said all that.
Sorry. Forget what I said.
It's totally fine. I'm used to it.
It'd be great if we both passed the audition.
I had the same thought!
Really?
Sorry, I know this was sudden!
It's fine.
I was glad to hear from you, Mitsuya-san.
So, listen...
Yeah?
I got a call after that.
Yeah.
They called me in for a final screening.
Really? That's great!
I wanted to tell you in person.
What about you, Sakura-chan?
Did you get your results yet?
No, nothing.
Then you still have a chance.
Really?
They're still deciding.
They didn't tell me anything else.
But I'm sure you'd pass another audition.
Yeah. I'm broke, so I can't
even go back home now.
If it comes to it, I'll ask
my father if he has any ideas.
What does your dad do?
Oh, right. Sorry.
You don't have to hide it.
It's embarrassing.
What? Why? You should hold your head high.
You passed the audition on your own merits.
My dad is a storyteller.
Do you know about rakugo?
Yeah.
He's on TV a lot.
He had a reputation for casually
saying things that upset people,
so I was a little embarrassed about it.
Maybe you know him. His name is Donraku.
Huh...
Mitsuya Yuki
...High School, Saitama...
Running Long Jump - Final Group 1
Mitsuya Yuki
Donraku
Donraku TV
Donraku child
...has commitment issues and previously
acknowledged affairs in the past.
...influential rakugo storyteller Master Shofutei Donraku.
Previously divorced...? A deep dive!
...children also storytellers?
Rakugo storyteller Shofutei Donraku-san...
...results of our investigation
revealed their identities...
secret lovechild
Donraku
...Master Shofutei Donraku has multiple secret children...
"I don't need to apologize!"
[Shofutei Donraku Interview Part Two]
[Shofutei Donraku Interview Part Two] Cheating and infidelity.
Living Room Advisor – Shofutei...
...denies numerous allegations.
What is it, Mom?
A letter arrived for you.
It said it was from a place
called Gray Dog Agency.
It finally arrived.
It must be the audition results.
I know that.
How?
Because I opened it right away.
Oh, right.
Mom?
"After a fair and impartial review,
we regret to inform you that
you did not pass the audition."
"The judges hope to see you try again should
the opportunity present itself," apparently.
What? That's it?
Right?
I thought there must be some mistake, so
I called them, but they wouldn't talk to me.
You should be able to pass
any audition you go out for.
You only live once.
You gotta do whatever it takes
to make your dreams come true.
Idol project "Mystery Kiss"
debut & debut concert announced!
Why did I fail?!
What? Who are you?
I'm Wadagaki. Wadagaki Sakura.
We met at the audition.
Oh, uh...
How can I get in?
Um, you know, we're a small agency that
was just established. We're short-staffed.
Three girls is the most we can look after.
Sakura-chan?
If I wasn't chosen to be one of them,
then I'd like to know why!
I don't remember the exact reason. Sorry.
Mitsuya-san.
What?
What about Mitsuya-san?
Mitsuya?
Um...
Come on. Let's go.
Oh, right. I remember now.
You were the runner-up behind Mitsuya.
You were so close.
If only you had a bit more charm.
Oh, I know. We're going to
hold another audition.
Why don't you practice until then?
I'll be in touch. Thanks.
Let's get going.
Take a 15-minute break, and then we'll
check your formation on the next pass.
Okay.
That girl was kind of crazy.
Who?
She was so desperate to know why she failed.
What? Of course she was desperate.
What's crazy about that?
You know, your dancing is sloppy,
and you're not getting any better.
Do you even want to do this?
My house is too cramped
to practice on my own.
Oh, really? That must be so hard for you.
You're full of excuses. That other girl
was way more motivated than you.
Hey, come on.
Is this really worth getting worked up about?
If you're so unmotivated,
why don't you just quit?
I told you, my family's actually really poor.
I need the money, so I'm not quitting.
Quit it, you two.
You know, you talk about auditioning, but
you've known the manager for a long time.
Sounds super shady to me.
Hey, come on. The three of us
are going to be a team.
Let's try to work together, okay?
Why should I? I don't have time for that.
I've been trying to this whole time.
We've been forced to bend to her every whim.
Maybe, but we're going to have to
work together like this for a while.
You're too soft. Someone needs
to give it to her straight.
Fine. Then you should go solo, Nikaido-san.
I want to go as far as I can with this team.
Maybe it's selfish,
but I understand how both of you feel,
and I want to respect that.
What's your deal?
If anything comes up,
let me know by call or text.
Good night.
Here.
What?
Sorry about earlier.
Nikaido-san, you eat this stuff, too?
Today is special.
Thanks.
Why did you two want to become idols?
I don't have my own room at home.
The bathtub's the only place
I can call my own.
So I want to move to a place with a huge tub.
In other words, I want to be rich.
Huh, I see.
You won't be able to afford a big tub
if you're barely managing the choreography.
I wish you at least wouldn't
hold me or Mitsuya-san back.
Sorry.
You're struggling with the B part, right?
I'll show you a trick to doing it.
Thanks, I think.
What about you, Mitsuya-san?
Why an idol?
Yeah.
From watching my dad, I think.
God, just how much of a good girl are you?
You think?
There aren't many girls like you these days.
Okay, let's try smiling more now.
Nice. Could you come forward?
This girl's got a powerful aura.
She's gonna be big.
I know Nikaido is a winner, too.
Actually, since her previous agency—
Oh, not her. This girl.
This Mitsuya girl.
Oh, yeah.
It's like she's on another level.
Like I told you before, Yamamoto-chan...
Yes.
I feel like Mitsuya-san was born
with something different.
She's gonna turn into something incredible.
Sounds good to me.
Nikaido's talented. As long as she
supports her, they'll make a good team.
Good morning. Good to see you again.
Good morning.
What? A debut tour?
Yeah. I worked really hard for this.
But I still don't have
the choreography down yet.
Oh, uh...
What is this?
Oh, um...
That's the artist photo we're gonna go with.
Be direct with them, Yamamoto-kun.
Mitsuya is going to be the center.
You girls back her up
and make Mystery Kiss big.
MAIN A Photo
Thank you.
Let's book all the domes. All of them!
What's the meaning of this?
Sorry, but the situation has changed.
This isn't what you promised!
Let me explain it you sometime.
I'm home!
How could you be so selfish?
I'm discussing it with you
right now, aren't I?
Dad, are you home?
I think Yuki's ready to meet them.
This is a difficult time for Yuki.
She can't do that.
Besides, if people find out about
your relationships from that time—oh?
Yuki?
Say something if you're home.
You're one of the top ten most
streamed artists in Japan right now.
That's incredible.
Because of the incident,
not because of our talent.
So, have you given any thought to the future?
Yes. I came here today with the intention
of signing on with your agency.
Me, too.
I actually put together a plan for your
future activities and upcoming schedule.
Wow.
That said, I'm not ready yet emotionally—
We're currently negotiating
for you to keep your name.
You'd be either the New Mystery Kiss or this.
Kiss Miss
What? Ugh, no way.
I certainly hope we can!
Oh, would I continue using
the same stage name?
What? You mean Mitsuya Yuki?
Yes.
I don't know about that.
Then could I get an advance on my rent?
Yeah, sure.
I look forward to working with you.
Yeah!
It's strange, isn't it?
Lost Cat!
Nobody paid attention to us before.
But I'm glad things turned out this way.
You are? I didn't like it before,
but now I want to wear a mask again.
I'd rather appear on TV
without being recognized.
Lately I feel like all kinds of people
are watching me, and it's scary.
Isn't that what it means to be an idol?
You mentioned wanting to
keep using Mitsuya-san's name.
Can't I?
You were serious? Isn't that kind of crazy?
Hey. Time to eat.
At first glance, they seemed
to be enjoying brilliant careers
in the entertainment industry,
but on the inside...
On the inside—
I realized something.
We couldn't stay here and keep
allowing ourselves to be exploited.
That's why we took our masks off.
We want people to see our real faces.
It was a difficult time.
I thought I'd become an idol, but
not only was I forced to wear a mask,
I had to get dinner every night
with a strange man my father's age.
I was paid to do it.
Sorry.
My dad abandoned my mom a long time ago.
I've never met my real father.
That's why I decided to become an idol.
If you're watching this, Dad, contact me.
I knew they'd be on their guard.
So, you were questioned?
I made it through that fine,
but I heard something interesting.
A few stray cats have died
around that apartment.
What are you looking at?
The video we took that day.
Watch the office.
The lights are on.
And then they go out.
Huh? Wait a minute.
Hey! What are you doing?
Found it.
Do you always have to be so loud?
This is before Nikaido entered the office.
23:47. 23:21.
Huh? You're right.
Hello? One moment, please.
Which means...
What does it mean?
Rena-chan, phone for you. It's Donraku-san.
Huh? Sakura-chan?
Mitsuya-san, why are you here?
What are you doing here?
I don't have anywhere to stay right now.
What? Do you want to stay at my place, then?
You're a really nice person.
I'm flat broke.
I figured I'd be lucky
if I could spend one night here.
It was pouring earlier, you know?
I jumped into a taxi.
I didn't think I'd be able
to get in so easily.
You don't have a home?
Not right now, so I'm prepared
to live anywhere.
We exchanged contact information.
You could've called me anytime.
What are you doing here
at this hour, Mitsuya-san?
Oh...
It's not work, is it?
Nikaido-san asked me to come.
Nikaido?
She's a girl in my group.
Huh. Why?
Probably because I might become the center.
The center?
Yeah.
Nikaido-san's been doing this a long time,
so I think she assumed it would be her.
Oh, so you stole the best position from her.
I didn't take anything from her.
I don't really get it either,
but it's people like the producer
who make those decisions.
I'm hoping we can talk it out
and resolve any misunderstandings.
Is it really a misunderstanding?
I'm glad you're here, though.
I felt anxious on my way here.
Ever since we met, for some reason
I've felt strangely at ease when I'm with you.
Huh.
I wonder if Nikaido-san will get here soon.
I was supposed to become you.
Hello? Is this Wadagaki Sakura-san's phone?
Who is this?
I'm Yamamoto of Gray Dog, Inc.
I wanted to discuss something with you.
Yamamoto-san? I don't know
what you're talking about.
What? That's odd.
Didn't you audition with us?
Did you join another agency after that?
What? No, nothing like that.
If you haven't changed your mind, I'd like
to meet with you in person and talk again.
Really?
Are you really quitting?
Next Time
She's claiming to be his
18-year-old biological child.
Do you remember who you
drove on October 4th?
Someone else killed Yuki.
Dad!
Where to?
This show is a work of fiction.