When did you receive these messages?
Just yesterday.
She's claiming to be his
18-year-old biological child.
This is a threat.
She wants to meet in person to confirm their
relationship, or she'll ruin the performance.
Scary.
We've experienced weird messages
and unhinged fans before,
but this isn't a good time for that.
You need the police or a lawyer.
We can't do anything for you.
We've received a ton
of nonsensical messages.
The police think it's some kind of prank
and won't do anything about it.
There's nothing they can do if it's
just threats to ruin the show.
Since Yuki's death, I've been receiving
more messages slandering me.
The entertainment industry sounds rough.
But thankfully, we've been getting more
supportive and encouraging messages as well.
People have always sent me their thoughts
on my shows or new rakugo scripts.
But this is no joke.
I guess the silver lining is that I don't know
the first thing about computers.
The most I do is occasionally
check my own videos.
What? You mean you don't write
your own posts on social media?
This guy writes all of them.
What?
Since we spend so much time together,
I can guess what he'd say.
If I really got into it, it'd get out of hand.
Actually, sometimes you get flamed pretty—
Enough about that.
Any idea who it might be?
Don't tell my wife.
I don't want to put anymore
emotional strain on her.
You know who it is?
A secret lovechild.
It's not a secret anymore, though.
And I only have one child
outside my marriage.
A man who grew up a long time ago.
Hello.
Why is this happening?
It's not my fault, right?
Hello?
What? Odokawa-san's...
My place has been empty.
Once you're out of the hospital,
you need to stop by for drinks.
Excuse us.
What? Rena-chan?
Sorry, who are you?
The rabbit from Imai-san's cabaret club.
I think you called me a Polish.
Oh, right.
Do you remember who you
drove on October 4th?
That girl from Mystery Kiss. The black cat.
Is this her?
I don't know. It doesn't match up
with people's faces.
Do you not remember Wadagaki Sakura's face?
Rena-chan, that's enough. I don't
want to cause him anymore trouble.
But if Odokawa-san is the only witness—
It's okay. I'll protect Odokawa-sama.
I owe him for getting my billion yen back.
You can count on me. Okay?
This is what I've investigated...
I summarized everything
I know about Yuki.
Huh.
Look at this right here.
See? It went out.
You're trying to say someone entered
the office before them, right?
Yes.
You can certainly see a silhouette, but...
I saw the news.
They say something might've
happened before Nikaido arrived.
You mean someone else might've killed her.
This backs up the time Nikaido gave, huh?
Isn't Nikaido Rui saying the same thing?
She's got nerves of steel.
She's never changed her story.
She hasn't committed murder. Am I wrong?
Abandoning a body is still a crime.
Someone else killed Yuki.
There's the messages Donraku-san received
and Odokawa-san's testimony.
They should be on the dash
cam data you collected, too.
Wadagaki Sakura said on TV
that she's looking for her father.
Hang on, do you really think this
is something you can figure out?
That driver has visual agnosia, doesn't he?
That casts doubt on his eyewitness testimony.
But we've brought you evidence.
Okay.
We're getting nowhere. Let's go, Rena-san.
We've already got plenty of evidence,
so take this with you.
Thank you.
I told you, you don't have to come with me.
If someone were trying to kill me,
I'd already be dead.
Then I'll hire a bodyguard for you
for as long as I can afford it.
I won't be able to work with a bodyguard.
I appreciate everything you've done,
but leave me alone.
Will she really come?
It's worth a shot.
I'll be waiting at this plaza on
January 10th. -Donraku
Are you sick?
Don't you have a bad feeling about this?
Remember that analysis we asked
Sekido-san to run the other day?
What?
On Wadagaki's cat food.
Oh, right. The one full of fertilizer?
Yeah, that.
I licked a little while I was on a stakeout.
What are you doing?
Actually, I ate it.
Dad!
She's here.
What?
Wadagaki.
Dad.
You're not him.
Wadagaki-san.
Rena-chan? What are you doing here?
I came to stop you.
Stop me? From doing what?
It's not too late to turn back.
Where's my dad? Where's Donraku-san?
I just wanted to meet him once.
He doesn't remember you.
I see. I've heard he
has kids all over the place.
But Donraku's only daughter was Yuki.
Has he forgotten about me?
He didn't forget about you.
Listen, Wadagaki-san.
I don't have parents, either.
But I've managed somehow. You could still—
You're not even an idol. You're nothing.
I have to do whatever it takes
to make my dream come true.
It already came true.
Not yet. I need to make sure.
So you're okay with killing people?
That's what my mom said, though.
That I'd make a good idol.
What?
Stay out of my way.
Watch out!
Hey! Sato! Sato!
Wait!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Wait! Wait!
Hello, Mom?
I thought I'd get to see Dad,
but it didn't work out.
Dad?
Isn't my dad Donraku-san?
The rakugo storyteller.
I finally got in touch with him.
There you go again.
More importantly,
I saw you on TV again today.
You should go back to
wearing the purple outfit.
I understand you don't want
to talk about it, but...
I don't want to hear about Donraku.
I knew it.
Have you forgotten?
I've been saying that for your sake,
so why are you digging up the past now?
What?
Your dad left us because he admired Donraku.
Seeing Donraku reminded you of
your father. It's hard for me, too.
You understand that, don't you?
He left me to take care of you by myself.
Hey Mom, that can't be right!
Enough! No more of this talk.
Why do you think I let you go to Tokyo?
It certainly wasn't to look for your father!
I entrusted all my dreams to you.
I'm disappointed.
Yeah, I transferred to a bigger agency.
Yeah. Things are going so well,
it's almost scary.
At first, I hounded the manager
after I failed an audition.
Thinking about it now makes me laugh.
I was frustrated, though.
If they hadn't become famous after that,
I think I would've been content.
But when I heard they'd be making their
major debut, I couldn't sit still anymore.
Yeah, everything's going well.
All I headed out to do was find the taxi
I rode in then, but I think I found it.
It was a total coincidence.
I must be lucky after all.
Everything's going my way.
Like you said, I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to make my dream come true.
Excuse me. This road is closed to traffic.
Closed to Traffic
Detour
Hello.
Long time, no see.
Where have you been?
Uh, in the hospital? I've got a bad back.
You still owe us a lot of money.
I'll pay you this week.
Let's go.
Wait.
I promise I'll pay you back
by the end of the month.
Where to?
It suddenly started raining that day, too.
I hopped into the first taxi I saw.
You don't remember me?
Sorry.
It's fine. I just thought you'd
freak out a little more.
So, where to?
Here's fine.
"Here's fine"?
Yeah, here's fine.
The city's full of cameras, you know?
Cameras?
Where's the guy with the money?
He'll be here soon. Yup.
Shut your face.
You're not making any sense.
All I've got is my good luck.
Oh, yeah? I'm lucky, too.
Then it's my luck against your luck.
Odokawa, I gotta ask you for a—
What? Hey, wait!
When he saw his taxi driver friend
being attacked by a suspicious person,
Letter of Appreciation
Kakihana Eiji-dono
he risked his life to defend—
Nice work.
I came today because
I'm quitting the agency soon.
It's all there. Are you
paying for this yourself?
Thank you for everything you've done.
Anyway, I'd like to dispose of the GPS
and stuff you installed for me before.
Oh, crap. I forgot about that.
I already took care of it.
I can't believe you turned it in
to the police as evidence.
I'm getting reamed from all directions
because of you two.
I'm really sorry.
Sorry.
By the way, did you look through
all the data I gave you before?
From the dead high school girl's phone.
No. I thought it would be too painful.
But there's something you've
gotta do before you quit.
What?
He's stubborn, isn't he?
He never listens to me.
You're really not going to do it?
Is the naming really that big a deal?
I'm just reaping what I sowed.
I doubt the world will forgive me.
Who cares about the world?
You should do what you want.
I think Yuki would be sad to hear that.
I've got too many things I can't say.
In public I act like I say whatever I want,
but I had too many secrets
I didn't want Yuki to know.
I wish I could've talked to her more
while she was still alive.
This is the data that was on Yuki's phone.
I think you could wait to decide
until after you've seen it.
Can you see me?
Wow, what a personal question.
My family is... kind of complicated.
My dad is a distinguished man, and
my mom basically raised me on her own.
That makes her pretty great, too.
Since coming to Tokyo, I've had more
opportunities to spend time with him.
I really wish we could all live together.
There's always been distance
between us and my dad,
and my mom and I used to fight
about it all the time.
Once, my mom was so angry that she only
put rice and pickled plums in my lunch.
My dad's experienced a lot
of twists along his road, but...
I've seen how he keeps
plugging along despite it.
Now I wish I could see
the same sights he does,
and I'd be happy if he worked even harder
to show our family even
more incredible sights.
If you ever feel like coming back,
we'd love to have you.
I'm off.
See you later.
Rena-san!
You're quitting? For real?
For real, yeah.
Will I ever see you again?
Oh, right. Are you interested in rakugo?
What?
Shofutei Hiraku
Hey, we're sitting next to each other! Nice!
Yeah, because I bought the tickets together.
Sorry I'm late.
I managed to finish up and make it here.
Thank you.
What? It's not just us today?
What? I was originally supposed
to go with just Rena-chan.
Hello!
Nice to meet you. You're so cute!
Wow, looks like everyone's here.
Shall we?
I guess I'll sit—
Oof.
Excuse me, Rena-san.
Our seats are great.
Yeah.
Shofutei
Hiraku
All day and night, the news has been
digging into my family matters,
so I didn't think anyone would show up today.
But if this many of you have gathered here,
then it's like they say. Another man's
misfortune is like honey.
Looks like a lot of people
wanted to see Donraku squirm.
No, wait. I'm not Donraku anymore.
I've been given the great
name of Shofutei Hiraku.
That makes me the third.
I've been named a tomena of my school.
A tomena is the biggest name within
a school. The final destination.
So all that's left is for the name to die.
Hey, Hiraku!
Thank you.
It used to be that out of "drink,
play, buy," I used to do all three.
Because of that, people would tease me
by saying the characters in my
name meant I fall into my drink.
But now, I'm clean. I'm all clean.
A lot of people used to say my
drinking would get me into trouble.
People say all kinds of things,
like alcohol is an addiction,
it's the best medicine,
it'll take years off your life.
But when it becomes a bad habit,
it destroys everything around you.
There used to be a man named Kumagoro.
He was a skilled carpenter.
He was a good person
as long as he didn't drink.
One day he headed out to a funeral
at a temple in Sanya.
Typically they don't
serve alcohol at funerals,
but accommodating temples will
serve alcohol and call it "hannyato."
He had too much of the stuff
and got good and drunk.
Feeling magnanimous, he decided
to head out to Yoshiwara,
where he got to know a working girl.
He had a wife and kid at home,
so naturally, it led to nonstop fighting.
Why don't you settle down and come back?
We can get remarried.
This is a difficult time for her, too.
Hey, I'm actually dealing
with something right now.
I'm sorry, Yuki. Were we too loud?
No. I'm just going out for a walk.
At this hour? You'll turn into a delinquent.
You're one to talk.
Well, you got me there.
My friend said she has
something important to discuss.
I'll be right back.
Be careful!
Okay!
You can't just act like her father
out of nowhere.
You don't have to put it like that.
Sheesh.
After all the selfish crap I've done,
I'm in no position to say this,
but if you want, I'd like the three of us
to live together again like family.
I'm begging you.
Are you serious? Really?
Thank you. I couldn't ask for better.
I'd given up on you.
Kame-chan, Dad's gonna
come back home for you.
The three of us can live together again.
They say children are the clamp that
holds a couple together, but I guess it's true.
What? I'm a clamp?
Oh, I get it now. That's why you said
you'll hit me on the head with a hammer.
That's time. Please set
your writing implements down.
This show is a work of fiction.