Wait. I nearly stepped on a frog.
Frogs are cute.
I don't like their hands.
They're like maple leaves.
These are good.
The new summer flavor is pretty all right.
Senpai, did you know?
The syrup we eat is supposedly fake.
What?
Doesn't that stuff come
from trees? Maples, right?
No. Apparently most of the stuff
they sell at the supermarket is fake.
Huh.
It's kind of sad that you can't be fooled
because you've had the real thing.
Yeah, Yuki's family is rich.
They've had the real stuff.
I bet you guys eat caviar
and steak all the time.
We don't.
You take tons of classes, too, right?
Like dance and voice training.
Sounds rough. Plus, you
run track on top of that.
Lucky. I bet you get to meet boys
from other schools when you take lessons.
Seriously?
Not only that, but your dad
lives in Tokyo, right?
You're winning at life.
You can sleep over all you want, too.
My mom's too strict for that.
Besides, I hardly ever see my dad.
Let's all go to Tokyo together sometime.
That sounds nice.
We can go look for real maple syrup,
get fancy ice cream,
and eat pancakes at a cafe.
Sounds nice.
In that case...
Let's go once Rena-san sets
a new personal record.
You're so disciplined, Yuki.
It'll be a reward.
How can I learn to jump like you?
It's easy. Boing!
Like a frog?
Hey, quit it! I nearly
stepped on one earlier!
Yeah. Just wait. I'll contact you.
I'm really sorry about today. Bye!
Sorry. I know you're busy.
It's fine.
Was that your boyfriend?
No, a customer.
He's a big spender, but he
doesn't know when to shut up.
He's probably trying
to entertain me, but still.
I always feel like it would've been better
if he'd kept his mouth shut, y'know?
Just now, he said he'd blow up
my phone if I didn't respond.
I'm glad you haven't changed, Kanon.
I know it's my job,
but it's a pain in the butt.
So, what'd you want to discuss?
Remember Mitsuya Yuki from
our high school track team?
Oh, yeah. Mitsuya Yuki. Is that right?
What?
Oh, that Yuki!
Yeah. I can't believe you forgot.
I didn't forget!
I've just been busy with my own
stuff since coming to Tokyo.
I don't have time to worry about people
who aren't a threat to my existence.
Thank you.
On Sale December 25th 2021
"Supernatural Love Phenomenon"
Release Event
Step right up.
Wow, thanks!
Okay, here we go.
Could I get pose number two?
Mystery Kiss
Random Can Badges
500 Yen/Play (Max. 10)
Mystery Kiss
Supernatural Love Phenomenon CD
This one? Sure.
Thank you.
Okay, here we go. Say cheese.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Next person.
Buy a CD now and receive a Polaroid voucher!
You still have time!
We're never going to
be popular, Ichimura-san.
As long as we're wearing masks,
we won't get fans like Nikaido-san.
I wouldn't get fans
even if I removed mine.
You desperately need more
self-esteem, Ichimura-san.
I used to perform unmasked,
and this is where I ended up.
If anything, it'd be crazy
if I had any self-esteem.
Wow. I've never experienced
anything like this.
It's not that different
from the nightlife business.
Can we go talk to them?
Can I help you?
Um, we're huge fans of Mystery Kiss.
Yes, that's right.
Really?
Oh, yes.
I'm so glad. We don't
have many female fans.
They say people who make it
are loved by men and women alike.
Yeah.
Um, Mitsuya-san?
Yes?
You're my favorite, Mitsuya-san.
Seriously?
Yes. I love you.
Really? Thanks!
What do you like about me?
Your dancing, of course, but you've
got this brilliant aura about you.
No one's ever told me that before.
She can sense all that when
you're wearing a mask? Crazy.
Right?
But don't you think I'd be
more popular than those two?
What?
Mystery.
Oh, Mitsuya-san.
Yes?
You don't remember me?
I'm sorry. Have we met?
I'm sorry, but today's event
is ending soon.
Oh, okay.
Let's go, Rena. I hope
we meet again someday. Bye!
We'll be waiting.
Thank you.
Even girls like them can become idols, huh?
Didn't seem like they're
very popular, though.
Apparently they get a fair bit of attention.
So, what was up with that Mitsuya Yuki?
Was she an impostor?
Or a stranger with the same name.
With the same age and name?
Yeah.
Huh. I think it's just a stage name.
She'd tell more people about it
if she became an idol.
Besides, she never seemed like
the type to go into the business.
Thanks, Kanon. I appreciate it.
It's fine. The only thing more important to me
than work is a request from you, Rena.
You should just work at my place.
You'd make good money.
Bye.
Sorry. Thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I knew this would happen.
I never imagined she was
your junior from high school.
Either way, all the more reason
for you to stay out of this.
Why won't you let me work an important
case after all the work I've done?
C'mon, you two. Cut it out.
I'm not doing this job to look
after that hopeless newbie.
See you later.
See you.
Have you kept up your
investigation of Odokawa?
Yes.
I tried questioning his neighbors, but
no one would talk to me. I got nothing.
Plus, most of these homes
are empty. Nobody lives there.
I guess you're right.
Besides that, he hasn't done anything
unusual. He's back to his ordinary life.
He mostly operates along set routes.
Oh, right.
He follows these trend-chasing
routes through downtown areas
and in front of TV stations.
Oh, right. Rena-san, how was your junior?
It was someone else.
Well, yeah. If the missing person were
a famous idol, it'd be a bigger story.
But you were so pissy with
the boss. You scared me.
Did you get confused
because she's wearing a mask?
Mitsuya Yuki
Anyway, masked idols sure is a novel concept.
Oh, she's cute.
This center girl's cute.
Let's see. Nikaido Rui, huh?
Oh, shit. I get why those nerds
obsess over them. She's really cute.
Don't forget, someone's gone missing.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're cute, too, Rena-san.
What?
No, that's not right. That was rude of me.
How should I put it?
You're in no way inferior to them.
What is it?
What? No, wait. Personally,
you're exactly my...
Where are you going?
To gather information.
You're coming with me.
I am?
Yes, on Odokawa.
Oh, right! Odokawa. Right.
See you later.
We'll be back!
Also, could you stop sexually harassing me?
Yes?
Ow! Not the jewels!
Yeah, I remember him.
We used to note down passengers'
traits. I saw his notes once.
There was some kind of shareholder meeting,
and we had to handle a ton of passengers.
His report that day just said
monkey, monkey, monkey.
Monkey?
Might've been a gibbon in there, too.
A gibbon?
I know humans and monkeys are similar,
but it gave me the creeps.
It is creepy. Maybe he was
under a lot of stress?
More like he's always been odd.
He can't recognize people's faces
or something. He's crazy.
But he did his job properly?
I guess. Rumor is he's done
a lot of gray work.
What kind of work?
Y'know, gray work. Don't tell anyone I told you.
Her?
Yeah.
Excuse me. May we speak with you?
I'm not selling. Shoo, shoo!
I don't know what's going on these days.
Weird people have been hanging around.
Around where?
There, in that building. The blue one.
Harada Building 3, I think.
Excuse me.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's okay.
We have a few questions.
Could we have a moment of your time?
We're researching neighborhood
connections at the college.
We're asking people for their stories
and about the local history.
You're that guy Dobu beat up.
Dobu? You saw that?
Then why didn't you help me?
You should stay away from them.
So, what'd you want to know?
We heard there's a strange
taxi driver who lives in the area.
Oh, him? Come to think of it,
the other day...
If you want the rest,
it'll cost you at least a hundred yen.
Seriously? You're so greedy.
Here.
The day you were beat up,
I saw a girl getting out of that taxi
driver's car in the middle of the night.
She was real pretty. She was
hiding her face, but I could tell.
I've got good eyes.
Oh. I got a picture of her.
What? Why didn't you say so?
I definitely did! You just weren't listening.
Huh? I'm not sure
there was a taxi, though.
Was this her?
After that, the girl...
She never came out of that building.
Was there anything else unusual?
Normally, nobody goes in or out
of that building at night.
Where's the data?
With Dobu. The pictures are
on the computer that Dobu guy took.
Also, sometimes there's
a huge car parked out front.
Definitely not an honest citizen's car.
Thank you.
Hey, you.
This is one of those things
that are popular now, right?
Some kind of paperweight or yokan.
There's gold in these, right?
Do they sell for a lot?
Ugh, where did you find that?
Wait, where did you find that?
We're with Ibusuki.
We'd like you to restore some data.
Leave it in that drawer.
Depending on the contents,
it could cost you.
Taeko-san, you've got a keen nose.
This taxi driver might be holding
a high school girl captive.
Taeko-san, what do you think?
Would Odokawa-san do something like that?
This isn't what I had in mind
when I asked you to investigate him.
Neither did we when we took the job.
We haven't found conclusive evidence yet.
But he's been in touch with a police officer.
It's possible Odokawa-san
is caught up in the case somehow.
Is there anything else you know?
He said he doesn't wash clothes
that don't directly touch his skin.
In any case, we know Odokawa-san
is an eccentric man.
We'll put together a report on that,
so give us some more time.
Also, Taeko-san, I've been wondering.
Odokawa-san's taxi may have been
parked outside a certain building
the day the girl went missing.
Harada Building 3.
Oh, my.
Does that ring any bells?
It's been about 15 years.
A few major businesses tried to redevelop
the neighborhood. The fighting was intense.
The land sharks came to my place, too.
One of their subsidiary fronts moved in.
They ended up taking
over the whole building.
So this is Harada Building 3.
Harada Building 3
A cram school, an English school,
a dance school, a yoga studio,
and even a capoeira school. What a mess.
Does this place have anything
to do with Odokawa?
What kind of high school girl
takes a taxi to cram school?
You're right.
What's Gray Dog?
Gray Dog, Inc.
It's a talent agency.
A talent agency?
What do you want? I told you,
I won't work for you.
Odokawa-kun, let's go for a drive.
Sure thing. You'll pay
your fare, won't you?
Good to see you again, Dobu-san.
Yano. I see you've still got
a crowd of groupies.
How am I supposed to get in?
Unlike someone I know,
my popularity has grown.
The only thing that's grown to make up for
your lack of substance is your shamelessness.
Hey, you two! Cut it out.
So, what happened with Odokawa?
I paid him a visit, but I'm
not satisfied with the results.
No leads?
I even reached out to
the police, but nothing yet.
More importantly, isn't the bigger problem
that Yano might be involved?
How long has it been?
About 20 minutes.
Since you got out of prison.
The tenth anniversary of my uncle's death
was the other day, so five or six years.
Don't you think it's time you got
used to the way the world is now?
We don't use this anymore.
We use this now.
I'm not changing my ways.
You're too old.
You can't be a lone wolf forever.
My underlings are at your disposal, you know.
Forget about me, boss. How's your health?
I'm doing better.
Maybe it's thanks to the sauna.
I'm scared of change, which is why I'm
thinking of leaving things up to you boys.
I have an announcement to make.
I, Taichi Kabasawa, will capture
Dobu by the end of the year!
For those of you who don't know who Dobu is,
I'm not sure if he's a thug or yakuza member,
but the police are after him.
As a matter of fact, I know people
who were beaten half to death by Dobu.
I'll put off finding a job
and my schoolwork to catch him!
What will I do once I catch him?
He'll apologize. I'll make him apologize.
Apologize?
I'll upload a video of him
on his knees. I'll rehabilitate him.
Nice.
If the law can't punish him, then I will!
Yeah!
No, we will. Including you,
person watching this video.
Together, we'll catch Dobu!
How did this boring crap go viral?
I'm Meisei University
student Taichi Kabasawa!
What? Don't you think it's amazing?
He said he'd catch Dobu.
I won't run. I won't hide.
I'll stand in the line of fire.
He's probably never paid
for his mistakes before.
So I'm accepting any
and all information. Help me.
See you later.
Crimes must be punished.
Together we shall defeat evil!
Is this Dobu-san really that famous?
Thank you.
Justice will win!
Apparently he's committed
every evil act under the sun.
Thank you very much.
I had no idea someone so dangerous
picked a fight with me.
Should you be bragging about that?
What was a big shot like him doing
wandering around there, anyway?
You mean Dobu?
Yeah. And send me the link
to Kabasawa's video.
I'm going to make an appointment.
What? An appointment?
I wouldn't meet with someone like him.
Hey. I heard you guys
have been visiting Sekido.
I never approved that.
Sorry.
I told you so.
Finding the high school girl is my job.
Your job is running a background
check on that taxi driver.
Private eyes don't find fault
with or judge people.
There's no need for us
to put ourselves in danger.
Danger? What do you mean, danger?
What happened to Mitsuya-san—
to Yuki after that?
They canceled the investigation.
Apparently, they heard from her.
So I want you to leave this
Mitsuya Yuki business alone. Got it?
Ow! That totally opened my cut.
Is that thing your favorite?
Huh?
You're always touching it.
Do I? I never noticed.
It's cute.
No way.
That's the first time
anyone's called it cute.
I put something ugly on it
so no one would steal it.
But maybe I've grown attached to it.
Then could I have that keychain
when you graduate?
But you've already got everything, Yuki.
What else was I supposed to do?
But why'd you end the investigation?
Because he said he heard from her.
We can't trust anything that manager says.
She would've told us
if she wanted to move out.
Maybe she heard about your past.
You really think so?
At least once, every man should go home
and earnestly face his wife and kids.
It's not like he brings home the bacon.
Feet.
Hey.
Hey, wait! You need to be careful with that.
That thing? What is that?
Yeah.
What is that creepy thing
that emits uniquely evil vibes?
How could you?
You're the one who bought that weird
keychain from a homeless person.
What? Are you saying that's not weird?
It's my lucky treasure boat eraser.
My dad bought it for me in grade school
when he went to China.
Sounds fishy to me.
Rare things started coming my way
since I acquired it.
Like what?
Like a La Sagrada Familia eraser
and a Leaning Tower of Pisa eraser.
Just erasers?
At the time, collecting erasers
was all the rage.
We were really competitive about it.
I looked for an eraser rarer
than my friend's dodo eraser.
What was it?
The world's only Donraku eraser.
Donraku?
I talked to my dad
and bid on an online auction.
We went back and forth for a while,
until suddenly they bid 100,000 yen.
That's when I dropped out.
Kids are bidding 100,000 yen on erasers?
What's the world coming to?
Seriously. I'm glad I didn't buy it.
Wow, you got a 50-50 right for once.
It's not like I always choose wrong.
You don't know that.
There's no way to know at the time
if you're making the right choice or not.
True. In that case, every wrong
choice I've made until now
could turn into successes by the time I die.
Optimistic, aren't you?
Was Donraku that much of a celebrity?
He was handsome when he was younger.
Had a wild side, though.
You're too young to know, huh?
Yup.
I watched his show every week.
Same.
I laughed so hard it made my stomach hurt.
These days it's like a talk show
with a prominent rakugo storyteller.
My mom got really mad at me.
She said, "Why's my ugly idiot
son watching this low-brow crap?"
Ugly idiot? You're kidding, right?
Excuse me, Donraku-san.
Next Time
Turns out he was just an ordinary old man.
Love is...
Did something happen to you?
We all have high hopes for you,
Kabasawa-sama.
What is it, driver?
I feel like I've seen her before.
This show is a work of fiction.
And if I say no?
I'll kill you.