I heard they're only having
one person compete in the long jump.
What? Then it's gotta be Rena-senpai.
She's been practicing every morning lately.
No, it could be Yuki. Have you
seen her recent numbers?
But she's still a first-year.
Let's go.
Gather round, track team!
We've chosen our lineup, so take a look.
This next meet will be the third-years' last.
Even if you're not competing, make sure
you cheer on the rest of the team.
Yes, ma'am.
What? Why? We're both
signed up for the relay.
Are we supposed to start
practicing our baton pass now?
Running Long Jump
Year 2 Year 1 Mitsuya Yuki
But I'm not a team player.
Wait, are all the third-years signed up?
What's wrong, Rena?
I can't accept it.
Didn't you talk to the teacher?
She said I was disrupting the team's harmony.
Wow, that's awful.
All you're doing is focusing on your own
training since we have a meet coming up.
She refused to listen
to anything I had to say.
I have to do well.
You mean for college?
Exemptions from school fees can be huge.
Why don't you try talking to Yuki?
Yuki's training hard, too.
I couldn't say that to her.
I know. I know. Yes. Yes.
Supernatural Love
Phenomenon
Countless times. Yes.
O-One moment, please! Yes.
Hello? Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry. Seems like
we've got a poor signal.
Oh, give me a break. Are you done?
Can you hear me? Huh? Hello? Hello?
Okay, bye. Bye. Yes. Yes.
I'm sorry. Yes. Yes. Thank you.
Do we have a poor signal?
Good afternoon, everyone.
Here you go. Here. Here.
What is this?
I put together a concert set list.
You can't expect us to sing
under these circumstances.
Why aren't you stopping this?
Please. Tickets are selling like crazy.
But...
Could you two leave us for a second?
This can't be good.
I finally learned the
choreography and song, too.
They said we'd only be wearing masks
until Mitsuya-san came back, anyway.
I've been thinking, why don't we
start over at another agency?
I don't want anything to do
with this stuff anymore.
I know. Let's talk downstairs.
Those girls we met the other day...
I trusted you then.
I knew it. That's why you
couldn't call the police.
Who else is there?
How would I know?
You're the one who said it.
What are you talking about?
Maybe I said I wish they were dead,
but that was just a slip of the tongue.
I really didn't do it!
I know that. You have no reason
to lie to me, Nikaido.
Could you stop looking at me like that?
Like you know everything about me.
Why did you show up then, anyway?
Mitsuya called me.
Hello?
Oh, hello.
Why are you calling so late?
Nikaido-san asked me to come to the office.
I'm scared.
Nikaido did?
Yeah. I hope I'm just overthinking it.
Could you come, too, Yamamoto-san?
Where are you now?
I'm on my way there in a taxi.
I'll be there in about 20 minutes.
Fine. I'll be right there.
Huh? Why are you sitting in the dark?
Don't scare me like that, Nikaido.
What?
What is it? What's wrong?
Huh? Mitsuya?
What is this?
What did you...
Wait, wait, wait! How could you do this now?!
We're screwed if people find out about this.
Let me think for a second.
Okay, we're good. We're all good.
I know someone who will do anything
for the right price. No, wait...
Did anyone see you come here?
Did you take the train?
Damn it! I shouldn't have taken a taxi.
I walked.
We need to hire a professional.
It's okay.
Yano-san, what should we do?
Don't give up, man.
I seriously can't with this.
Looks like she was bludgeoned
by a pissed off Nikaido,
then strangled by Yamamoto.
"Never murder no matter how fat
the stacks" is the boss' roots.
Now it's my rule.
But you played fast and loose,
now you went and screwed the pooch.
To me, that's how it looks.
Hey, you. Spread that tarp over there.
Come on.
We're gonna move her. Hurry up.
Okay.
Hey.
Hurry, hurry.
Um, where are we going?
Out to sea, then towards Kawasaki.
Land routes are too dangerous.
What? We're going to toss her into the sea?
She'd come floating back
up right away, idiot.
We're gonna melt her.
Wouldn't that construction site
be a better place to hide her?
That's our last resort.
Last resort?
No one ever resorts to using a last resort.
That land belongs to the group, idiot.
We're doing this without
the higher ups' knowledge.
We're screwed if they find out.
Hurry up or the sun will come up.
Push that side. We'll dump her.
Let's dump her.
Are you okay?
Unbelievable. Yano-san,
could you handle the engine?
What?
Hey!
You idiots! What are you doing?!
Hey, Nikaido, um...
Hello.
What? Yuki?
Yuki! Are you okay?!
Hey! Are you okay?
Someone get a teacher!
Got it!
Yuki? What's wrong?
It's Yuki!
This is bad.
Are you okay? Yuki? Yuki?
Are you okay? Yuki!
Yes?
You came to see me?
Yeah.
Yuki-chan, we're gonna go.
Okay.
We'll visit again before you move.
Thanks. Bye. Thanks.
See you later.
Bye.
Take care.
It's good to see you again.
Good to see you.
I'm amazed she showed her face here.
Right? Talk about shameless.
Yuki, you're moving?
Yeah. I'm transferring schools.
What?
It's not your fault, Rena-san.
I was always planning to move in
with my father who lives in Tokyo.
I see. So, how are you doing?
A lot better. See?
Rena-san, I heard you were suspended.
I'm sorry that happened because of me.
No, uh...
Tokyo, huh? Lucky. I'd love to go hang out.
Kanon-san, you're thinking
of Harajuku, aren't you?
My father's house is in Nerima.
It's not that different from here.
No way! When are you moving?
As soon as I'm out of the hospital.
I see.
Hey, Rena. Yuki said she wanted to see you.
What?
I thought we'd regret not seeing
each other before we parted ways.
Right?
I still like you, Rena-san, so...
Wait, what about me?
Kanon-san, you'll forget
about me before long.
How could you? You know that's not true.
Let's hang out in Tokyo
together sometime, okay?
Agreed!
Right, Rena?
Oh, right. That keychain.
Thank you. I'll treasure it.
It's so cute.
Rena-san? I hope you're not crying.
It'll make it harder to see you again.
Thank you.
Rena-chan, thank you so much
for coming today.
We were just going to invite family, but
we wanted to make an exception for you.
I'm sure Yuki is happy, too.
Thank you for all that you've done.
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything to help.
That's not true at all. You kept
searching for her until the end.
Are you two all right?
Yeah.
I'm relieved Yuki finally came back to us.
Right.
Rena-chan, you can come talk
to us anytime you're hurting.
Um, I did a terrible thing to Yuki-san.
What do you mean?
I'm the one who injured her
on the stairs in high school.
That's in the past.
I liked Yuki.
She was so brilliant, it frustrated me.
I still don't understand what
I did then or why I did it.
It eats away at me so much
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
Yes! I hope you'll come!
I'll pick you up. Okay, thank you!
Excuse me.
Yamamoto-san.
Um, Nikaido-san.
You know why we're here, don't you?
You're under arrest for the murder
of Mitsuya Yuki on December 24th
and abandoning her body.
What? Wait, what do you mean?
On the 30th, police arrested Mystery Kiss
member and suspect Nikaido Rui
who was voluntarily undergoing
questioning for the murder
of fellow group member Mitsuya
Yuki-san and abandoning her body.
The suspect is denying some of the charges.
Suspect Yamamoto
Group manager, suspected of abandoning and
mutilating a corpse with suspect Nikaido Rui
The police have also arrested the group's
manager Yamamoto Fuyuki,
What?
Suspected of Murdering Idol
Fellow Group Member Arrested
Suspect Yano Haruhito (27)
Arrested & detained for one billion yen robbery → Rearrested
Under investigation for involvement in criminal organization
and rearrested self-proclaimed company
managers Yano Haruhito and Sekiguchi Togo,
who were previously arrested and
detained on separate robbery charges,
Suspect Sekiguchi Togo (33)
Arrested & detained for one billion yen robbery → Rearrested
Under investigation for involvement in criminal organization
this time for abandoning
and mutilating a corpse.
I'd like to try disguising myself.
Sure, do it. What?
Hello.
Hello. Feels like it's been a while, huh?
You should've let me know you were coming.
Sorry. The Yuki stuff has calmed down
for now, so I came to tidy up.
What about the future? Have you
already decided what you're going to do?
Not really.
Don't be so secretive.
I've been learning on the job
for a while now,
so I figured I'd do some
classroom learning for a while.
What classroom learning?
You're going to college?
I'll start by getting my
secondary school certificate.
Then I'll study the law properly.
What about an online program?
Then you can keep working while you study.
That's what my second cousin's
husband's sister's friend did,
and she makes tons of money now.
Why don't you do that while
you come back to work for us?
Finding a new investigator would be
a lot of work. Right, boss?
What are you talking about? We've got me.
Who, you? Where?
According to their investigation,
Hey! I'm already right here, aren't I?
police found signs that Mitsuya-san
was struck on the head with a blunt object
You just joined recently.
and strangled with something like a cable.
Also, there was no weapon
found at the crime scene.
Based on the method used,
the police believe the culprit held
a strong grudge against Mitsuya-san
and are currently
questioning multiple people
who may have had interpersonal
issues with the victim.
What happened to you today?
Sorry for suddenly asking to meet.
It's totally fine. It's not like
I have anything else to do.
Everyone's been arrested.
My schedule's wide open.
Thank you for waiting.
Wait, really?
You have my support.
This is so awkward.
Now I'm famous for something weird.
Did you see the news?
Yeah. Sorry I didn't notice.
It's fine. Now I don't have to wear a mask.
I figured out a bunch of things
because you called me the other day.
I wanted to thank you for that today.
Really? You mean about Nikaido-san?
Yeah. It made me realize there are
unimaginably scary things out there.
Wadagaki-san, what are you going to do?
I've actually been recruited
by another agency.
Another agency? You're going
to keep being an idol?
I can't let that bring me down.
It's the reason I came to Tokyo.
I can't go home until
I've accomplished something.
Right.
Besides, I haven't been paid yet.
I can't even get in touch
with the company president.
I've gotten caught in the crossfire.
Crossfire?
Huh?
Come to think of it,
you and Ichimura-san must've been asked
what you were doing the day of the incident.
Yeah. This again?
The police asked me too,
but it was a normal day for me.
I went to my dance lesson,
and then I went home.
Why do you ask?
Your dance lesson, huh?
What about Ichimura-san?
I don't know. Probably
doing her sugar daddy job.
Maybe that was the reason.
What caused Nikaido-san
and Mitsuya-san's disagreement?
Nikaido-san had a harsh personality.
Is that a reason to do that?
What's gotten into you?
I feel like I'm being interrogated.
Do you?
I'm trying to move onto
my next step, so could you not?
You're right.
Wadagaki-san?
Sato?
She just left. Be careful.
I thought if I became an idol
I'd be able to meet my dad.
Next Time
My dad is a storyteller.
His name is Donraku.
If you're so unmotivated,
why don't you just quit?
We've been forced to bend to her every whim.
I want to go as far as I can with this team.
This isn't what you promised.
This show is a work of fiction.
You gotta do whatever it takes
to make your dreams come true.