[Soichi] Gaku!
[Yoko] Gaku!
-[blade rasps]
-[blood squelches]
[uneasy music playing]
[inaudible]
[propeller clattering, crunching]
[music fades]
[grunts]
[moans]
[woman] Two weeks.
That's how long you slept.
[Gaku moans]
Who are you?
You fell into the sea.
You got stuck in the ship's propeller.
[Gaku grunts softly]
[Gaku breathes shakily]
[breathing shakily continues]
Wonderful. Back from the brink of death.
[Gaku gasps]
[panting]
As to be expected from a son of Hattori.
This is the Fuma base.
And you are?
I'm the 19th Fuma Kotaro.
Take your time to heal.
-[thunder rumbling]
-[rain pattering]
[grunting, panting]
[panting]
[grunts, groans]
[thunder rumbling]
[breathes deeply]
[panting, grunting]
[Gaku] Kill me!
I'm a shinobi!
Just let me die!
I refuse to be your bargaining chip.
[Tsujioka] That wasn't my plan.
Then what?
I want to show you something now.
This is the grave
of a woman you killed on a mission.
Why did this woman die?
-I was just following orders.
-Adultery.
Eliminated to avoid
an inconvenient political scandal.
Deaths for a cause are understandable,
but all this woman did
was simply love a man.
Do you think that's justified?
I'm sure you had some idea?
Those in power were using you
to build their own agendas.
Fuma decide for themselves.
We decide why we kill and who we kill.
We're planning to completely uproot
those who've been leading us astray.
You may be a shinobi,
but first, you're a human being.
Take your time
to think about what really matters.
What you're against,
and what you stand for.
What I'm against…
and what I stand for.
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
[Gaku] You're pretty good at that, Ayame.
[Ayame] Sorry.
I shouldn't have touched it
without permission.
If you like it, it's yours.
But hasn't this been in your family
for generations?
You're right, but, uh,
I don't care.
[birds squawking]
[ninjas chanting]
[bird squawks]
[shakujo jingles]
[chanting continues]
-[shakujo jingles]
-[chanting subsides]
[Tsujioka] Tonight,
here before En no Gyoja,
we appoint a new officer of the Fuma clan.
Come forward.
Today, I appoint you as Goki,
Fuma Kotaro's deputy head.
[Gaku] I humbly accept this honor.
[Tsujioka] As tradition
from ancient times,
you are bestowed a name.
Your name… is a symbol of Fuma.
Crow.
[uneasy music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[Haru panting]
[automated voice] The person
you are trying to reach is not available.
[music swells, stops]
[panting]
[Mukai on video] I understand
that I'm not the favorite candidate
to win the election for party leader.
There is a long road ahead.
Though I am well aware
of our country's need for an overhaul.
Please stand--
MUKAI RUNS FOR OFFICE.
FUMA MAKES A MOVE.
COINCIDENCE?
[phone buzzes]
NO CALLER ID
Who is this?
[Kuze] Look in the mailbox.
There's information about the incident.
Do you mean… Mukai?
[dial tone]
[Riku moans]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Kuze] Go.
[door slides open]
[door closes]
Where'd she go?
[engine hums]
[Soichi] They've been driving erratically
all night long.
East. West. U-turn.
What's their plan here?
Probably worried about being followed.
Looks like they're getting off.
[car horn blares]
[yawning]
[Soichi] What the hell is he doing?
Don't tell me it's the wrong truck.
[inaudible]
[Yoko] "All good, man."
"Nobody's been following."
"Three o'clock."
"Don't worry."
"I'll be there on time for sure."
All right.
-We've got their plan now.
-Mm-hmm.
[birds chirping]
[footsteps in headphones]
[automated voice] The number
you have dialed cannot be reached.
It has been turned off or is out of range.
Karen-san, are you there?
[Riku groans]
[grandmother] Don't make any noise.
All right, start over.
[Riku sighs]
Hey, Master,
is this really gonna make me stronger?
Learning stealth
is the first step to being a shinobi.
So a loud rustle of fabric
could lead you to your death.
But I wanna practice shuriken more! Can I?
[grandmother] Nonsense.
Maybe in ten years.
What?
I have to do this stuff
for ten years first?
[Riku sighs]
[grandmother] What's wrong?
Have you seen Karen-san?
[Riku] She went out this morning.
[gears clattering]
[phone line ringing]
[Haru] Hey. Didn't I tell you
not to leave the house? Where are you?
[Hamashima] Where do you think she is?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Haru] Why do you have her phone?
You hid a civilian in your house,
breaking our protocol.
I never would've guessed
you'd be stupid enough to do that.
You bugged our house?
You knew the consequences.
You knew what would happen
if she found out about you.
Is she okay?
[Hamashima] Of course she's not okay.
Rules are rules, Haru.
The same goes for you too.
Prepare yourself.
[music intensifies]
Cat's out of the bag.
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap!
Crap, crap, crap. [whimpers]
Ow! Crap!
-[loud thud]
-[Oki gasps, whimpers]
It wasn't my idea!
Hama-san told me to do it!
[Oki gasping, choking]
[panting]
What do you want?
-If you're not--
-[Kuze] Stop! Don't step off the sheet.
It'll make the cleanup harder.
The cleanup?
[Kuze] You, uh…
You found out
something you shouldn't have.
It's not ideal, but…
[music swells, fades]
[footsteps approaching]
Nagi, we have to talk.
You saw me, right?
That man? Who was he?
You don't need to know that.
Stay away!
What's behind your back?
What is it?
Gaku-nii, um…
are you Fuma?
Nagi, don't be ridiculous.
Really?
That man you saw was Fuma.
Can I trust you?
[Gaku] Yes.
Where did you get this?
And we are going to be holding
a total solar eclipse countdown event.
[clown] Go ahead! Nice, good choice!
Next customer, please.
-[clown] Rock, paper, scissors. Oh no!
-[boy] Yeah!
[clown] Pick whatever you like, kid.
[whimsical carnival music plays quietly]
Good job getting rid of Sawabe.
-He was messy.
-Drop your mask.
Why did you go behind my back?
-Behind your back?
-It had to have been you.
You tricked my sister
by pretending to be me.
Were you planning
on never telling me that?
Answer me.
We were only using your sister
to get the scroll.
Where is it?
It won't be easy to find.
My grandmother must have stashed it.
The eclipse is coming. We don't have time.
Use force if you must.
My family won't be harmed.
You promised me that.
That's if they had stayed hidden.
They've already been hostile to us.
Please don't do this.
Crow,
we have a mission.
You now belong to our family.
Do you not?
[carnival music plays clearly]
[crowd cheering]
[whimpers] This is an extremely bad idea.
I am gonna be in so much dog shit.
[Hamashima] Tawara-san!
Just the man I want to see.
This way.
Sorry about this.
Do you have any idea
of what you've done here?
Please spare her life.
I'll devote my life to the BNM.
I'll serve as a shinobi till I die.
I don't think you grasp
the situation you're in.
This is your end as well.
If you're willing to spare her life,
I'm willing to die.
I'm begging.
Haru,
are you willing to kill?
If it's something I can't avoid.
What if Gaku turns out to be a Fuma spy?
Are you willing to kill him?
[Yoko] It just looks like
a regular everyday truck terminal.
Maybe they're switching trucks
to transport it somewhere else.
Like a layover?
Maybe.
All right, I'm going in.
Wait, can't we go in tonight?
We don't have time.
I look like a truck driver.
Make sure the BNM knows.
Soichi!
Don't you worry.
I won't be an idiot.
You're my teammate.
[trucks beeping]
[indistinct chattering]
[Soichi] Good work today.
Thanks.
[Haru breathes deeply]
[door lock clicks]
[door opens]
I'll spare both of your lives
on one condition.
You promise
that you'll never see each other again.
I promise.
Could I see her one last time?
You have one minute, all right?
[door opens]
[door closes]
I'm sorry for all this.
I handled it.
-They're going to let you go now.
-What's gonna happen to you?
Are we not… allowed to see each other?
We didn't know each other long.
[Karen breathes deeply]
Two weeks.
It's only been two weeks.
I memorized your Gyudon order
from when we first met.
[Haru chuckles]
You really remember that?
Extra broth, extra green onion,
and a raw egg.
Large, tons of garlic, kimchi on top.
[both laugh]
[emotional music softly playing]
It wasn't a long time, but…
it felt like an eternity of memories.
[door opens]
[Hamashima] Time's up.
[music intensifies]
[music stops]
Now you're going to make good
on this favor I granted you.
[Kuze] That went well.
Haru's in the palm of your hand
for the rest of his life.
[cart rattling]
[machinery humming]
[uneasy music playing]
[mysterious music playing]
[keyboard button clicks]
Everyone,
the time is almost upon us.
Soon enough, it'll be your turn.
Everyone will receive
the powder of hope to purify souls.
Spread the circle of joy.
Raise your arms. Raise your hands.
Up until now,
we had been the moon.
The moon, that which could not shine
without the light of the sun.
Everything will change.
The sun will become ours.
The moon will devour the sun.
Shadow will devour the light.
Soon enough,
the eclipse will lead us to glory.
[mysterious music playing]
[voices laughing]
[grandmother] Mm-mmm!
Master,
I'm not allowed to eat meat anymore too?
Mmm, you know, a skilled shinobi
can even sniff out the smell of meat
coming from someone's body.
I'm allowed to eat meat.
It's because I'm retired, okay?
[grandmother laughs]
Mmm!
Then… what about soda?
-[Riku grunts]
-[grandmother laughing]
[Riku] Not fair!
[wind gusting]
Master?
It looks like some rats
have come to visit us.
[wind gusting]
NO SIGNAL
[grandmother] Oh great!
All modern devices are pieces of crap!
Wait. What's wrong?
I'm thinking about your debut.
[Riku] Do I really have to wait
ten whole years?
No.
You're debuting tonight.
[Riku] What?
[cord clatters]
[gears clattering]
You're gonna fight by my side, Riku.
[clattering stops]
Are you ready for that?
[tense music playing]
[wind whistling]
[tense music continues]
[in earphones]
♪ Deep down inside, there's a secret ♪
♪ And I won't ever let it out ♪
[tense music playing]
[metallic clattering]
[loud thud]
[groans]
[tense music continues]
[grandmother gasps]
[gasps]
[in earphones]
♪ Deep down inside, there's a secret ♪
♪ And I won't ever let it out ♪
♪ But if you swear that you'll keep it ♪
♪ Baby, you can have it
But only if you want it ♪
♪ I wanna be your… ♪
[both grunt]
[pants] Really sucks for you.
I'm in a really shitty mood right now!
[Ayame] So am I.
You really pulled one over on me
with that fake scroll.
[wind whistling]
[cat purring]
[Nagi grunts]
Well, you're a bold
little old lady, aren't you?
[panting]
I'm sure you can handle
the rest on your own.
[funky music playing]
[Riku] Grandma.
You kids.
You're such a handful.
Come on. Move it!
[laughs]
[breathing nervously]
[tense music playing]
[funky music resumes]
[blade rasp echoes]
[grandmother hisses]
I probably shouldn't have
eaten all those burgers.
It's impossible to hide
with this smell on me.
I'm ready.
You seem to have some skills, hmm?
[Fuma ninja] Where is the scroll?
I wonder where it is?
[back cracking]
[groans]
[Fuma ninja groans]
[Riku screams]
It… stings!
[grandmother grunts]
[Fuma ninja] Old lady and a brat.
[tense music playing]
Little brat.
The kunai you're holding is mine.
I got it from your brother.
Your dear Gaku-nii
gave the blade to me voluntarily.
[dramatic action music playing]
[screaming]
[loud thud, clattering]
-[Nagi groans]
-[Ayame] That really hurt!
[laughs]
This Tawara house is a piece of shit.
Hattori Hanzo's rolling in his grave.
[Nagi panting]
[Ayame grunts]
[gasps, coughs]
[coughs]
[grandmother groans]
[Nagi groaning]
[Riku] Look!
[grandmother] Nagi!
[Nagi panting]
[grandmother] Nagi, are you hurt?
[Ayame] It's time to stop playing games.
Okay, grandma, hand over the scroll now.
[grandmother scoffs]
That's too bad.
I wasn't planning on killing you.
Now I have to.
[grandmother gasps]
Gaku-nii!
Hand it over to me now.
You have it, don't you?
[grandmother] The only person
you can trust is yourself.
It belonged to Fuma in the first place.
Do what you want.
You lied to me.
About being a Fuma.
[sobs] Say something!
Someday…
it'll all make sense to you.
[sniffles]
[sobs] Gaku-nii!
[door lock clicks]
[door opens]
[Kuze's footsteps echoing]
[gasps]
[footsteps approaching]
[Haru] What happened?
Gaku-nii… is Fuma.
[grandmother] They raided our home.
They came to get the scroll.
A scroll?
Your grandfather took it.
It belonged to Fuma.
It was the Hojo family tree.
It seems like…
it's really important to them.
[Nagi] This morning…
Gaku-nii, um, killed a man by the water.
Gaku killed Sawabe.
[uneasy music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[Yoko] Gaku.
[Yoko breathes shakily]
No, Gaku.
[Yoko crying]
What do we do?
Haru-nii…
what do we do?
What's our plan now?
[wind whistling]
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[ethereal music playing]