[woman on PA] The "A" train
will soon be arriving at platform one.
Please stand behind the yellow line
for yours and others' safety. Thank you.
…will soon be arriving at platform one.
[high-pitched squeal]
-[Haru] Are you okay?
-[Karen grunts]
Where's the flower?
And my article?
We need to leave. It's dangerous.
It was you, right?
We have to go.
Tell me everything.
[pensive music playing]
Please!
[Karen panting]
No more lies.
Just please, we have to leave.
Trust me.
[Soichi] What happened?
What were you doing there?
Nagi.
I thought it was Gaku-nii.
It wasn't him.
I was tricked.
I'm sorry.
[Soichi] Hmm?
[man] I have a message for you.
It's from Kotaro-sama.
[Soichi] Huh?
[man] "Thank you."
"Thank you
for saving my life six years ago."
Your son has more information.
[seat belt clicks]
[Riku] Okay.
[man on video] And after that,
you'll see that there are
three pin stacks.
I've unlocked this part.
Slide this, and this will open.
Do you see this H-shaped part right here?
If, uh, the grooves on both ends
of this H-shaped part are stuck,
you can take your tool and…
[gears clicking]
[silence]
Is… it… safe?
[mysterious music playing]
No way!
[mysterious music continues]
[Riku grunts]
[Riku exhales]
[tense music playing]
[Riku gasps]
[gasps]
[Riku] Wow!
[music subsides]
[Riku] Grandma?
[floor creaks]
Is…
is our house…
It's a shinobi house.
Shino…
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
-[Soichi] Haru!
-[door closes]
[Soichi gasps]
[Haru] Did, uh,
something happen?
Who's that?
I'm Karen Ito.
Nice to meet you.
-[Soichi] Oh.
-W… welcome.
Um, why is she here?
Come here.
-Are you out of your mind?
-She was attacked by the Fuma clan.
You thought bringing her here
was a good idea?
-You're being too loud!
-She had nowhere else to go.
-She'll be safer here.
-[Oki] Whoa!
This place is huge! Cool!
Is that a well? What?
-This place is amazing, Hama-san!
-[Hamashima] Take it down a notch.
-[Oki] Sorry.
-All right.
[Oki] I can't believe this is…
Just please don't say anything, okay?
She's important to me.
-[Oki] How old do you think that is?
-Come this way.
[Karen] Huh? [grunts]
[Hamashima] We're coming in!
[Nagi] Wait, wait, wait!
-What about Grandma?
-Grandma?
Grandma will wanna murder her.
[door closing]
Oh wow! Look at this place!
-Over here. Hide under the table.
-[Yoko] Go hide. Hide.
[Haru] Do not come out.
We'll both be dead if they see you.
-[Oki] Sorry for the intrusion.
-[Soichi] Hey! Why are you here? Hey!
[Hamashima] Huh?
You're all here?
[whimsical music playing]
And what about that woman?
It's over.
-[Hamashima] Oki!
-[Oki] Yes.
-What the hell is that?
-Excuse me. I'll set this up in here.
Passing through.
You look like you've been through hell.
Well, you all did excellent.
Soichi, I'm glad
you finally got my message.
[Soichi] Don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't do it for you.
[Hamashima] Nagi finally made her debut.
It's fantastic that you're
all working as a unit again.
[Riku] Hattori Hanzo?
He's our great ancestor.
You mean the famous ninja, right?
That's right.
Tawara is…
is our fake name.
I'll tell you our real family name.
Hattori.
[pensive music playing]
I didn't know that.
Then what about Fuma?
Fuma are our enemies, so to speak.
That's what they said on our field trip.
Okay.
Ninjas. We're ninjas.
Shinobis.
Only clueless fools ever call us ninjas.
We're shinobi.
[Riku] Shinobi.
Hey, what's that?
[grandmother chuckles]
Your ancestor Hattori Hanzo took that mask
when he defeated Fuma Kotaro the 5th.
It's a war trophy from the time
when he defeated the Hojo clan
and drove the Fuma clan out of Odawara.
Oh. Where'd the Fuma clan go?
No one really knows.
[uneasy music playing]
[birds squawking]
[Fuma ninjas chanting]
[elder] Everyone, take a cup.
[chanting continues]
This holy water will make you a true Fuma.
[all coughing, choking]
[chanting continues]
[dramatic music playing]
Only heaven governs life and death.
Chosen ones, welcome to the Fuma clan.
[music swells]
[music fades]
You're not done yet?
High-tech things
take a little more finessing.
This one goes…
Mirroring, mirroring…
-Huh?
-[Oki tapping device]
[Oki] Weird. Where's the Wi-Fi?
Hmm.
Oh, wait a sec. I think I got it.
-It should work if I click this here.
-[cat purring]
[Oki] Never mind. How does this work?
Hmm.
Sorry to keep everybody waiting!
I got it!
[Hamashima]
Let's get straight to the point.
The Fuma clan have emerged from hiding.
[pensive music playing]
[Oki] Right.
And in order to hide their identity
as the Fuma clan,
as well as to increase their membership,
they were operating as "Gentenkai,"
a religious group.
They have 30,000 members.
They've been drawing the younger crowd
by pretending to be
invested in the environment.
But in reality…
they're just a cult.
This is the Gentenkai headquarters.
There was confirmed activity
up until yesterday,
but when we checked this morning,
the whole place had been cleaned out.
It's completely deserted.
[Hamashima] We don't have any leads
to where they disappeared,
but I'm sure we can all guess
what they're up to.
The clues are there.
Next.
[Oki] Oh, right.
Sorry about that.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
Just dropped my pen.
[intriguing music playing]
[Oki] This is the yellow flower obtained
from the Gentenkai headquarters.
Our analysis has shown that it contains
a brand-new type of neurotoxin.
Yoko-san investigated the incident
where we believe it was used.
It bears some resemblance to aconite,
but it is so much more toxic.
This toxin is almost impossible to treat.
[Hamashima] It's just the beginning.
The person behind these incidents
is the leader of Gentenkai.
Tsujioka Yosuke.
Also known as Fuma Kotaro the 19th.
Your son did a nice job investigating him.
You're telling me… you made contact?
Yes.
Some guy gave us a message today.
The message was,
"Thank you for saving my life
six years ago."
[Yoko] He said our son would tell us more.
Haru?
That night…
we were fighting the Fuma…
I had a… a chance to kill one.
But…
I didn't.
I couldn't kill him.
[Hamashima] Was he the 19th?
He was Gaku--
He murdered him.
[Soichi sighs]
Sorry I kept it to myself.
So your weakness brought about
the creation of the 19th--
Enough!
Stay out of this. It's a family matter.
[Riku] I know everything now.
[Yoko] Riku?
We're a shinobi house, right?
[Soichi] Riku.
Mom, did you tell…
Riku figured it out on his own.
[intriguing music playing]
Why did you keep it a secret?
[Soichi] Riku, it's not what you think.
I wish you would've told me!
[Yoko] Riku! [pants]
[Soichi] Hey!
[wistful music playing]
I hope you know…
it's not your fault.
You can't blame yourself.
-Open the door.
-[Riku] Go away!
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
There's a reason.
What was the reason, then?
[Soichi] I didn't want
to put you in danger.
It can't happen again.
I thought I was different from everybody.
[Riku sighs]
So can I be a shinobi?
Not gonna happen.
Riku, listen.
It's not so simple, you know?
[Soichi] It's not all fun and games
like you think it is.
You don't fly through the air
with a furoshiki.
[Yoko] And the clone duplicate technique?
Oof, overrated.
[Soichi] Plus, you don't get to eat
the hamburgers you love.
-So--
-I'm fine with that.
I wanna be a family.
[Yoko] What?
A real family.
I'm the only one who's not a part of it
because I'm not a shinobi yet.
Can I, please?
Can I please be a shinobi?
I'll work really hard.
Please. Can we be a real family?
All right.
Yes, yeah!
Fuma Kotaro has finally appeared!
[whooshing, grunts]
[grandmother] It was you.
You took the scroll.
I'm so sorry.
You had your reasons.
But don't…
[whispers] …tell anyone about it.
[Nagi] That scroll…
That scroll?
What could that scroll be?
Hmm?
[birds squawking]
[woman] We reclaimed what was stolen.
The eclipse has no obstacle now.
HOJO FAMILY TREE
It seems like you've been fooled.
[uneasy music playing]
You think you can kill me?
Why don't you try?
[breathes shakily]
[breathing heavily]
Stand aside.
Here for revenge?
Beautiful.
[breathing heavily]
What are you waiting for?
Make a move.
[breathes deeply, grunts]
[grunts]
No human being can kill me.
[whimpers]
[Oki] Oh! I understand.
Yes. Thank you so much.
[alarm beeps]
[Oki sighs] Okay. [grunts]
Matsuura has been brought
to BNM headquarters.
[Oki grunts]
I hope we can get
something good out of that guy.
Oh, so he's being tortured?
What's going on with that potato-face?
The detective.
That has already been handled.
[snoring]
Leave me alone. [groans]
[groans]
Stop!
[people murmuring]
[people laughing]
[Omi exclaims]
TRADITION AND CRAFTSMANSHIP
[man 1] Did you sleep well?
[Omi] No.
What's going on?
Art pieces.
You've been quite
the art collector, haven't ya?
You even used your position
to come and go as you please.
And the stolen items were in your home.
Quite the coincidence.
Is there anything you'd like to say?
I was framed.
I'm innocent.
Hey! What's going on here?
Omi-san!
Forget it.
I didn't witness anything
at all.
Forget about it.
This case doesn't exist anymore.
Got it?
It's over.
What the hell are you talking about?
Omi-san.
[man 1] Step out of the way. Move. Leave.
[man 1 sighs]
Let's go.
They let you stay the night?
You're super lucky.
-You're the first person ever.
-[laughs] I feel super lucky.
Dad and Mom said there was no, uh, choice.
-Uh, oh.
-They have more stuff to worry about.
I can tell.
Sorry you have to put up with me.
-I don't mind at all!
-[laughs]
I never get to have friends over,
so this is fun.
I'm glad to hear that.
[both laugh]
[bell dings]
[Soichi sighs]
It'll be all right.
I guess Riku got what he wanted.
But, Haru…
for so long…
We're bad parents, aren't we?
We pretended the past didn't happen.
[Soichi sighs]
He held it in…
because of us.
[intriguing music playing]
[pigeon cooing]
[music fades]
[knock at door]
Can I come in?
[Haru chuckles] You already did.
[Karen chuckles]
How long will I be staying here?
Until the Fuma are gone.
It's safer here.
Okay.
So,
is it true that you are a ninja?
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Um… Okay. [chuckles]
I understand.
Mmm, kinda. [laughs]
So do you use shurikens?
We don't use those.
They'd give us away.
Oh, right. You can't be discovered.
It's the number one rule that we have.
Having me here
is pretty much breaking it, right?
[Haru] Hmm.
Have you done this before?
I mean, broken the rules.
Uh…
I'm also not supposed to eat any meat.
But you ate gyudon.
Wasn't supposed to.
Oh. What about other stuff?
I feel like I'm kinda being interviewed.
Sorry. [laughs]
Work mode.
Don't write an article.
All right?
I won't.
[chuckles] What else? [chuckles]
Um, a mission is the only time
we can use our skills.
No alcohol.
Need permission to travel. And no photos.
Also…
we can't date.
No dating?
We need the okay.
We need permission.
Yeah, but
didn't you ask me out on a date?
Against the rules?
Pretty much, yeah.
Actually,
I was going
to the gyudon place for work.
I was investigating you.
[Haru] Mmm.
But, um…
gradually…
I liked you.
I liked you from the start.
Hey.
Have you ever had a girlfriend?
Really?
Then, um,
are you a virgin?
-Why would you ask that?
-[chuckles] Sorry.
I'm trying to understand.
Mmm, do ninjas not have sex?
"Shinobis."
No one says "ninjas."
You're changing the subject.
How about your parents?
Arranged.
A lot for them was, uh, controlled.
What about you?
I want…
to fall in love… like everyone.
[Haru] Mm-hmm.
On my own.
Okay.
What would happen if we got caught?
We'd both be killed.
Really?
[uneasy music playing]
AGENCY FOR CULTURAL AFFAIRS
[mysterious music playing]
[Kuze] The guy does not crack
under pressure.
That's oddly impressive.
All right.
[Hamashima] The "Professor"
will get it done.
[music swells]
[silence]
[tires squealing]
-[ominous music playing]
-[clattering]
-[sword slashing]
-[man screams]
[door clatters]
[tense music playing]
[blood squelches]
[grunting, groaning]
Thank God!
[Fuma ninja distorted voice]
What did you tell them?
Nothing. My mouth was shut.
[Fuma ninja] Information is worth
more than your life.
Kotaro-sama ordered us to kill you
if we believed you leaked information.
[Matsuura] I… I didn't say
anything at all.
[Fuma ninja] Is that the truth?
What about…
What about?
[Fuma ninja] Tell me now!
The eclipse?
[Fuma ninja] Yes.
I didn't. I would never talk.
It scares me too.
If it happens, so many people will die.
[Fuma ninja]
Can you prove you didn't talk?
How would I prove that?
What more could I say?
I know nothing else.
[Hamashima] Nice. [groans]
Well, that worked out.
[intriguing music playing]
Oh man!
[funky pop music playing]
Eclipse.
Huh?
[sighs]
[wind gusting]
[Yoko] Hey.
[Soichi] Hmm?
When we saved Nagi,
I thought about something.
Wouldn't you agree
that we make a great team?
Absolutely.
We've been doing this together
for so long.
You were…
impressive.
Really.
You were great.
Beautiful.
[car horns honking]
[young Nagi] Wait for me!
-[young Nagi laughs]
-[Gaku] A little further.
[young Nagi] Wait.
Wait.
[Gaku] What? Nagi, I'm leaving you behind.
[young Nagi] Wait!
[wistful music playing]
[inaudible]
[young Nagi laughs] Wait!
[crying]
[music fades]
♪ I'll light the fire… ♪
-[Riku] It's hard!
-[Nagi] No, it's not!
-[Riku] Yeah, it is!
-[Nagi] Run quietly!
-[Riku] Huh? This is too hard.
-[Nagi] Be careful when you turn.
-[Riku] I almost slipped!
-[Nagi] Huh?
-I'm doing good, right?
-You are.
-Oh!
-[grandmother] And you're dead.
[all laugh]
[Nagi] That was only six laps.
[Riku breathless]
How many laps can you do?
Uh, let me think…
[grandmother] Nagi usually does
about 170 laps.
-[Nagi] Mm-hmm.
-What? That is totally a lie!
-No, it's not.
-[Riku] You're lying.
-I can't run anymore.
-Okay.
-[Nagi] Let's go!
-[grandmother] Start again.
-[Nagi] Ready…
-Wait a sec.
-And go!
-[Riku grunts]
[Nagi] Go, go, go! Faster!
-Faster!
-[Riku] All right.
-[Riku] I'm trying as hard as I can.
-[Riku] Okay!
-Brings back memories.
♪ Such a cozy room… ♪
It does.
[grandmother] You died again.
-[Nagi] You have such a long way to go.
-[Riku groans]
You two want some tea?
-[Soichi] Sure.
-[Haru] Yeah.
♪ Fiery gems ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Only for you… ♪
[grandmother] Ready, go!
♪ Our house… ♪
[Haru] Hey, watch out there, Riku!
Watch out!
[Nagi] Go, go, go, go!
♪ With two cats in the yard… ♪
-Come on, come on!
-I'm trying! I'm trying!
-[grandmother] One more lap!
-[Nagi] Faster, faster, faster, faster!
Come on, keep it up!
♪ And our ♪
[singer vocalizing]
[laughs]
-[Haru] Faster!
-More, more, more!
[laughing]
♪ Our house ♪
♪ Is a very, very, very fine house ♪
♪ With two cats in the yard ♪
♪ Life used to be so hard ♪
♪ Now everything is easy 'cause of you ♪
♪ And our ♪
♪ I'll light the fire… ♪
[siren blaring]
♪ While you place the flowers
In the vase ♪
♪ That you bought ♪
♪ Today ♪
[music fades]
[mysterious music playing]
[funky mysterious music playing]
[music fades]