[insects chittering]
[birds chirping]
[baby crying]
[baby continues crying]
[crying fades]
There once was a baby
abandoned in this very forest.
Right next to it
were the dead bodies of its parents.
They hung themselves.
They had left a suicide note,
wailing about the harsh world.
The parents didn't have the courage
to kill their baby.
So they just left it here to die.
Although,
the baby didn't die.
Over time, the parents' bodies
began to decompose.
The baby continued to cry
in this same spot.
The baby would never give in
to the destiny its parents had designed.
[water splashing]
What allows one to survive
while the others die?
It's the strength to take control
of one's own destiny.
Those with such strength…
shall dominate the rest.
[uneasy music playing]
[lighter clicks]
-[shakujo jingles]
-[chanting]
[chanting fades]
[reporter] It's four days
until the solar eclipse.
Since this is
the first celestial show in 15 years,
many events and people
are preparing for the special day.
[Yoko chopping food]
[reporter] An eclipse is the occurrence
in which the moon blocks the sun…
[phone buzzing]
[Soichi] Your phone's ringing.
[Yoko] Oh.
[reporter] This is known
as a "solar eclipse…"
Yoko speaking.
[Soichi] What's wrong?
Hello?
What?
[Yoko sighs]
What is it?
[phone ringing]
Hey, what's going on?
[ominous music playing]
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
[camera shutter echoes]
[water blasting]
[Kuze] Tell me why the Fuma released you.
They didn't release me.
I ran.
[Kuze] Do you think I'm stupid?
It's true.
I bet you're a Fuma.
I'm not.
[Oki] Hama-san.
There was an overturned van
discovered four kilometers away
from where Tawara Gaku was found.
The driver and one more,
they were murdered.
[uneasy music playing]
[Kuze] Where are the Fuma?
I don't know.
More like you don't wanna tell us.
I really don't know.
They kept me blindfolded
except when I was working.
Working on what?
Where?
A field.
A field of yellow flowers.
[Hamashima] Mount Fuji.
How long did you work in the field?
How long has it been
since I disappeared?
It's been six years.
Six years.
What happened to your leg?
I fell in the water.
It got caught in the ship's propeller.
[Hamashima] Do you know him?
That's the man who tortured me.
[Hamashima] What's his name?
[Oki] Great work, sir.
Find out where this place is.
[Oki] Yes, sir.
[door opens]
[Kuze] Why don't we polygraph him?
It's useless to polygraph a shinobi.
So what's the plan, then?
Chances are pretty high
he's a plant sent by the Fuma.
[Yoko sighs]
[uneasy music fades]
[Soichi sighs]
Gaku-nii!
[prosthetic leg clanking]
Gaku.
[Yoko sobs]
You're alive.
Gaku.
[Yoko crying]
[Yoko sniffles]
Nagi.
I never gave up.
I knew you'd come back.
Oh. Come on. Go on, Riku. Say hi.
Nice to meet you.
[chuckles] Riku, you've met him before.
He lived here with us
until you were two years old.
-[prosthetic leg clanks]
-[Soichi] Whoa. [grunts]
You all right?
It seems his leg doesn't fit so well.
I'll come back tomorrow
to reconvene about what'll happen next.
You all have a lot of catching up to do.
-Let's go.
-[Oki] Sir.
Haru.
Welcome back.
[Soichi] Let's go inside, everyone.
[birds squawking]
[squawking intensifies]
Nice and fresh.
[Gaku chuckles]
You look exactly the same.
Thank you.
Well, why don't you go and take a nap
in your room until dinnertime?
[Gaku] Mm-hmm.
[Soichi] We're all back together
at the table.
It's been too long.
Definitely.
Would you like some more?
-[Gaku] Oh, mm-hmm.
-[Soichi] Mmm.
-[Riku] Me too, please.
-Yep.
Nagi, you're in… high school?
Mm-mm. College now.
Oh.
College already, huh?
[Gaku] Hmm?
So what's it like with just one leg?
Riku!
Riku.
-Don't be so rude.
-[Gaku] It's fine.
Here.
[Gaku moans]
Wanna feel it?
-Does it hurt?
-Not really. Try.
[Gaku grunts, groans]
-[Riku] Oh man! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
-[Gaku groans]
[Gaku chuckles]
-I knew you'd fall for it. I'm joking.
-[Riku laughs]
-I fell for it.
-[Gaku laughs]
You really got me so good!
[Gaku, Yoko laugh]
[Riku sighs]
[Soichi laughs]
Haru.
-[Haru] Hmm?
-So will you introduce me to her?
She's staying here a while, right?
Mmm.
[Yoko] Here you go.
-Thanks.
-[Yoko] Sure.
-Riku.
-[Riku] Hmm?
[dial clicking]
-Press this button to play the Switch.
-[Gaku] Mm-hmm.
-And press this button to watch TV.
-[Gaku] Hmm.
Gaku.
So, uh…
Karen Ito.
Tawara Gaku. Nice to meet you.
Thank you for letting me stay,
even for a bit.
Glad you're here.
You know everything about us?
Maybe not "everything."
Uh, but yeah. I am aware.
She's hiding from the Fuma.
We're keeping it from Hama-san.
Yeah. [chuckles]
-Karen. Let's play Switch.
-Next time.
Oh, why next time?
Hey, Riku. Let's watch TV together.
Let's go.
[woman on TV] Revitalize Japan!
This country needs a change.
Someone fresh who can blow open new doors.
I am that leader.
Elect Mukai Toko as your leader.
[reporter] Ms. Mukai was involved
in an abduction case
amid Tokyo's gubernatorial election
six years ago.
Despite such adversity,
she won a large following
and became the governor of Tokyo.
Ms. Mukai later entered national politics
and is garnering attention
in the upcoming presidential election.
[Riku] Why'd you turn it off?
Ah, because you still have
a lot of homework you need to finish.
[Riku] Okay.
The politicians and bureaucrats in power,
whose only motivation
was self-preservation,
they are the ones to blame.
I, Mukai Toko,
will drastically change
the politics of our country.
I will do so by eliminating corruption.
Our country will change
if the politics change.
Our stagnant economy.
Our diminished presence
on the world stage.
We will recover them all.
Our country can be revitalized.
[uneasy music playing]
Six years ago, Mukai was kidnapped
during the gubernatorial election.
Now she's running for president.
I just have a bad feeling about this.
Also, um…
your brother.
The timing seems weird.
What do you mean by that?
[phone buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
SAWABE
Hello?
-What do you want? Why are you calling--
-[Sawabe] They killed my family.
I want revenge.
Why's a cop working for the Fuma?
The central government
is filled with Fuma collaborators.
Do you have information on the eclipse?
[Sawabe] Yes.
Tell me what it is.
I'll give you the information
if you help me kill that man.
[Haru] Look, we want the same thing.
Let's meet face-to-face.
I'm being tailed.
All right.
[Sawabe] Where?
[Haru] Come out to Odawara.
[uneasy music playing]
[music fades]
[door opening in distance]
[uneasy music playing]
[music fades]
We must have a rat.
But not to worry.
[laughs]
I've hidden it away. [laughing]
What are you doing?
[Gaku] Reminiscing.
You coming home
brought us all together
for the first time in a while.
You've always been
the core of this family.
When we were kids,
we were always in this room.
You were always slacking off.
I trained like my life depended on it.
Our skill level was the same.
If you actually tried,
I wouldn't have had a chance against you.
Why don't we give it a go?
What's the matter?
Everything is my fault.
I could've killed that guy.
I chickened out.
I just stood there.
I regret it all.
He's… he's the one who stabbed you, and…
he became Fuma Kotaro the 19th…
because… I couldn't do it.
That's…
You have always been kind…
but for shinobis…
kindness makes us weak.
When someone shows up and blocks you
from acting on your convictions,
you have to kill them.
If you blocked me, I'd kill you.
[chuckles softly]
Maybe you should stay
the way you've always been.
A bugging device?
Excuse yourself and plant it
while I explain the mission to everyone.
Gaku cannot know what you're doing.
I'm bugging the Tawaras?
No, no, no, no, no!
-Do you have a problem with this plan?
-I have a big problem!
That is a house of shinobis!
I'm fully aware of that.
So what happens if they find out?
Do not get caught. Be very discreet.
[whimpers] I don't think
I can be discreet enough, Hama-san.
It's impossible. [whimpers]
[car door closes]
Why in the holy hell
is he making me bug them?
[whimpers]
[Hamashima] Hey! Move it!
Yeah! [whimpers]
[Oki] I'm gonna sue this guy someday.
-There.
-Yes, sir.
[Oki] It's heavy.
Come on. We don't have all day.
[Oki] Ow!
[Yoko] So, according to Matsuura,
the Fuma is planning
to carry out a mass murder.
[Hamashima] Unfortunately,
that idiot wasn't privy to the details.
What we do know
is that whatever plan they have
is named "Solar Eclipse."
The actual solar eclipse
occurs on November 9th.
In two days?
[Hamashima] Mm-hmm.
If they are, in fact,
carrying out their plan on that day,
it is important that we locate them
in order to stop it before it starts.
Gaku drew this.
I was forced to work there
the entire time.
They warned me about
the toxicity of the yellow flowers.
They said that just breathing its pollen
could be lethal.
[Hamashima] I want you
to track and find this location.
Uh, sorry. Would it be all right
for me to use your facilities?
Right now?
Well, I've been holding it in for a while.
Uh, down the hall to the left.
Okay, thank you.
-Ah, can you do this?
-Okay.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I was always blindfolded by them
before we got to the field,
but I could make out some things.
Like a fallen torii
and a broken stone staircase.
A fallen torii?
[breathes nervously]
[Oki sighs]
Yes!
[cat hisses]
[hisses]
[Hamashima] According to
what Gaku mentioned,
the estimated location
of the flower fields is
around this area.
Soichi, Yoko, I'm sending you.
This is where the Fuma are based.
Be careful.
Gaku killed two Fuma members
in his escape.
This guy here
seemed to be one of their top members.
Haru.
Here's his info.
Go check it out.
Good luck.
What's my mission?
Nagi, your mission is to make sure
you take good care of me.
Okay?
[Nagi] Mm-hmm.
[intriguing music playing]
[music continues]
[Yoko] We're about five kilometers away.
[phone buzzes]
[Yoko] "Mayuko-kun"?
Don't you need to answer it?
Isn't she your head of sales?
Now's not the time for that.
What are you--
Yes, hi, I'm here.
[Mayuko] Hi, sir. Are you on your way?
It's time for the meeting
with our new wholesaler.
Ah! I'm sorry.
Something urgent came up.
Oh, I understand.
[chuckles]
No big deal.
Don't worry. I'll manage.
[Soichi] I'm really sorry.
It's all good.
Uh, a bit of a bummer kinda.
I checked and made sure
I wore your lucky color today.
[Soichi clears throat]
Do you want to know what it is?
Today, your lucky color is cochineal.
[clears throat] Thanks.
Mmm, talk to ya later.
[Mayuko] Okay.
Hmm.
[uneasy music playing]
[music fades]
Oh!
She checks your lucky color
and makes sure to wear it.
Cochineal, right?
She's quite a character.
Sure.
I bet someone's hiding a secret.
What? I'm-- There's nothing I'm hiding.
I was talking about Gaku.
Ah.
[Yoko] He was trapped
with the Fuma for a long time.
They might have brainwashed him. Yeah?
Not a great way to put it.
[Oki] Is this working?
Come on, come on.
[radio static]
Oh! Sh, sh, sh, sh.
[Riku] Oh, no. Uh-oh! No, no, no!
Yes! Phew. Safe.
That one next.
Ready? Run, run, run.
Yes!
Next one.
All right.
-Hey, Karen! Did you see that?
-[Karen] Yeah.
Did I look cool? I'm training.
-It's official.
-[Karen] Cool!
I'm gonna jump here to there.
-[Karen] Sure.
-Showtime.
-Uh, hey, you better watch yourself!
-[Riku] Are you watching me?
-[Karen] Be careful!
-[Riku] I'm okay. See.
-Who is that woman?
-[Riku] I'm totally fine.
[Riku whooshing]
Haru-nii, look at me. I'm cool, right?
Mm-hmm.
[Riku] You know what?
I'm gonna catch up to you really soon.
Yep.
Be careful.
You look a little different today.
[Riku] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's an official shinobi outfit.
Wow!
-[Karen] It's kinda cool.
-[Haru] Seriously?
[Karen] Yeah, it's like, stylish.
[Karen, Haru laugh]
Are you going out?
A mission.
Is it dangerous?
Nope.
I'll be meeting with Sawabe after.
I'll be back a little late.
Just make sure you don't leave the house.
Mm-hmm.
[gasps] Oh my God!
Oh my God! No way!
What in the freakin' heck
is going on here?
[gasps] Hello, Hama-san?
[whispers] A woman.
[normal voice] The Tawara family
has one extra member!
Copy that.
[pensive music playing]
Why is that idiot Haru
making me do extra work?
We have enough shit
to worry about as it is.
[Kuze] What's wrong?
It's time to go to work.
[Hamashima] Get rid of Haru's girlfriend.
[music fades]
[Nagi] Watch.
Shwoop.
[chuckles softly]
[laughs]
Whoosh.
Whah!
[both laugh]
I never stopped training all this time.
That's great.
I wanna be just like you.
Be like me, huh?
"You should be proud."
"Shinobi becomes one with the shadows."
"Nobody knows we exist." Right?
The country is protected by us.
I used to think that.
Although…
Although?
Who were we really protecting?
What?
The shinobi's duty is
to always serve someone.
We haven't been questioning.
You sound weird.
I do not want you to be like me, Nagi.
Why not?
I don't get you.
One day, you will.
[seat belt clicks]
Worst case…
Let's say Gaku really is
brainwashed by the Fuma.
This may be a trap we're entering into.
[Yoko] Hey.
-[wings flapping]
-[birds squawking]
[uneasy music playing]
[breathing nervously]
[music intensifies]
[Yoko] The flowers are gone.
[Soichi sighs]
The truck.
Huh?
The truck that drove past us earlier.
[music intensifies]
[Yoko] It must've been
carrying the yellow flowers.
[uneasy music continues]
It's me.
All the flowers are gone.
The Fuma aren't here.
Hama-san, can you
look something up for us?
One-eight-nine-nine. Got it.
[man slurping]
[paper tears]
Hey, look this number up.
[Hamashima] Now!
[uneasy music continues]
[typing]
Look.
[Hamashima] This is it.
[music fades]
[Yoko] I'm glad
Gaku didn't send us into a trap.
Yeah.
[phone buzzes]
[Yoko sighs]
Yeah?
The truck is currently near
the Tahara Interchange,
and it's headed toward Nagoya.
You need to follow it.
I'll keep you posted. You got this.
We're on it.
[woman] Preparations are moving forward
for the solar eclipse.
And Crow?
All according to plan.
[door rattles]
THE HOLY POWDER WILL ARRIVE SOON
TOGETHER WE WILL FULFILL THE ECLIPSE
[Hamashima] Gaku killed
two Fuma members in his escape.
[uneasy music playing]
-[girl] Daddy?
-[music stops]
Daddy, are you here?
Mitsuki, what's wrong?
[Mitsuki] Where's Daddy?
[Mitsuki's mother]
I don't know. I still can't reach him.
I don't know.
[sniffles]
[Mitsuki] I want Daddy.
[Mitsuki's mother] I know. [sobs]
[crying] I wanna see him too.
[crying continues]
[wistful music playing]
[Gaku, Haru grunting]
[Gaku laughing]
[inaudible]
[Gaku's voice] If you blocked me,
I'd kill you.
[wistful music continues]
[music fades]
[phone buzzes]
[sighs]
Hello?
[Sawabe] I'm already here.
Were you tailed?
I lost them.
I'm on my way. Stay there.
We just passed Minami-Ohara Interchange.
The truck's 500 meters ahead.
500 meters.
[engine revs]
[metallic clattering]
Confirm you have a visual on the truck.
Don't be so impatient.
[Yoko gasps] There it is!
Confirmed. Up ahead.
-[wind gusting]
-[leaves rustling]
[door opens in distance]
[footsteps approaching]
Crow?
-[blade rasps]
-Oh, goddammit, no!
[both grunting]
[footsteps retreating]
[gasping]
[groans, grunts]
[Sawabe panting]
[flesh tearing]
[Sawabe grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[Sawabe screams]
[Sawabe panting]
[Sawabe groans in pain]
[Sawabe groans, gasps]
-[flesh tears]
-[Sawabe screams in pain]
[spits]
♪ Should I try to hide ♪
♪ The way I feel inside ♪
♪ My heart for you? ♪
♪ Would you say that you ♪
♪ Would try to love me too? ♪
♪ In your mind ♪
♪ Could you ever be ♪
♪ Really close to me? ♪
♪ I can tell the way you smile ♪
♪ If I feel that I ♪
♪ Could be certain, then ♪
♪ I would say the things ♪
♪ I want to say tonight ♪
♪ But till I can see ♪
♪ That you'd really care for me ♪
♪ I will dream ♪
♪ That someday you'll be ♪
♪ Really close to me ♪
♪ I can tell the way you smile ♪
♪ If I feel that I ♪
♪ Could be certain, then ♪
♪ I would say the things ♪
♪ I want to say tonight ♪
♪ But till I can see ♪
♪ That you'd really care for me ♪
♪ I'll keep trying to hide ♪
♪ The way I feel inside ♪
[music fades]
[intriguing music playing]