[crowd cheering, clapping]
[Mukai] Political complacency.
Our country… has become weaker
because of it.
[uneasy music playing]
[man 1] Yeah! That's right!
[Mukai] The past is gone.
The days when Japan was considered
an economic powerhouse are over.
[audience shouting]
We have been neglecting our progress
for far too long.
Isn't that right?
[crowd shouts] Yes!
[Mukai] We pretended
the status quo was fine,
and we simply accepted it.
[crowd shouts indistinctly]
That leads to nothing but a decline.
[crowd cheering]
The only choice we have is to change.
[woman 1] We need change!
You can count on me.
You've got Mukai Toko on your side.
-It's about time.
-[woman 2] Yes!
Reformation for a stronger Japan!
[crowd cheering]
[Mukai] Thank you so much! Thank you.
-You're gonna be our next president.
-I'll do my best. Thank you very much!
-I'm on your side 100%
-Hello, hi. How are you? Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Thank you. Thanks so much.
Thank you.
-I'll be supporting you.
-You can do it.
[uneasy music continues]
[sighs]
HOJO FAMILY TREE
[Fuma Kotaro] The moon devours the sun.
The shadow erodes the light.
The solar eclipse is all that's left.
So are you ready, Crow?
Yes.
[Fuma Kotaro] Even if you harm
your family?
My only mission
is to make the solar eclipse a success.
[Haru] Are you okay?
-You can stay--
-I'm going.
[grandmother] That boy is already gone.
He passed away six years ago.
You are shinobis.
Be sure that you make the right decision.
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
[gasps]
Get out.
Don't go near the Tawara family again.
Everything you saw in that house
doesn't exist.
[intriguing music playing]
Otherwise, you'll see this face again.
I won't be seeing you again.
Don't go back to your house for a while.
The Fuma are after you.
[pensive music playing]
Come on!
Get ready.
Quick, or you'll be left behind.
[Riku] Grandma!
[Yoko] Gaku
must be doing this for a reason.
Yoko.
[Nagi] Gaku-nii…
Yeah.
We know. We saw him.
He chose to become a Fuma.
What do we do?
He's not the same person anymore.
[Yoko] I know.
But still…
Even so…
he's still our eldest son.
Your big brother.
Our family.
We will return
together.
[Oki] Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
Your mission isn't getting Gaku-san back.
It's stopping the poison.
Sorry.
Hama-san told me to make sure.
[Soichi] We know that!
But, uh, I'm hoping Gaku-san
will come back to us.
[uneasy music playing]
All right. Let's go.
[Riku] Master.
Master!
Why are you ignoring me?
Tell me where we're going to.
Please?
[uneasy music continues]
Wait here.
[blades clanking]
[Riku gasps]
-[blood squelches]
-[woman groans]
[energetic music playing]
-[horn blaring]
-[tires squealing]
[driver 1] What the hell?
[grunts groans]
[driver 2 gasps, grunts]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[energetic music continues]
[panting]
[grunts]
[pensive music playing]
We're here.
MOCHIZUKI RARE BOOKS
[energetic music continues]
POWDER OF HOPE
[Nagi gasps]
[music intensifies]
-[blood squelching]
-[ninjas grunting]
[blade rasps]
[music stops]
["Seuls au Monde" playing softly]
[uneasy music playing]
[blood squelches]
[Soichi] Get Gaku!
[breathes nervously]
[Soichi] Haru! Go!
[Yoko] Go!
[Nagi] Haru-nii!
Bring Gaku-nii back!
[panting]
[grunts, groans]
[elevator bell dings]
[ninja gasping]
[music fades]
[breathing heavily]
[Gaku] I never would've guessed.
That we'd end up here.
[Haru] Why are you doing this?
I've changed.
The Fuma showed me the real truth.
[Haru] "The real truth"?
Of who we've been serving.
You must know by now.
You felt guilty.
When the Fuma captured me,
you blamed yourself.
But you know what?
You freed me.
The lineage.
Traditions.
The BNM.
The rules.
Family.
I was liberated from all that.
I could finally be myself.
Haru.
Come join us.
I know that you want to be free
from all this.
Gaku, let's go.
Let's go home.
Back to our family.
I told you, Haru.
Your kindness is ultimately your weakness.
Don't do this.
We have to cut off the head,
or else nothing will change.
-[skin tears]
-[grunts]
[breathes nervously]
-[skin tears]
-[grunts]
-[blood squelches]
-Gaku…
[Haru moans, gasps]
For me, brother…
"family" doesn't exist.
[both grunt]
[grunts]
[Fuma Kotaro on PA] How naive.
[uneasy music playing]
You're repeating the same mistake.
[tense music playing]
[breathing nervously]
[breathing heavily]
[Fuma Kotaro] The day has finally come.
After the solar eclipse,
I will govern this land.
This is the last ritual.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[Haru breathing heavily]
[Fuma Kotaro] Once I kill you,
he who created me,
I will truly be a god.
Rejoice.
You are the sacrifice to a god.
-[blood squelches]
-[Haru grunts]
[Haru grunting]
[Fuma Kotaro]
The bloodline of Hattori ends tonight.
[all grunting]
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
[breathing heavily]
-[blood squelches]
-[Haru grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[blood squelching]
[Haru grunting, gasping]
[tense music playing]
[all grunting]
[Soichi] Who are you?
[female ninja 1] Who are we?
Guardians of the Demon Gate.
[Nagi] But aren't we the last shinobis?
[uneasy music playing]
[Riku gasps] Master!
-Is this place where the Fuma--
-Sh!
Fighting doesn't mean you always
have to step foot on the battlefield.
[grandmother chuckles]
[soothing music playing]
[Soichi] Mayuko-kun?
[music continues]
[Yoko] Did you say something?
[Soichi] Never mind.
[music continues]
[music fades]
-[uneasy music playing]
-[breathing nervously]
[groaning]
[skin tearing]
[blood squelching]
[Haru panting]
[Fuma Kotaro] I am a god.
I am a god.
Impossible.
You haven't changed.
I hear a gentle sound from you.
Please join us.
Help complete the solar eclipse.
So many souls will be set free
in our country.
Your plan is over.
Not yet.
The solar eclipse means something else.
"Something else"?
Aren't you a bit curious?
Tell me.
The solar eclipse…
[blood pattering]
[blade whooshing]
Now it's over.
[skin tearing]
-[blood squelching]
-[grunts, gasps]
[uneasy music playing]
[weakly] Crow…
[music stops]
[wistful music playing]
Why?
Brother,
stay the way you are.
Gaku!
[groans, gasps]
-[Soichi] Haru!
-[Nagi] Haru-nii!
[Yoko] Haru!
[Soichi] Haru!
Hey! Are you okay?
Where's Gaku?
[Oki] I knew you would do it!
What a success!
And thanks to you all,
we effectively stopped
the spread of the poison
and prevented the solar eclipse plan.
They were planning to deliver the poison
to the Gentenkai disciples
all over the country today.
[Oki] Each of the 30,000 followers
were going to give the Powder of Hope
to everyone around them.
We completed our mission, so please…
[Hamashima] There's something else
to discuss.
Tawara Gaku is now considered a felon.
Family or not, you'll be charged
if you come in contact with him.
We have no choice but to keep a strict eye
on all of you for the time being.
Yeah, we know.
[Hamashima] One more thing.
I highly doubt that either you or the Fuma
use this kind of shinobi tool.
[grandmother laughs] Wow.
[grandmother laughs]
Can you believe
the Fuma are using such an obvious tool?
[laughs]
Here. Take a good look. [laughs]
Here.
[Haru] Hey.
Do you know
what else the eclipse signifies?
We're still investigating all of that.
I'm hoping that part was a lie.
Well, you've been doing a great job, kid.
Hey, where's Karen?
I really wanna see her.
[reporter] Many people have been
heading outside to check the sky.
The solar eclipse starts soon.
The whole country
is brimming with anticipation
and eager to witness
the celestial show of the century.
Next up.
The New Democratic Party's
presidential election.
With two days before the election,
the party's senior members
will gather together
at the Royce Tokyo Hotel this afternoon.
All eyes are on this gathering,
as all four candidates
will make their final appeals.
The candidates are
Yamabe, Minister of Finance.
Mukai, Policy Research Council Chair.
-Naka, acting Secretary-General.
-The eclipse.
[reporter] Tanabe, former Minister
of Internal Affairs and Communications.
A total of 500…
[mysterious music playing]
So cool.
Master, do you see that?
The moon devours the sun…
[indistinct chattering]
Yeah!
Okay.
…and the shadow…
erodes the light.
[panting]
-[man] It's nice to see you again.
-[Mukai] Yes. Oh, hello.
[woman speaks indistinctly]
[Mukai] Yes, it has!
[breathing heavily]
-Oh!
-Excuse me. Evacuate.
-Everyone.
-What?
-Please! Everyone needs to evacuate!
-Ma'am.
-Whoa! Hey, stop!
-Representative!
-Mukai! Please listen to me!
-[guard] Sorry.
[Karen grunts] Representative!
[Mukai] Wait, just a moment.
What do you want to tell me?
The people
who kidnapped you six years ago,
they're in this hotel right now.
They're here to harm you.
You have to leave now!
Would you escort her outside?
-Yeah, sure.
-Come on.
-You're crazy.
-You're in danger! Everyone leave now!
You have to believe me!
Mukai-kun, it's time for you
to propose your toast.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
[woman on PA] Thank you,
and we welcome you all
to the New Democratic Party's rally
for the collective future
beyond the election.
Representative Mukai,
Chair of the Policy Research Council,
will propose a toast.
Representative Mukai,
please go ahead whenever you're ready.
Representative! Let go of me now!
It's important!
[crowd clapping]
[Mukai] Thank you.
Thank you, everyone, for being here today.
Your presence is appreciated.
[dramatic music playing]
[Mukai] The path
that we all are determined to take
leads to a stronger Japan.
We unite.
During the campaign, we're competitors.
But once the election is over,
we work together here in the NDP.
Isn't that right, gentlemen?
[all laugh]
Now then,
please raise your glasses in the air.
Ready?
To the New Democratic Party.
NDP!
[all cheer]
[alarm blaring]
[gasping, choking]
[crowd shouting]
[uneasy music playing]
-[uneasy music continues]
-[people shouting indistinctly]
[panting]
It's across the board.
NDP, police, special forces…
[reporter] And now, we go live to…
This was it.
The true solar eclipse.
[phone ringing]
…the link between incidents
is currently being investigated.
Due to the possibility
of a chemical weapon
or dangerous virus being spread
from coast to coast,
police have sealed off the sites
to be investigated
by the counterterrorism special forces.
As of now, the country's government
is scrambling to deal with this emergency.
Yes.
[Ayame] There's been a change
in the chain of command.
I will be giving you the orders
from now on.
[reporter] …Fujimiya will be holding
an emergency press conference later today…
[Ayame] Are you listening?
Understood. Loud and clear.
[dial tone]
…Kato fell unconscious
and was rushed to a hospital.
And we just received new information.
NDP lawmakers Yamabe,
Horikawa, Furuya, and Ohmura
were also rushed to the hospital.
The Chief of Staff
of the Joint Staff, Kato
was just confirmed dead at the hospital.
The exact cause of death
is unknown at this point in time.
Police confirmed that he had shown
the same symptoms
as Superintendent General Shioya,
and they're investigating
the possible link between the two deaths.
The sudden death
of the head of the National Defense
has shocked all sectors.
The Chief of Staff of
the Ground Self-Defense Force, Yoshikawa,
will replace the deceased
Chief of the Joint Staff, Shigeru Kato.
We have an interview
with Representative Mukai Toko,
who barely managed to survive the ordeal.
[Mukai] It's a tragedy.
So many precious lives were lost today.
We still haven't found out
the cause behind
this horrible incident.
But we cannot… keep our heads… hung low.
As the largest party,
we will do our very best
to rebuild from where we are
and continue to lead the nation.
[reporter] The NDP election
is drawing attention amid chaos.
If the election proceeds as is,
will Representative Mukai,
who is the sole survivor
among the candidates,
be elected as the NDP president?
Let's take a look
at Representative Mukai's profile.
Representative Mukai Toko was born in 1964
as the eldest daughter
of the distinguished Sakaki family
in Aoba Ward, Yokohama City.
After graduating from Toshuin University…
Sakaki family?
…at the age of 25.
Master?
She served as a secretary
to the lawmakers and former ministers,
Ojiro and Nabeshima…
Sakaki.
[uneasy music playing]
[music fades]
My lord, the 20th.
Things don't seem to be going smoothly.
My sincere apologies.
What's the importance of your family tree?
HOJO FAMILY TREE
Why did we conceal the fact that
you're a descendant of the Hojo family?
TOKO SAKAKI
Since I took office,
I have been doing my best
to revise the constitution.
The anti-revisionists
certainly put up a fight.
[Ayame] Shut up.
[uneasy music playing]
You're a disgrace
to the legacy of the Hojo clan.
Do better in your role
as a puppet for the Fuma clan.
I will.
[Gaku] Good.
As long as we have possession
of the scroll, the Demon Gate will open.
Our nation will be on top when it opens.
We will be the dominant threat.
And Japan will be strong once again.
[grandmother] Sixty-five.
-You need to be quick.
-[Riku] Yeah.
[grandmother] Sixty-six.
Sixty-seven.
[Soichi] Yoko.
[grandmother] Sixty-eight!
Sixty-nine.
Seventy.
[Riku grunts]
[grandmother] Very good.
Seventy-one.
-Good. Seventy-two.
-[Riku grunts]
[grandmother] Good, come back.
Quickly!
[Riku] Oh man.
-[grandmother] Okay, seventy-three.
-[Riku grunts]
[grandmother] Seventy-four.
Seventy-five.
-Good job!
-Okay.
-Seventy-six.
-[Riku grunts]
-Back again. Move.
Come on.
Ready? Seventy-seven.
[Riku] Mmm, okay.
[grandmother] Seventy-eight.
[Riku] Okay.
-[grandmother] Seventy-nine.
-Ew.
-[grandmother] Keep going!
-Okay.
[grandmother] And back again. Eighty.
-[Riku] Okay.
-[grandmother] Eighty-one.
[Riku grunts]
[grandmother] Eighty-two.
Eighty-three.
[Riku grunts]
[grandmother] Eighty-four.
[Riku] Okay.
[grandmother] Eighty-five.
[Riku grunts]
Eighty-six.
[grandmother] Eighty-seven.
-Eighty-eight.
-[Riku] Okay.
[grandmother] Eighty-nine.
[Riku grunts]
[grandmother] Ninety!
Ninety-one.
Ninety-two.
-You can do it.
-[Riku] Yeah.
[grandmother] Ninety-three.
[Soichi] Good!
[grandmother] Okay, come back.
[man] I'm so gonna miss you
when you're gone.
Do you really mean that?
Junmai sake will be enough.
I won't ask for the expensive stuff.
You're taking over the brewery, right?
[Haru] Uh…
That's great.
Family issue is all sorted out.
All right, wanna go
to our "Last Supper" together?
You can even order an extra-large.
It'll be my farewell gift to you.
I can't.
Oh. You're a vegetarian now.
Yeah, I guess.
I walked past the shop the other day.
She was still in there.
Come on. Talk to her already.
I'm pretty sure you'd hit it off.
A great couple if you ask me.
Whoo!
[gasps] Talk to her!
[wind whistling]
[silence]
["Nothing's Changed"
by The Zombies playing]
♪ It's a mistake going back ♪
♪ They tell me that ♪
♪ Nothing's the same ever again ♪
♪ But when you walked through the door ♪
♪ It was just like before ♪
♪ Oh, nothing's changed, no ♪
♪ When I saw you again, little girl ♪
♪ Something stopped here inside ♪
♪ And I wanted to hold you ♪
♪ And tell you I loved you
Just like before ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ This is just one day ♪
♪ But one day is enough
To start all over again ♪
♪ Give me just one day ♪
♪ And we will begin all over again ♪
♪ You didn't mean to hurt me before
But you did ♪
♪ You did ♪
♪ But now, you're sorry now, I know ♪
♪ Oh, you're sorry now, I can see ♪
♪ 'Cause when you saw me again
You smiled at me then ♪
♪ Like nothing's changed, no ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh-oh ♪
♪ This is just one day ♪
♪ But one day is enough
To start all over again ♪
♪ Give me just one day ♪
♪ And we will begin all over again ♪
♪ It's gonna be easy this time, I know ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ Come on, just try me one more time ♪
♪ I know it's gonna work out just fine ♪
♪ Start all over ♪
♪ Again ♪
[rhythmic drum music playing]
[music fades]