[guide] A long time ago,
this Odawara area where you all live
was ruled by a clan named Odawara Hojo.
[children] Wow.
[guide] And the ninja clan
that was devoted to this very clan
was the Fuma!
-[children cheering, clapping]
-Oh yeah!
[guide] Wow!
Whoa!
And here comes their leader, Fuma Kotaro!
[ninja 1 exclaims]
[children cheering]
[Riku] Wow!
Oh yeah!
[ninja 1] I am the fifth Fuma Kotaro!
[ninja 2] Your time is over!
-[guide] Look!
-[Riku] What?
[guide] That's Hattori Hanzo!
Fuma and Hattori
were the two super famous
rival ninja clans!
-[children exclaiming]
-[Riku] Whoa.
[Fuma] You shameful Hattori!
We'll teach you a lesson!
[Hattori] Go ahead.
Attack!
-[dramatic music playing]
-[cheering]
[Riku] Get 'em!
Come on, Fuma, get 'em!
Come on, come on! Fuma!
Fuma! Come on!
[Riku] Fuma! Yeah! [echoes]
YOU CALL YOURSELF A SHINOBI?
THE BEST SHINOBI ARE LIKE SHADOWS
[Yoko] It will only be on weekdays.
But why?
Because.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm telling you now.
-You got a new job?
-That's right, honey.
Wait a minute.
You didn't ask my permission.
Why does she need your permission?
I need to do my part too.
But you shooed away that pigeon.
So I decided to help us
with a little part-time job.
-[Nagi] I support you, Mom.
-Same here.
[father] Mother!
Can you buy me a video game
if you work a lot?
Mmm, of course!
I support ya!
[Yoko] I guess that's settled, then.
Riku, you went on a field trip today.
You had fun, right?
It was more than that.
Odawara Castle was the best.
And Fuma Kotaro was awesome!
I'll show you. He had shurikens,
and he threw them like this.
Then his sword went
ka-ching, ka-ching, ka-ching, like this.
Punch, punch, kick!
Oh wow! You're like a Fuma!
Riku-chan, you're being very observant.
Although you're wrong.
If Yoko-san was really a shinobi,
she'd be third-class.
Why?
Hmm? Remember.
A shinobi should always be careful
not to be caught.
You saw your mom.
That's why she's third-class.
Hmm? Or fourth?
-[grandmother laughs]
-Oh, Mother. Quite the imagination.
[all laughing]
[laughter continues]
[funky mysterious music playing]
[music fades]
[cicada buzzing]
-[Haru] Hey.
-[Gaku] Hmm?
I heard fried food
and cold beer go best together.
Oh.
Wanna try? Just once.
[Gaku chuckles]
Just once?
-You're such a freakin' nerd.
-[chuckles]
Okay.
Time to head back.
-[Haru] Already?
-Have you forgotten our mission?
What's going on?
Can you, uh, maybe, go alone?
I wanna quit.
I can't do it.
Haru, what do you mean you can't do it?
It's part of being a shinobi.
-I can't kill someone.
-[Gaku] Yes, you can.
Haru.
Did you forget? You killed me.
[uneasy music playing]
[tense music playing]
[breathing heavily]
All right. Ready for your gyudon?
What? Were you asleep?
[engine starting]
[reporter] Just after
11:00 p.m. last night
at the Sel Octagon Tokyo dance club
in Minato City,
multiple patrons at the club
were attacked and stabbed
by an unknown assailant
disguised in what authorities revealed
as a clown mask.
Upon fleeing the club after the stabbings,
the unidentified perpetrator
was struck by a vehicle
and police have confirmed
he was found deceased at the scene.
-Local police will continue…
-[employee] Welcome.
…sending findings to official prosecution
for determination of motive.
Good evening.
Where were you last night?
-[reporter] Our next story…
-What do you mean by "night"?
Around 11:00 p.m.
11:00.
-Uh, I was working.
-[camera shutter clicking]
Can I take a picture?
But you already took one.
What's that for?
Did you hear about
what happened at the club?
Yeah, I just heard about it on the news.
I was there at that time.
What?
Was everything okay?
Mm-mm. Not really. It sucked.
Some weird guy threw an ashtray.
It cracked my phone.
You know who did it?
[reporter] And our final headline
involves new information
regarding the Frontier Roots incident,
where all passengers
aboard the pleasure cruise perished
just off the Port of Kawasaki
in Kanagawa Prefecture.
According to police reports,
all crew members
and passengers on the cruise
unexpectedly went into
death-inducing convulsions…
That's so awful.
Yeah, it is.
The cause of the convulsions
and subsequent deaths
is still unclear at this point…
There's something I haven't told you.
What?
I'm a…
I'm a journalist for this magazine.
[Haru] Oh.
Hey! Mu!
You're teasing me, aren't you?
Not at all. I'm really into aliens.
[Karen laughs]
This is kind of last minute.
Do you have any time tomorrow?
[funky pensive music playing]
AGENCY FOR CULTURAL AFFAIRS
-[camera beeps]
-[lock clicks]
BOILER ROOM
[door closes]
[indistinct chattering]
-Hello.
-[men] Morning.
[music continues]
[door opens]
[man 1] I wasn't expecting your call.
So?
We don't have proof yet.
But…
You smell something.
Let me know if there's any movement.
We'll be on standby.
Huh. I guess you were working
while we were away, eh?
[Hamashima] Even if
there isn't any shinobi activity,
we still need
to keep track of their reputation.
Is that what you do all day?
That's hardly working.
[Hamashima chuckles]
Uh, excuse me.
These gentlemen are…
Right. Our old members.
They were on a break,
but they're needed now.
You are?
-Oki.
-[man 1] And what do you do?
Oh. I was brought in
as a technology specialist.
I wanna help with their missions
by adding this technology
to the six tools of shinobi.
Shinobis are pretty stubborn.
They won't accept this right away.
We can't be stuck in the past.
We need to change with the times as well.
This is Kuze, known as the "Cleaner."
[Oki] Pleasure to meet you.
Change with the times?
Still using flying pigeons?
Carrier pigeons are
the best for communication.
They're small, they're incredibly swift,
and they elude hackers.
However, this technology
does what carrier pigeons cannot.
[woman] All right, everyone.
Let's have a great time! Cheers!
-Here, cheers!
-[man] Hey, cheers! Yup.
[guests laughing on video]
-[man chokes]
-[woman] Huh?
[gasping, choking]
[woman screams] Oh my God!
[all gasping, choking]
Where did you get this?
I hacked into the police database.
That's all.
[phone ringing]
Yes?
[man 2] Any updates?
Wonder who that could be?
Nobody knows.
Probably one of the higher-ups.
[Hamashima] I assigned Tawara's second son
to keep an eye
on the dance club murder case
and the investigating journalist,
Karen Ito.
What about the cruise company?
[Hamashima] Tawara's wife is on it.
She's investigating if anyone on board
wasn't on the passenger list.
Right. We have no comment on that.
That's right.
We are currently suspending operations.
Apologies. Huh?
God damn.
Hey, you!
I wanted coffee, not this.
What?
-Get me coffee.
-Ah!
-[coffee splashes]
-[man] Ah shit!
-What the hell? You idiot!
-[Yoko] I'm sorry!
Don't touch me!
-And this my best suit.
-Sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
[mysterious music playing]
2024 PASSENGER LIST
[music fades]
[paper shredder humming]
Hello?
Can I interest you in some tea?
Ah, I'm sorry for interrupting.
Apologies.
I just started working here
this week, and I--
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[phone chimes]
WHEN WILL YOU RETURN IT?
DON'T GET CAUGHT
-[Kyotani] Can I sit down?
-[Nagi] Sure.
You've been pretty sad all day.
I'm sorry for making you think so much.
Wh… what? Think?
Yeah, 'cause…
Well, I confessed my feelings,
and now you're thinking about it.
Sorry, but
I wasn't thinking about that.
What? [chuckles]
Wait. Wait.
Then what?
I've got this, um…
a stalker?
[loudly] A stalker?
-Who? Where are they?
-[Nagi] Wait.
No, no, no.
I'm pretty sure they're not here.
I'll protect you.
Don't worry, I'll be your protector.
One stalker's kind of already enough.
Uh-huh.
RÉSUMÉ
Thank you. Have a nice day.
[man sighs]
[applicant] Any questions for me?
Not at all.
[man] Thank you for coming.
What's going on?
We're hiring a sales manager.
You haven't even been asking them
any questions about their résumés.
No need for that.
He wrote the wrong kanji.
[man groans]
There's only one person left.
Don't just ignore them.
At least ask them some questions.
Don't worry about it. Do you know why?
I'll meet my destiny.
It's my lucky color today.
RÉSUMÉ
Stunning.
What?
[Mayuko] Yes?
Your Kanji.
It's impeccable.
[man] Really?
-You're hired.
-Huh?
When can you start?
I'm actually available to start today.
Sorry I'm late.
-And for dragging you along.
-It's all good.
Where are we headed?
Here.
It's Akiyama Sota's place.
Huh?
The person who was trying to give me
some information at the club.
He's not with us anymore.
He was murdered.
Huh?
-So you're--
-It might be my last chance.
I wanna interview his family,
but I didn't wanna go by myself.
I thought maybe you'd come with me.
Oh.
[Karen] Let's go.
[mysterious music playing]
[Haru] What do we do?
[Karen] Let's wait until they come back.
[Haru] Just wait?
We don't really know when they'll be back.
[Karen] I'm used to waiting.
One time, I waited for three days.
[Haru] Three days?
Oh.
[Karen] Huh?
[Haru] It's unlocked.
[mysterious music continues]
Maybe we shouldn't…
I'll be quick.
[Haru] Do Mu reporters always do this?
I remember this.
But from where?
[camera shutter clicking]
-Can we go now?
-In a minute.
-[door opens]
-[Karen gasps]
[door closes]
[keys clatter]
[clattering]
[door opens, closes]
[Karen breathes shakily]
-[clattering]
-[distant scream]
[clattering]
[gasps]
[uneasy music playing]
[grunts]
[breathing nervously]
[door closes]
[phone chimes]
[breathing nervously]
-[Haru] Shouldn't we call the police?
-[Karen] No.
I don't want us to become suspects.
I'm sorry for bringing you.
Who's that guy?
No idea.
I just went there to interview his family.
But now two people are dead.
So, uh, yeah, maybe you should stop here.
He had the same scar in the same spot.
Scar?
He had to have been the real killer.
The other guy was a scapegoat.
I'm willing to bet
his real target was Akiyama-san.
He also mentioned a yellow flower.
I'll help. Let's do this.
You've done more than enough.
I'll take it from here.
I can't leave you.
Because I wanna eat gyudon with you again.
[wiping]
-Grandma.
-[Grandma] Hmm?
What was Gaku-niichan like?
Your brother was like the sun.
The sun?
Yes.
That's the best way to describe him.
Hot like a sweaty shoe?
[laughing]
Grandma.
Grandma?
[inaudible]
[mysterious music playing]
-[Hamashima] What did you find?
-[Haru] I'm not here about your mission.
[Hamashima] Then why are you here?
[Haru] How long
have you been spying on her?
[Hamashima] You found out she's dangerous?
[Haru] That's not it.
-[Hamashima] Then what?
-[Haru] What aren't you telling me?
If you want to know, I'm sure
you can figure it out on your own.
You're a shinobi, aren't you?
Well?
Do you have something else,
or are we done here?
That's a woman's body
made to look like a suicide by hanging.
-There a suspect?
-The same killer from the club.
You should've
gotten rid of him that night.
A shinobi who can't kill. Hmm.
It's bad?
Yeah, that company really sucks.
They look down on me like a female peon.
A shinobi losing composure?
You're out of shape.
Since when have I had any composure?
Did you find the name of the survivor?
Anything?
I haven't found anything
on the passenger list yet.
Except there's a guy
I'm keeping an eye on.
[Hamashima] Okay.
Give me a call when you find something.
EARLY PAYMENT IS APPRECIATED
[mysterious music playing]
A puzzle box was recently stolen from
the Kanagawa Prefectural Museum of Art.
Judging from previous cases,
it is very likely
that it will be returned.
The police are tightening security
as their intention is
to capture the thief in action.
As these serial steal-and-return cases
are highly unusual,
they have attracted media
and public attention.
-[mysterious music continues]
-[camera shutter clicks]
[funky music playing]
[man] What is she saying?
-[camera shutter clicking]
-[man] I can't see anything.
[camera shutter clicking]
[indistinct chattering]
[music fades]
[phone buzzing]
-[man 1] I'll take a tea.
-[Yoko] Here you go.
Here's your tea.
[Yoko] Would you like some tea?
[inaudible]
[high-pitched squeal]
NO ONE WILL FIND OUT, MR. MATSUURA.
"Matsuura."
You made a proposal your first day.
I'm not sure if it'll be accepted,
but please talk to your family about it.
Yes, I will.
-Okay. Tomorrow, then.
-Uh-huh.
[chuckles softly]
YOKO
[phone line ringing]
[voice mail] The person you called
is not available.
Please leave a message.
[man] Hey, sir,
come out for a drink for once.
Oh, I don't think today is the best, uh…
[man 2] Come on.
You can order Calpis Soda.
[laughing]
You know what?
His wife was cheating on him.
She lied about having a part-time job
and stopped answering his calls.
She was banging her side piece instead.
[laughs]
[man 2] Forget this.
I'm gonna get black-out drunk.
You idiot.
[man 1 laughing]
I hope you all have fun tonight.
Great work.
Thanks, boss.
[woman] Do you really think
they're going to show up?
Yeah, you need to learn how to relax.
If the thief went through the effort
to leave a note behind,
most likely, they're trying to show off.
Who could it be?
Probably a young woman.
[scoffs]
Am I gonna get canceled
because I said that?
You're confusing me
with someone who cares.
Whatever. It's about time
we had some fun around here.
Are you hoping for a handsome thief?
-Sorry I'm late.
-I figured out the logo.
[Haru] What's "Gentenkai"?
[Karen] It's a new religious group.
They have 30,000 followers and growing.
Crazy.
Tsujioka Yosuke is the leader.
Most of his followers are younger.
He comes off as a naturalist
and addresses environmental issues.
He's super shady.
He holds a gathering every month.
You mean you're going?
Yeah, I'm gonna go.
Why?
"Why" what?
Why do you have to go so deep into it?
It's unsolved.
I get really curious.
There was an incident years ago.
[Haru] Mm-hmm.
A fire at a hotel.
Probably arson.
The hotel burned down.
They thought
all the hotel guests had died.
And then a three-year-old
was somehow found unharmed.
For some reason, no one tried
to figure out how it happened.
It's exciting.
The cruise incident reminds me of that.
It has to be a conspiracy.
[chuckles] Sounds like Mu, right?
And your job?
Are you passionate about vending machines?
Not exactly.
I'm not cut out for my family's business.
I know I'll have to take over,
but I'm procrastinating.
[Karen] Hmm.
I bet they're going to the event.
See you tomorrow.
[man] Hey, you!
I'm still working. Get me a coffee.
Put extra sugar and milk.
Absolutely, sir.
[mockingly] "Put extra sugar and milk."
As you wish.
Ah!
[typing]
[mysterious music playing]
[man gasping]
[mysterious music stops]
[body thuds]
[mysterious music playing]
[Nagi] Hey!
Wait!
[Nagi gasps]
[tense music playing]
[coughing]
What the hell was that?
[Nagi] Give it back!
[phone buzzing]
SOICHI-SAN
-[gasps]
-[man grunts]
[man grunts]
[phone buzzing]
[phone line ringing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] There!
What the hell is security doing?
[woman] No idea.
[snarling]
[straining]
-[man snarls]
-[Yoko strains]
[music fades]
Which way?
I don't know!
-You guys didn't see?
-No, sir.
No, nothing.
Damn it.
Call backup.
-Yes.
-Yes, sir!
-Go check the security camera.
-Yes, sir.
-[bus horn honks]
-[man gasps]
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
Another cover-up by hanging.
They really have no imagination at all.
-Get to work.
-[funky music playing]
Time to work.
[all] Yes, sir.
And don't forget about
all the security cameras.
Yes, sir.
[funky music continues]
Uh, it's been six years.
[Yoko] Nice to see ya!
-What's been six years?
-The Mukai abduction case.
We had to clean up
a mountain of Fuma corpses.
[Yoko yawns]
Take it home with you.
You can put it all together on your time.
[sighs]
This is gonna be a waste of time.
-[cleaner] We're done here.
-Good job.
What should we do with the body?
[Hamashima] Why ask me? Make it a hanging.
[all] Yes, sir.
I had the newbies pull up some research.
He made a phone call to Matsuura
just before he was murdered.
He works for a travel agency.
Something is fishy here.
It's time for
"Misa-san" to take the stage.
[playfully] "Misa-san"?
[laughs]
It sure has been a while.
Excuse me. Who exactly is Misa-san?
By the way, you all right?
Uh, it's just a scratch.
It'll be healed up by tomorrow.
Oh, I didn't mean that.
You're extremely late
getting home in time for dinner.
[gasps]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[slurps]
[panting]
-[sighs]
-[music fades]
[indistinct chattering]
-[man 1] Excuse me.
-[woman 1] Right? I'm glad we came early.
[man 2] He's gonna be there.
He'll be standing right there.
-I heard Tsujioka is coming today.
-You kidding me?
-Yeah.
-You mean for real? Seriously, for real?
-It's so cool.
-[woman 2] Yeah.
[panting]
-[man 3] I actually joined last month.
-Oh, really?
[man 3] Yeah.
[man 3] Oh, it's time. It's starting now.
[audience claps]
[Tsujioka] Let us stop.
Let us laugh.
[audience laughing]
[Tsujioka] Let us stop.
[laughter stops]
[Tsujioka] Let us scream.
[audience screaming]
[Tsujioka] Let us stop.
[screaming stops]
[Tsujioka] Let us cry.
[audience crying]
[footsteps approaching]
[Tsujioka] Why do we cry?
That is right.
You're crying for the sake of our world.
But please, have no worries.
None of us are alone.
Let us believe.
When we all become united…
we will be able to regain
everything we lost.
♪ Gee whiz ♪
♪ Look at his eyes ♪
♪ How they hypnotize ♪
♪ He's got everything a girl could want ♪
♪ Man, oh, man ♪
♪ What a prize ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Gee whiz ♪
♪ He's all the joy ♪
♪ I could find in a boy ♪
♪ He's awful nice, it's paradise ♪
♪ I hope I'm not his decoy ♪
♪ Decoy ♪
♪ Heaven up above ♪
♪ Knows how much ♪
♪ I love that fella's soul ♪
♪ Angels sing ♪
♪ Of a love like this ♪
♪ I hope our love will grow and grow ♪
♪ 'Cause, gee whiz ♪
♪ Gee whiz ♪
♪ I love that guy ♪
♪ My, my, oh my ♪
♪ There are things we could do ♪
♪ I could say I love you ♪
♪ But all I can say is ♪
♪ Gee whiz ♪
[music stops]
[funky mysterious music playing]
[music fades]