[insects chirping]
[blows gently]
What? That's so cool.
[Gaku] Where did it go?
I don't know where it went.
Hmm…
-Oh, this?
-Whoa!
[chuckles] Hey, teach me how to do that!
-First, it disappears.
-Mm-hmm.
-Then reappears.
That's pretty much all there is to it.
You try.
[whooshing]
-Oh. [chuckles]
-Ah! I dropped it.
-[sighs] This is hard.
-Hmm.
[Nagi laughs]
It's your first time.
We can make anything disappear.
Even ourselves.
[mysterious music playing]
We can disappear and come back?
[mysterious music continues]
[music fades]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[door opens]
-[Nagi] What do you want?
-I saw you.
What?
I saw you run across the rooftop
and into your room.
I knew it!
-[Nagi] Get out.
-Wait! Teach me!
-No! No way!
-Teach me how to do it!
Get out!
-Teach me!
-Listen.
You can't tell Mom or Dad.
Do you understand?
-Understand?
-Okay. Teach me!
-Forget it.
-[Riku] No!
[Nagi grunts]
-Teach me!
-Get out.
-[sighs]
-[Riku] Meanie!
Meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie!
[phone chimes]
NINJA-X SENT YOU A PHOTO
[uneasy music playing]
THIS WILL FETCH A GOOD PRICE
GIVE IT BACK
I'M WILLING TO TRADE FOR A CERTAIN SCROLL
WHAT SCROLL?
THE ONE IN OUR HOUSE
"Our house"?
OUR?
[Tsujioka] "If a tree falls in a forest
and no one is around to hear it,
does it make a sound?"
The first time I heard
this famous philosophical question,
I was in awe
at what arrogant creatures humans are.
Even if no human is listening,
all of the birds,
the deer,
and all of the plants are listening.
When it falls, of course it makes a sound.
"Sound does not exist
if there are no humans there to hear it."
[employee] Thank you!
Is this isolated?
Applying only to the forest?
I don't get it.
Get what?
What's his appeal?
Says the person who's been staring at him.
It's my job.
I just wonder
what his followers must be thinking.
[employee] Extra broth,
extra green onion, raw egg.
-[Haru] Thanks.
-[employee] Large, extra garlic, kimchi.
You want a bite?
-[Haru] Mm-hmm.
-[Karen chuckles]
[Tsujioka] Now, let us come.
Let us raise our voices together…
[Karen] Mmm.
-[Haru] Mmm.
-[Karen] Mm-hmm. [chuckles]
[Tsujioka] We are not merely miserable
and voiceless victims.
-Let us not forget.
-[employee] Welcome.
[Tsujioka] Just as you all
are watching me now,
I also watch all of you.
Always.
[mysterious music playing]
[tense music stab]
Mmm! Hold it!
-[Haru] Mmm.
-Mmm, mmm. What?
-It's a live stream.
-Can you pause?
-No.
-[Hamashima] Large.
[employee] Got it.
One large coming up.
[man on TV] I apologize for the amount
of inconvenience and distress
that I have caused everyone.
The information published
about my affairs with multiple women
is admittedly true.
What?
[man on TV] I was thoughtless
and irresponsible.
Nothing.
[man on TV] I committed
an unforgivable act.
Um, Dad?
Uh-huh.
What's an "affair"?
[man on TV] I am truly very sorry.
My wife, who has been
my biggest supporter…
[grandmother] It's forbidden love.
It's something
that makes it exciting for them.
[man on TV] I intend to apologize
directly to her…
-[Soichi clears throat]
-[grandmother laughs]
So, uh, our brewery's new head of sales
has managed to get us prominently featured
in a foreign magazine.
So we're, uh, going to take a family photo
just for the article.
-[Yoko] What?
-[Soichi] Mm-hmm.
-Photo?
-[Riku] In a magazine?
-[Soichi] Yep.
Let's do it!
-[laughing]
-You never told me about that.
That's what I'm doing right now.
Hey, Nagi. 2:00 p.m. Brewery. Saturday.
[Nagi] Mm-hmm. Why?
Come to the brewery
on Saturday, all right?
-We're taking a photo, got it?
-You should've asked.
[Soichi sighs]
[tuts]
Haru's the last one left.
[funky mysterious music playing]
[music fades]
[Hamashima] Report?
There was a yellow flower
in Tsujioka's room.
Sneak into Gentenkai.
Don't get caught. Get the flower.
Could you stop giving me orders?
It pisses me off.
[Hamashima] Apparently, Tsujioka
hardly ever leaves the building.
What about the young lady?
What about her?
Does she know anything about the flower?
We can use her if she does.
I'll be going alone.
You've got a crush on her, don't you?
Whatever. Either way,
make sure the job gets done.
And stop showing up there.
She's gonna notice.
Hey, I just happen to be
a fan of their gyudon.
Nah, let's get something else.
You look great, Misa-san.
So?
Right.
Your target, Matsuura, is currently…
quite active on this matchmaking app.
He looks like an average guy,
but he's our only lead
in the pleasure cruise incident.
I created your profile to match his type
and sent a message saying,
"I'd like to meet you."
Ugh!
By the way, Matsuura's a jazz enthusiast.
Your profile says that you like jazz, too,
so please keep that in mind.
Jazz is the worst music ever.
Jazz is just… so cool.
I'm a fan, also.
[chuckles]
I'm so glad we met, Misa-san.
[Yoko] So am I.
Tell me, what do you do for a living?
I travel, but it's dull.
[Yoko laughs flirtatiously]
Do you travel all over the world?
No, I'm only working inside
the department of domestic sales.
[Yoko] Sure, but there are
so many wonderful places
to travel within Japan too, right?
Uh, I'm just the middleman
between all of our clients.
It's kind of boring. Yeah.
But I focus on my hobby on days off.
Jazz, right?
Yes.
I thought so.
[laughs]
You're great.
[both laugh]
IS YOUR PARTNER ACTING STRANGE?
DID YOU KNOW?
INFIDELITY AMONG WOMEN IS ON THE RISE
A WHOPPING 24.1% INCREASE IN 10 YEARS!
[sighs in frustration]
That's not it.
Hi, sir.
Uh… Yeah.
Yes?
[Mayuko laughs]
[both chuckle]
So did your family agree
to be part of the magazine?
Yeah. All good.
That's great.
They're sending a crew
straight from France
to cover the photo shoot.
Let's make sure all goes well.
-[Soichi] Mm-hmm.
-Oh. The title of the article…
-Title?
-Yes.
"Familial bonds give rise
to traditional flavor. Tawara Brewery."
Is it bad?
Great.
Great, Mayuko-kun.
Familial bonds.
It's nice.
You'll never believe it, Kuze-san!
I worked my first mission today,
and guess how it went?
Good luck.
[man 1] It's this one.
No, never mind. It's not.
It's like looking for a needle
in a haystack.
Still got a lot to learn, rookie.
[mysterious music playing]
[devices chime]
[device chimes]
[phone buzzing]
Yeah?
[Soichi] Haru, it's me.
Can you take some time
to come to the brewery
at 2:00 p.m. this Saturday?
We're taking a photo.
Sorry, I need to go.
[mysterious music continues]
Oh! Sorry.
[devices chiming]
[man 1] I guess we just have
to leave it up to fate.
[man 2] You don't think it needs to have
any kind of structure or anything?
[man 1] I think for a chance to be chosen,
you have to have
a change in consciousness or something.
[man 2] Oh. How does that happen?
[mysterious music continues]
[man 3] Hello.
Are you a new member?
Yes.
I'll give you a tour.
[music swells, stops]
[Haru] Do you think that I might be able
to meet Tsujioka-san?
[man 3 laughs] I understand how you feel.
I've been here two years
and haven't met him yet.
Although, I pray every day
that my turn is next.
But he is actually here, isn't he?
Of course he is.
Right here.
This way.
Welcome. Welcome to awareness.
I'm Tsujioka Yosuke,
and I represent this association.
Firstly, let me
express my gratitude to you
for knocking on Gentenkai's door
of your own free will.
-[woman 1] Have a seat.
-[Karen] Thank you.
[Tsujioka] In today's society,
everything is overwhelming and busy.
I think it's a sign of hope
that such like-minded individuals
are able to take the time
and gather together in community here.
[professor] So when an externality
has a negative impact,
it's aptly called a negative externality.
When the impact
on the third party is adverse,
it's said that it has resulted
in a negative externality.
What does that mean in practice?
THE SCROLL IS TITLED "VISION OF CALAMITY"
Some of you may have learned
about this incident in high school.
THE ONE IN OUR HOUSE
[whispers] A scroll.
…into the water, contaminating…
What did you say?
It's not important.
[professor] In this case,
this particular unnamed company
imposed a negative externality
upon the local residents.
Excuse me, we're in class.
As I was saying, another example is
if there's someone making noise on a train
or on the street,
and it bothers others, it's a negative--
-[woman] Sorry to interrupt your class.
-[professor] Yes?
-[woman] We are from the police.
-[professor] Police?
[woman] We'd like to talk
with one of the students.
-The cops are here?
-[professor] Right now?
Sorry, yes.
[thumping]
-Ah, ah. [clears throat]
-[high-pitched feedback]
Uh, Kyotani Kohei.
Is Kyotani Kohei
from the economics department here?
What?
I'm right here.
-[Omi] That's you?
-Uh-huh.
Come with us.
A word.
[student 1] Kohei?
[student 2] He's so busted.
-[Omi] Come on! It's the middle of class.
-R… right. Sorry, sorry.
[Kyotani] It was amazing, Nagi-chan.
I've never been questioned
by the police before!
[Nagi] Get to the point.
[Kyotani] Okay.
You know that thief
that steals and returns stuff?
Mm-hmm.
Apparently, I've been at
every museum that's been targeted.
What is up with that?
What's that mean?
It… means they think I'm a suspect!
-What?
-[laughs]
Yeah, it's no big deal.
We're each other's alibi
because I told them we were together.
-[laughs]
-Good for us.
[Kyotani] Man, that was so freaking scary!
[Riku] Ten, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Seven, eight, nine.
One, two, three.
INSIDE
OUTSIDE
It still doesn't add up.
[Omi] Hey, kid.
Is Tawara Nagi here?
Omi-san, you're gonna scare him.
[Omi groans]
-You're the police?
-Mm-hmm.
Tawara Nagi.
She must be your sister, right?
I'm not so sure.
Hey, kid, what do you mean?
I heard some kids get kidnapped
and then raised by somebody else.
And were you kidnapped?
I don't know.
Can you investigate that for me?
Maybe we can
after we find your older sister, okay?
How late does she stay out?
Really, really late.
Last time, it was 11:00.
Oh! You know what?
See that roof?
Over there. She ran across that roof
and went into that room.
[Omi] Oh.
-[Omi] Take photos.
-[woman] Copy that.
-[mysterious music playing]
-[camera shutter clicking]
Follow me to the next area, please.
[Karen gasps]
[Haru] Sh! Why are you here?
Why am I? Why are you here?
Did I tell you that I was coming?
I could tell by the look on your face.
-Sawabe-san! Thank you for the other day.
-What's happening?
[mysterious music continues]
[lecturer] Open your eyes.
Your thoughts
have manifested into reality.
Sawabe-san has come.
[members] Sawabe-san…
-Two of you.
-Oh, me!
[all] Me!
-Come up.
-[man 1] Oh, thank you.
-[woman 1] Oh, thank you!
[woman giggles anxiously]
[member 1] Sawabe-san…
[member 2] They were chosen. Why not me?
[indistinct chattering]
[member 2] They must've done
something right in a past life.
[Oki] Okay! Time to get prepared.
Your second date slash mission
with Matsuura will be this Saturday.
Saturday?
That is correct.
He said he'd like to see you again.
[Yoko] Saturday is no good.
Wait. You already have plans?
Um, I mean, kind of.
But also, Matsuura is boring.
The man only talks about jazz.
He's not suspicious at all.
But he is the only lead
that we have right now.
[sighs]
He mentioned a jazz performance
for the date. Do some research.
-[mysterious music playing]
-[wind gusting]
[clattering]
[Nagi] What is all this?
[moans]
Where is it?
Oh.
-[grandmother] Who's there?
-[tense music stab]
[Soichi] Hey, Nagi.
-What are you doing?
-[Nagi] Huh?
Nothing.
Don't forget. This Saturday.
Um, for what, again?
The family photo.
Family photo?
[groans] I'm talking to myself here.
[Nagi] Um, Dad!
-[Soichi] Hmm?
-[Nagi] Saturday.
Is Grandma gonna be there?
Yeah.
[man] Yes, I've found the issue.
There was a loose connector,
but I fixed it pretty easily. No worries.
I'm sure it'll be a while…
-[boy] Excuse me, Mr. Officer!
-[officer] Coming.
I found this phone over there.
Oh, thanks, buddy.
Aren't you just a little angel?
[both laugh]
[phone buzzing]
MR. SAWABE
[phone buzzes]
[mysterious music playing]
NO CALLER ID
[Haru] A cop committing murder?
[Sawabe] Who is this?
What do you want?
[Haru] The yellow flower.
-I don't know what that is.
-Well, I guess this video goes public.
I wonder what Tsujioka will do.
They will kill you.
Give me the flower.
Do it, and I delete the video.
Where do you take
the members at Gentenkai?
Take me next time.
You'll know me by…
a red bracelet.
[sighs]
[Karen] Something's different.
Pretty sure it's the same bowl.
I'm not talking about gyudon.
It's you.
You were so confident.
The guy on the phone was a murderer.
I copied it.
From some movie. [chuckles]
I'm coming along with you.
It'll be too dangerous.
You can be my protector.
Like before.
Like before?
[Karen] I know.
I know that you're
hiding something from me.
I can tell.
You can tell me.
Let me know you.
I'm protecting you, Karen-san.
I'm going alone.
[jazz music playing]
-Ugh.
-[music stops]
I really don't get this stuff.
[jazz music plays in earphones]
Jazz? [laughs]
That's new. What brought this on?
[Yoko] I can listen to jazz if I want.
Just checking in.
You're coming
to the shoot tomorrow, right?
[sighs] This again.
Probably.
Probably?
What kind of answer is that?
[Yoko] I've got a lot going on right now.
I'll try my best to be there.
Don't "try," just be there.
Our brewery's future depends on it.
Don't you get that?
I get it. You can give it a rest.
It's obvious.
You are clearly jumping through hoops
because Mayuko-san asked you to do it.
But it doesn't matter.
It's all fake anyway.
It's been a while
since our last photo.
[Yoko] Hmm?
It's been six years.
I just wanted to take a new one.
That's all.
[Soichi sighs]
Good night.
Wait.
[Soichi] Hmm?
I will be there.
[Nagi] Why are you coming in
through the window?
[Haru] You scared me.
[Nagi] There's something I wanna ask you.
[Haru] What?
That night…
Gaku died for real, didn't he?
What?
You're absolutely sure?
Why are you asking?
[Nagi] Because.
You sure it was confirmed?
It was obvious.
[Soichi] Gaku!
[blood squelching]
[masked ninja] Please!
Don't kill me.
[tense music swells]
[music fades]
-He might be alive.
-Stop it.
-Just listen.
-There's no way.
-Just accept it.
-Never mind.
[funky music playing]
TAWARA BREWERY
[Soichi] This way, please.
This is where we store
all the extracted sake.
[speaking French]
[Soichi] Hmm.
[chuckles]
[in English] Do you enjoy
a bit of sake after work?
I do not partake in any alcohol.
Ah… [chuckles]
Hey! Hurry up, or we're gonna be late.
I'm still deciding what to wear.
Go with Grams. I'll catch up.
But they already have
our photo clothes there.
Get out.
-[Riku] They're already wait--
-Get out!
-[host] Ogino Misa-sama?
-Yes.
Right this way, please.
[jazz music playing]
Thank you.
[crowd exclaims]
[jazz music fades]
[mysterious music playing]
[man 1] Thank you. Thank you for coming.
[man 2] Sure, go ahead.
[phone buzzing]
DAD
[lecturer] Everyone,
welcome to our blessed place.
Are you ready?
This way.
Go ahead.
Please.
Now then, everyone, please hold hands
with your neighbors and form a circle.
Listen to the voice of the Earth.
We agreed.
We made a deal.
[lecturer] Close your eyes.
I'm not about to write an article
without seeing it.
[lecturer] Notice your closed heart,
your body… And release.
-[Riku] Hey, Grandma, how should I pose?
-[grandmother laughs]
-What do you have in mind?
-[Riku] Look.
-[grandmother] Mm-hmm.
-[Riku exclaims]
[grandmother laughs] Come on. Let's go.
-We'll be late.
-[Riku] Okay. Let's go.
[mysterious music playing]
[switches clattering]
[clock chiming]
[cuckoo sound]
[arrow whooshing]
[gasps]
-[funky music playing]
-Grandma.
[speaking French]
[in English] Why don't we
give them a few minutes?
[Soichi] What the hell is she up to?
[jazz music ending]
[Matsuura] Someone very, very special
to me is here today.
Misa-san.
[funky music playing]
This next one, I'm dedicating to you.
[gasps]
[all clapping]
-[employee] Sir, your family is here.
-[sighs] Hmm?
They are? Oh, thank God!
Dad, I have a pose I came up with.
Look.
-Ka-ching!
-Oh my.
Just you two, huh?
[funky music continues]
YOU'RE ALMOST OUT OF TIME
[Nagi] Hmm?
[lecturer] Okay, everyone. Open your eyes.
Sawabe-san has arrived.
[all] Me!
[mysterious music playing]
Hidden in the ceiling.
So cliché.
VISION OF CALAMITY
Hanzo?
[jazz music playing]
Oh, I have to go.
[inaudible]
MATSUURA ARATA - SUBJECT OF INVESTIGATION
PLEASURE CRUISE INCIDENT
[music fades]
Man, you guys have it easy.
[clears throat]
[man 2] Look at this bag here.
[man 3] There's so much.
We'll be here till we're 80.
[sighs]
Hmm?
BOARDING LIST
3:20 PM
[music fades]
Please excuse me.
Please have a seat.
It's nice to meet you.
-I'm Karen--
-No need.
Names only get in the way of things.
I want to know the real person.
Behind you, I'm seeing something.
It's red.
Ashes?
I understand.
You lost your parents, didn't you?
[gasps gently] You see…
You are the lone survivor.
Much too young. Poor thing.
And from you, I get…
I hear a gentle sound.
It's a little too gentle.
[footsteps approaching]
Would you please stand?
This is a test.
All the members who come through here
take the same test.
-[Karen gasps]
-[uneasy music playing]
[breathing nervously]
Take this chance to liberate her.
-Let's go.
-What?
You haven't changed at all.
How about we do this?
[muffled grunting]
This man has been a precious person to us.
He has liberated
countless people for our cause.
[Sawabe groans]
Now's your chance
to set this precious man free.
[groaning]
[Sawabe grunting]
Well?
[exclaims]
[breathing heavily]
Let him through.
Be careful on your way home.
I'm sure your wife and your child
will need you beside them.
Please don't.
I did it all.
It's about time you left as well.
Oh, right.
Here.
You came for this.
You take care.
Go.
[door closes]
I think we're alone now.
I have been waiting.
[uneasy music playing]
[uneasy music continues]
[breathing heavily]
Don't worry. I won't harm you.
I won't harm that woman either.
For now.
Do you know why that is?
Long ago,
you gave me my future.
"Oh please!"
"D… don't kill me."
"I have a future ahead of me."
"Just like you
have a future ahead of you."
"I beg you."
You may have defeated me then.
And yet,
I've returned from death, born again.
I've inherited the souls
of 18 generations of my ancestors.
I'm a god.
Fuma Kotaro will never die.
Shall we test it out?
[breathing nervously]
Go ahead.
Try to kill me.
Did you really think
it would be that easy?
[Tsujioka chuckles]
You still can't kill anyone,
even after your brother's murder.
Should I kill that woman next?
-[Haru straining, groaning]
-[skin tearing]
Do not disappoint me,
son of Hattori.
Remember,
you created me.
[panting]
["Blue Skies" by Irving Berlin playing]
♪ Blue skies ♪
♪ Smiling at me ♪
♪ Nothing but blue skies ♪
♪ Do I see ♪
♪ Bluebirds ♪
♪ Singing a song ♪
♪ Nothing but bluebirds ♪
♪ All day long ♪
♪ Never saw the sun shining so bright ♪
♪ Never saw things going so right ♪
♪ Noticing the days hurrying by ♪
♪ When you're in love ♪
♪ My how they fly ♪
♪ Blue days ♪
♪ All of them gone ♪
♪ Nothing but blue skies ♪
♪ From now on ♪
[music ends]
[funky mysterious music playing]
[music fades]