[heavy breathing]
[swords clanking]
[grunting]
-[sword slashing]
-[man groans]
[blood squelching]
[gasps]
-[sword slashing]
-[grunts, gasps]
[blood squelching]
-[Soichi] Gaku!
-[Yoko] Gaku!
[tense music swells]
[somber music playing]
[Fuma ninja] Shikkoku-sama.
[gasps]
[groans]
[blood squelching]
[Yoko crying]
[crying continues]
[Fuma ninjas chanting]
[shakujo clanks]
[chanting continues]
[chanting stops]
It has been decided
that the 19th Fuma Kotaro shall be…
Shikkoku!
[mysterious music playing]
[Fuma Kotaro] Today…
the Fuma clan has died.
It is the will of the 18th.
A strategic move, ensuring that
our ancient clan's desires are fulfilled.
Our late leader has willingly
sacrificed himself for this purpose.
We Fuma answer to no one.
We shall remain underground,
emerging the day
shinobis cast off the shadows
and stand in the light.
When we wake from the dead,
the world will know.
They will know their true leader.
[music fades]
Rina.
Rina?
[panting]
[gulps]
Rina?
Rina.
[sobs]
-I'm sorry.
-[baby mobile rattles]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[sobs]
[crying]
[uneasy music playing]
-[device chimes]
-Thank God.
You okay?
Did he hurt you?
What happened?
You knew Tsujioka?
Why didn't you tell me?
Hey.
Why did he just hand this to me?
I really have no idea.
Don't lie to me! You know something!
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to protect you.
[mysterious music playing]
[music fades]
[mouse clicks]
-[man 1] I'm back from my break.
-[man 2] I'm back too.
I was hoping we'd see
the whole family together again.
-[man 1] He can hear you.
-[man 2] Oops.
[Soichi] I'm sorry.
I know you did a lot to make this happen.
[gasps] It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
Although…
[Soichi] Although?
An apology dinner would be nice.
-[Soichi] Oh.
-[chuckles]
Ah.
-[laughs]
-Ah. All right.
Aw man. Riku-kun looked so cute
in his little toji gear.
[Soichi chuckles]
Oh. [gasps]
I forgot.
-Congratulations.
-Huh?
I heard the Agency for Cultural Affairs
granted us a subsidy.
I didn't know.
[Mayuko] It's been six years
since the last one.
Subsidy?
Yoko's behind this.
[opening theme music playing]
[music fades]
[Yoko sighs]
SOICHI-SAN
[phone continues buzzing]
[Matsuura] Misa-san.
Matsuura-san.
You were so amazing.
[laughs]
-You liked that?
-Uh-huh.
You played those notes with so much
heart and confidence.
[Matsuura sighs]
Misa-san,
how about I take you out for dinner?
That's what I was going to ask,
but now I can't.
What?
I'm sorry about that,
but I'll be in touch, all right?
[footsteps echoing]
[uneasy music playing]
[mysterious music playing]
What?
I was just
hoping that you could stay.
[music fades]
[curtain opening]
[Karen] Why won't you tell me?
What if I tell you my secret?
It's about the hotel fire.
You might've figured it out.
I was that three-year-old child.
One of the victims that day
was a bureaucrat
with government information.
He was my dad.
Haru, you have to tell me
if you know anything, okay?
I know something.
I'm not as naive as you think.
[uneasy music playing]
[Karen] I've been researching,
and I believe there's an organization
behind the unsolved cases in this country.
UNSOLVED CASES
ONIWABAN SPIES OF OLD JAPAN
MYSTERIOUS RESCUER?
A MAN IN BLACK
SPLIT-SECOND MIRACULOUS RESCUE
THREE-YEAR-OLD SURVIVES FIRE
SHADOW GROUP?!
[Karen] Six years ago,
Mukai was kidnapped.
These deaths happened on the same day.
[uneasy music continues]
SUICIDE
UNCONFIRMED
NO INFO ON FAMILY
EXTREMELY PRIVATE
[inaudible]
Our meeting wasn't just random.
No, but
you lied to me too.
You're the person
who saved me in that club.
I know you're not just some regular guy.
Haru, who are you, really?
Is that even your name?
Who I am doesn't matter.
Your brother,
I don't think he killed himself.
These deaths, including your brother's,
there's something odd.
I don't think they're coincidences.
Am I right?
I know something's going on.
Somebody faked the deaths
of all those people.
But why did they target Mukai?
Tell me.
-Why was your brother--
-It's all my fault.
What do you mean?
I'm gonna leave now.
Haru, don't leave.
I'm planning to write an article
exposing everything.
[mysterious music playing]
PASSENGER LIST
10/24 - 3:20 P.M.
SHIP: FRONTIER ROOTS
[Hamashima] I'll be right back.
I got it. Hama-san, Hama-san!
Departing at 3:20 p.m.
on October 24th, 2024.
Vessel name, Frontier Roots.
This passenger list is the one!
Anyone on this list who's not
on the victims list is the perpetrator.
All right.
This is definitely it.
Find all the rest now!
[all] Yes, sir!
[man 1] Hey, hey, clear the desk.
-[man 2] You want it here?
-[Oki] Yeah. Put it here.
[man 1] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Don't mix them up.
-[Oki] Hey, let's start with this list.
-[phone buzzing]
Yeah?
You sent her on a mission behind my back?
We're a normal family.
We quit!
Do you got that?
We want nothing to do with it.
[Hamashima] "Normal family," huh?
What was that?
Then why is it that your "normal" wife
jumped at the job?
Don't lie to me.
You really must not know your family.
Why doesn't Haru take over at the brewery?
Did Nagi really give up being a shinobi?
Is Yoko happy with her current life?
And what about you?
Are you really over Gaku's death?
Face it, Soichi.
-Stop being so stubborn.
-[sighs]
It's what your family wants.
It's time for you
to become a shinobi again.
[Soichi] Stay away from my family.
[sighs]
[phone chimes]
WELL DONE.
I'LL TRADE THE PUZZLE BOX FOR IT
IF I GIVE YOU THE SCROLL
IF I GIVE YOU THE SCROLL,
WILL YOU COME HOME?
[phone chimes]
SURE
I CAN TAKE MY MASK OFF
AND GO HOME WITH YOU
[mysterious music playing]
Hey, it's me. Yeah. I need a favor.
[mysterious music continues]
Misa-san.
Well, it's about time I drop the act…
because…
I have fallen under your love spell.
[sighs]
Until now, I've sacrificed everything
and devoted myself to my work.
But today,
I deliberately ignored my boss
for our date.
I had to see your pretty face.
Matsuura-san.
There's something else.
I've been keeping something from you…
because…
[phone ringing]
[Matsuura sighs]
Don't answer the phone!
I love what you're saying.
Please don't answer it.
Thank you, Misa-san.
It breaks my heart.
I can't disobey my boss again.
Yes, I'm on my way.
[Haru] The Fumas are back.
[Hamashima] So they've appointed someone
to succeed the 18th.
Turns out it was Tsujioka.
The Fuma have been building their power
for the past six years.
They're in the police department.
They know about me…
and my family.
So then, why haven't they
attacked you at all yet?
I don't know.
Haru,
how much does your lady friend know?
[ethereal music playing]
[Hamashima] If the Fuma are on the move,
we have no time to waste.
[typing]
Do what you must.
[typing continues]
GENTENKAI AND THE CRUISER INCIDENT
-[employee] Here's your order.
-Thank you so much.
♪ 4, 5, 6, try to solve the riddle ♪
♪ 7, 8, 9, get ready to count back ♪
♪ Down, down, down, down, down ♪
♪ 10, 9… ♪
-[customer] Blueberries. Strawberries.
-♪ …8, 7… ♪
[woman] It's delicious.
♪ …6, 5… ♪
Sorry about the wait!
-♪ …4, 3, 2, 1 ♪
-[man] Oh, no worries.
-[indistinct chattering]
-♪ 10, 9 ♪
-♪ 8, 7… ♪
-[laughter]
♪ …6, 5, 4, 3, 2 and 1 ♪
♪ Down, down, down, down, down ♪
-[mysterious music playing]
-[gasps]
[Kyotani exclaims]
[breathes deeply]
You're not getting away
so easy, kitty cat.
[mysterious music continues]
-[grunts]
-[music fades]
TAILING MATSUURA NOW,
SENDING CURRENT LOCATION
[whimsical music playing]
[gasps]
-Cute, right?
-[woman 2] How much was it?
-98 yen.
-[woman 2] That's cheap.
-At Nakamuraya.
-[woman 1] That's great.
-[woman 2] Cheaper than this.
-[woman 1] That's a steal.
[whimsical music continues]
[Hamashima] I'm back.
[Oki] Hama-san.
I finally found the person
who wasn't on the victims list.
Matsuura Arata.
It's Matsuura.
Is Yoko with him now?
Actually, we haven't
been able to reach her.
I asked Beppu to track her,
but I don't know how reliable he is.
He looked very reluctant.
[whimsical music continues]
SOICHI TAWARA
[phone line ringing]
Huh? He just hung up on me!
We don't have time for this.
Hey! Let me know
as soon as you're able to locate Yoko.
[Oki] Yes, sir!
[intriguing music playing]
Ready?
Time to shine. Get over here. Good pigeon.
Come here!
Ah! We don't have time for this!
No! Hey! [groans in frustration]
[music fades]
Ito!
-[Karen] It's been a while.
-Let's go.
[indistinct chattering]
-[former boss] So you're with Mu now?
-[Karen] Yes.
[former boss] Huh, I thought you were
with a major media company.
Thank you so much
for letting me pitch this story.
Sure.
Don't screw it up. He's interested.
-[editor] Good, let's go with that.
-Sir?
Sir, this is who I told you about.
-I appreciate you taking the time--
-Tell me what you got.
What evidence do you have to show me
that connects Gentenkai
and the cruise incident?
I have this.
What's this?
[intriguing music playing]
Wait. I… I have more evidence.
What? Why is…
We're done. You're wasting my time here.
-No, please wait! Just one sec!
-No, no!
-Just one second!
-That's enough. Thank you.
[mysterious music playing]
FACTORY RESET IN PROGRESS
[music fades]
[phone buzzing]
KAREN ITO
[train running overhead]
[uneasy music playing]
[gentle music playing]
[Soichi] I'm home.
[music fades]
You need to stay normal, at least.
[Soichi sighs]
[grandmother laughs]
Is it my eyes,
or is that alcohol in front of you?
[laughs]
I'm just, um…
[grandmother] Pour it back.
You know you can't drink it.
That's not true.
I know your body could handle it.
You can't drink it
because you're a shinobi
down to the roots.
Oh boy.
My, my, my.
You're still so awkward
when it comes to your feelings.
[sighs]
[uneasy music playing]
[Nagi] I know you're here.
Show yourself.
[music fades]
VISION OF CALAMITY
[Nagi] I knew you were alive.
I never gave up.
Let's go home,
Gaku-nii.
[uneasy music playing]
What the hell?
[tense music playing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[whooshing]
[Yoko] What do you think
you're doing here?
[Nagi] Mom? What are you doing here?
[tense music continues]
[Yoko] Fuma clan?
[Matsuura] Misa-san?
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[exhales]
[wings fluttering]
[clattering]
[distant clattering]
[moans softly]
[wings fluttering]
[uneasy music playing]
Huh?
[music intensifies]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
-[blood squelches]
-[groans]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[blood squelches]
[Yoko] Nagi!
[grunts]
[Nagi grunting]
[dramatic music intensifies]
[tense music playing]
[Matsuura] I wish we'd met
under better circumstances.
[Yoko] You know, there is one thing
I do have to thank you for.
[Matsuura] Huh?
[Yoko] It turns out
jazz isn't so bad.
[Matsuura scoffs]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[Matsuura growls]
[Yoko grunts, pants]
[Yoko] Nagi, I'm so sorry.
[loud thud]
-[Matsuura] Huh?
-[loud thud]
-[metallic clattering]
[loud thud]
[rattling]
-[menacing music sting]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-[groans]
[gasping, choking]
[ethereal music playing]
[Soichi] Time to hunt.
♪ Girl, I know
You're not coming back anymore… ♪
-[grunting]
-[blood squelching]
♪ So, why, oh why
Do I keep on watching the door? ♪
♪ I talk to you
As though you can hear what I say ♪
♪ But I'll lose my mind
If I keep on acting this way… ♪
He's a beast.
♪ Got to get a hold of myself ♪
♪ Got to make believe I don't care ♪
♪ Got to go someplace
Find a brand-new face ♪
♪ Got to get out and get somewhere ♪
♪ Got to get a hold of myself ♪
♪ Got to take what life has to give ♪
♪ Got to give it a try
Can't lay down and die ♪
♪ Got to get a hold of myself ♪
♪ Late at night ♪
♪ I hear footsteps sound down the hall ♪
♪ And I kid myself ♪
♪ That you're coming back, after all ♪
♪ The telephone rings ♪
♪ But there's no one on the line ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ When I stop and think ♪
♪ I know it's all in my mind ♪
♪ Got to get a hold of myself… ♪
[Yoko] I get to kill this one.
♪ Make believe I don't care ♪
♪ Got to go someplace
Find a brand-new face… ♪
[Yoko] You're going to tell us
everything you know.
♪ Got to get a hold of myself ♪
♪ Got to take what life has to give… ♪
[Yoko] So are you ready
to be a shinobi again?
♪ Got to get a hold of myself… ♪
[Soichi] I'm doing this to protect you.
[Yoko] Nagi's here too.
[Soichi] That's even more of a reason.
[moaning]
-[grunts]
-[Nagi moans]
[sighs]
["This Will Be Our Year"
by The Zombies playing]
[sighs]
♪ The warmth of your love's
Like the warmth from the sun ♪
♪ And this will be our year
Took a long time to come ♪
♪ Don't let go of my hand
Now, the darkness has gone ♪
♪ This will be our year
Took a long time to come ♪
♪ And I won't forget
The way you held me up when I was down ♪
♪ And I won't forget the way you said
"Darling, I love you" ♪
♪ You gave me faith to go on ♪
♪ Now, we're there
And we've only just begun ♪
♪ This will be our year… ♪
Stop! Hey! Whoa, whoa! Stop the car!
We need more backup.
It's a madhouse in there.
[grunts, gasps]
♪ The warmth of your smile
Smile for me, little one ♪
♪ And this will be our year
Took a long time to come… ♪
That was great.
♪ You don't have to worry
All your worried days are gone ♪
♪ And this will be our year… ♪
Kuze-san.
Look at that.
♪ And I won't forget
The way you held me up when I was down ♪
♪ And I won't forget the way you said
"Darling, I love you" ♪
♪ You gave me faith to go on ♪
♪ Now, we're there
And we've only just begun ♪
♪ This will be our year
Took a long time to come ♪
♪ And this will be our year ♪
♪ Took a long time to come ♪
[singer vocalizing]
[music ends]
[train rattling]
[woman on PA] The "A" train
will soon be arriving at platform one.
Please stand behind the yellow line
for yours and others' safety. Thank you.
The "A" train will soon be arriving
at platform one.
Please stand behind the yellow line
for yours and others' safety.
[silence]
[funky mysterious music playing]
[music fades]
[mysterious music playing]