[gentle ambient music plays]
-[music stops]
-[water rushing]
[silence]
[gentle ambient music resumes]
[music fades]
[grunts softly]
[gasps]
[gasps] No.
[breathing shakily]
Ryo?
[gasping] Ryo?
Ryo!
[somber, emotional piano music plays]
-Anyone, please!
-[rumbling]
-[man] Hello? Who's out there?
-[panting]
-[man 2] Be careful not to get stuck.
-[man 1] Can you hear us? Anyone there?
-Hello? Anyone in there?
-[man 2] Watch your step.
-[man 1] Anyone?
-[man 3] We need help!
-[man 2] So many people under this rubble.
-[man 1] Watch out! Hey! Anyone?
Excuse me!
My son! Have you seen my son?
Do you know
where they're taking survivors?
[man 1] Is anyone here?
-Is anyone around here? Hello?
-[helicopter hovering overhead]
[mother gasping]
[somber music continues]
[breathing shakily]
[gasps] Ryo?
Kanda, I'm glad you're here.
Yuko, hey.
Holding up okay?
[man] I'll get some blankets.
Senpai, have you seen my son anywhere?
Senpai!
[silence]
[music resumes]
What is going on?
-[rumbling]
-[people gasping]
[mother sobbing]
Can anyone hear me?
[wind gusting]
Somebody?
[crying quietly]
[music fades]
-[clattering]
-[grunts]
[vehicle approaching]
[grunts]
[man] Hey, be careful over there!
Hang on.
[driver humming softly]
Huh?
[mother panting]
Wait!
[driver] Hey! Are you okay?
Oh, thank God. [gasping]
[sighs] I woke up on the beach all alone.
Nobody answered to anything I would say.
I couldn't feel physical touch anymore.
I didn't think I was still here…
-Now you're here, you talked to me, and--
-I know, I understand.
I think…
I think that you need to breathe.
You need to calm down first.
-[driver exhales]
-Aah!
-[driver] Yeah…
-[wheezing]
[driver exhales]
Yeah, that, uh… quake was huge, huh?
Well, for now…
Why don't you come over to our place?
Oh, can you walk?
Yeah.
[mother gasps]
-[driver] Okay.
-[yelps]
[breathing heavily]
[door slams]
[engine starts]
[poignant music plays]
[man 1] Like I said, right?
You remember Star Sand?
That was all my idea.
-See?
-[playful music plays]
You've seen these in souvenir shops,
haven't you?
[man 2] I used to buy them for my family
on my business trips.
[man 1] You see? Huh?
-That… was all me.
-[man 2 chuckles]
Here we go again with the stories.
[man 1] I'm telling you the truth, okay?
Listen. It was… way back in the '60s.
During the student protests, I went broke.
I ran away to I… Iriomote Island.
And you bottled the sand
and sold it, right?
-I think we've heard.
-[woman laughing]
[van approaching]
Oh?
Do we have a new guest?
[music fades]
-[driver] Go ahead.
-Ah… Earthquake?
I suppose so.
Well, hello. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
[chuckles] Well, I'm sure
you've been through a lot.
-I mean, that was huge. Earthquake, right?
-[woman] Michael!
Uh… I, um…
Where are we?
[sighs] Mmm, well, uh,
it's a little bit hard to say this, but…
Nah, it's all right. Don't worry about it.
We have time for all of that. Yeah?
Hey, Kaori. Uh, give her the tour, yeah?
Sure. Hi! I'm Kaori.
-Well, let's go!
-Uh, but…
It's a little confusing.
Um… What is… what is this place?
Who are you guys?
Oh… oh, I don't think
I should explain it though. You…
[sighs]
Whew. Well, uh…
So, it's…
a gathering spot for the people like us.
Uh… well, anyone with regrets.
There are more places like this
all over the country…
Regrets?
-What do you mean by regrets?
-Uh…
Hey, Akira.
Just come out and tell her the truth.
Okay. Then you can tell her, Shori.
Hmm. What to say…
Yeah, basically,
you're dead.
You have some unfinished work here,
so you can't move on just yet.
I died?
[wind gusting]
-[gasps]
-[gentle music plays]
I di… died…
[sobs]
Mmm…
[mother sobs]
-[Kaori sighs] Ah…
-[sobs]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Oh… oh… My, my, my, my, my.
You should rest here tonight, hmm?
-Have some alcohol. Uh…
-[mother] I… I don't need any.
[sobbing]
[Kaori] Why don't you
follow me anyway, hmm?
-You'll be okay.
-[crying]
-[Michael] Ah. There must be a guy.
-[man 2] Must be.
[Shori] Really?
She looks pretty old to me.
[Kaori] Just hang on, okay?
Come here.
[sighs, sniffles]
The last occupant
left recently, so
this room is all yours.
I know this was
a lot of new information all at once.
Try to get a good night's rest.
So you're like me?
You're all in the afterlife too?
I guess so. We're experts.
Think of us like your mentors.
I hope you sleep well.
[poignant music plays]
[baby gurgling]
[woman 1] And here is your baby.
Congratulations.
[baby fussing]
-[mother] Why is that so difficult?
-Come here, baby boy!
[man] I'm just trying…
[mother] That's just what you want!
I told you that I don't need it!
-Ryo, come back.
-Mom, did you see?
[mother] ♪ Happy birthday to… ♪
-Yay, Ryo!
-[laughs]
-Hey, look!
-[mother] What are you doing?
-Why did you do that?
-[Ryo] Mommy, look at this.
[mother] Stop!
[crying]
-[mother] You need to go now.
-I don't wanna!
-[mother] I'm going to be late for work!
-[Ryo] No… I don't wanna go!
Mama!
-Wake up.
-[gentle music continues]
-Mama!
-Ryo!
[music stops]
-[Shori] Hey.
-[Kaori] Hi, good morning.
-[group] Good morning.
-[Michael] Hey.
Hi there. Hey, hey. Good morning.
-[Kaori] Hey.
-Morning.
[Michael] Good morning.
Kaori, can you get me some coffee too?
Sure thing.
[Michael sighs]
-Here.
-[Michael] Great.
-Aah.
-[Kaori] Whew.
-[Michael] Aah.
-[Kaori] Ho!
-What's that?
-Yoga.
You're doing yoga?
Aren't you a little dead for that?
-[chuckles]
-Oh, shut it.
Yoga.
You know, that was all me.
-Yoga in Japan.
-Okay…
I was the first one.
Yeah, that's how
I screwed up my back, you know?
Right there. [groans]
-[man 2 chuckles]
-Hey, good morning.
[Michael] Ah, young miss. Good morning.
Oh! You look pretty cute in that light.
[chuckles] Her name is…
You can call me Minako.
[Michael] Minako.
Wow. You're a real looker, you know that?
[Kaori] Michael!
In modern times,
we don't say things like that.
What? Is that true? Why's that?
-The old guy sitting here is Michael.
-[chuckles]
[Kaori] And the guy
who found you on the road, Akira.
And the young man over there is Shori.
-Hmm.
-[Kaori] He was a yakuza member.
And that's Mr. Tanaka,
who was a banker, and then…
I owned my own bar!
I'm Kaori!
[Michael, Kaori chuckle]
[Michael] Oh, here. Have some b…breakfast.
Here, come on.
[chuckles]
Excuse you!
STOCK MARKET CRASH
OCTOBER 2, 1990
[Minako] Wait…
Aah, I suppose it's an old habit of mine.
Um, do you think
I could use your car today?
[Akira] Huh?
Oh…
Sure.
Uh…
[Michael] Bit of an attitude on that one.
[van door closes]
-[rescuers calling out]
-[man 1] Hey, Doctor!
-[man 2] Hey! Hey!
-[man 1] Hello!
-[man 2] Hey!
-[man 1] Doctor!
-[man 1] Try over here.
[sighs]
[man 3] Public phones are
available for free over here.
[man 4] There's water over here.
[Minako gasping]
[man calling] Chinatsu!
Kazuki!
Aiko!
PLEASE CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE INFORMATION
ON MISSING CHILDREN LISTED BELOW
Chinatsu!
Aiko!
Kazuki!
-You're like me.
-Ah.
I was separated from my family.
I've been calling their names every day,
trying to find them.
[grunts] Even though
they would be dead too.
If they could hear my voice,
that'd mean they're dead.
Hey, miss, I hope
you find your folks.
[man] Fortunately,
the highway acted as a breakwater,
so urban areas were less affected.
They haven't found Kawakami yet.
Let's all pray for her safety.
All the teams are working hard,
working round the clock to find survivors.
So all we can do now is be patient.
We'll continue
to cooperate with the police
and provide accurate news reporting.
I'm counting on you.
[all] Yes.
Hi, Kanda. Can you see me? It's Minako.
[Kanda inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[Kaori giggles]
-[Kaori] Oh! Welcome back.
-Welcome back.
[Minako] Uh, yeah.
-Oh, here. Thank you so much for this.
-Oh, sure.
Glad that you're here!
We're about to have nabe for dinner.
Would you like a bowl?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm not feeling very well.
That sounds like a great reason
to sit with us, then.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[gentle guitar music plays]
Ah…
[in Japanese] ♪ It is now autumn ♪
♪ At this empty beach ♪
♪ Even if ♪
-♪ A single dream breaks ♪
-[laughing]
[in English] He does this one constantly.
[in Japanese] ♪ I won't forget you ♪
♪ Because I promised the sand ♪
♪ No matter how sad I am ♪
♪ I will not die ♪
[in English] That was "The Empty Beach."
What a classic. Right, Shori?
Yeah, sure is.
[Michael] Okay. Hey, Minako.
D… do you sing?
No, that's okay.
[Michael] Oh, yeah?
Seems depressing.
-Ah! Okay! Nabe is served!
-[Michael] Oh, oh, oh!
-[Tanaka] Yes! Okay!
-[Michael] Ooh.
-[Kaori] Whoo!
-[Michael chuckles]
-Come on. Eat.
-[Kaori] Okay, okay!
-[Tanaka] Wow, looks great.
-[Kaori] Over here!
-[Michael] Right here.
-[Akira] Wow!
-Looks great! Oh, thank you.
-[Kaori] Clear some space. Good!
-Oof!
-[Tanaka] Aah!
[Kaori] My special, Kaori Nabe!
[all] Wow!
-Delicious!
-[Kaori laughs]
-Let's eat.
-Thanks! Get some meat.
-Yeah.
-For you.
-Meat gives you energy. Keeps you healthy.
-[Kaori] Thanks.
-[Akira] Some more?
-[Michael] Perfect!
-[Kaori] Please go ahead!
-[all] Thank you for the food!
-[Shori] Mmm!
-[Akira] Mmm!
[Kaori giggles]
-[Michael] Ohh, this is so good.
[Kaori laughing]
-[Minako] Excuse me…
-[Akira] Huh?
So you all…
have things you regret from life?
Just about.
My regrets are all I have. [chuckles]
Yeah.
Is that why you're all
just lazing around here?
I mean, it's not laziness, it's, uh…
Huh? [chuckles]
Well, I could see how it seems
like we're doin' nothin'. [laughs]
I'm sorry to say it like this.
I cannot keep wasting my time
with you all.
[wind gusting]
[sighs]
Oh.
Minako, wait.
Could you stick around today?
Spend some time with all of us here?
Why would I do that?
[Akira] Well, you're already here, and
we may be able to assist you.
Yup. Well, that's what
I was gonna offer, huh?
-[chuckles] Every time.
-Is that so?
-[church bell rings]
-[Michael] Oh, it's late.
-[all exclaim]
-[Kaori] It's time. Hurry up, eat. Here.
-[Michael] Oh!
-Mm-hmm.
Mmm! Mmm!
[mouth full] Gonna have a little more.
-Thank you. Mmm!
-[Kaori] Hurry up!
Uh…
-[Shori] So good!
-[Tanaka] All right.
-[Michael] Okay. Thank you.
-[Akira] Okay.
-[Michael] Hmm.
-[Akira] Yes.
[mysterious, emotional music plays]
[lights buzzing]
[Michael] Yo. Hi there. Hey, hey. Hello.
[spits]
For good luck.
We can't start without it, right?
-[chuckles]
-Can't start what?
Ah… Every new film,
I'd always do oharai as a ritual.
Michael says he's a film producer.
Watch my films some day.
Mind-blowing cinematic journeys.
Th… that theater has the collection.
All my work, yeah?
-[Kaori] Okay, okay! We need to get going.
-Okay? Huh?
Oh… Well, all right.
Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
[whines]
[music swells]
[Minako] What is…
What are we all doing here?
[Akira] Ah…
Every single month,
on the night of a new moon,
we all get together and search.
[Minako] What?
[Akira] For whoever it is we want to see.
[Shori] Man, it's weird, isn't it?
I never thought I'd be
around other people after I died.
Yeah!
-[Tanaka] Shori.
-[man] Can you help me…
[Tanaka] Trying to make sense
of a contradiction is a contradiction.
-[Michael] Yeah, just there.
-[Kaori] That's very true.
[emotional music continues]
[Michael] Okay, okay.
Oh, hey! Hey!
I found them!
Over here, come on! Hey, look.
[father gasps]
[sobs]
-Chinatsu.
-Honey! [gasps]
[father] Aiko…
-[Aiko] Papa…
-[Kazuki] Daddy?
Kazuki!
[Chinatsu sobs]
[father] I'm sorry…
It's fairly strange.
We died, and yet here we are.
There is no doubt
that we still exist in this world.
We exist…
[father] I'm so sorry
I couldn't protect you.
[Michael] Aah… cramping up.
-[Shori sighs]
-[Michael] K… Kaori, how about a beer?
[Kaori] Okay.
-[Michael] Ah…
-[Tanaka] Have a seat.
-[Michael] Ow, my back.
-[Kaori] And this is for Minako.
[Akira] I'll take one too.
[Michael] Oh, that's good!
Here.
[Michael sighs]
What'd you think, Minako?
What did…
Well…
[Kaori, Akira sigh]
Well, I was…
-[Kaori sighs]
-I'm confused.
That's understandable.
Hey, Minako.
Take heart. Your boyfriend
will get found soon enough.
-Huh?
-[Kaori] Hey!
-That's enough out of you. Stop it.
-Eh? What? Why?
It's my son.
[mouths]
[Minako] I…
I have a seven-year-old son, Ryo.
I'm a single mom. He's all alone.
Ryo's safety is…
That's all that really matters.
[inhales]
May I stay with you all?
Just a little while longer?
[emotional music plays]
Sure, that's "goo"!
Be our pleasure. [chuckles]
You bet. [chuckling]
[Shori] "Goo!"
He says "goo." [laughs]
[Michael] Hey, come on.
"Gooooo!"
[all laughing]
Okay. Over here. We'll make a toast.
Yeah?
Hey, right?
Come on, have a seat. Hmm?
Hmm!
Uh… Oh, oh! Kaori.
-[Kaori] Well… kanpai!
-[Michael] Kanpai.
-[all] Kanpai.
-[Minako] Kanpai.
[bottles clink]
[Michael] Aah!
-[Minako sighs]
-[Michael groans]
[music fades]
[scribbling]
[knocking at door]
Yeah? Door's open.
Ah…
-Come in.
-[door closes]
[Minako] Uh… wh… what is all this stuff?
[Akira] Well, I spend a lot of my time
taking notes.
[Minako] Ah…
Eventually, all of this…
is going to be collected and published.
Professionally.
Uh-huh…
Is something wrong?
Uh, well…
I'm grateful that I got
a little bit more time here.
-Thank you for making me feel so welcome.
-Uh… of course.
We all remember what it's like.
Are they helping you
find a loved one as well?
No, nothing like that.
I just…
I just want
to have a record of everything.
My goal is to share this with the world.
To show everyone
that there's a life after death.
So, then, that is
your unfinished business, then?
Mmm…
I hadn't considered it.
Ah. You're looking for the keys, right?
Yeah, feel free to use it any time.
[Minako] Thank you very much.
Good luck. I'm sure he's out there.
Don't worry.
And don't…
be afraid to ask us for a hand, okay?
Minako, hey.
Would you… consent to an interview?
I'd be honored to listen to your story.
Sure, if you'd like.
[sighs]
[Michael] Hey, there. Hey, hey, hey.
-[chuckles]
-[Shori] What's up?
[Michael] Oh, nice. Real nice!
-Pretty cool suit, huh? [chuckles]
-[starts engine]
[Shori] You messing with me?
[Michael] You know,
I made a yakuza film once.
Did you do a typical half-assed one?
No, this was a real gangster show.
I'll make you watch it.
-Yeah, yeah.
-[Michael laughs]
Well, I'm gonna go.
CHIEF CABINET SECRETARY
CONFERENCE IN CHAOS
NUCLEAR POWER PLANT "STABILIZING STEADILY"
DECEASED
Maybe they'll find her.
Minako, I mean.
MISSING
FROM HOSHISUNA, MINAKO KAWAKAMI (35)
-Boss. From us. Happy birthday, sir.
-Mmm.
-Thank you, sir.
-[pouring]
[boss sighs]
I appreciate it.
Hey. Drink up.
-Thank you, sir.
-Boss.
-Thank you.
-Dad…
-Happy birthday.
-Ahh.
[boss sighs]
-[boss] Eat.
-[men] Thank you, sir.
[crockery clinking]
[Rick Blaine] Ilsa,
I'm no good at being noble,
but it doesn't take much to see
that the problems of three little people
don't amount to
a hill of beans in this crazy world.
Someday, you'll understand that.
["As Time Goes By" playing]
Now, now.
Here's looking at you, kid.
[music swells]
[music becomes foreboding]
[footsteps]
[Victor Laszlo] Everything is in order?
[Rick] All except one thing.
WHAT'S ON THE OTHER SIDE?
[Michael] I'm back.
-[Kaori] Oh, hey.
-[Michael] Hey, Kaori.
-Beer, please.
-Sure thing.
-[sighs]
-[Kaori] I'll leave it here?
[Michael] Yeah.
[Kaori] What's wrong, Shori?
You're looking glum.
Hmm? Was I? [chuckles]
Today's your father's birthday, right?
How's he doing?
Man,
he looks okay.
He's aging, though, just a bit.
[Kaori] That's how it goes.
It's already been about seven years
since you first got here.
I do wonder
how it'd be if I hadn't died
and was still rollin' with the yakuza.
[Michael] You know,
I made a yakuza film once.
I mean, it's gotten hard,
mmm… for the yakuza.
They represent society. [sniffs]
But with how divided we are,
we can't even offer them basic rights.
Hey. Next time you're at the theater,
I'll let you see it.
-Great cinema. Promise.
-[Shori] Hmm, yeah, I got it. Okay, okay.
[Michael chuckles]
Shori, do you also
have unfinished business?
That came out of nowhere.
I just thought you might
be willing to share now.
[Shori] Hmm…
Well…
[gentle, poignant music plays]
Okay.
I've been… here seven years.
Died in a shootout. [tuts]
Left a wife behind,
and there it is.
Huh? You were married, then?
Well, not married just yet.
We still had to register.
[Michael] Shori has
quite a soft side to him.
-Hey! Watch it!
-[Michael, Kaori chuckle]
You've tried to find her
for seven years now?
[Shori] Yeah…
Well, I don't know.
May stick with the memories.
I wouldn't be able to hold her anyway…
[sighs]
WHAT HAPPENS
IF UNFINISHED BUSINESS IS LEFT UNRESOLVED?
[music fades]
[sighs]
[music thumping inside]
Excuse me?
[man] You there? It's Koga.
Is everyone else safe?
Okay. Don't let 'em get to you.
Yeah.
Bye.
[warm, gentle ballad plays]
1970, OKINAWA
[singing in Japanese]
[projector whirring]
[in English] Sasaki.
-Tamashiro got busted.
-I see.
This is it.
The fascists are getting scared.
They might go after you next.
Just keep a low profile.
Yeah, I know.
Comrade Tamashiro arrested.
That should be on tomorrow's flyer.
[Koga] Yeah.
I'll get it done by tonight.
So, Maiko.
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
Hey, Koga.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Don't worry about it.
[man] The other day,
one of our comrades, Tamashiro,
was unlawfully detained on the street.
We will never bow down to this oppression
from unrecognized authority!
-[woman] That's right!
-[all shout] Yeah!
[man] Now is the time
for students, workers…
The university will no longer tolerate
this unlawful demonstration.
-[man] …take back our land!
-[official] Remove the barricade.
-Come out immediately.
-[all] Yeah!
Sprechchor!
[all] Sprechchor!
-[man] Okinawa is our land!
-[grunts]
[all] Okinawa is our land!
[man] American soldiers, get out!
[all] American soldiers, get out!
No more war in Vietnam!
-[plane flying low overhead]
-[all] No more war in Vietnam!
Take it down!
[clamoring]
[man] Hold the line!
Hold fast!
Unite!
Hold the line!
-[Sasaki] Koga!
-[yells]
[Sasaki] Koga!
[man] Unite!
[crowd clamoring]
[fighting continues]
[door closes]
[grunts]
[sighs]
-[Koga] What time is it?
-It's around midnight.
You should go back to sleep.
[Koga sighs]
[ice rustling]
[gasps]
-[grunts]
-Uh… Is it painful? [gasps]
[poignant music plays]
[projector whirring]
You startled me!
-Oh, I'm very sorry. I just got here.
-Ah! Aah… M…M… Minako…
-Wh… what a surprise. [chuckles]
-[sighs]
It's fascinating. What is it called?
Oh. Remembrance of Things Past.
Good film, right?
-[chuckles] Yeah.
-Huh!
-Ending's a little abrupt.
-Yeah.
Sadly… I died
before I could finish making it.
-Oh. Really?
-[sighs]
[tuts] It would've hit today's youth
like… bang!
Really gotten huge. Oh yeah.
A generational lightning rod, you know?
Just outstanding. [laughs]
-[cello music plays]
-[Michael] The poster, right?
Our heroine, Maiko,
standing alone on the beach.
And then, bam! Title up top.
I think we could've gone places with it,
you know?
-Poster was all ready to go, huh?
-Oh, y… you bet, you bet, you bet.
Had it all planned out,
right down to the last detail.
Theme, story, the whole bit!
[chuckles]
Tell me, how did… you come to make a movie
about the student protests?
Oh, this ol' thing?
REMEMBRANCE OF THINGS PAST
Yeah. Funny… [chuckles]
It's a true story, yeah.
-[chuckles]
-It's yours?
Well, it's not totally true,
but I was at that uprising, and…
maybe you agree, maybe not,
but… regardless,
m… messaging aside, there was unity there.
Film is like that.
Man. [chuckles]
Full-grown adults at play,
telling stories. It's great.
[Minako sighs]
Film is really your love, isn't it?
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
If it's an autobiography,
then Maiko was really
your college sweetheart?
Could be. [chuckles]
My, my. I guess you figured it out.
-[laughs]
-So what happened to you after that?
Mmm, uh…
Uh, well… well, a lot…
a lot happened with us.
-[chuckles, sniffles]
-[sighs]
-[music fades]
-[Michael tuts]
She was always waiting
to see the completed film.
[sighs]
She'd still like to see it.
I'm sure of it.
Hmm… Nah.
Don't know about that. [chuckles]
-[man] I'm home.
-[woman 1] How was work?
Hey, dinner's ready!
[grunts]
-[Kaori] Hey, Kenta.
-Ooh!
[Kaori] Your sister said dinner's ready.
Hey, Kenta. Game time's over.
Oh, Riko. Hey, for Mom.
[Riko] Oh! Uh, yeah, okay.
-[sister] Kenta!
-[Kenta] Hmm?
[sister] Come on, dinner.
-[Kenta] Hmph.
-[sister] Here.
-[Kenta] Thank you.
-[sister] How much for you?
-[Riko] Normal amount.
-[sister] You, Kenta?
-[Kenta] A lot.
-[sister] A lot… This much?
[Riko] Hmm! Thanks!
[slurping]
[chuckles] You're gonna
make yourself sick, Kenta.
-So, how's sports going?
-[Kenta] Mmm.
-Some more?
-[sister] Hmm?
-Mmm.
-[Kaori chuckles]
[sister] Mmm.
-Aah.
-There a game next week?
-Mmm.
-What do you think? Gonna win?
Yeah, easily.
-Yeah, maybe you get a mercy win again.
-Man, shut up, come on. Dude!
-How dare you?
-Mom saw that game too.
-Oh…
-You're so annoying.
The baby kicked.
-Really?
-[sister] Yeah.
Huh? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
One more time.
-[Riko] Wow!
-I felt it!
-You felt that, right?
-[man laughs] Kenta, come here!
-[Kenta chuckles] I'm good.
-Come here!
[warm, emotional piano music plays]
[scribbling]
[Minako inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[music fades]
-[Kaori] Wow!
-[Michael] It's vintage.
But these things are built like anchors.
-[Kaori] Look at that!
-[Michael] Look.
-It's still so shiny and clean.
-[laughs]
[Michael] Hey, Minako!
Ohayo. [laughs]
-[Minako] What are you getting up to?
-Okay.
Yesterday, Minako said something to me
that really kicked up my motivation.
-[laughs]
-Huh? What do you mean?
You got him all excited.
I had plans today.
No, I don't know what this is.
[Michael] Minako.
Hmm… You worked in show business, yeah?
-Huh?
-Uh, I was in journalism… Uh…
Oh, good. Here you are.
-[grunts]
-Uh…
Listen.
I… decided I should finish it.
[lively music plays]
-What?
-Mmm. Okay!
All right, guys. Listen up.
TV shows will always come and go.
The films will last forever.
I can't have you do this
half-heartedly. Got it?
-So, then, maybe you could tell us about…
-Right.
Akira, you're a little dull,
so why don't you hang onto this?
-[Akira] What?
-[Kaori laughs]
-And, Kaori, you'll…
-You just hold it.
-Kaori. Audio.
-Oh.
-That's an important job!
-Yeah. Hah…
-Tanaka.
-Yes.
-Tanaka, you're the AD, yeah?
-[Michael] And then, uh… well, Shori.
-[Shori] Hmm?
You and I look basically identical.
So you will play my son.
Here, read this. Here, take.
-Huh?
-[Michael] All right.
REMEMBRANCE OF THINGS PAST
Uh, Michael, you're directing too?
Director and star.
Yang Ik June style.
Huh? In… what style? Huh?
Okay, crew?
Begin!
Roll camera.
And
action.
How long…
It was 50 years ago.
Thinking of back then…
-What's the line?
-[Akira] Um, it's, uh…
"Just once more, I'd like to see her--"
-[Michael] What? I can't hear you.
-"Just once more--"
"Just once more, I'd like to--"
-[Michael] Cut!
-[Akira] Um…
Ready! Action!
What's the line? All right, come on.
-Hang on.
-[Shori] Dude…
-[Minako] Hang on, I can see the board.
-[Akira] Where?
"Just once more, I'd like…"
It's not about the lines though.
It's more the emotion.
-[Minako] I got it. Let's just do another.
-I'm in the scene. I can't--
[thumping]
The door got stuck.
-[Kaori] Just a bit!
-"Just once more, I'd like to see her."
-[Michael] Well, I know that one!
-Okay!
-It's too bright, anyway.
-How long do I have to wait?
Just watch and… I mean, just…
Okay, just watch everything
and be prepared for your role.
-[Kaori] Let's get this in one take!
-Of course. One take.
-[click]
-Oh…
-[Akira] "I'd like…"
-[Michael] "…to see…"
-[Akira] "…see her again."
-[Michael] Right. Got it.
Wh… wh… what? Is there…
-Were we filming?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Uh…
-[Akira] No, remember…
-[Michael] No, no.
-[Akira] It starts "How long…"
-[Michael] "How long"? Well…
-Still early days. We just…
-[Kaori sighs]
We've gotta come together
as a team a little more.
-[Kaori] Is that all it is?
-[Michael] Yeah, of course it is.
-[pouring]
-All of this.
It's all about a group effort. Right?
-Why are you asking the dull guy?
-[chuckles]
Anyway.
Review meeting. All department heads. Hmm.
M… Minako, hey.
-Let me show you this camera thing.
-No, I'm good.
-Huh? Why not? Hey.
-[Kaori] Hmm?
Is that a new guest there?
[Michael] Ah…
I can go speak with her.
I wonder who…
[Minako] Hey, there.
Am I here?
Mm-hmm.
[breathing shakily]
[sighs] What is going on?
[Minako] I'm new here myself.
So why don't we be good guests
and sit down?
I'm Minako.
Nana.
Hi there. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. You like movies?
-[chuckles]
-Why?
How are you doing?
[wind gusting]
[sighs] I get it. Must be quite a shock.
-But I'm sorry to tell you--
-Why are you sorry?
It all sucked anyway.
[Shori] Man.
Little doom and gloom girl in the house.
-[scoffs] Get bent.
-[Shori] Oh?
Okay! Young lady.
There's an open cabin I can show you.
Let's go.
[Nana sighs]
That girl…
Well, Tanaka. You know.
-I think so.
-Mmm…
Right, I'm gonna go.
-Shori.
-[Shori] Huh?
Congrats on the anniversary.
-Yeah, okay. [laughs]
-[Michael chuckles]
I am sorry, Shori.
I must dismantle the crew.
KATO FAMILY
[Shori sighs]
[breathing shakily]
[gentle, emotional piano music plays]
[van door slams]
[engine starts]
[van pulls away]
[alarm bleeps]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[music fades]
THANKS FOR LETTING ME
RIDE ON YOUR PRECIOUS MOTORBIKE!
[chuckles softly]
[door opens]
[man] I'm back.
-[door closes]
-[Mizuki] Oh…
Welcome home.
-Ah! You're here early.
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, did you get my text?
[Mizuki] Ah, I didn't see it, sorry.
[man] I got us curry for dinner.
[Mizuki] Thank you.
[footsteps]
[man] Oh, Mizuki.
So I've got a day off next week.
What do you say? Wanna meet my parents?
[gasps]
I still haven't been able
to properly introduce you.
Mmm…
Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
-[man laughs]
We could also start planning.
Maybe discuss our future?
[Mizuki] Of course…
[emotional music resumes]
It's been a while.
Ah, but you haven't
changed at all, have you?
This guy seems good.
Yeah…
Doesn't have my looks,
but that's okay. Hmm?
-[Mizuki sniffles]
-Uh…
I'm sorry.
[Mizuki sniffles]
Live a good life.
[sighs]
["The Empty Beach" playing]
[Michael in Japanese] ♪ …memories of you ♪
♪ Even if you do not return ♪
♪ I won't… ♪
-[in English] Oh, hey, it's you.
-Yo.
Kaori, a stiff drink, please.
Coming up.
[in Japanese]
♪ Because I promised the sky ♪
♪ No matter how lonely I am ♪
♪ I will not die ♪
♪ No matter how lonely I am… ♪
[in English] Shori, where were you today?
Uh…
[in Japanese] ♪ I will not die… ♪
[in English] I saw her.
Huh?
[music fades]
[wind blowing gently]
[chuckles] You know,
I think she's moved on.
She looked good though.
It's nice. I think she's getting married.
That's wonderful.
Yeah.
Yeah!
You know though?
Her new man is such a great guy.
[laughs] Not like how I was.
So it's good.
I think she'll be okay.
Yeah, I'm sure.
[swallows]
Aah…
-[Kaori sighs]
-[chuckles]
Oh, Shori, hey!
You have to watch
my yakuza m… movie still, yeah?
[both laugh]
Gotta head out.
But I'll see it before.
Your super boring yakuza show.
[Michael] Yes!
That's w… what I'm talking about!
[all chuckle]
W… well then, let's go!
Huh? Right now! Eh?
-Akira, hey.
-Yeah, let's move out.
-You'll be driving. Get the car. Come on!
-[Shori] Hmm…
-[Michael] This'll blow your mind!
-Are you sure?
-[van door closes]
-[Shori] Hey, doom and gloom.
Just make sure you try and enjoy it.
What?
[engine starts]
[man 1] Got anywhere to go, kid?
Wanna join the clan?
[man 2] Hey, boss,
are you sure about that?
[boss] It'll be fine.
Doesn't hurt to grow the family.
What's your name?
[man 3] Masashi…
Yamada.
Shori, hey. What do you think?
-[boss] Sound good to you?
-Pretty good, right?
Pretty mediocre.
-[laughs]
-[boss] Come by when you're settled.
Let's go.
[emotional music continues]
[Tanaka] Shall we get going now?
Yeah.
-[Kaori exhales]
-[Minako laughs]
-Hey. Did you know…
-Mmm?
Back in the '70s, I made yoga popular.
-No way!
-Oh boy!
-There we go.
-Oh yeah. 30 years ago, right?
-I was working mostly in advertising.
-Oh!
-A big fitness boom was sweeping Japan!
-Without Shori, no one can stop him.
-This could be rough. Oh! Nana.
-Correct.
-[Michael] I made it popular…
-[Minako] Morning.
[Michael] Morning.
Hey, where's the yakuza?
Well…
Shori has gone.
He's beyond us.
You aren't making sense.
[Minako] Do you have any regrets
or unfinished business
from when you were alive?
[Nana] What?
I'll bet that's the reason
you're still here with us.
You sound crazy. Is this a kind of cult?
Come now, a cult? You're really so rude.
Hey, Nana.
Would you… like to shoot a movie?
-[Akira] Minako.
-Creep.
-[Michael] What?
-[Akira] Let's go?
Oh, sure.
[Kaori] Hey, Nana, sit over there.
DECEASED
[Minako] Every day,
I'm scared to look through this.
If Ryo's name is in here,
what's going to happen to me?
I understand.
Uh, so… you'd like an interview.
That right?
[Akira] Sure.
I'd like to ask you just a few questions
before your soul goes to the other side.
Well…
Kawakami Minako. 35 years old.
Here at the station,
I worked as a journalist.
And I was a single mother to my child.
And your husband?
We split up soon after I had Ryo.
When I wanted to return to work,
he just didn't understand it.
Since then, it's just us two.
Minako, I'd like to know.
How was your time in this existence?
-You mean in the living world?
-Yes.
[sighs] I don't quite know.
It was hectic to work and raise a child.
I probably didn't have to be
trying so hard back then.
If you went back today, what would you do?
Ryo and I…
-[poignant music plays]
-I would take us on vacation.
He's never had that chance.
And…
And then I want to apologize.
[man] Many things in nature are
invisible to the naked eye.
Things like atoms, electrons,
elementary particles.
-They still have mysteries.
-So stupid.
-[man] We experience three dimensions…
-[girl 2] Loser. She keeps apologizing.
-[girl 2] I have to watch it again.
-[girl 3] She's so sad.
[all giggling]
-[man] Lisa Randall proposed…
-[girl 3] So going viral.
-[man] …theory of five dimensions…
-Genius, Rina.
-[man] Some research suggests as many…
-[girl 1] I think it's best!
-[man] …as 11 dimensions.
-[girl 1] Do Yasuko.
-[man] This has yet to be widely accepted.
-[girl 1] Yasuko!
-[man] It's clear there is far more…
-Please don't slit your wrists.
-It's played out at this point.
-[man] …to our world than meets the eye.
-There's much more to be learned.
-[girls giggling]
Hey. Over there, are you keepin' up?
-[girls] Yes!
-[Rina] Yes, I'm sorry.
[teacher] Okay, so in review,
what is a dimension?
Um, it is defined as a measurement
of space in any one direction.
-[thud]
-Okay? So one dimension.
-[giggling continues]
-One would be what? Correct, it is a line.
[Michael] Sure.
-[Kaori] Okay, dessert is served.
-[Akira] Thank you, Kaori.
-[Nana] Hey.
-Oh, hey, Nana.
I do understand that I died…
[breathing shakily]
Can we kill others?
There's this girl I want to kill.
Hey, Nana.
Not good karma to say things like that.
Those on our side and those on their side
aren't going to affect each other.
[Nana shudders]
That's stupid.
Sounds like this just sucks.
Hey…
[Minako sighs]
[Nana gasping]
[sighs]
I couldn't even taste that.
How long am I going to be stuck?
I shouldn't be here! I just wanna be gone.
[Nana breathing shakily]
[church bell rings]
[sighs]
[bell continues ringing]
-[Nana sighs]
-[Minako] Nana…
How about we go on a walk together?
I wanna show you something.
[sighs] What?
It's better in person. Just tag along.
[gentle, emotional music plays]
[Michael] Hah! Yes! Let's go.
Hmm!
[Nana] Huh?
What is this?
[Minako] All of us died,
leaving unfinished business
and our closest loved ones behind.
So we band together every month.
Searching as a group.
Our closest…
Nana, I don't know what your regret is.
However…
we'll help you find it, okay?
[man] Hey! Over here, over here.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
[music swells]
-Oh my God!
-Dude, dude!
-Right? What now?
-So weird!
-What does it say?
-"I do not have the energy…"
Oh wow! Yeah, that's a lot.
[sighs]
I think that…
there's someone I should say sorry to.
[sighs]
[music fades]
[doctor] And here we see the baby's face.
-[gasps]
-[doctor] Oh, and there's the eyes.
-[father] Oh, yeah.
-[doctor] The mouth.
[Kaori] I couldn't accept dying
before seeing my daughter give birth.
-The baby seems healthy!
-[Kaori] I fought my destiny. Here I am.
-The world's lenient about this.
-It's a boy.
[Kaori's daughter] A girl!
-Aw, she's so beautiful!
-Apparently, that is the case.
[daughter] Yeah.
I'm lucky to have
gotten the time that I did.
[daughter chuckles] I'm fine! Yeah, it's…
It's… it's incredible.
-This was my last regret.
-[daughter] Mm-hmm.
Yeah. I…
I never wanted anything more.
Through all those years
I got with the kids, I realized…
they are tough.
-[daughter] Aw.
-[chuckles] I'm sure that…
they would've been okay on their own
all these years.
[daughter] Yeah…
I think about that now and then.
-[daughter] Do you know how long?
-That's not true at all.
DAY 32, NOTHING ON SHELTER'S NOTICEBOARD
HOKUTO TV, NO PROGRESS
[footsteps approaching]
Oh my, what is this?
My goodness, Michael. Hey!
Come on,
you don't want to sleep here, do you?
-[grumbling]
-Okay, let's go to your room, yeah?
-Mr. Tanaka, give me a hand.
-[Tanaka] Sure.
[sighs] Come on, wake up.
-[grunts]
-Michael, hey. Yep.
-Okay, there. One, two… Mmph!
-Okay, come on, you.
-Okay, here.
-What's goin' on?
-Stop. Okay…
-When did you drink this much?
-What happened? [laughs]
-[Tanaka] We'll be back. Yes, yes. Got it.
[Akira chuckles softly]
How's it been goin'?
Good. I enjoy writing.
But I can't quite manage the end.
I thought I could ask you some questions.
Is that okay?
No, no, no. [laughs]
Maybe I'm just not interesting.
[laughs] Whenever things turn to you,
you dodge the questions.
Is that so? Well…
I'll just listen.
I'd guess you have an interesting story.
Minako, um,
I'm sensing that journalism in you.
[both laugh]
-That's true!
-Mmm.
[Minako giggles]
I suppose…
I guess there's no harm in you knowing.
The reason why
I can't go to the other side.
[birdsong]
[cows mooing]
[Minako] Is this… where you grew up?
[Akira] Yeah.
Dad looks as stubborn
as those cows, right?
I was always… let's say, infirm as a kid.
Dad was always the most
frightening guy in the world.
Your bento always stinks.
[girls giggling]
-[girl 1] Oh my gosh!
-[girl 2] Is she picking them up?
-[girl 1] So sad!
-[girl 2] Ew!
-[girl 3] She's like a dog!
-[girl 2] What's she doing?
-[girl 3] What the hell?
-Um, is she eating that?
[girl 2] What? Really?
-She is, that's nasty!
-[girl 1] Ew, no!
-What a freak.
-Bye, Yasuko!
-Ew, ew, ew.
-[girl 3] So creepy!
[girl 2] I think something got on me.
Nasty!
-Is she contagious?
-Are you okay?
Nana…
[sniffles]
Yasuko!
Yasuko! Yasuko, I'm sorry!
[sobbing]
Na…
Nana…
[poignant music plays]
[sobbing] Why'd you go? I needed you…
Nana…
-Nana, why did you…
-Please, Yasuko… I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-I just want it to stop…
-Yasuko…
-I'm sorry, Yasuko, I'm sorry.
-Nana…
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
Why?
-Nana…
-I love you…
[sobbing]
Nana…
[Akira] I practically lived in my bed.
Imagine being the son of a rancher
and saying that you can't work. [chuckles]
I always thought
my dad could never see me as
much of a son because of all of that.
When I was given just days to live,
I thought, "Why me?"
And then I began taking
it out on all of them.
I've hurt them a lot.
[footsteps approaching]
I believe that's…
most likely why I can't
go on to the world beyond.
[gentle, emotional music plays]
[scribbling]
He's worked on this novel
every day for years.
He decided to write a story
about me, even though, well,
books aren't his interest.
If I was still around…
maybe he wouldn't be writing a novel.
Or he could've been.
I guess I'll never really know.
I'm glad he's doing it though.
It feels like I've gotten to know him
for the first time.
AKIRA CHEERED ON THE NEWBORN CALF…
But…
if I had known about it
when I was still alive…
[continues writing]
[writing]
[music fades]
[door opens]
Hey, Nana.
[sighs] It's chaos in here.
Oh, sorry.
[Nana] What are you writing?
Ah… Well, since I got here,
I've been keeping a record.
Everything that happens.
[Nana] Oh, yeah?
BEFORE GOING TO "THE OTHER SIDE"
(WORKING TITLE) CHAPTER 14
Something wrong?
[sighs] You know…
I apologized.
Even so,
nothing has changed.
Why is that?
I'm sure that one day…
your voice is going to be heard.
Don't worry.
-That's not really an answer.
-[chuckles]
Hmm.
Ah…
You should hang on to that.
[gentle, emotional music plays]
Hmm.
[woman sobbing]
[sighs]
-[woman 1] Well, have a good night.
-[group] Good night.
[woman 2] Have a good night.
[Michael] Minako! Minako!
[music fades]
Minako!
Minako, he's alive!
[panting]
Y… your son!
He's been found!
[panting]
[whimpers]
[trembling]
[breathing unsteadily]
[chuckles]
He's still alive!
[Michael] We'll be waiting for you
right here.
Professor.
Hey, Ryo is running a fever again.
[Professor] It's already been
a whole week.
-Let's take him to the doctor again.
-[man] Sure.
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[Ryo] Mama?
Mama?
[thermometer bleeps]
[man] Hey, Ryo, we'll take you
to the doctor tomorrow, okay?
Mama, where are you?
[man] She's not here.
I'm… sure we'll find your mom.
-[shudders]
-[Ryo whimpers]
[breathing unsteadily]
Mama?
Mama.
Ryo.
I'm sorry that I left you.
[light buzzing]
Mama?
Is that you?
-[gentle music plays]
-Yes.
I'm here. [gasps]
I wanted to apologize to you. [sniffles]
I was on my way to get you
from school that day,
but the tsunami swept
me away in the ocean.
I'm sorry.
Mama?
We're gonna go home now, right?
[sobs]
[whimpers]
I wish we were.
[sniffles]
But do I have to stay here forever?
[gasps]
I'm sorry. [sniffles]
I'll always look after you, okay?
I won't ever leave you alone again.
-[Ryo] Okay.
-Mmm.
Mama?
Hmm?
-[sniffles]
-Tell me a story while you're still here.
[sniffles] Okay.
What kind of story?
Make it a fun story
about something you did.
[laughs]
Mmm…
Among the people I see right now,
we all gather together
and try to join our loved ones.
A bit like a parade.
That sounds so great.
Mm-hmm.
I would never have found you
without their help.
-I think I see.
-[sniffles]
So now you're helping everyone else out
since they were helping you?
[sniffles]
[sighs] Mm-hmm.
You're right.
[sobs]
[sighs]
[continues sobbing]
[music fades]
[birdsong]
[Ryo sighs]
[Minako] Hey, Mr. Tanaka.
[Tanaka] Yes?
I could use assistance
with this unfinished work.
What do you think?
I will do what I am able.
[Michael] Akira.
You're what we used to call
a major bummer, man.
Why would you say that?
I'm just sitting here.
Well, you know, Minako was a real looker.
If I was much younger, I might even…
-Ew. Do you mind?
-[Michael] What?
What do you mean, "ew"?
[Minako] Ew.
-[Akira] Minako!
-[laughs]
Guess I'm back.
Come here. [chuckles]
-Minako, you want coffee?
-Thanks, Kaori.
[coffee pouring]
Michael.
I didn't… say thank you in earnest.
Thank you so much.
Oh! It's embarrassing.
-Quit it.
-[both chuckle]
[hopeful music plays]
That show…
let's finish it together.
Eh?
I'll stay until we do.
You want Maiko to see it, right?
[laughing] Ohh… Oh!
Oh, stop it, I'm gonna cry!
-This is incredible! Stop!
-[all laughing]
Okay! Well, let's do it. Yeah.
This will be the c… cinematic event
of the decade.
-[Kaori laughs]
-Nana, you too.
-Huh? So what do I do?
-Mmm!
-Nana, we will not let you say no.
-No way. No, no, no, no!
-[Michael] Tanaka.
-Yes.
-Get the camera.
-Right away, Michael.
-Good!
-[Kaori] Hup!
-I'll get these.
-[Michael] Let's begin!
[waves rushing]
-Camera rolling.
-Good.
[Minako] Take one.
And…
action!
[romantic, mournful music plays]
It's been 50 years.
This film is, ah, approaching completion.
Our protagonist, Koga,
a believer in the power of student
protest movements and revolution.
The night before a demonstration,
he begins to fear arrest,
and so he goes home to Tokyo,
leaving his girlfriend behind.
He ran away.
What a cowardly fool.
Koga! Please, wait!
I'm sorry.
I'm not the man to start a revolution.
[Maiko sighs]
I'm not asking you for all that.
I just want you to stay. [trembles]
-[sobs]
-[Koga] We'll meet again. I promise.
[sobs]
[Michael] And so, Koga…
abandoned the student movement.
-This is our latest line, Star Sand.
-And ran back to Tokyo.
I guarantee this'll be huge.
[man] Congratulations!
[Michael] Maiko and Sasaki were married.
[all calling out]
-And Koga got to work.
-Any thoughts on our Star Sand deal?
Maybe "creepy cute"?
[Michael] We said
we wouldn't think about the past
and went on with our own lives.
Bye-bye, Mom! Goodbye!
[Michael] Fifty years have passed
since then.
And so Koga returned once more
to the city of Okinawa.
Old, dead moments rose up
like the scenery of those days.
M… Maiko, I, uh…
Minako, he's getting pretty into it.
[Nana] Are you Mitsuru Koga?
[Michael] And then, by some coincidence,
Koga has a chance encounter
with Maiko's young granddaughter.
Is that…
Mr. Koga?
You know my grandmother, don't you?
Huh? That makes you…
M… Maiko is your…
Come and see her. That's all I ask.
She wants to see you.
She's asked for a while now.
And cut.
She's good!
What's going on? You already an actor?
-That was great!
-Wow, Nana!
-Wow, wow!
-[Nana] Thanks!
-She's good! Goo, goo!
-Goo, goo!
-Okay, okay!
-You're a natural!
-Nana, wow!
-[Nana] Okay, stop. You have to stop!
"She wants to see you, Koga."
-Hey! Douche!
-[Akira laughing]
-Michael! Don't mock her.
-Complete disrespect.
[Michael] In the end,
you passed away before I could see you.
-[giggling]
-Sh!
Kaori, stop!
[Nana] Mr. Koga!
Goodbye!
Remember!
Always seize the day!
[Maiko] Koga!
Maiko?
Maiko!
[Minako gasps]
Koga!
Maiko!
-Maiko!
-Wait. What?
-Where's he going? Wait…
-Oh, wait…
-Michael?
-Michael!
-Hang on! Michael!
-[all] Michael! Michael!
[Akira] Hey, Michael! Where are you going?
Maiko, hey!
-Michael! Michael!
-Hey! Michael, hang on!
Michael, wait!
Maiko!
[music becomes quizzical]
[music fades]
[all gasping] Whoa!
[Kaori] Wow! [laughs]
-Let's have a screening for it soon!
-Yes, please!
-[Tanaka chuckles]
-[Akira] Wow.
[Kaori] Whew!
[Michael gasps] Oh…
What's going on?
Mmm, s… so about that, well…
I do have a… specific person in mind.
But I am a little self-conscious,
so maybe…
Mmm, could, uh…
-Well, why don't you guys just do it, huh?
-What? You should do it yourself.
[Michael] Oh, no, no, no.
I s… see your point, but, uh…
[Minako] Michael.
We'll go together.
I'll come along with you.
-Mm-hmm.
-[chuckles]
[chuckles]
W… well! Oh, I could get used to
this camaraderie thing.
[all laughing]
[sniffles] Okay.
So… let's go.
Uh… hmm.
[all laughing]
[horns blaring]
[trains chugging]
For real? There's so many people!
Yeah, it… it's crazy.
Hey, hey, hey, you guys.
Ooh! There's something of mine up ahead.
This way, this way.
[laughs]
Oh, oh, oh! Ah, yes!
Hey, this way. Oh, uh, look at this one!
This one, this one!
Wow!
-Whoa…
-Come on. Look, look, look!
-[Minako] What? Is this you?
-[laughs]
-[Akira] You're a big-time producer!
-Oh, it's nothing.
-[Minako] Amazing.
-So you weren't totally full of it.
-Why would you doubt it?
-No, no. I think we all doubted you.
-[all] Yeah.
-What? Rude!
-And that?
-[Minako] I'm in shock.
-[Akira] Amazing.
-[Kaori] Isn't it?
"FILM SHOULD BE FREEDOM"
Oh boy, this is nerve-racking.
I'm really… bad at stuff like this.
You'll be fine, Michael.
We'll be waiting for you right here.
[Michael sighs]
[sighs]
I changed my mind.
-No, come on!
-We came all the way out here.
-Uh, yeah, but…
-[man] Koga? Is that you?
S… Sasaki, right?
So,
why after all this time?
M… Maiko
deserves an apology.
I would love to see her.
Come in.
[Sasaki sighs]
[Michael] Sasaki,
when did you die?
[Sasaki] Two years ago. Cancer.
I see.
What is that?
Oh, this? [chuckles]
This is my most recent work.
It… it's on me and you…
Maiko too. It's, uh, all of us.
[chuckles]
Still doing movies. [scoffs]
-Even in death.
-Well, uh, that's true.
It's the only thing I can do.
Uh…
She's here.
[slow music playing]
-What about you?
-I'm staying here with him.
-Till the plane gets safely away.
-No, Richard, no!
-Last night, we said…
-Last night, we said a great many things.
You said
I was to do the thinking for both of us.
I've done a lot of it since then,
and it all adds up to one thing.
You're getting on that plane with Victor
where you belong.
-[Ilsa] Richard, no!
-[Rick] You've got to listen to me.
Listen.
Do you have any idea what you'd have
to look forward to if you stayed here?
Nine chances out of ten, we'd both wind up
in a concentration camp.
-Isn't that true?
-[Louis] I'm afraid Major Strasser…
[Michael] Maiko.
You haven't changed at all.
[Rick] I'm saying it because it's true.
Inside of us, we both know
you belong with Victor.
You're part of his work,
the thing that keeps him going.
If that plane leaves the ground…
She's always been your biggest fan,
Maiko has.
[Rick] …maybe not tomorrow, but soon…
Hmm…
Yeah, but, uh, Maiko chose you.
-[Rick] We'll always have Paris.
-In spite of all of that, huh?
[Rick] …until you came to Casablanca.
-We got it back last night.
-[Sasaki sniffles]
[Ilsa] And I said I would never leave you.
[Rick] And you never will.
But I've got a job to do too.
Where I'm going, you can't follow.
What I've got to do,
you can't be any part of.
Ilsa, I'm no good at being noble,
but it doesn't take much to see
that the problems of three little people
don't amount to a hill of beans
in this crazy world.
-Someday, you'll understand that.
-[Michael sighs]
["As Time Goes By" playing]
[Rick] Now, now.
Here's looking at you, kid.
[sobbing]
-[horns blare]
-You know…
I still think
about all the years we spent.
[Rick] There's something you should know
before you leave.
[emotional music plays]
Didn't manage to start a revolution.
And yet…
we were united once.
At least that's true.
[sobbing]
[inhales]
Maiko…
M… Maiko, I, uh…
[exhales]
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
[emotional music continues]
Aah…
[music fades]
-[Michael] Hi there. Hey, hey, hey, hey!
-[Minako] Oh…
How did everything go?
Couldn't have gone better.
-Excellent! Good. Goo, goo.
-Wait. You didn't give her the movie?
Well, movies aren't really,
you know, made for outside the theater.
-I'll bring her a copy of the DVD.
-[Kaori] Ah!
-It's not coming out on DVD though!
-[chuckles] My, my, my. It's okay though.
Now, shall we go back?
Huh? [laughs]
[Minako chuckles]
[wind gusting]
Hey, everyone.
We have the theater.
We should just screen it.
People are bound to be interested.
Ooh, hey! [chuckles]
That's what I was about to s… suggest.
That's a great idea though.
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Let's do it.
-[Akira] Let's do it!
-[Michael] We're doing this!
-[Tanaka] Great!
[murmur of voices]
Michael, we're all set. Mm-hmm.
[coughs]
[sighs]
Um…
G… good evening, everyone.
M… my name is Michael.
With the help of my great friends,
we have finally completed this film.
Well… t… this film is actually, well…
It can truly move generations
and inspire revolution
while being a conduit that connects
the past to the present and future.
Mmm.
Uh… uh…
Still directing, even after I've died.
-[laughter]
-[Michael] That was pointed out to me.
But I tend to think
that fortune favors the bold.
Please, everyone,
enjoy the movie.
[sighs]
[fingers tapping]
[gentle ambient music plays]
[Minako chuckles]
[Michael chuckles]
[projector whirring]
[waves rushing]
[music fades]
[Michael] You know…
So, for the next feature…
-You have more ideas?
-[Michael laughs]
Well, the next chapter…
On the years that I've b… been here.
Something I'd like to try. [laughs]
Hey, Michael. I had that idea too.
-[Nana] Really?
-[Michael] Well!
Well, let's do it together!
If you thought this last one
was a masterpiece…
I can't allow that. [chuckles]
-[all chuckling]
-[Michael] Okay.
Minako.
-Are you okay?
-Uh, yes.
It just
hasn't sunk in yet. [sighs]
I understand that.
[wistful music plays]
To be honest, I was feeling…
pretty uneasy about it too. [chuckles]
Hey, Tanaka.
-[Tanaka] Yes?
-Uh…
Can you tell us anything
about the other side?
I am afraid I cannot.
Huh?
So, Tanaka… Think of him as a marshal.
Nobody said anything? That's so scary.
[all laughing]
W… won't you just tell us already?
Come on.
You will learn soon enough.
-[Kaori] Aah!
-Tanaka, why are you being so stubborn?
[laughs]
But you know what?
The show was fun. I had a good time.
I know!
There's nothing like filmmaking.
Us… full-grown adults at play,
working towards this story…
-It… it's phenomenal!
-[Minako laughs]
-It is.
-[Michael] Right?
Now… Nana.
Keep making more movies.
Th… there's notes in my room
that you can use.
Nana, you're going to be great!
[laughs] Why's it only me?
[Michael] Akira.
Everything else is up to you.
It is essential that you continue
to document this world.
I promise that I will.
But you always have to stay
on the offensive.
-Never let your guard down!
-Who's he competing with?
[Michael] Hmm. Well.
Let's have a toast. Kanpai. Mmm?
-Ting!
-[Akira] Sure.
[Michael] Yes! Let's toast.
[Kaori sighs heavily]
Kanpai.
[all] Kanpai.
[glasses clinking]
Aah…
Well, we have plenty of food left.
-So eat up.
-[Michael] Oh.
-[Tanaka] Yeah, let's eat.
-[Akira] All right.
[Tanaka] Could you pass me some kinpira?
-[Nana] This one?
-[Tanaka] That one.
-[Akira] You want chicken?
-[Tanaka] Oh, just one, please.
-Yes, thank you.
-[Akira] Sure.
-[Tanaka] And…
-[Akira] Ah, the fries.
-[Tanaka] Thanks.
-[Akira] This much?
[Tanaka] Yes, thank you. A bit more.
-[Akira] A little more?
-[Tanaka] Yes, thank you.
-[Akira] What can I get you?
-[Nana] Not kinpira.
[Tanaka, Akira laugh]
-[Nana] Why laugh?
-[Minako] It's nothing.
-[Akira] Here. Anything else?
-[Nana] Just…
[poignant music continues]
[scribbling]
[music fades]
…SOUND OF WAVES, AND AN EMPTY BEACH
Knock, knock.
[Akira] Everyone else went to sleep?
[Minako] Yeah.
Seems like Michael fell asleep
while all of us were talking.
[Akira chuckles]
That guy has so much energy.
[Minako sighs]
-Here.
-Thanks.
[sighs]
[grunts]
Akira, do you really plan to keep writing?
Yeah.
At least until Dad finishes his book.
Then I might stop.
I see.
Don't forget to put me in there.
Of course.
I think I'll turn you
into the main character.
-Oh, no, don't! That's okay.
-[laughs]
Just a little part. [giggles]
I was really wishing…
that you could stay longer.
[laughs] Where'd this come from?
I kinda have…
a little crush.
-[gentle music plays]
-What's with this confession?
-Was it strange?
-[laughs]
Yes, it's strange.
[both chuckle]
I wonder how things would have gone
if we had known each
other a little earlier.
"Coulda, woulda, shoulda," right?
That's right. [sighs]
Akira.
Thank you.
I've had a good time.
So have I.
Thank you, Minako.
[music fades]
[Minako humming softly]
[continues humming]
[humming stops]
[emotional music plays]
[man 1] Okay, let's go.
-All right…
-[all talking]
-[man 2] Hey!
-[man 1] 'Scuse us. Just coming through.
[man 2] Watch out!
[emotional music continues]
[wind sighing]
[bird sings]
[music swells]
[music quietens]
[birdsong]
[music fades]
[waves rushing]
Wow, it's so crowded.
-[man] We'll need to get started.
-[Nana] Ah, I see.
-I really appreciate it.
-[man] We'll get on it.
-[Nana] I appreciate it.
-[man] Of course.
Uh, there's also these ones right here.
[Nana] Oh, then this one should be…
Is that… Sorry, excuse me.
Ryo!
Oh…
-It's been a long time. [chuckles]
-Yes, it has!
We still have a little while.
You wanna go for tea?
-Yeah, sure.
-Mmm.
-You got so tall!
-[both laugh]
[Nana] Thank you for coming today.
-Your first time in Tokyo?
-Oh, yeah.
-It's crazy crowded.
-[laughs]
-I suppose, compared to home for sure.
-Yeah. Seriously.
Wait, Ryo, you graduate next year, right?
Yeah, that's correct.
Any plans? Thought about what's next?
Well…
I'm not… totally sure right now.
I think I'm interested in news.
The same work my mother did.
[chuckles]
I'd like to ask you some more questions
about my mom one of these days.
Sure. Of course.
Anyway, I'm looking forward
to the film today.
Mmm. I think you'll like it.
-[chuckles]
-[woman] Oh, Nana!
It's been a while.
-Oh! Hey, so good to see you!
-Yeah, hey!
Long time no see. Hello!
-Okay, say hi. [chuckles]
-Hello!
Goo!
[all laugh]
[woman] Go ahead.
-Tickets, please. This way.
-[Nana] Go ahead to theater two.
-[usher] Your ticket?
-[Ryo] See you later.
[Nana] Hope you enjoy.
Phew…
-This is it, huh?
-Why do I feel nervous?
Yeah…
[gasps]
[man] Thank you, enjoy the show.
[soft music playing]
[Nana gasps]
-[laughs] You're sitting so low!
-[child laughs]
-You don't wanna sit up a little?
-Hmm, no.
-I like this.
-Oh, hey, it's starting!
[emotional ambient music plays]
[wind gusting]
[waves rushing]
[music fades]
[ballad in Japanese plays]
[song continues]
[song ends]
[lively song in Japanese plays]
[song fades]
[gentle instrumental music plays]
[music fades]