"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time
Final Episode"
What is this?
The smell...
I don't like to say goodbye.
I hate it.
So much that I bawled when we had a
class shuffle two years ago.
When I have to say goodbye
to my friends,
or when I have to say goodbye to a
time I treasure, I'd feel lonely.
I think of time as my life.
Hey...
Will you cry?
Will you cry if our time dies?
Keita,
are you going to keep loving
your mom?
Of course I am!
You'll listen to her, and talk to
her about interesting things?
Of course I will!
Thank you!
Mi-kun, too, please continue
to take care of mom.
Sure. Cheers.
I have to keep making you like me,
too.
What?
You know, my father hated me,
so he left us.
- No, that's not true.
- It is true.
I remember it.
"7 years ago"
Hey, stop there!
Pay for the food!
He got away and it's all your fault!
You idiot!
Actually...Why did you cry?
It has nothing to do with you.
Has nothing to do with you!
Who the heck are you?
She has paid off her debt,
hasn't she?
Wait...What are we here for?
Well...She has paid off her debt.
Bon appetit...
Miura...
What about "Mi-kun"?
Mi-kun.
Well done!
Seven years have passed since then,
and Keita has grown up a lot.
It's been seven years, huh?
My body aged many times
quicker than that,
and it's seriously damaged.
When the doctor told us
the results of your checkup...
I think it was my fault.
That's not the case at all.
I think maybe the food I make
isn't healthy enough.
You aged so much that there is
no medical explanation...
I just don't get it.
Sometimes I'm worried...
...that when I wake up in
the morning,
and I will find that you're gone.
So when I wake up and see you here,
I feel like I had
a fateful encounter.
When you meet someone, you only feel
the delight for a brief moment,
but I feel that every single day.
How blessed I am!
On that night,
I kept thinking about what is the
right way to say goodbye.
Wheat noodles...
- Oh!
- It's hot, isn't it?
I'll drive you home.
No, thanks. I haven't been
exercising enough.
I would like to ask you a favor.
What?
I come from the 22nd Century.
Yes?
To collect samples of
the environment here.
But then, I met Yuri.
So I decided to stay in this era
and form a family.
But after a few years,
I felt a change in my body.
When I had my cells checked,
they showed signs of rapid aging.
It is a self-cleansing action caused
by time energy.
Time flows faster for people
from the future.
I cannot live long.
You're seeing Shohei, aren't you?
You should break up with him
as soon as possible.
Shohei is from the future, too.
Wow...Is he?
Anyway, the introduction was
too long.
It'd be more simple and interesting
if you tell me that we're siblings
related by blood,
like they do in the lunch time
soap opera.
What?
You want to ask me
to break up with Shohei, right?
No, that's not the favor
I want to ask.
Please make my family gone.
What?
I mean, please do a time-leap
and make my family gone.
Make your family gone?
What do you mean?
Please don't let me meet Yuri
seven years ago.
What...No, I can't take this!
This is not for you.
What?
If you pay off her debt with the
money, then we wouldn't have met.
Yuri is gorgeous,
so she would meet someone
and live happily forever.
I'm sure that she'd be happier
like that.
Please, help me.
No way!
And I didn't say I can
leap through time.
No need to feign innocence.
You can, can't you?
When you leap through time,
you jump a bit, like this, right?
Wow...Jump a bit...Is that so?
Be careful,
or you'll hurt your back.
I said, I cannot leap through time.
Mihane!
Please!
Is it okay to just conclude what
Mr. Miura said was a lie?
- He's a pathological liar.
- Yeah, I guess.
But...
He knows that I jump a bit
when I do a time-leap.
- He is a pathological liar.
- You're absolutely correct.
Of course Shohei can't come
from the future.
I told you...
Where are you from, then?
Let's pretend that I'm a foreigner.
Yoshiyama.
I don't think you know me, but...
Yes, I do...
Onishi.
I've decided to transfer to
a school in Tokyo.
What?
I actually wanted...
...to be friends with you.
Please let me take photos of you
someday.
Eight, nine, ten.
The photos are ready.
Thank you.
Oh, wow. I look handsome
in the photos you took.
I don't get why you lied to me.
The reason I lied?
There isn't any,
because it wasn't a lie.
My body can't hold out for long.
I'll have my last supper with them
later.
The two of them don't know this.
It will be our usual supper.
I'll be gone after they fall asleep.
You're running away.
I think you should take the
responsibility of your encounter.
The responsibility of our encounter?
- You should say goodbye properly.
- I won't.
I can't.
I, Yuri and Keita will not be able
to stand the pain of saying goodbye.
Because we're very close.
Then you should stay...
The best way is to avoid
meeting them at all!
You can leap through time, right?
I know.
Please help me!
I love my family.
I don't want them to be sad
because of the problem I have.
I want them to smile.
Please!
To me, my family is more important
than my own life.
Please make our encounter
never happen!
I can't really control when I leap
to recently.
I don't know whether I can
go back to 7 years ago smoothly.
You will help me?
But please don't run away from
your family.
Thank you!
- Supper is ready!
- Thank you!
- It looks delicious!
- There you go, Keita.
Thank you.
It's gorgeous!
What's wrong?
I have to tell you something.
This is the last day
that we are a family.
What?
The last day?
The seven years that we've been
a family will be gone.
Don't worry.
We're only going to spend the
seven years again separately.
I said separately,
but we won't feel lonely or sad
because we can't see each other.
Because we wouldn't have met
to begin with.
You mean because you'll stay in
hospital next week?
But the doctor said that it will be
a simple checkup.
Don't make a fuss.
What I want you to understand,
is that...
I love you both from the bottom of
my heart, Yuri and Keita.
I love you very much.
If possible, I wish I could spend my
whole life with you two.
But if I do that,
I am going to make you sad.
I'm going to break your hearts.
So please, understand that.
Keita, do give your mom
the support she needs.
No matter what happens,
you should live your life
with all your might.
And...
Find the person that you care for.
Living is to love the people
you care for.
This is what I learnt from you two.
You're just going to have
an endoscopic examination,
don't say it like you're leaving us
forever.
Thank you so much for being my
family in these seven years!
We have been a real family.
I was very happy.
What are you talking about?
We are a family,
and we always will be, right?
We're a family forever.
Mi-kun is crying.
You look so stupid.
- Don't cry, dad.
- What...
Okay.
You are my dad.
You're one of our family.
Keita...
That reminds me.
Look at this...
We took them the other day.
We all look so happy.
We're the greatest family in Japan.
No, in the world.
In the universe!
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
It was a sad last supper.
If we had never met,
then all the sadness will be gone.
I wonder if this is the right way
to say goodbye.
It's your own turn next.
What?
How are you going to
say goodbye to Shohei?
I'm not going to say goodbye to him.
People from the future
can't live long here.
I told you, I grew up with Shohei.
He hypnotized you.
Hypnotized me?
Do you remember what Shohei looked
like when he was a child?
Go away! Go!
Hey! Go away!
Are you okay, Mihane?
Mihane, it's okay now.
It was Goro...
It was Goro who saved my life
at that time.
It wasn't Shohei...
"Okonomiyaki Ribon"
(Your life is short,)
(so go and fall in love, maiden.)
Oh? Where is Goro today?
What is he doing?
I think he has gone to
his cram school.
Seven years later, you told me to
give this to you.
Stop there!
Hey...Stop!
I don't want it.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Welcome!
There is something that
we would like to tell you today.
- We're getting married.
- What?
We hope you two would be
our witnesses.
- Wow!
- Congratulations!
Thanks. We have to thank
the two of you for this.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, we scared you.
- Good job, Mr. Yano!
- Don't tell anyone yet.
- But...
- Choose what you say.
We'll do what we should do.
Hey, wait for me.
You...
Who the heck are you?
What?
What do you mean?
You want to hypnotize me again?
Are you going to rewrite my memory?
What? You know?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
My real name...
...is Ken Sogol.
In our era, the environment on Earth
is different from now.
It's covered with snow
throughout the year.
There is no season after
the 21st Century.
We've came to study summer.
I was supposed to go back after
staying for a few hours,
but I carelessly lost the potion
for doing time-leap.
What?
You lost it?
It was a small bottle...
with a green lid and some purple
liquid in it.
Have you seen it?
- Why would I have?
- True.
- And?
- Oh...And...
If I use the spare potion
to mix with the ingredients I can
get in this era as well,
I should be able to have finished
making the potion, but...
But what?
You were too careless again?
You knocked over all the potions.
It was after school on 7th July,
in the lab's storage room.
What?
You mean it was my fault that you
can't go back?
Well, if you put it that way,
then, yes, it was.
But thanks to that,
we fell in love, didn't we?
Mihane?
You can't go back now?
I'm making the potion from scratch
again,
and it will be completed soon.
But don't worry,
I'm staying in this era.
What?
I thought you would be happy.
You have to go back!
- If you stay in this era...
- But I want to be with you.
If that Mr. Miura
really cared about his family,
he should have stayed in this era
until his last moment.
Go back.
But I've made up my mind.
Does it bring you so much trouble?
Just go back!
Go back to the future
as soon as possible.
Come and help me, Mihane.
- Help you with what?
- Put this on the table.
This?
- Yes...
- Okay.
- Hey...What are you doing?
- You're so clumsy.
- Step away.
- Gosh!
Why is the newspaper placed here?
Apologize before you blame others!
I'll just turn it back, okay?
Oh?
Why?
- What are you doing?
- Why?
Why? Turn it back...
Turn it back...
"To you, who never know summer.
A photo collection"
You're going now?
What?
Mix the rice like you're cutting it.
Take it.
That's it. Well done.
Have you noticed who I actually am?
On the night you didn't come home,
I got so worried that
I went to ask for the police's help.
I didn't have a son.
So...
You're not going to ask...
...who I really am?
I enjoyed having you here,
and I know that you aren't
a bad person.
Thank you very much
for all the delicious dishes
you've made me.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
Then please do the washing up
tonight.
As your rent.
Mom!
"Barber Asakura"
What's the matter?
There is no reaction...
What?
Seriously?
Oh, my god...
I have to grow old and die
in this era!
This is amazing...
I can stay in this era!
You darn idiot!
This is awesome! Fantastic!
Yes!
Mihane.
Mihane!
Good news.
The ingredients in the potion didn't
react in the final stage.
What? Say that you're happy.
Be happy for me.
I can't.
You can't live for long.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't knocked over the lab's
apparatus on that day,
you would've been able to
return to the future.
I wish I hadn't...
What?
Pardon?
I said, I wish I hadn't
fallen in love.
You'll get many questions on the
area of quadratic functions
in your exam,
so make sure you do some
revision on them.
Is there any problem
you can't solve?
I said something that
I didn't actually mean.
And?
The way I said goodbye...
...was wrong.
If you realize you've made
a mistake,
then you'll not make it again.
- Mayuka, let's go.
- Okay.
Could this be...
It has a green lid
and purple liquid inside.
Shohei!
He's not here.
I can use it instead.
It's faint, but the smell...
I'll go back to the lab afterschool
on 7th July.
Just when I thought that,
I realized something important
and I hesitated.
If I return to that day,
that means my first love with Shohei
would never have happened.
But it's just my first love!
It's the first love
that I'm going to forget anyway.
that I'll just make fun of someday
and have a good laugh.
I don't have to be hesitant.
For the person I care for,
I'll throw away something trivial,
like my first love.
It's just my first love.
But it's still my first love.
Please...
Please!
7th July...
"8th August"
In the lab, after school.
Please! Let me go back!
Please be my Juliet.
Julio!
"7th July"
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
Shohei.
You're here, right?
Hey...
Hey.
Where are you?
Over there, huh?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to help you return
to the 22nd Century.
The last time...
I knocked over the very same set of
apparatus.
And that's why...
you couldn't return to the future.
I inhaled it,
then I passed out.
It gave me the ability to
leap through time,
and I had a lot of fun.
So it was the smell of lavender...
You don't know this now,
but we...
We were a couple.
What?
It's not right to say that
we were a couple, though.
It should be in the future.
You fell in love with me,
then you rewrote my memories,
so that you could take advantage
of it.
You're awful.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize!
You still haven't done it.
This is you, when you had
iced pineapple for the first time.
You looked happier than
when we watched the fireworks.
But after this...
The decoration of the frame
hit right at you.
Seriously?
But I protected you by
turning back time.
I saved your life,
so I felt relieved and cried.
You saw me...
...and you laughed.
Why are you wearing sweat suit
alone?
15 minutes before this was taken...
You...
...kissed me for the first time.
I tried to run away and fell
into the swimming pool.
Sorry for dodging your kiss.
Our class did a performance
in the Garyosai Festival.
You played Julio.
Julio?
It was Romeo and Julio.
When we had a party afterwards,
you confessed your love for me
in front of everyone.
I'm not good at dealing with
situations like that,
but...
I was happy.
This was taken when we went
on a picnic.
We had a date in an amusement park.
The dinner party at your home.
At the swimming pool
in the middle of the night.
Your funny face...
What about it?
It's pretty awful.
Though it's a funny face...
I don't want my boyfriend
to look like this.
It's bad for
people who come from the future
to stay in this era for too long.
To help you go back
to the future,
coming here today is the only way.
But you told me
that you were not going back.
You said you'd rather have your life
cut short than separate with me.
But I don't want that to happen.
I don't want you to have your life
cut short
just to be here with me.
So...
Go back.
I see.
Are you really okay...
...with me returning to the future?
I've been holding back,
but when you ask me that...
I don't want you to go back.
Of course I want to be with you
forever.
Because it is my first love.
I really don't want to lose it.
But if I don't get you back
to the future,
you're going to die.
So I'll give up.
I see.
Take it.
If you've finished making
your potion,
then go back as soon as you can!
Just go!
Hey...This...
"To you, who never knew love"
You wrote this, didn't you?
It's a photo book made
by an unknown photographer.
This...
Isn't it yours?
No...
This is...
the photo book that
you are going to make.
"To you, who never knew summer.
A photo collection"
All the photos are great, right?
This is an amazing collection
of photos.
I see.
I have to thank you for everything.
Thank you.
I'll take...
the summer,
and my love back with me.
I love you.
Farewell.
Thank you.
There she is.
Mihane?
I have to submit the form of
my plan after high school.
Your first choice is
the University of Tokyo?
Kyoto University? Harvard?
- Which one?
- Harvard!
Just joking.
It's a university, which I can
do a photography degree course.
You're serious?
I...
There is something I want to do.
I took it!