Summer...
I hate it.
I used to like it before,
but I started to hate it
since attending middle school.
It's a nuisance when you sweat,
right?
I even wanted to go to school naked.
Amazing!
We're here!
No, not naked.
It takes so much trouble
to get rid of my body hair.
Like hair on your arms, armpits,
the back...You name it.
You do it for
the most absurd reasons
and like you're worried that
others might see it.
Things like flying in the sky
or reading people's mind...
I don't believe in superpowers,
but if I can have one,
I want one that will let me get rid
of my body hair at once!
Watch out!
Gosh, you must be kidding...
What, it's stupid?
But it's still more useful than
bending a spoon.
What is this?
I think it's a giant oarfish.
I'm in my third year in high school
before I knew it.
I'm old already.
My friends, parents and teachers
keep talking about college
entry exam.
Yeah, all right, I'll do it soon!
But there are things that
I have to do now...
Maybe not.
What? How boring!
It's my last summer in high school!
You lost the potion?
You mean we can't go back?
It's not totally impossible...Hey!
No way...
I've made up my mind!
I'll enjoy this summer
to the fullest extent.
Oh, hang on.
I thought it was too quiet
and you're gone.
Where have you gone to?
Come on, don't just leave me here
and go away.
You're so mean.
What are you doing in my home?
Hey...Seriously, where are you?
Just the right amount...
Don't go somewhere far away.
I'm lonely. It hurts.
Please don't. Wait...
We'll meet again, right?
No...I'm scared...Please!
Come back...
Who is there?
Is someone in there?
What is this?
The smell...
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
I like the barber more than
a hair salon.
It feels so good
to have my face shaved.
Girls do grow a moustache, too.
It's fine hair like peach fuzz.
You don't have to see if I grow any.
What the heck?
Don't tell me...
Goro, you fancy me?
Even if I do this?
No way!
You've got to be kidding!
Ouch!
Gosh, my hairstyle is horrible!
You had it cut in the hair salon
yesterday, right?
I did try to stop you, though.
It doesn't suit me at all!
Today is 7th July,
the Star Festival.
Perhaps you would like to write your
wish on strips of paper...
I can't go to school
wearing this hairstyle!
Why? It's cute, like a helmet.
But helmets make you look stupid!
...a giant oarfish was found
here on the Fujiura Coast,
Shizuoka Prefecture.
Oh? The Fujiura Coast
is just round the corner, right?
Isn't that girl from Higashi High
School like you, Mihane?
Wow, she is on TV and the whole
nation is watching it.
Something horrible might happen...
I've finished breakfast.
...and this could be the sign.
- See you.
- Okay, see you.
The ice-cream in the freezer
is mine.
You'll swallow a thousand needles
if you eat it.
Mihane, you'll be late for school
if you don't hurry.
I said, I'm not going to school.
What? Really?
You've never taken a sick leave
since kindergarten!
I didn't know I was digging my
own grave by being healthy.
Bon appetit.
Mom!
Where is my camera?
What? I have no idea.
Where is it...
Oh! It is here!
Let's go!
Good morning...
Your hairstyle is great.
It suits you.
You're lying, but thanks anyway.
It's true! But my dad would be sad,
if he knows you stop coming to our
barber shop to have your hair cut.
I'm fed up with hair salons.
I'll go to Barber Asakura
to have my hair cut next time!
All right. Let's go!
- Go without me.
- What?
I'll get my gas tank filled.
Gas tank?
Did you cut it for me?
Because I said I liked
girls who wear a mushroom haircut?
Of course not...
Hey...
Your gas tank...
I filled it with
high-octane gasoline today!
High-octane?
What do you mean? What high-octane?
- Five more minutes.
- Five more?
Good morning...
Hey, you like guys like him?
Yes! I like handsome guys like him!
- You like that kind of guys?
- Yes!
Oh, Goro!
Goro, what are you doing?
I'm sorry...
Sorry, I'll go to
the classroom later.
You dropped the flowers.
Please forgive her.
I'll lecture her later. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
Why did you make him angry?
I just bumped into him...
I bumped into him because
I was calling your name...
Weird? What do you mean?
- It's round, like...
- You mean mushroom?
- Yeah...
- What?
Good morning...
Your hairstyle is lovely!
- It really suits you.
- You've cut pretty much.
- Yeah, I have.
- It really suits you.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- What the heck?
Good...morning.
You got your hair cut.
You look like a Kokeshi doll.
Kokeshi doll!
- Calm down!
- Well done, Shohei, it's so funny.
I knew Shohei would make
a fool of me.
This is a bit too bad.
The trick to solving this question
is to divide it with
the denominator's inverse number.
3 minus 1 is 2,
so you times it by 1 over 2,
and this...
is the trick of doing
a partial fraction decomposition.
Got it?
Now, let's do a similar question
after this.
Let's see who should I get
to do it...
Mihane Yoshiyama!
Girls in their swimsuits are lovely,
but let's do maths now.
Where is your textbook?
You must have brought
a notebook, right?
I only have this...
My, my. How romantic...You idiot!
- What have you come to school for?
- Sorry.
Darn.
Mihane Yoshiyama.
Why does that dying message mean?
I think it means this question
cannot be solved...
But it actually reads, "Please give
me some special questions."
No, thank you...
I told him I want to break up
and I was serious.
But we ended up kissing.
What? Why did you end up kissing?
Then we kept kissing for 2.5 hours
until we went to cram school.
My lips got chapped.
Oh, you're really a grown-up,
Erichin!
I want a boyfriend, too!
But I don't want you to have
a boyfriend, Ojo.
And you, Mihane?
Are you going to the Star Festival
event with Asakura this year, too?
Yeah, I guess.
We do that every year.
Will Asakura wear his yukata?
I want be held in his arms, tightly.
Oh, he's so handsome...
Why do high school girls love
talking about boys? It's awful...
You said the college student at the
convenient store was cool, right?
Well...That...It's not like
I have a crush on him...
It's like filling a gas tank.
- Really?
- I really don't!
- Congratulations!
- Wow.
Give Yoshiyama a round of applause!
Aphrodite is smashed into pieces...
I am sorry!
I'm thirsty...
My luck seems to be bad today.
- I'll go to throw away the rubbish.
- Okay.
- Put the stools down.
- Got it.
She's so cute! Let's take a photo...
- Okay, say cheese!
- She's so cute!
Who is there?
Is someone in there?
What is it?
This smell...
There is just no man who can
make my heart skip a beat.
Then...What about Mr. Yano?
Mr. Yano?
He's too loud, and I'm fed up with
his "chic-ish" shirts.
- Don't tell him, though.
- Okay.
How are you feeling? The boys are
waiting here and they're worried.
Worried? But you were gossiping
about love and crushes.
Why were you having a nap
in the lab's storage room?
I wasn't having a nap!
A sweet aroma came from
a broken test tube,
I was wondering what it was and when
I inhaled it, I felt dizzy...
Was there a broken test tube?
- No, there wasn't.
- What?
Only you passed out there.
What?
But there were broken flasks,
beakers...And it was a mess, right?
Someone was doing an experiment.
- Then I turned them over...
- I told you,
there weren't any.
- Right, Shohei?
- What?
- There was absolutely nothing.
- You see?
Enough of that.
Are you really okay, Mihane?
Have you felt any changes
in your body?
What's the matter?
What?
I'm starving...
Gosh, you're ridiculous!
- This is horrible.
- Let's go!
Our conclusion is, she got anemia
and she was starving,
so she experienced an hallucination.
Gosh, you two are so mean!
They asked whether my brain was okay
to have my college entry exam or not
and told me to have it checked.
Oh, you'll have your
college entry exam?
It feels like you've just
entered your high school.
Time flies.
Our Keita is in primary 3 now.
I have to write what
I want to do after graduation...
What should I write?
You'll succeed the barber's,
won't you, Goro?
But my parents told me to
go to college.
Just pursue your dream.
It's your own life after all.
He studies arts,
but his marks are high enough
to enter a medical school.
Go and be a doctor. A scalpel earns
you more than a pair of scissors.
Come on!
That's not what you just said.
Hang on. Have we asked Shohei what
he wants to do after graduation?
That reminds me. No.
I'll go to a pharmaceutical
research center.
- That's your dream?
- No, it's not a dream.
It's just because my DNA makes me
suitable for this.
Your DNA makes you
suitable for that?
- Wow, what the heck?
- It's so cool.
So, what does your DNA make you
suitable to be?
What?
A guy and a lady suddenly appeared
on the boat?
Don't make up stories.
I'm telling the truth!
They appeared yesterday.
Why don't you remember it?
Are you still taking photos?
I don't know what to photograph
and the photos my friends take with
their smartphones look prettier.
I haven't got any talent.
It's frustrating.
Do you know her?
She goes to our high school.
Atsumi Onishi, right?
She's an internet idol,
and this incident got everyone
really excited on the internet.
Why?
"The idol of miracles, whom the
Dragon Palace sent a messenger to."
She just found a deep sea fish
that was washed ashore.
But idols nowadays need
a catchphrase.
I heard the girls in Class 2
suddenly became friendly to her.
Right after she got famous.
I want to get famous, too!
If it was some years ago,
you might have been popular,
because you are cute.
But nowadays, it's difficult to be
popular just because you're cute.
- What a pity.
- What a shame.
You were born in the wrong time,
Mihane.
It was wrong?
- I'm home.
- Welcome back...
Don't eat my brain!
What?
What's wrong with Keita?
No idea.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
Pineapple...
I think it might be the last time
we go to the festival together.
Why?
We might not be in this town
next year.
I see...
Ojo said that she wanted you to hold
her in your arms in your yukata.
Why don't you go with her?
Rock, paper, scissors...
Yes!
Chocolate...
Yeah, perhaps.
Mihane makes me eat the octopus
in the Takoyaki,
it's awful every year.
I'm not having any Takoyaki
this year.
Rock, paper, scissors...
Pineapple!
Apple...
Gosh, he's annoying!
You didn't win even once. It doesn't
make sense in theory.
I was serious when
I played the game.
Mihane, thanks for the juice.
Thanks for the juice!
Darn...
Ryu, sorry to have kept you waiting.
My gasoline has a girlfriend?
And she has long hair.
I'm so angry!
I'm really angry!
Anyway, my back feels itchy.
Scratch it for me.
Mihane doesn't act like a lady.
Because it's Goro.
Come on, be a lady!
Everyone will criticize you
for saying that.
Okay!
Bye bye bi...
Everything is the same as usual.
What should I take in my photo?
Would you like an ice-cream?
Ice-cream...
That's not it...
That's it...Over here.
A turtle?
Why is this turtle here?
Watch out!
Somehow my luck is bad today.
I'm going to die!
What?
Why?
I'm dead, right? Am I...
A ghost?
Oh, old lady!
Can you see me?
Someone from the other world has
finally come for me, too?
I'm a god of death?
What's going on?
- Mihane.
- What?
Shohei!
Stop...It's okay...Calm down.
- Calm down and tell me.
- Am I dead?
- I'm a god of death? A ghost?
- No, you're not dead...
The same period of time
repeated itself.
It's your imagination.
But the turtle! Is it possible that
I was holding it before I knew it?
Oh, that.
That?
I'm saying,
that you've got...
your camera and the turtle mixed up.
I see.
They're similar.
They're totally different!
I've read it in comic books,
I think it's like "time-leap".
Impossible.
It's impossible.
You're not Urashima Taro...
That's it!
This turtle has such power!
What?
Mihane...
Mihane?
Again.
Mihane...
Miss Mihane?
You don't want people to think
that you're creepy, right?
So, the story about you
leapt through time...
You'd better not tell anyone.
Got it?
Have you got it?
No, I don't.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
What are you doing?
It's a secret.
If I tell you I can leap
through time,
you'll make a fool of me and
won't believe me.
I'll definitely keep it a secret.
Mom! Mihane became an imbecile!
Why did I have my hair
cut like this?
Okay, I'll make you look cute.
No...No!
"6th July"
"7th July"
What?
What just happened?
What happened, Mihane...
A cockroach!
- I'm too confused for that!
- Dad, there's a cockroach!
Come and get rid of it now!
It's not the turtle.
Dad!
I...
I...leapt through time?
"6th July"
Okay, I'll make you look cute.
Stop!
Yes! I don't have to get my hair
cut into a weird style!
I can do it!
I can leap through time!
Watch out!
Today is 7th July,
the Star Festival.
Perhaps you would like to write your
wish on strips of paper.
Look! I look good, right?
I look good, right?
I gave you money to get it cut in a
hair salon but it wasn't cut.
That's why I look good!
Bon appetit!
It was found by Miss Onishi here.
Would you tell us how you found it?
Something horrible might happen,
and this could be a sign.
You have a girlfriend!
And you don't care about
my hairstyle!
I've got a stomachache.
3 minus 1 is 2,
so you times it by 1 over 2.
This is the trick of doing
a partial fraction decomposition.
Got it?
Now, let's do a similar question
after this.
- Let's see who wants to do it.
- Me!
I think it's going to snow, right?
I've done some reading.
Well done.
Amazing! You caught it!
Oh, my god!
What the heck?
Oh, darn...
She is soaked...
Water!
Hang on...No...Don't use this.
- Why?
- It's broken.
Use this.
Rock, paper, scissors...
- What the heck?
- Why?
Chocolate...
I reached the goal!
Hey, hang on!
It doesn't make sense in theory
that you didn't lose even once.
Because I was serious
when I played the game.
The one who loses
will treat us to fruit juice!
- Keep your promise.
- I'll definitely win this.
Rock, paper, scissors...
Once more!
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
"Barber Asakura"
The sound...
The rhythm...
It makes me feel so safe
that I got sleepy.
You used to sleep when
you were small.
I miss the days when Goro had to
support your head
when I cut your hair.
I guess Mihane is the beauty of our
shop when she comes here.
Most ladies don't come anymore.
- Most young men don't, too.
- I see.
- So, do you like it?
- What...
Well...
I can do stylish and trendy
hairstyles, too.
But the way you say it
sounds old-fashioned.
Your dad used to be handsome.
You used to be gorgeous, too.
Time is a cruel thing.
You're one of our family, too.
Oh? There's a power cut?
Hey, Mihane, bring me a torch.
Thanks...What are you doing?
What's that?
I hear something.
What is it?
Be careful.
- Mom, there's a fire!
- A fire?
- Yeah.
- Where is it?
- Over there.
- The light can't reach there.
- There's smoke coming out.
- Yes, there is.
It's where Goro's home is.
Goro...You mean the Asakura family?
Oh, I have to go!
What...Mihane!
Mihane.
Goro, glad to see that you're okay.
There is a small fire
at the substation.
Shohei...
Are you okay?
The fire has been put out.
Really? Glad to hear that.
"Star Festival 2016"
"Atsumi Onishi will be performing"
She got people's attention because
of a small incident. Amazing.
But she has the ability to shine on
stage to begin with.
Shine on stage, huh?
I have got that, too.
- What did you just say?
- I have got that, too!
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
Five seconds to go.
Four, three, two...
This is the so-called
"phantom deep sea fish",
that is, a giant oarfish.
It was found on the Fujiura Coast,
Shizuoka Prefecture.
It was found by Miss Yoshiyama.
Would you tell us how you found it?
I think it's the sign of
something horrible.
- The giant oarfish has always...
- Amazing!
The whole country can see it.
The "phantom deep sea fish",
that is, the giant oarfish,
has a gold colored body...
What are you plotting?
I want to become famous.
Like an idol.
You know, at a time like this,
- even if your looks...
- ...are cute,
but I can't be an idol, right?
Yes, I know.
- I'm amazed that she said it.
- Indeed.
That's why...
I'll be an idol who makes
prophecies.
Sure.
I'm going to shock the world!
- Film it properly! Like this...
- Yeah, I'm filming you...
Tonight, at 8:10 p.m,
there will be a small fire
at a substation near Barber Asakura,
causing a power cut in Fujiura Town.
Hey! Don't say something imprudent!
But it's true!
The fire will be put out very
quickly, so please don't worry.
That's all right, then.
Okay, let's introduce our crew.
This is Goro, his dream is to become
a charismatic barber.
And this is Shohei, who loves
his polka dots pajamas.
- You do?
- I haven't got any.
But I saw you wearing them!
- What? You saw that?
- Hey.
You're going to get laughed at if
you upload it to the internet.
Well, I doubt it.
Okay, everyone! Don't miss the show.
Here it is...
Another fire engine is here.
You see? See? See?
My prophecy came true!
What?
- Polka dots...
- Here he is.
- That's a pair polka dots pajamas!
- No, this...
- My mom bought it today,
- What?
I couldn't refuse her,
so I'm wearing it...
No, seriously...
"A miraculous prophecy idol, Mihane"
"3,539,304 views"
Amazing!
"12,431,502 views"
A video of prophecy uploaded by
a Japanese high school student
has gone viral.
The first video uploaded predicted a
small fire that occurred
at 8 p.m. on the same day at Fujiura
Central Electrical substation
in Shizuoka Prefecture.
The time, the place and the details
in all the prophecies are correct...
In the hostage case occurred from
9 p.m. to dawn on the same day
in a junior high school in
Wisconsin,
the suspect arrested was a man of
Southern Ireland descent...
Prophecy videos uploaded by the
Miraculous Prophecy Idol, Mihane...
"8th July"
I have become super famous!
My life is more enjoyable now!
I think you should stop.
You mean I should do more?
I hope the efforts the girl makes
will pay off someday.
You're saying it like
I make no effort whatsoever.
Do you?
I just don't do it in front of you.
You worked really hard before you
quitted the boat club.
What else could I have done?
I hurt my back.
Then you joined
the photography club, right?
Doesn't it interest you?
Do you seriously want to be famous?
It seems to me that
you don't know what you want,
so you just give up
and try to have fun.
What do you know, Goro?
Wow, it's Mihane!
She's so cute!
Do your best! We're rooting for you!
What are you doing in the Star
Festival tomorrow?
You'll go, right?
I don't think it's possible.
My fans will all go there.
Mihane! Goro!
Hello...
- Hello...
- Mihane,
I'll control the bow of the boat
in the contest.
- I'll succeed the Mihane Spirit!
- We'll do our best!
- Good luck, girls...
- Thank you...
- Good luck with your work!
- Please come to see the contest!
Good luck.
The girl has leapt through time,
no doubt.
Yeah, so what do you want to do?
We can only watch.
Now you're angry with me?
Whose fault is this to begin with?
The world might descend into chaos.
The potion will lose its effect
soon.
You're very famous in our class,
too.
You finally respect me?
I've always thought that
you're gifted.
Give me your autograph.
Do it!
Go and swim!
Onishi!
Swim now!
Come on, swim!
Go and swim now, we're filming you!
Go! Do a backstroke!
We're filming, look!
We'll upload it!
Just leave them.
Let's go.
Hey! Stop bullying her!
I've called the police!
The police?
Let's go.
The police...
How boring.
Onishi...
Are you okay?
"9th July"
Mihane!
The police is here.
The police?
Miss Mihane Yoshiyama?
Yes.
We'd like to ask you something about
the small fire occurred on 7th July.
What were you doing here?
I thought there should be
a fire soon.
Why do you know
when it was going to happen?
Well...
I can't tell you.
- You set it on fire, didn't you?
- No, I didn't!
Come on, tell us the truth.
If I tell you the truth,
will you believe me?
I...
I can leap through time.
Don't look down on adults!
It's about time for you
to tell us the truth.
I can leap through time.
Hey,
- just tell us...
- I can leap through time.
It's the fireworks?
The town is holding
the Star Festival event now.
I guess I'm really...
...not cut out to be an idol.
We'll start filming now.
"6th July"
Five seconds to go.
Four, three, two...
It didn't occur to me that
I would find a giant oarfish.
Something horrible might happen,
and this could be a sign.
Wow, she's on the news program that
is broadcasted to the whole nation.
I'm happy to be
a normal high school student.
I can't use something that is going
to cause a big fuss.
- I've finished breakfast.
- Okay.
Mihane, the ice-cream in
the freezer is mine...
What? You're eating it?
Don't worry, I'll put it back later.
Gosh, you're horrible!
Mom, get this jerk to swallow
a thousand needles!
Naho, don't use the word, "jerk".
See you.
Come on, Mihane, go get dressed.
- I'll sleep for a bit more.
- What?
But you've never taken a day off
since kindergarten.
Don't worry, I'm still not going
to take a day off.
What?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
"9th July"
Sorry.
I think Shohei is busy,
so he can't come.
What?
What a shame!
It could be the last time
we come together.
Let's enjoy it for him, then.
Anyway, I'm wearing my yukata,
and you haven't said anything.
You're really...
...cute.
You sound like I made you say it.
You really have to look at
the fireworks at a close distance.
Octopus.
One more.
When are you going to be able
to eat your octopus?
The shell is the delicious part.
I'm happy that I can go to festivals
as an ordinary high school student.
That's what girls who
became idols say.
But I did.
I was a world famous idol.
Wow. In your dreams.
Be grateful!
You could come to a boring festival
in the countryside with me.
Well, thank you.
Sure.
By the way,
will you be my wife?
- Idiot.
- No.
Seriously,
can you be my girlfriend?
What?
You can't?
Goro, you look so funny
when you get serious.
I am serious.
Please be my girlfriend.
It's hot!
Sorry.
I think Shohei is busy,
so he can't come.
Oh, is he?
You yukata is cute.
I mean, you look cute
in your yukata.
Thanks.
What's the matter?
You're acting weird.
No...No, I'm not.
We used to hold hands like this,
so that we wouldn't get separated.
Takoyaki!
You can eat your octopus now?
I would've eaten it for you.
Well, I'm 18 years old now.
- Goro, octopus...
- Will you try dating?
I mean the two of us.
We were talking about octopus,
why ask that out of the blue?
Tonight, I have been...
...waiting for the right time
to ask you.
Mihane, I...
I love you.
I love you!
I said, I love you!
Sorry.
- I think Shohei is busy and he...
- I don't want a boyfriend now!
Why say that out of the blue?
Okay.
Let's go to see the fireworks.
I...
I want you to be my girlfriend.
I love you.
Ouch!
Why didn't you come to the festival?
"8th July"
I didn't come?
But the festival is tomorrow.
Yeah, it is...
It's tomorrow.
Tomorrow!
You won't come to the festival
because you're busy!
If you don't, Goro...
Anyway, I'll be in trouble!
Okay...
Come to the festival with us!
Please.
But Goro told me that we're not
going to the festival...
That's what happened...
I mean...
Goro...
...is in love with me.
In love?
We've always been close,
and I treasure the friendship
between us now.
Love...
What does it feel like?
I mean "being in love".
I heard that such thing existed
in the past,
I mean, I've heard of it...
Oh, I'm sorry...
Not in the past, I mean, nowadays.
So...
What does it feel like?
Being in love.
I've been seeking advice from
the wrong person...
Anyway!
Make sure that you come
to the festival!
Remember!
In love...
Wow, it's so good!
By the way, mom,
have you ever been in love?
- Why ask me out of the blue?
- Well...
I'm just wondering whether
I'm able to fall in love or not.
I mean, you can't take for granted
that you can fall in love.
Like 500 years ago from now,
in the Sengoku period, when people
marry for political reasons,
in the future 100 years later,
love between men and women
does not exist.
You're allotted a partner based on
how good your DNA match.
Everybody can fall in love.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Just find your love
in your own time.
I see...
"The Ultimate Manual of Love
for Beginners"
Every single one of them
are horrible!
The match-making party
didn't go well again?
Well, I was popular,
but all the guys were too shy.
If they had approached me
more passionately,
I would have fallen in love
with them right away.
- Welcome!
- Hello.
Miss Maekawa?
Mr. Yano?
- You come to dine here, too?
- Yeah, from time to time.
Why do you sit so far away from
each other? You don't get along?
I...
Would you mind if I sit next to you?
No...Be my guest.
- What would you like to drink?
- Beer, please.
- Sure.
- A glass of beer!
- Please...please try some.
- Oh, thank you.
Help her out in a difficult
situation and she'll fall in love.
Help her out in a
difficult situation...
Fall in love?
"9th July"
Okay...
Sorry.
I think Shohei is busy
and he can't come.
- He said he's free now.
- What?
Wow, this shaved ice is so good!
Oh, my god!
It could be the last time,
I'm glad that
we can all go together.
It's so good.
It's really good.
Just because I can now
leap through time,
I just can't get myself to
just try and date him.
My first boyfriend...
My first love...
I want it to be something
that definitely can't be repeated.
- You're blocking me...
- Okay, I'll take the photo.
- Ready?
- Yes!
Okay.
Okay...
- Have you got it?
- Have you taken it?
- Have you?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Really?
She is so late...
That's why I said I'd go to buy it.
The frozen pineapple is so good!
Really?
It's so scary...
It's so good that it's scary!
The frozen pineapple is so good!
Thank you.
- Thanks for coming.
- Thank you.
Fried noodles...
What?
Someone is injured! Call for help!
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
Hey!
Someone, help!
Are you okay?
Shohei!
Hey!
No!
Shohei!
It's so scary...
It's so good that it's scary!
Watch out!
Shohei!
What are you doing?
My pineapple...
What a relief!
I'm glad that you're okay...
I'm not okay at all! My pineapple!
What's wrong?
The lanterns collapsed
and then fell on top of Shohei.
It was really horrible.
It's true...
That was a close call...
We'll change the rope.
Get me a new one.
Okay.
I thought you were dead.
I thought I couldn't save you.
So I'm relieved now...
I'm so glad to see you alive.
Why are you crying?
I was worried!
You idiot...
- Don't laugh!
- You're crying too much.
Don't laugh!
- It's because you're crying.
- No, I'm not.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
The Frankfurter is too good.
Anyway, why is it called
a Frankfurter?
Look it up on the internet.
What has it got to
do with the place?
I don't know.
It's so good.
I'll see you home.
I'm going to shout at Shohei,
- so I'll go with Shohei.
- What? Hang on.
You're still angry?
- I have no idea.
- See you tomorrow.
I mean, on Monday.
Bye bye bi.
Goro.
See me home, please! Goro!
So...
Why do you have to shout at me?
I lied.
I can't be with Goro alone tonight.
Because he'll confess his love?
I'm horrible, am I not?
I'm not sure,
but she must have turn back time
and saved my life.
She looked weird when she cried,
but...
I was happy.
Sorry.
I had once been chased by two dogs.
They kept chasing only me...
Go away!
...and I was really frightened.
Are you okay, Mihane?
Mihane, it's okay now.
At that time...
Goro saved my life
with all his might.
No.
I did.
Shohei...
...saved you with all his might.
At that time...
Shohei saved my life
with all his might.
It brings back memories.
Yeah.
- Hey!
- Cut it out!
How do you explain this text?
Don't check my mobile
without asking.
You're horrible!
Ouch!
Two more people fell out of love
in this world.
If you fall in love,
it will end like that someday.
So I'm scared.
About Goro?
I want to be great friends with him
forever.
When was the last time
we talked so much like this?
I can't remember.
But I'm glad that
we've talked so much.
See you.
Your yukata is cool.
Good night.
Mihane, five more minutes.
- Five minutes.
- Five minutes?
Good morning...
In the time when I cannot go back,
Oh?
There is...
...summer, and love.
It's all your fault.
Please make the potion now.
I want to go to meet the person
with my power.
I wonder if the girl was in love.
I think I can convey her love
with my photos.
Do you want to try to kiss?