One, two...
I used to play soccer until
I was in middle school...
One, two...
But I joined the boat club
in high school.
One, two...
One, two. Once more! One, two...
Guys, put out a last spurt!
In my last competition,
I just couldn't cry.
Why is that?
It sounds dubious
if I say this myself,
but I have quite a lot of friends.
But none of them know
how lame I am.
When I had to choose my high school,
my middle school's class teacher
recommended a private one to me,
my parents had high hopes that
I might be accepted, too,
but I chose the public school,
Higashi High School.
- It's this month's payment.
- Okay.
My parents thought that I was
worried about the school fee.
But no...
Good morning!
- Good morning.
- Gosh...
I wanted to go to the same school
with Mihane.
The reason I joined the boat club,
too...
But Mihane hurt her back
and quitted in her second year.
The reason that I couldn't cry...
This could be why.
I don't remember when I started
to develop a crush on Mihane.
- Hold Mihane's head up.
- Okay.
Maybe since I was jealous of
even the pair of scissors?
My dream is to become
a pair of scissors.
He wants to be a pair of scissors!
I was so jealous of the pair of
scissors that cut Mihane's hair.
Come to think of it,
I was a pervert.
Bye bye bi.
I made up my mind to confess my love
for her in the Star Festival event,
but my plan failed.
You're in love with Mihane,
aren't you?
What?
Shohei knows that
I'm in love with Mihane...
Is it okay for two people to
fall in love with the same person?
What kind of question is that?
And he declared that
he would fight for her with me.
Hey, are you serious?
I don't...
- You almost got it...
- Hang on, I'll get it.
...want to have Mihane
stolen from me by Shohei.
Oh, no! It's sinking!
What are you doing?
Mihane looked even more adorable
than usual.
Stupid Shohei...
How rude of him to suddenly kiss me!
Anyway, that's not the point!
I wanted to shout at him,
but I couldn't tell Goro, who didn't
see that.
I thought about doing a time-leap,
but I was hesitant to do so.
It was kind of my first kiss,
so I don't know whether I should
just pretend that it didn't happen.
It won't be gone from my own memory.
Why can you sleep without
worrying about it?
It's annoying to see that!
Mihane did not leap through time.
Does it mean she didn't hate it?
I think I'm more and more
in love with her.
Oh, excuse me...
Hey! We're having a lesson!
A transfer student?
Nobody told me about it.
Okay, let's continue our lesson.
What are you doing here?
It was you who told me to enjoy
our time in this era!
Fukamachi, Aihara, raise your hands
if you've got any question.
Yes, sir!
Oops, I haven't got any.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time
Episode 3"
Oh?
I thought Goro was cutting my hair.
Who is Goro?
Oh, come on. It's the friend I grew
up with, Goro Asakura.
The son of Barber Asakura's owner.
Don't feign ignorance.
Do you really not know him?
Where has Shohei gone?
- Mihane.
- What?
- Mihane!
- Yes?
- No...No!
Mihane!
Wake up! It's time for supper.
I've grilled some meat.
Mihane, we're having steak.
Wow, thank you!
It looks delicious! Thanks, mom.
Bon appetit.
We only need three more ingredients
to make the potion.
I can finally return to the
22nd Century!
Yeah, it will be really soon.
Anyway, "the school"? Why do you
enjoy going to school so much?
"Lessons" are too inefficient!
I mean, everything is written
on the textbook,
why do they copy the text out on a
blackboard
and tell the students to
write it on their notebooks?
This is pointless.
You third year students will have
your college entry exam,
so you don't have to work too hard
for this,
but what is our class performing
in this festival?
The Garyosai Festival.
Will you do anything in your last
school festival?
Well, I guess the first and second
year students
will do most of them,
but I think it's not a bad thing.
It will become a fond memory.
Perhaps a singing performance?
Why don't you do it as a break from
your revision, Tamotsu Hase?
I have to go to cram school
after school.
Mana Tabuchi, you're in
the dance club.
Perhaps you can perform Para Para?
I have to compete in the national
competition soon.
Anyway, what is Para Para?
You don't know what Para Para is?
It's like this.
You don't know this dance?
Then...I guess our class
won't participate in the festival.
"60th Garyosai Festival,
Fujiura Higashi High School"
The class performances
will start soon!
Wow, look at the dance!
Isn't it awesome?
Isn't it amazing?
Only Class 2 of the third year
did a performance.
They are united.
Is that Internet Idol, Onishi,
popular?
She has 200 thousand followers.
200 thousand!
She'll make her major debut soon,
so the whole class is rooting for
Atsumi Onishi.
200 hundred...
Atsumi...
This is the end
of the first school term,
and your summer holiday
begins tomorrow,
but be very careful not to do
something too reckless
and bear in mind that you should be
responsible for whatever you do.
Students in their third year should
get down to work and study
for their
university entrance exam...
Summer holiday begins tomorrow,
but we have to attend extra lessons.
It doesn't feel like
summer holiday at all.
I wish we had done
the class performance.
In the Garyosai Festival?
I wanted to do a performance,
actually.
It didn't feel right to voice that.
I wanted to do a performance, too.
What? You, too?
I don't think we can do it
ever again,
and it's our youth.
Actually, I wanted to perform, too!
What?
- Let's do it.
- What? The festival was held.
- Oh!
- You got it.
Come on...
You want us to do a time-leap?
Yes...
I definitely think that
we should do a class performance.
Let's do it.
But will our classmates agree
to do it?
They will, if we can persuade them.
We will help you, too.
- Please...
- Please!
Please...
This.
The Garyosai Festival.
- What?
- Oh, my god...
Guys, let's do a class performance!
It's the last time in high school,
let's do it together!
Hey, Goro, Shohei,
help me persuade them..
Hang on.
I don't want to perform
in front of so many people.
But actually you want to do it,
don't you?
No, not really...
You traitors!
Wait...
Don't be so forceful!
You said you would help me!
But that's what our future selves
said a few days later.
Our present selves
have never heard it.
We said we would persuade our
classmate and do the performance!
But it was difficult to do so
at that time.
But you said you could!
Did I say that?
You did, in the future!
That means, you didn't. Not yet.
The point isn't whether
he said it or not!
You'll regret it if you don't do it!
Got it?
I think this will become a fond
memory for our whole class,
so we'll definitely do
a successful performance.
I will do something about it.
You don't want to?
We don't know what we're going to
do, so it's hard to answer that.
Well, we haven't decided it yet.
What about Para Para? Look.
We don't want our performance
to be a failure.
Here?
- Hase, you're right.
- Well.
Class, you really don't know
what Para Para is?
Let's perform Para Para!
There...you go...
Watermelon!
You like watermelon?
It's so much more than "like".
I had it for the first time the
other day and I got addicted.
You had it for the first time
the other day, huh?
We might sing together
or do a dance performance...
But some people might not want to
perform in front of people...
I think we should let them
work backstage.
Oh...
Why are you eating watermelon alone?
- Would you have some with me?
- No, I won't!
That's not the point!
Think and come up with some idea!
- Watermelon burst.
- Forget your watermelon!
It must be hard to get someone to
work when they don't want to.
But if only a part of people are
excited about it,
doesn't it make you feel lonely?
If we're doing it, I want us to
create a great memory together.
I am exactly the kind of person who
doesn't like doing things together.
What? I'm surprised.
The cool guys would enjoy events
held at school,
and I used to think that it was
boring for some reason.
But when I look at you, I think
maybe I shouldn't have thought that.
We used to strongly refuse to
participate in the school's events,
so perhaps they used to think hard
to come up with ways
to get us to participate
and enjoy the events.
Hey, Yuri, perhaps you can go
and participate too.
Oh, I would love to!
Do I look like a high school girl?
No, you don't look like one at all.
Keita!
It must be difficult for
the three of them.
They have to perform soon, right?
I don't mean the preparation,
I mean their love triangle.
Is that so? Shohei, too?
Well, Mihane is cute.
Let's do a play!
A play?
It's the most difficult performance
of all...
What's the title?
Romeo and Juliet.
I know you're worried,
but when I was thinking
what the whole class can participate
and enjoy,
it's a surprisingly good idea.
Some people can work backstage,
and we need people to make the
props, costumes and backdrops,
so I think you can all do
what you're good at.
You don't want to do it?
Sorry!
I want to play Romeo,
no matter what.
I'm really sorry for dragging you
guys into this.
But I really hope that you'd help to
make my selfish wish come true.
Thanks in advance!
Goro! Why did you say that? You want
to make my efforts go in vain?
Well, I guess we have to,
if Asakura asks for our help.
- What?
- Indeed.
I have to participate in a
competition soon,
so I don't know how much I can do...
It's okay, just do as much
as you can.
I'll help you with whatever
I can, too.
- Good.
- Me, too!
Thanks!
Now everyone of us will participate?
Good!
Why are you not happy?
We could've started sooner if you'd
persuaded them at the beginning!
You see how much other classmates
like you, stupid nice guy.
You're angry?
Was it a compliment?
You're so annoying!
I'm depressed...I'm so depressed.
Come on...
Everyone wants to do it now,
so isn't it great?
Please say it if you want to
play a certain role.
I want to make the costumes.
- Costumes?
- I'll do that with her.
Would you like to do
the choreography?
Sure, but I'm a strict teacher.
What...I'll make the props?
Goro will be Romeo, right?
I think Shohei will make
a good Laurence.
What?
- I'd like to see that.
- Why not?
I'll do that?
Now, Juliet's Nurse...
Me!
I'll play Juliet's Nurse.
You sure it's okay
for a man to play her?
Why not? It's new!
- I think it will be funny!
- Indeed!
Okay, thank you, Mr. Yano!
Thank you!
Those who haven't gotten a role
are Mihane
and Aihara.
One of them will be Juliet and the
other will do the backdrop.
Well, I'm the one who suggested
playing Romeo and Juliet,
so I'll do whatever that is left.
Aihara, please choose one.
- I'll be Juliet.
- What?
I'm very sorry...
So, we're all set?
We're all set!
Are you happy to work backstage?
Lovely. Thank you!
Juliet?
Why are you Juliet?
The name in that line
should be Romeo.
It wasn't the line!
I mean your role!
Oh, my role.
Are you really doing it?
But if I have to make the backdrop,
I'll have to draw pictures, right?
I don't like to get my hands dirty,
so it's impossible.
So you'll play the heroine?
It's better than making
my hands dirty.
What? "Better"?
You shouldn't choose to play the
heroine because it's "better"...
What? Where has Shohei gone?
No idea.
What?
I'll go and look for Shohei.
Please go and return the key.
Not here.
There he is.
Oh? Where is Shohei?
- He was busy.
- What?
Never mind. Let's go!
Why are you angry?
Sorry, I was late...
They left without me...
I'm home.
Welcome home. We have a visitor.
He says he would like to
talk to you.
Welcome home.
What?
Are you in love with Mihane?
Well...
Yeah.
Give it up, then.
What?
Which year were you born in?
Why ask that out of the blue?
You're not from this era, right?
Just like you,
I came from the future.
Go back at once.
What are you doing in this era?
I lost my potion,
so I can't go back.
What?
What a fool...
What are you going to do?
I've extracted the necessary
ingredients
and I'm making the potion again
from scratch.
You're a researcher?
I should be the one asking
what are you doing here.
I'm living here with my family.
I decided to stay in this era.
It's not about me.
Anyway, give up on starting
a relationship with Mihane.
I'm asking you why I should.
You should not fall in love with
a girl from a different era.
You have the guts to say that?
You have your own family here.
I have warned you.
Give up that idea.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
Aihara will play Juliet.
Who is Aihara?
Why isn't it Mihane?
I wish Mihane would play Juliet!
Exactly!
Can't you do something about it?
No, I can't.
Why didn't you tell Mihane to do it?
Exactly!
Welcome...
Hello.
- The gown, please.
- Okay.
- It's lovely.
- Yeah, I think so.
Ow...
- Which one?
- This one.
Are you okay, Hase?
Why did you kill my friend?
Now, change positions!
Hatakeda, get more serious.
Juliet took the potion and it
wrought on her the form of death.
She was actually alive...
Alas...
Alas!
Five more days to go!
- Which way is it? This?
- This way.
- One more spin?
- Then turn...
This way.
Four more days to go!
Wait...Hang on...
Excuse me.
We'll measure his shoulders' width.
His shoulders are 51 centimeters
wide...
Not yet...We're not done with you.
- Do you have to do it now?
- Yes.
Three more days to go!
Fly in the sky with
your wings of love!
Okay!
Your soft lips...
- cannot say my name again...
- Done! Hey...
Try it on.
It's torn!
Sorry.
Romeo isn't the only man in this
world, Madam.
Two more days to go.
Let's work for a while more.
One more day to go!
Would you dance with me?
I'm sorry!
Okay...
I'm sorry...
What?
Drink this distilled liquor.
In this borrowed...
Didn't it break too easily?
Romeo, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Romeo!
She's horrible.
Can she not speak properly?
Romeo!
What's the next line?
"He thought I was really dead."
- He thought I was really dead.
- Okay...
Stab the knife in your chest.
You are ridiculous!
- "Stab the knife in..."
- No...
Thank you all for your efforts.
We'll finally do our play tomorrow.
Well, I think we're all worried
about many things...
"Many things"?
Just "many things"?
If just one person
doesn't want to do this,
everything we've done
will be in vain.
Hey! I'm talking about you!
I don't blame you for your bad
acting, but at least be serious!
- But I am.
- We can't feel that at all!
The national competition
will be held soon,
and I should be putting my efforts
on that!
But I want to do it well
if I am doing it.
It just annoys me
when you don't even care.
Well!
We didn't have much time
to rehearse,
and the heroine has to remember
a lot of lines.
Fix the props that you broke.
And why do I have to make the props
to begin with?
What? Hase, you actually wanted
to play a role?
I should have volunteered to
play Juliet.
It would be funny, at least.
- Yeah, indeed, it would be.
- Well, yeah.
I'll quit.
- Aihara!
- Hang on.
I did work hard for my part.
I stayed awake at night to practice
and that was the best I can do!
Though I have done my best, you
still said I didn't seem to have.
I actually can't do this.
Sorry for being self-assertive.
Wait, Aihara, I'll teach you
how to act.
That's why I told you
not to do this...
What should we do?
- It's tomorrow.
- Will it be okay?
Hase!
Are you really playing Juliet?
Wait...We'll do the play tomorrow.
It's impossible.
If it's not tomorrow,
- you'll say yes?
- What?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
What...
We'll return to the time
we assign the roles!
It's too much of a trouble to
explain to him, so come with me!
Come with you? How?
I held a turtle in my hand when I
did a time-leap for the first time.
If the turtle could do it with me...
What? But human and turtle
are different.
Just shut up and close your eyes.
Think strongly back to the time
we assign the roles.
What's the matter?
Seriously?
What the heck?
It was amazing!
Let's correct this.
Though we've assigned most of
the roles, I'm very sorry!
I have a suggestion now.
Isn't it more interesting to let a
guy play Juliet?
That's what I thought, too.
Well said, Hase!
Then will you be Juliet?
What...Why should I play Juliet?
Hase, you actually want to
play a role, right?
No, I don't.
Really?
Why do you ask me that?
That role shouldn't be played by me.
I want to make props!
That's not what you said.
Why don't you play Juliet, Shohei?
No, I mean, Julio.
What...Me?
Asakura and Fukamachi playing
Romeo and Juliet...
Gosh, it's erotic.
What are you fantasizing?
Indeed! It's a good idea!
What?
Then who will play Lawrence?
Well, I'll play him.
Good!
The person who hasn't got a part...
Aihara.
Will you make the backdrop?
I have to make it, haven't I?
Fine!
I'll do it...
Let's give it our best.
This is the best I can do...
I'm sorry...
I thought you said
you were not good at this?
I just said I hate to
get my hands dirty.
Whoa! It's so dirty!
Thank you for
the wonderful backdrop!
Thank you so much!
I'm glad that you're happy!
- I'm so impressed!
- Amazing!
She is the best artist!
"Lesson five."
"Shout out your love boldly..."
No way...
Shohei, dinner is ready!
Coming!
I tried to make dishes
with watermelon.
Wow...
Bon appetit...
- Yummy!
- Glad to hear that.
Watermelon?
Watermelon.
Wherefore art thou watermelon?
The forbidden love?
When we are forced to be apart,
it makes me love you more.
It's the Romeo and Juliet effect,
right?
Such effect exists?
When there is an obstacle,
you'd want to overcome it and you
get more passionate.
Just overcome it.
Obstacle is nothing
in front of the power of love.
Yes, indeed.
Drink this distilled liquor.
In this borrowed likeness of shrunk
death, you shall continue two days.
If I can be with Romeo,
I will do anything.
You have made up your mind?
Yes.
Your soft lips cannot say
my name again.
My only love...
The love between you
will certainly defuse the conflict.
I shall go to the peaceful kingdom,
where you are waiting.
I shall come to you!
When I learned of this...
it was already too late.
Please trust your beloved
and be persistent in your love.
It's today!
"60th Garyosai Festival,
Fujiura Higashi High School"
- Okay!
- Ready...
A bit to the left.
We now only have to fully enjoy
ourselves and let's make it work!
Third year, Class 6.
Let's give it our best!
I am Julio!
I'm madly in love with Romeo!
Madam Julio!
It's time to do the Para Para dance
in the morning.
Now, cheer up!
Madam!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Because my grandfather...
...named me Romeo.
My family are fans of Giants,
but your family are fans of Hanshin!
So please, I beg you,
stop being a fan of
the Hanshin Tigers!
Asakura, hurry!
Nobody told me the girls would help
me change! Get the guys here!
You do it...It's embarrassing!
Why?
Why did you kill my friend?
Why do I need a reason?
- Darn you, Tybalt!
- Romeo!
You can feign your death
after drinking this potion!
So I'll just drink this
and make myself dead, right?
Yes.
Please remember to take the right
dose properly.
Thank you, Lawrence!
Good luck.
Thank you, Lawrence...
Everything went as planned.
It'll be perfect if the last scene
goes all right.
Julio!
Why?
Why did you leave without me?
Julio!
What...
It's that basketball.
What should we do, Mihane?
Anyway, we have to help Goro...
Oh, no!
Oh, no...
Oh, my god!
This is really bad...
Why is Romeo dead?
I won't forgive you for dying alone!
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
"Garyosai Festival"
"Rubbish"
Sorry.
Sorry for making you guys worried.
Are you okay?
I thought I was going to die.
But I'm totally fine now.
Guys, I'm really sorry.
Glad to hear that...
What do you want to do?
Do you want to do it again
and correct it?
Yeah, before the show starts,
I'll tell Goro about the basketball.
This time, I have to make the play
a successful one!
Okay.
Let's go back.
Asakura looked so funny
the moment he passed out, though.
Yeah, but Shohei's last pose
was fantastic, too.
The audience laughed so hard
and we got a standing ovation.
And the moment when the painting
Aihara worked so hard on broke,
I saw it in slow motion.
Yeah, same here...
It broke because I tripped
on something.
I am very sorry!
But it ended in a climax that was
more excited than the original one.
Well said, Hase!
I guess it's not necessary
to go back and make it perfect.
Everyone here is smiling happily.
I enjoyed it a lot.
I don't want to change it.
It ended in an unexpected way,
but I think we've all enjoyed
our last Garyosai Festival,
and I'm really touched!
Now...
Let's toast to
our miraculous failure.
Cheers!
Cheers...
Thank you!
Oh, sorry...
Okay, say cheese!
You're close...
Fantastic!
I'm glad that we did the
performance.
Youth is worthless
if without failure.
I can say that now.
Failure is fantastic.
Failing is fantastic!
Failing is fantastic...
Hase!
Well done, Hase!
Go!
Fantastic!
Failing is fantastic...
Okay!
I'd like to take this opportunity
to say something.
Mihane Yoshiyama!
You do everything
with all your might,
and I love you for that.
He loves her?
I love you!
What...
Please...
Be my Juliet.
Juliet...
Juli...
Kiss her...
"Okonomiyaki, Ribon"
I love the way you acted, Mr. Yano!
I'm just a radish.
I absolutely love dishes made
with radish!
Oh, do you?
Okay...
If you don't mind,
would you give me a personal lesson
and teach me how to act?
- Please!
- Another glass of beer, please!
Don't be so mean! Please!
Just teach me a bit!
- Mr. Miura?
- Just for a bit...
Is he too shy?
Mr. Miura!
- Mr. Miura, are you okay?
- Mr. Miura!
- Please call an ambulance!
- Okay.
Mr. Miura...
Hang in there, Mr. Miura!
Oh?
I can't find any photo of Shohei.
"Class trip in Okinawa"
"We're always close! And always in
the same class, too!"
Why?
Shohei isn't here.
I'm happy that you confessed
your love.
Will our romance end when she knows
my real identity?
Why don't you have photos
of your childhood?
Why can't I live my life
the way I want?
- Goro...
- Goro!
I was in love with you, too!
Break up with Mihane and go back.
It's for your sake.
I'm tired of being Goro Asakura.
What is "the real you"?
I don't want to be left alone again.
I won't leave you on your own.
I want to be with you no matter
what, Mihane.