What...Hey, what are you...
Come on!
You're heavy!
Let's go picnic...Picnic...
Why?
I want to go to an amusement park.
The three of us will go together,
right?
Just you and me.
Why? What about Shohei? The three of
us are always together.
We won't tell him.
We'll have more fun without him.
Somehow you sound weird.
We are a couple now...
What?
Mihane Yoshiyama!
You do everything
with all your might,
and I love you for that.
I love you!
Please be my Juliet.
Please don't escape from
this moment.
I want a romance
that won't disappear.
If she knows who I am,
will our love end, too?
I have rewritten her memory...
...in a way that will give me
an advantage.
You look like a Kokeshi doll.
Kokeshi doll?
No, Shohei rescued you
with all his might.
Shohei rescued me
The holes in our love
are filled with lies...
It won't become real, will it?
What are you doing?
You've slept too much.
Going on a picnic is nice,
but going to an amusement park
is nice, too.
Let's start our day from
the morning again.
What? Are you sure?
Sure.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time
Episode 4"
It's an amusement park! Wow!
Let's go for a ride
on the roller coaster!
What is that?
What? You don't know what
roller coaster is?
I've never been to an amusement park
before.
You've missed out a lot
in your life!
- You're joking!
- Let's go.
You'll learn about the conjunction,
so that, today.
We'll start from doing a translation
of a sentence.
"The water was so cold."
It means...
Wow!
What?
I won't let you off.
Please get on the roller coaster.
Okay!
The roller coaster ride
will begin soon.
- Get on your way to heaven!
- See you!
Saying that brings bad luck!
No!
- Idiot! Idiot!
- It's going down!
I can't stand it!
Ride again!
- Ride again!
- No way...Seriously, no way!
Mom!
My DNA tells me that
I can't do this!
- We'll take another ride...
- Spare my life, please...
Encore...
I guess we should get off
the roller coaster.
Yeah?
- It's so good!
- Yummy!
They didn't notice us, right?
No.
But that's what youth should be.
You're staring for too long.
I'm full now...
- Ouch!
- What?
They fell at the same time.
You're too loud.
Bon appetit...
It looks delicious!
They suddenly fell...
They'll see us!
Hamburger, aha...
Hamburger, oh, yeah...
Can you see which part of the
sentence is defined
by the relative pronoun, who?
If you look at the verb here...
That cloud looks like a lion.
It's a safari in the sky.
Look! That's a fat kangaroo, right?
To its left, it's either
an elephant's nose...
Oh! The polar bear is
standing on its hands!
"Barber Asakura"
Welcome home!
We've been talking about you.
You might be accepted by
the medical school, I heard.
I just got lucky in the mock exam.
When you become a doctor,
please marry Mihane.
We're all very happy to have Mihane
as one of our family.
We'll dye your white hair for free
when they get married.
Really?
My daughter isn't the most
well-mannered,
but please take care of her.
What? You'll give us your daughter
for free hair coloring services?
Wow, you're horrible!
Well, Mihane is sitting her
university entrance exam, too,
but she's going to the amusement
park with her friend today.
Wow, she is confident.
No, I don't think she can be.
You can't really go out so carefree
at a time like this...
"University Entrance Exam 2017"
Welcome.
The usual haircut?
Okay.
You look lovely.
I wanted to make you beautiful,
but...
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Go and do your revision. I'll tell
you when supper is ready.
Oops, I forgot the natto.
Gosh...
I don't want to sit for the exam.
What?
So I won't go to medical school.
I won't go to college, too.
Darling...
Darling!
Okay...Welcome...
Oh? Where is the customer?
Goro said that he wouldn't go to sit
for the university entrance exam.
What?
What are you going to do
if you're not go to a university?
I'll do what I want to do.
What you want to do?
You don't mean you want to succeed
this shop, do you?
Give up the idea.
You're not cut out for it.
Don't just assume that.
There is no future for you
if you stay here.
You have to think properly
about your future.
- I am doing it.
- Why?
You're worrying about the fee?
No, I'm not...
I just don't want to do it.
Don't just think about
what you want.
Why do you want to succeed
the shop so desperately?
It has always been my dream.
What kind of dream is that?
Don't decide your future by
unrealistic things
like motivation and dreams.
Face your own ability!
Gosh...
It's a shame that my parents can't
even help me to pursue my dream.
It's a real shame.
Then, what?
Parents have to be affirmative about
their children's every single dream?
I don't think so.
Don't mistake your impulse
for your dream.
Okay, I'll ask you.
Are you going to ignore your mom's
and my expectation for you?
- Darling...
- Gosh, you're so annoying.
It's my own life, why can't I do
what I want to?
Don't decide it for me!
Your expectation is nothing
but a nuisance.
Darn you!
You really want to become a barber,
don't you?
I've been saying it
for my whole life.
Fine!
But I won't let you succeed
this shop.
If you want to be a barber,
go somewhere and be one.
Fine.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
The paella is gorgeous!
- It's so good!
- Yummy!
I put a lot of effort in it
and I have been making them
since yesterday.
Since yesterday? Oh, thank you!
You're welcome. I love having people
eat the dishes I make.
It's so good! Hang on, what is this?
I wrapped pieces of apple with pork.
Is that a film camera?
Yes, it is.
It is really good.
- Can I take some photos?
- Of course!
Okay.
You don't really see cameras like
that now.
No, you don't...
That reminds me. I haven't got a
single photo of Shohei at home.
We've been growing up together,
so I can't help but wonder.
Shohei's childhood photos...
I wonder if we have any at home...
What? You must have some, right?
Like photo albums.
I think so...Oh, hang on, mom!
Hey, Shohei,
why haven't you got
any childhood photos?
Hey, this is really delicious.
What is it?
I wrapped pieces of apple with pork.
But...Why do you wrap pieces of
apple with pork?
Mihane, it's ringing.
There you go.
- Hello?
- Mihane?
Are you with Goro now?
Goro? No, I'm not.
I'll let Goro's mom speak to you.
I'm Mrs. Asakura.
Sorry for calling all of a sudden.
Goro hasn't come home
after he went out.
What? He ran away from home?
Have you called his mobile?
He left it at home.
It's fine if he's okay,
but if there is the slightest chance
that he had an accident...Oh, gosh.
Where would a high school
student go? Manga cafe?
It's summer after all,
maybe he went camping?
- Camping?
- Let me speak to her.
Mihane, will you ask your friends
for us?
Oh, I'm sorry! Good grief!
Goro...
Goro.
Where have you gone?
Seriously?
Thank you very much.
"Okonomiyaki Ribon"
Goro!
Hello? I still haven't found him.
If anything happened to Asakura...
I will die.
If you die, Ojo, it will get
even more complicated.
Goro!
Darn...Seriously?
Where has he gone?
Anyway,
maybe he'd think that he would lose
the fight if he went home too soon.
I guess we have to go back.
To when he ran away from home.
Let's go.
Why?
You look like you're not going to
take me with you.
Oh, it's not what I'm thinking,
but...
But?
I think I'd better go alone.
Why?
I think Goro will not feel
comfortable if you're there, too.
Why? I'm worried about Goro, too.
Hang on.
Does Goro...actually hate me?
Well, that's not...
That's not a problem, then.
Let's go.
His mom said that he left home
at after 7 o'clock, right?
Yeah.
The Star Festival Event? Why?
I got it wrong! We'll do it again.
You have to hang up.
Do hang up this time.
I said, you hang up first, Jun.
Oh, no!
- This is my room!
- Oh, that's...
Oh?
No, it's nothing.
Why?
What? It's a stomach band?
- Once more. One, two...
- Okay.
Why are we here again?
- It's weird!
- You're kidding me!
I can't go back to the
time I wanted to!
- Idiot! Idiot!
- Oh, no!
Oh, my god!
We're back to the bus station
from the amusement park!
He'll run away from home in
15 minutes! Let's go, Shohei!
I can't...I'm too tired!
Run!
Goro will...
Goro!
There he is!
Don't go!
Mihane?
Why?
It's so hot...
Have you leapt through time
to stop me, by any chance?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
Why did you run away from home?
I told them that I don't want to sit
for the university entrance exam.
Then they said that I shouldn't
ignore their expectations for me.
But you've been saying that you want
to be a barber.
My dad said that I'm not cut out for
it, so I should give up.
But you never know!
I'm supportive, though,
of your dream, Goro.
But I'm tired.
I'm tired of being someone who wants
to meet others' expectations.
Just let me do what I want!
That's how I feel now.
Okay!
Let's do it!
Do whatever you want.
Don't hold it back.
Do what you want to do most now
and don't worry about anything.
We'll let loose our emotions
tonight!
Good! Good idea!
This is totally awesome, right?
Well, even if we cause any problem
or do anything,
Mihane will do something.
Yes, I'll do something.
What do you think?
Well, thanks for cheering me up,
but...
You're on your way home after going
to the amusement park, right?
I wish I could take a ride on
the roller coaster, too.
But I'm a third wheel, right?
You should have just left me alone.
I'm here exactly because
I can't leave you alone.
Okay, we'll start from doing
what Mihane wants first!
On the contrary.
Why?
This is the night that Goro Asakura
lets loose his emotions.
I'll think about it.
- So you'll do it first.
- What?
Then...
(Can the two of us lose ourselves
in love?)
- (I love you, ah...)
- Mihane!
(And my friends plan to run away
from home tonight.)
(Anyway, I don't want to go back
to school or home!)
(Grown-ups tell me to throw away
my heart, but I don't want to.)
Let's sing this, guys!
(I ride the motorcycle I stole,)
(without knowing my destination,)
(into the darkness of the night.)
"Okonomiyaki Ribon"
Okay...
Okay, there you go.
- Mr. Miura, is your health okay?
- Yes?
I'm totally fine.
The doctor gave me a thorough check
up, and said it was just fatigue.
Don't stress yourself too much.
So...Did you enjoy your date?
We just went to check out the place
for our school trip.
That reminds me!
We saw something strange.
Our students, Mihane Yoshiyama and
Shohei Fukamachi were on their date.
Those kids...
No, that's not what I said
was strange,
the two of them suddenly fell a bit,
like this.
They acted like nothing happened
and just kept having
their hamburgers.
Isn't it strange?
They fell a bit?
Yes, like this.
They seemed to be used to it
already...
- Cheers. Thanks...
- Thanks...
You don't need a glass?
No, or I'll have to do
more washing-up.
Mihane is staying at Ojo's home.
What? But she will sit for her
university entrance exam...
Okay...
Here we are.
Let's jump!
Oh, my god!
I've always wanted to sneak into a
swimming pool at night!
It's awesome to have it to
ourselves!
I'm so jealous! Guys can swim
in their pants!
Jump in, too, Mihane!
Good, Mihane...
- Wait, I'm a girl.
- What?
- I'm a girl.
- You're a girl?
- Yes, I am!
On your mark...
If I win...
Ready...
- break up...
- I won't lose this.
Go!
You can do it...
- Oh?
- Where are my panties?
Shohei is disqualified!
I'm sorry.
- They really are off?
- Yeah, really. Sorry.
Hey, no! Seriously,
you're doing this?
No, seriously...
No! Hey!
Altair.
Vega.
Deneb.
The Summer Triangle.
The Milky Way is stunning.
The light of the stars
is the light they gave out
a long, long time ago,
and it finally reaches the Earth...
What...what are you...
What are you doing? Hang on...
One, two...
That was a new record!
Oh, my god!
Mihane, this...Shohei suggested
doing this.
Don't be ridiculous!
No, it was Goro!
Well, we can just turn back time.
It's Goro's turn next.
Have you decided what you want
to do?
I want to do something bad.
But sneaking into a swimming pool
at night
is something that a well-behaved
child shouldn't do, too.
Got it?
I want to do...
...something bad.
Okay.
Okay, you can break all the windows.
We only have to turn back time.
It's pointless...
...doing this.
I know what I want to do now.
What is it?
I want to stay in today
for the rest of my life.
We'll keep repeating today.
What do you think?
Isn't it fantastic?
I hope tomorrow will never come.
I don't want it to come.
When people don't expect anything
from me,
I can do whatever I please.
That's what I think.
That's why I have an impulse
to do some bad deeds.
But in the end, I'm not brave enough
to do any bad deed.
Becoming the good boy that
everybody wants
is really boring.
You mean becoming a doctor?
That's what my parents want.
If you don't want to be a doctor,
then don't be one.
You don't exactly don't want
to be a doctor, do you?
It's difficult, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
You know...
I have always wanted to be
a barber, right?
You wanted to be a pair of scissors
at first, though.
What? An object?
It was when I was in kindergarten.
But still! A pair of scissors?
That's too weird.
He was a dangerous boy.
Yes, indeed.
But recently...
I don't know whether my dream
really is becoming a barber or not.
I've been telling my friends and
parents that it was my dream.
I can't help but feel that I can't
throw it away irresponsibly.
Baseball club's Shigemi
has been playing baseball since
Year 1 to Year 12,
but he told me that he didn't know
whether he liked it or not now.
Wow...
And...
I really understand how he felt.
How he felt?
I can do it with all my might,
regardless of if I like it or not.
Both Shigemi and I can.
So if I'm not obsessed with it,
I can't really be persistent, too.
In this era,
it must be hard for you because you
can do everything freely.
You have to find out by yourself
what role you should play among
so many possibilities, after all.
You're saying it like
it doesn't concern you.
People in the future are given
suitable roles in an efficient way.
Wow...
Is it in a movie?
Actually,
Goro takes his work seriously,
he's hard-working,
and most importantly,
he is kind to people.
So I think...
you're cut out to be a doctor.
Goro, I think maybe your parents
didn't tell you to be a doctor
just because you got good results in
the mock exam.
They've been watching you grow up,
that's why they told you
that you should.
Sometimes, people around us know us
better than ourselves...
...surprisingly.
My stupid face was caught
on her camera...
To me,
you look like you're prepared to
face and fight for your own future.
How can you say that?
Actually...
I want to keep taking photos
in college, too.
So I'm going to Tokyo.
What?
Why?
When did you decide that?
Just recently.
I just said it for the first time.
Gosh, it somehow makes me
angry at myself.
Why are you kneeling like that?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
What was tomorrow has become
today again.
We can't stay in "yesterday"
forever.
"Tomorrow" keeps becoming "today"
and "today" becomes "yesterday".
Then we will all die someday.
We won't be here 100 years later!
Can I do just one evil deed?
What?
Anyway, I'm doing it!
I was in love with Mihane, too!
I have been for my life, but I have
never been able to say it.
Then Shohei stole her away right
under my nose and I was so angry!
I am really jealous!
Shohei!
Promise me you'll make Mihane happy!
Got it?
I've made up my mind.
I won't return to the 22nd Century.
I will make Mihane happy!
I will, with all my might!
Idiot.
Thank you, Goro!
Don't thank me!
(When I look at the sun through
my palm,)
(I see my red, flowing blood.)
(The earthworms, the mole crickets,)
(and the pond skaters...)
(...are all alive,)
(all of them are friends.)
Idiot!
- Is it set?
- Yeah.
- Is this okay?
- How many seconds?
Six, five, four, three, two, one...
Where have you been?
If you want to succeed the shop
no matter what...
Do whatever you please.
I won't be a barber.
What?
I will study for my
university entrance exam.
And...
I'll face the reality
and see what I'm capable of doing.
You must be starving now.
There is natto.
Oh, right...We turned back time.
I forgot about the dinner party.
Oh, no...
I am sorry.
You took so much effort to make
the dishes here,
but I...
I just happened to forgot it...
Oh, this is the dish you made by
wrapping pork around piece of apple?
It was really delicious!
I'm sorry, it might seem that
I didn't have it,
but I actually did.
Mom?
Do you know how much
I've been worrying about you?
I really...
...don't want to be left alone
again.
Don't just disappear
without saying anything!
I'm not going anywhere.
"Sample collection point.
Blood sample, urine sample"
I hate the smell of hospital so much
that I could get ill.
The results of your check-up...
Frankly, it is really bad.
Your illness is pretty serious.
It can't be that bad.
Only your irregular lifestyle
wouldn't have
harmed your internal
organs to that extend.
The aging of your bones
is significant, too.
Do you have any clues
what might have caused this?
Any clues?
"I am from the future."
Of course I can't tell anyone that.
Pork and egg, and a mixed
Okonomiyaki. 1900 yen, please.
The reason that I'm staying
in the 21st Century...
Keita, no, you can't have beer.
Hey! Don't go! You haven't paid!
There is only one reason.
It's because...
Stop there!
...my family, Yuri and Keita,
are here.
Yuri and I didn't get married,
and I'm not related to Keita
by blood.
But still, to me,
they are still the precious family
that is irreplaceable.
You got in my way...
Pay me 1900 yen! Or I'm not going to
let you go easily!
He got away and it was your fault!
You idiot!
Our fateful...Well, it's not exactly
the right word. It's been 7 years...
...since we first met each other.
An encounter can change a person.
If someone from the future
keep staying in this era...
...he will die an early death?
I knew this, too, only after I spent
three years in this era.
Break up with Mihane and go back
soon. It's for your own sake.
Are you going to keep staying here?
I don't mind dying. My family here
is more important than my life.
If I can be with Yuri and Keita
until my life ends,
then I'll be happy.
But is it okay that I'm the only one
who is happy?
What?
Hey.
Mihane can leap through time, right?
You got it right.
I have to tell you about
Ribon's Mr. Miura.
What happened to Mr. Miura?
He might come and talk to you
about something weird,
but don't believe anything he says.
Everything he says is a lie.
What?
He is trying to break us up.
- What?
- Anyway.
Just trust me.
I want to be with you
no matter what.
I mean...
I will.
I was wondering what you've been
doing, skipping the extra lessons.
You're suddenly eager.
- Zoe.
- Yes?
You have to return to the 22nd
Century as soon as possible.
I do want to.
The self-cleansing action of space
and time
is trying to expel
all alien objects.
- Pardon?
- We are from the future,
and time flows quicker for us.
Well...What does that mean?
If someone from the future
continue to stay in this era,
they will die an early death.
What?
What...
Die an early death?
Die an early death...
Are you not...going back with me?
The lab after school...
Please! Let me go back!
It's hypnotization.
Goro was the one who saved my life
at that time...
But I want to be here with you.
You have to go back!
Please do a time-leap
and make our family disappear!
But I think you should be
responsible for your encounter.
I have been very happy
in the few years with you.
I actually don't have a son.
I have made up my mind. Does this
really trouble you?
I don't want your life get cut
short, Shohei.
Of course I want to be with you
forever!
Farewell.
But don't run away from your family.
Thank you for all your
fantastic dishes.
Please take care of my mom forever.
What is a "right goodbye"?
If you've realized your mistake,
then don't make it again.
I'm here to help you go back
to the 22nd Century.