First, I want to point out
that it's all your fault.
Wow!
We're here!
We are here!
And it's hot!
It's hotter and more humid
than I thought!
Help!
First of all, don't tell anybody
about us.
If you break our promise, we'll melt
your brain and eat it!
It's safer to hypnotize him.
But it's difficult to hypnotize
a child.
And we'll be here for just three
hours, so it's not a problem.
What a gorgeous season!
Summer...
Because of what happened that day,
we don't have seasons
in the 22th Century,
and our world is covered with snow
throughout the year...
I guess people of this era
won't believe this.
I hope there is summer
in the time we live in.
Let's bring it back.
"Barber Asakura"
Hey.
You won't be popular with girls
wearing that hairstyle.
- What?
- Darling!
Do something about his hairstyle!
You won't be popular with girls
wearing that hairstyle!
I am, so don't bother.
Hang on, seriously...
I simply don't want this. No, stop!
You're going back
wearing that hairstyle?
It's awful. This is really horrible.
In my opinion, girls who wear a
mushroom haircut are masochists.
The professor is going to praise us
on our research sample, too...
What's the matter?
I lost the potion...
What?
You lost the potion?
- You mean we can't go back?
- It's not totally impossible now,
If we add the spare drug,
Crocus Silvius,
to a herb made with dried lavender,
a kind of evergreen undershrub in
the Lamiaceae family...
"Fukamachi"
All right...
What are you doing in my home?
Have we got any
experimental apparatus at home,
Mom?
We haven't got any
experimental apparatus at home.
Shohei!
I think the school will lend it to
you if you ask your teacher.
I see.
The school...
It's so good!
Oh, slow down...
What the heck?
Good morning.
Who is it?
Is someone in there?
It is all your fault.
You mean...
We cannot go back to Year 2122?
- Well...
- You said we could go back!
- We will...
- You said we could!
Rock, scissors, paper...
I repeat...
This is all your fault.
The story about you have leapt
through time...
You'd better not tell anyone.
I just came to this era...
Shohei, watch out!
...to do some research on summer.
It was me. Shohei saved your life
with all his might.
But before I knew it...
Your yukata looks nice.
Good night.
Good night...
I've fallen in love...
...in this era.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time
Episode 2"
I still remember what your dream was
when you were in kindergarten, Goro.
You dreamt of becoming
a pair of scissors.
I thought you were
a dangerous boy.
What?
Goro, you still haven't given up?
I told you,
I want to remain friends with you!
"The Ultimate Love Manual"
Mihane.
Have you ever kissed anyone?
Why ask that out of the blue?
I heard that it tastes like lemon,
lemon flavored shaved ice.
It tastes good, right?
Wait, where is Goro?
Do you want to try kissing me?
What are you talking about?
I'm not kissing a friend!
But you kissed Goro.
No, I didn't!
Shohei, do you have a crush on me,
too, by any chance?
No, please don't do that!
Please don't do that!
Don't do what?
You're the one who did something I
don't want you to, Mihane Yoshiyama.
You'll be tested on the quadratic
equation written on the blackboard.
Mr. Yano, will we be tested on the
solution of cubic equations?
No, you won't be tested on that yet.
You will be tested on topics till
quadratic equations this time.
What troubled you in your dream?
What? I won't tell you two.
It's so erotic
that you can't tell us?
- It's the first thing you think of?
- Idiot!
- It wasn't!
- She got defensive.
No, I didn't! Why have you got
a watermelon?
This is my lunch!
The slowest one has to
do a quick trick.
No! Wait for me!
- I got here.
- Darn, I lost...
- Hang on...
- Ow...
- Look...
- Oh!
It's Nishioka?
- This is dangerous...
- Isn't it dangerous?
This is bad...
Don't kill yourself!
You almost killed me!
I just love heights a lot.
It makes my heart race,
and it makes me feel alive.
This is bad...
Actually, today is the anniversary
of my death.
- Your chest looks good.
- Indeed.
No...
That's not the point.
I had my heart transplanted
on this day, two years ago.
So, to the old me, today is
the anniversary of my death,
and it's the two-year-old birthday
of the new me.
The new me is me, too,
but it isn't me at the same time.
What do you mean?
My personality changed.
I used to be afraid of heights,
but now I love it for no reason.
Also, my heart always beats quickly
after 8 o'clock every night.
I have no idea why, though.
You mean the original owner of your
heart has something to do with this?
I don't know, because nobody told me
anything about the donor.
But I was told that the donor was
15 to 18 years old.
Anyway, I am grateful to
that person.
So...
At least,
I want to live my life in a way that
will make the heart happy.
This is unbelievable.
What does it take to make you
believe that?
I do think there are aliens, though.
What, aliens?
That person tumbled...
Guys, I think I will tell you
my secret.
- Your secret?
- I don't want to know.
I can leap through time!
What?
She said it.
I have no idea why
I have this power,
but I think I had it since I passed
out in the lab's storage room.
Now I can turn back time.
Should I laugh?
- Should I laugh?
- Let's play rock, scissors, paper.
- I am surely not going to lose.
- You're sure?
- I'm sure!
- You're exaggerating it.
I will surely win!
Fine.
Rock, scissors, paper...
Hang on.
Rock, scissors, paper!
Wait...
How can I possibly believe this...
Right?
Shohei, do you believe that?
Well, I seriously don't want to
believe this.
She'll tumble three seconds later.
- What?
- Three, two, one.
See? See?
So, I want to go to meet the person
using my power.
You mean the original owner
of Nishioka's heart?
Yes.
The person absolutely loved heights!
Aren't you curious about
what the person was like?
Not really.
I'm curious about the mystery of why
the heart beats quicker after 8 p.m.
No, you shouldn't.
If there is the slightest chance
that the person's life was saved,
then Nishioka wouldn't have gotten
his heart transplanted.
You should not do it, definitely.
It'll cause many problems.
I'm not trying to change the past.
I just want to know.
- Don't be too nosy.
- Exactly.
You two take it too seriously.
If you do possess such power,
you can use it on other things.
You're absolutely correct.
Will you be my girlfriend?
I...
I hope you'll be my girlfriend.
Mihane...
I love you.
I have used it.
To make what bothered me
didn't happen.
What bothered you?
- Don't be too nosy.
- You're annoying.
I am going to meet the person.
I'm curious about
what the person is like.
Take it.
You'll leap through time, right?
Try and do it. We'll be looking.
But I'll get nervous if you
stare at me.
- Don't look!
- Idiot!
What?
She's gone. What?
What? Seriously, Mihane!
This is impossible...Shohei...
This is real, right? Yeah?
Mihane!
I hope this won't cause
any trouble...
- What just happened?
- Ouch!
This is impossible!
She is back.
Back? What is back?
Wow! Why, Mihane? Why?
You're okay, right?
Are you injured? Is there anything
wrong with your body?
- Wow, this is awesome!
- So,
- how did it go?
- Wow!
Wow!
She wasn't someone
who loved heights.
- What?
- Wow!
This is awesome!
"Barber Asakura"
A bicycle accident happened
on the day before this two
years ago in Shizuoka.
The slope was steep,
and the brake was broken.
She couldn't stop her bicycle.
The victim died in the accident
was a girl in her third year
in high school.
Wow, she is gorgeous!
She always went to the library
and revised for her exam until the
library was going to close.
She was a hard-working girl.
Oh, no!
Then...Why does Nishioka love
heights now?
More importantly, was that
the right person?
Well, she was the right person.
What about the mysterious beating of
the heart after 8 p.m?
No idea.
But...
She always went to the train station
when she went home from the library.
Station...
She wasn't meeting up with anyone,
she'd just saw the 20:20 train off,
then she would go home.
I see.
What?
What? Have you solved it?
- Yes, it's obvious.
- Of course.
- Say it.
- She's a railway nerd!
What?
- What?
He was on the train.
- Who? Me?
- No.
The guy she loved.
- Oh.
- What?
Oh...
I'll go and check.
- What?
- Hey, Mihane!
She said it like she was just going
to a convenient store.
- Is it okay to leap through time?
- No, it's not...
I don't think so...
- Watch it...
- Wow!
Are you okay? Anyway,
have you found that out?
The girl...She was in love,
wasn't she?
Rather than being in love, she...
She was trying desperately
to hold back her love.
Try to hold back her love?
We should avoid contact with the
locals by all means.
That's what the professor told us.
Though we have hypnotized them, I
still don't think it's a good idea.
What are you trying to do by
slipping into the school?
People living in this age...
They fall in love.
Love?
Oh! In the first half of the
21st Century,
people could still fall in love
freely, couldn't they?
They would go on dates,
or look at the train that the person
they loved took until it was gone.
They would kiss their loved ones.
Kiss?
Like they put their mouths together?
Sometimes it's more than just
putting their mouths together.
Is that so? You know a lot.
I've done my research.
What?
Do you...want to fall in love?
No, it's absurd...
Love between men and women is
inefficient and bears great risks.
98 percent of the people in
the 22nd Century
agree on marriage based on the
compatibility of DNA.
Of course, I'm one of them, too.
Until we've made the potion,
we can't return to the 22nd Century.
Now that we're living in Year 2016,
why don't you enjoy it, too, Zoe?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
You uploaded this to the internet?
Yeah, everyone is doing it.
Good morning.
Hey, Shohei, look at this!
Spiderman Kiss!
Yes!
You're going to regret it.
It'll be there forever!
That's why! He is really romantic,
and he said that our love would stay
forever if we did that.
It's like something that Nagashima
would say.
- It's fantastic!
- I know!
Hang on.
Who is Nagashima?
All the photos are great.
Yeah, they are!
- What? These are good?
- Show me more...
These?
It's not because she loved heights.
Sorry.
I checked it without telling you.
You mean the donor?
Please, tell me what she was like.
The person...
She was a hard-working girl...
"I hope the love between my teacher
and I is mutual,"
"but I'll hold back
until I graduate."
She fell in love with someone
who she shouldn't have.
Well, you might not believe it,
but that's why.
I see...
She did that after 8 o'clock
in the evening...
Thank you for doing this.
No, it's not a big deal...
I actually did something
uncalled for...
No, you didn't.
The reason that the heart beats
quickly every day after 8 o'clock
is because she wanted to stop
holding back
the love she had been
stopping herself to feel.
I see...
You have to do what you want to do
while you still can.
But I don't think she'd appreciate
being dragged to high places.
She'd say that it wasn't why she
wanted her heart to beat so fast.
I didn't tell Nishioka...
everything about the girl.
What?
She had a crush on Mr. Yano?
Nobody knows about it.
It happened before Mr. Yano came to
teach at our school.
I'm the type that always poke my
nose into what doesn't concern me.
Don't forget your cubic functions,
too.
Guys, you're fed up with this
already?
If you want to enter
a national public university,
you should work harder on
the main subjects.
Mr. Yano...
Have you ever fallen in love
with a student?
Why ask that out of the blue?
Of course not! It'd cause a problem
if I had.
But...
A student had fallen in love
with you, right?
Why?
How did you feel towards that girl?
Nobody has fallen in love with me.
In the last school you taught in.
There really was nobody?
If you count someone who
misunderstood their feelings,
then, yes.
Perhaps...
She didn't misunderstand it.
I didn't know for sure in the end,
and I will never know.
Don't say anything you shouldn't.
It's a tragedy that one dies before
they can convey their love to
the person they love.
It's a super tragedy.
It's because no one would think
about when they'll die.
And the person she loved thinks
she didn't understand how she felt.
It makes me frustrated!
Why are you frustrated?
She had endured what made her suffer
and had worked really hard,
but suddenly everything ended.
Do you know how frustrating it is?
I understand how it feels.
Are you talking...
about having to quit the boat club
because you hurt your back?
All the efforts and dreams vanished.
Without a trace.
He denied her love for him.
But she did love him.
Mihane...
Just because you can leap
through time,
doesn't mean that you can
change the girl's fate.
If you do, you're going to take
Nishioka's life away from him.
Yeah, I know that.
- Anyway, Goro...
- Yes?
You're in love with Mihane,
aren't you?
What?
Actually, I think I might be in love
with Mihane, too...
Is it okay for two people to fall in
love with the same person?
What kind of question is that?
I have never fallen in love before,
so I know nothing about it.
I hope it's okay...
Well, I think...
we'll leave this to Mihane
to decide?
Yeah, we should...
See you.
Goro...
Have you ever kissed anyone?
What?
I wonder whether Mihane has kissed
anyone or not before.
I have no idea.
That means,
you and Mihane have not kissed yet.
Good...
Good?
Yes! Yes!
What is so good?
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
Bye bye bi...
Bye bye bi.
I didn't tell anyone!
Don't eat my brain!
I won't eat your brain.
But, please...
Give me something...
...to eat.
- I'm home!
- Welcome home...
- Hey, Mi-kun,
- Yes?
my friend is hungry,
so I want to give her
a pork and egg Okonomiyaki.
To your friend?
Yeah, sure...
Why don't you bring
your friend here?
Haven't you got a home?
Where is your family?
They're somewhere very far away.
I can't go home now.
But you have a friend, right?
Oh...My senior?
He made me really angry.
- You had a fight?
- Something like that.
What is it called? Pork and egg?
This tastes great!
It's because Mi-kun made it.
Mi-kun? Who is that?
He's not my real father,
but he's my dad.
I see...
That was my blind spot.
You're kidding me, right?
"Chapter 7."
"Make your crush fall for you
with a kiss."
Oh, my god...
Wow...
- Welcome home!
- I'm home.
Here...
Taco-Rice...
Somehow this feels strange.
I forgot that I actually
love to cook.
He can't eat what I cook now,
but I'm happy enough to have you
to eat the dishes I make.
Mom, are you in love with me?
I do love you.
Then...Can I kiss you?
Don't be absurd!
Your friends will laugh at you for
being obsessed with your mom.
Sorry, I just want to practice.
How awful of you! Use your own hand.
"Barber Asakura"
No...
"Can we both fall in love
with the same person"?
Don't be ridiculous!
Darn!
I've got you some information of
different universities. Look.
But it's months away.
- You'll have to apply soon!
- I'm doing my homework. Thanks.
There is natto if you're hungry.
- Give it your best!
- I will.
Good.
Jun, you hang up first.
I'll hang up, then.
Let's hang up together.
Okay...
One, two...
Hey, you should hang up...
Do hang up this time.
Let's hang up.
One...
- What are you doing?
- Who is Jun?
My boyfriend.
What? You have a boyfriend?
Of course! I'm in the 2nd year
of my middle school.
What do you do?
Stop asking such childish question.
You know, Naho,
in the world,
there are people who want to fall in
love but force themselves not to.
And?
Go and fall in love, Mihane.
"Okonomiyaki Ribon"
Men nowadays are too shy!
Why?
I think you've drank enough
for today.
Gosh...
Is Mr. Yano not interested in women?
Are you okay, Mi-kun?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just got a nosebleed.
I'm okay, it's no big deal.
Gosh...Don't scare me.
Mr. Yano is too closed-off,
really...
What is that?
Light poles and electric cables.
Why?
What?
I just thought the combination
is good.
That's often the case.
Well, it is, but...
But somehow,
all of them don't seem like what
you really want to photograph.
Sorry.
I don't know what
I should photograph anyway,
and there is nothing I want to
photograph.
You don't have to take photos
of things, do you?
Take a photo of time.
Time?
Which moment you want to save?
That's what I want to see.
Sorry for being arrogant.
But I like photographs.
You can save a certain moment
forever.
That's it!
What?
Perhaps the girl's love...
...can be conveyed using photos.
"The Girl Who Leapt Through Time"
I'm in Higashi High School's
photograph club
and I'm looking for a model...
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
Of course she would get suspicious
if I approach her suddenly.
- I'm sorry.
- You don't like taking photos?
Please...
I can't be your model.
There is a bug on you...
It's true.
I'm looking for a model...
Oh? It's easy.
I'm very sorry to bother you
when you are busy,
but I'm looking for a model,
you look really pretty and I really
hope that you would be my model!
What's wrong with you?
Someone, help!
I'm not someone suspicious!
Really, I am not!
Do you need any help?
Yeah...
I've been looking for a model,
and I've asked that person
many times,
but I kept getting refused.
- It must have been tiring.
- Yeah.
Is there anything
I can help you with?
Oh...
Yes!
I would like to take some photos,
so would you be my model?
Are you going to submit it to
some competition?
I suppose.
Don't blame me even if
you don't win it, though.
I won't!
Finally!
I want to get the proof
that you had been in love.
Are you happy with me?
I have never been anybody's model
before...
Actually...
Please get naked.
What?
Show me your heart.
What do you mean?
If you want to fall in love,
you don't have to hold back.
Think of me as the person you love,
and reveal your love to me.
I love you.
I love you!
The proof that she was in love
isn't something that I can
photograph by asking.
How did I do? Is it good?
It's lovely.
I'm so angry at myself
that my skill is so poor.
I couldn't take a good photo,
and I'm sorry.
How do you know that I'm holding
back my love?
Your heart has been seeking that.
A photographer knows even that?
This is fascinating.
Why don't you tell the person
about your love?
He's my teacher.
I mean the person I love.
I'll confess my love if I got
accepted by the medical school.
This is the last day of her life.
I have to do my maths...
Please tell me about your love
next time.
I cannot change her fate.
Why?
Why are you crying?
What a weird girl.
You're crying like we'll say goodbye
here forever.
Come on, stop crying.
You look lovely, so smile a bit.
I'm looking forward to seeing
the photos.
Just because you can
leap through time,
doesn't mean that you can
change the person's fate.
At least,
I want to live in a way that will
make the heart happy.
Come on.
See you again.
I could not tell her that
her bicycle's brake is broken,
and I saw her off.
"Taken at Izukyu Line's
Shimoda Station, at 20:20..."
"She didn't misunderstand
how she felt."
"Social Dance"
Mr. Yano?
Oh...Miss Maekawa.
I got some free tickets for this.
Would you like to go with me?
It's Barber? That would be great.
If you don't mind...
Sure, let's go together.
Thanks.
This is good.
Yeah?
I like that one.
It think it's good.
All the photos are good.
They're good.
I like this one, though.
I wish I had taken them better.
The length of time that people
can be in love
is actually very short.
"Life is short,
so fall in love, maiden."
I guess romance is great, too.
Oops.
- Sorry, I'll take it back now.
- Hey!
It fell...
Go on!
You almost got it.
What are you doing?
"Make your crush fall for you
with a kiss."
I don't think this is what it means.
- We'll leap through time together?
- Yes...
Let's do a class presentation!
A transferred student?
Nobody told me.
You should not fall in love with
someone who is from a different era.
Just overcome the obstacle with
the power of love.
Please be my Juliet.
I want to play Romeo,
no matter what.
We only need three more ingredients
to make it.
He was busy. Let's go!
What about Para Para? Look!
Let's give it our best!