THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING, GOODBYE
So, it's goodbye.
I wasn't enough for you?
I'm sorry.
AOI MINASE
Hello?
Hey, Soseki!
I heard you have a cold
and you took the day off.
I have a slight fever.
I see.
I got the news that
the Midsummer Skies are Dreams proposal
went through.
You pushed it, right? Thank you.
It was nothing.
I was planning to work with it.
-With "Lemon Page…"
-Soseki?
Oh god.
Soseki?
What's wrong?
Where are you?
That person isn't family? Strange, right?
Mom's Blood type O. I'm Type AB.
-Maybe you remember wrong.
-I'm going to go check.
No! Don't let her take the test!
I shouldn't have tested for my blood type!
What should I do? Sora's leaving me.
Sora's going away.
Must be hard, working this late.
I'm on my night shift.
I see.
He works for me.
Oh, yes.
He suddenly got a
105 degree fever at the Kasumigaoka
intersection and couldn't move.
I took a taxi to go find him
and brought him here.
I'm sorry.
Here she is.
Are you okay, Soseki?
Oh, Konishi-kun.
Thank you for going to find him.
Alright, then.
I'll leave you two youngsters to it.
Sorry. Not young.
Bye!
Sorry you had to come all the way here.
I thought you got in an accident!
Yeah. I thought I died too.
There's something in your hair.
Oh.
It looks like pertya fluff.
Already that time of year, huh?
I'm glad.
What?
You scared me.
Ms. Aoi?
I don't know what I'd do without you.
Thank you.
That's not what I mean.
Please… Wait.
Wait a minute.
Huh?
I think I'm going through
a major life event right now!
Such a strong rejection!
I may not get over it, ever!
Am I okay?
Can I continue living like this?
No, I'm saying that right now,
I have a cold. A 105 degree fever.
Oh. You're right.
I can't make you sick.
-Is that your excuse?
-Why?
Is this workplace harassment?
Sexual harassment?
If so, tell me!
It's neither of those things.
If it was, I'd be very sad.
But Ms. Aoi, you're the type
to kiss people
in the same way you find
a really cute puppy and
can't resist kissing him.
Are you a puppy?
You consider yourself a puppy?
You're that cute?
I'm sorry. My metaphor wasn't appropriate.
I got carried away.
But you do tend to get caught up
in the flow.
Have you thought about
what this might mean in the future?
The future?
Well…
I mean… I may not look it,
but I'm a man. A straight one, at that.
I'm currently under the weather
with a cold and all, but still.
The other time,
thanks to Sora coming home,
everything ended without a fuss.
But what if it recurred…
-Recurred?
-Yes, recurred.
That's the wrong word.
I'm not talking about a disease.
I know what you mean, so go on.
So if it happens again and we kiss,
then I could never turn back.
Do you really like me?
Why are you thinking about it?
If you can't respond right away,
you shouldn't kiss anyone.
But don't you start liking people
after you've kissed them?
Yes. If we kiss, we'd like each other!
It'd be a done deal!
We'd start dating and stuff!
You're so cute!
You're one to speak.
That's how it goes in all your novels!
And you're saying your personal life
is different?
So what are we saying?
I'm saying,
let's put a lid on this. On these vibes.
What?
Let's put a lid on it,
and come back after three months.
Why?
Not a week, or two weeks,
but three months?
What?
Are you saying that you're unsure
if you'll feel the same
after that much time?
You're saying you're unsure right now?
I checked in with how I feel just now.
When I saw your chubby little left cheek,
I totally thought I felt something.
But from the front, maybe not so much.
Maybe it's not so bad.
Huh?
Looks aren't everything.
Wait. Sounds like you're saying
I'm ugly?
No, come on! No way!
Please don't assess me.
Let's stop checking how we feel.
It's too fuzzy.
Whatever the answer is, it's scary.
Scary.
Anyways, should we be doing this
right now?
What?
The proposal for your new book
got approved today.
Right! You're right.
Midsummer Skies are Dreams.
And it's not a romance novel.
It's totally new territory.
We have to succeed.
I have to succeed at this too.
It's my last shot.
You're right.
Is now the time for romance?
It's really not.
Midsummer Skies are Dreams is
a story about a mother and daughter.
Romance would be pointless.
Pointless…
Yes, you're right. Now's not the time.
I'll work hard on my novel!
For now.
What?
ODAYA
Welcome!
Eventually, Sally started working at Odaya
out of admiration for Shunichiro.
What! Soseki got a 105 degree fever?
And he almost got
into an accident?
You didn't know?
-I didn't know.
-Shit. I told you.
TAIYAKI
We've broken up now.
I thought you were lying about that,
and cheating with Shunichiro.
I'd never do such a…
I might, huh?
Yeah.
But I didn't this time.
"This time"?
I broke it off completely.
I see.
Is Soseki better now?
When did that happen?
What is it?
I'm stopping your heart
from flying back to Soseki.
I see.
Shunichiro is so old!
What if you kill him of a broken heart?
It's totally fine.
My heart is solid.
Solid as a rock.
-Really?
-I think.
"You think"?
-Hello!
-Oh, hello.
We had a four o'clock meeting planned.
I called her cell too.
Mom started working on a new idea, right?
Once that starts, she can't stop.
She's been writing a ton at Hana Café
on her laptop.
That's what you call a true writer.
-You're in the zone, huh?
-Can you tell?
Wow.
Right now, I could even fly the sky!
Can you listen to my new idea?
It's a story about heaven and this world.
Two stories in two different worlds,
moving forward at the same time.
Wow!
I don't get it, but it sounds fun.
You don't get it?
Wait.
What day of the week is it today?
I think I'm forgetting something.
What is it?
The dentist? The spa?
I didn't bring my phone. Well, whatever!
Can I get something sweet?
The other day, when Mom ran out
in the middle of the night,
yelling out, "Soseki's in trouble!"
I thought you were
already together.
We're not. Nothing's happening.
What? Why?
You're not gonna date Mom?
You won't look after Mom in her old age
instead of me?
She forgot about today too.
Oh, that's unrelated.
She's that kind of person.
When she was young, she called
her boyfriend in the middle of the night
because she had a scary dream,
but when he arrived,
she was fast asleep,
with the door chains on.
He spent the whole night outside,
waiting for morning.
Could I survive that?
You want to?
I'm going to keep observing
how Ms. Aoi feels about me.
That makes me nervous.
Mom's feelings change so often
that they even surprise me,
after all our years together. It shifts
like the high-altitude weather.
I can totally understand that.
That's why I'm worried.
My heart is weak right now too.
I shouldn't act on anything yet.
Your heart is weak?
Oh, Sally's Shunichiro, right?
"Shunichiro"?
-What?
Who's Shunichiro?
Huh? I'm not sure.
A dog?
A small dog we recently got as a pet.
That's his name.
Shunichiro!
Is he out for a walk?
Ah!
This is so good.
Really? That makes me happy.
-Can I have another?
-Coming up!
Shunichiro! Another taiyaki!
Coming right up!
I remember Shunichiro.
He's totally Sally's type.
He's perfect.
Plus she loves dads.
Okay. I'm leaving now.
Right now?
You haven't noticed how dressed up I am?
Why did I change into such nice clothes?
I have a date!
It wasn't for me?
I'm a college girl.
You think it was for you?
You're an old man, you know.
That was just like Mom!
This holier-than-thou,
narcissistic attitude!
I was just joking.
A date, okay. I understand.
It's okay, Soseki. Wait for Mom here.
Just like a loyal dog.
Woof!
You scared me.
This is our spare key, just in case.
I fell in love.
-I see.
-You're gonna get dumped again?
Why do you assume that?
Because whenever you fall in love,
you get dumped.
It's a two-in-one set.
That's how it always is.
How rude!
You're like Tora-san, Aoi.
A female Tora-san. He always gets dumped.
"Me, born and raised in Suzuran,
Minato Ward.
Last name Minase, First name Aoi.
People call me… Sakura!"
Wow, that's just like him!
I love those movies.
I wanted to play the heroine, though.
The heroine has to be pretty.
What did you say?
Don't waste food!
I'm eating it.
Wow! So good!
Right? We had some good pouches
for inari sushi.
I simmered it in ginger for a long time.
Don't lie. We got it
from Kitsune-ya next door.
It's good. It doesn't matter.
Yes, it doesn't matter!
We're in a fuzzy area. A gray zone.
What are you saying?
Gray? The color?
Yes. Not black, not white, but gray.
Not red, not white, but pink.
Not blue, not white, but sky blue.
What's she saying?
I get it.
Love is the most fun
when those questions are unanswered!
See, you get it, Shunichiro!
What's going on? You're having fun
without me.
So who's this next guy?
Someone who shares the same dream.
-Is he from work?
-Yeah.
We have these dates called "meetings"…
Our next one is Wednesday.
Aoi, today's Wednesday.
What? It's still Tuesday, right?
It's Wednesday.
No way!
Shoot! You're right!
My strong and ongoing desire of wanting
an extra day until the deadline
messed with my internal calendar!
Oh!
Ouch!
Thank you, come again!
I WAITED A BIT, BUT I'VE HEADED HOME
SOSEKI
"I waited a bit,
but I've headed home… "
-Come in.
-I'm home.
I got this for you.
Cream puffs from Pop Dip.
We went to Harajuku.
Wow! They have the best custards!
Were you on a date? That's Valentino.
Yup.
How nice to be young!
You can restart any time.
You're eating that now?
It's Pop Dip! You need some nice tea…
I want it now.
And on the bed?
I want to eat it now, on the bed!
Are you a child?
Oh, Soseki was here today.
Did you see him?
He went home.
This is how my life is.
You stepped away from me.
You were going into a spiel.
I'll give you the
half custard, half whipped cream.
Really?
Huh? What is it?
I'll never let you go!
I don't need any more men!
Are you a toxic mother?
You only realized just now?
Burr-burr-burr-bulldog!
BULLDOG
I'll give you the first star
that falls on the ground!
Ouch!
How was your date with Doctor Wataru?
It was really fun.
It was a perfect date.
Wonderful!
I'm so happy you know what love is.
All my emotions are bursting!
I'm going to explode!
That's so nice!
Will you become an adult one day
and leave me?
Mom, I'm already an adult. I'm 20.
-I see. 20 is an adult?
-Yeah.
Would you marry Doctor Wataru?
What? No way!
If that happens, I'll be alone.
That's not true.
Once you really love Doctor Wataru,
you'll forget me.
No, I won't.
I'd never forget you, Mom.
Never in a million years.
I felt like I had to say that,
or Mom would go far away.
I see.
I've never had a boyfriend, so
Mom was always my closest person.
I see.
Are you listening to me?
I'm listening so attentively!
Pay for my second latte, okay?
You love Doctor Wataru
that much?
I held his hand.
I see.
No. It was a handshake to say goodbye.
A long handshake.
Too long for a handshake.
It was hard for either of us to let go.
So it felt like we held hands.
I see.
I'm meeting him again tomorrow.
Tomorrow at six, at Hana Café.
I see.
I'm so nervous!
I'm about to explode.
I've never felt that way,
even after sleeping with them.
-"Sleeping"?
-Yeah.
Oh, right. That.
Will I ever do something like that
with Doctor Wataru?
Why are you panicking?
No.
It was just unexpected.
It's hard to talk to Mom
about these things.
I'm counting on you.
I'll ask you lots of questions.
Seriously?
Now, I'm nervous.
Well, it's only fair.
I'm having you draw.
I draw manga because I want to.
I'm sorry about the way I talked
last time.
You're finally drawing manga, Sora?
It's just a hobby.
Sorry I couldn't say that
we're aiming for Jump.
Wait.
We are?
Yeah. We are.
Let's take our manuscript to Jump!
I looked up how to do that.
You're on fire!
So full of energy.
Is it the power of love?
I thought about it. I figured,
I'm Aoi Minase's daughter after all.
Maybe I do have a talent.
Yeah.
The family blood line is important.
It might be genetic.
Aoi Minase's Blood type O, huh?
Yeah. I'm an outsider, so I'm Type AB.
Thank you.
-It was delicious.
-Hey, let me pay.
Let's split it. You listened to me talk.
I just got paid. Let me pay, alright?
Why are you acting all cool?
It's fine.
-It's fine!
-Why?
A Blood type O can't have
a Type AB kid, right?
Welcome!
-Welcome!
-Just you?
-Yes.
-What's your name?
It was something bright…
Watt! Watt, right?
You're Sora's classmate!
I'm Hikaru.
Here you are.
Thank you.
How nice. An all-carb meal?
You're young, so I bet
you don't even gain weight.
Are you training?
No. I did track in high school,
but I don't do anything now.
I see. What a waste.
You should play something!
Um, excuse me?
About Ms. Aoi…
What is Aoi Minase's blood type?
I think she's Type O.
I see. And Sora?
I'm not sure. I've never asked.
Really?
Are you doing a personality test
with blood type?
Is that trending again?
Well, something like that.
Can I bother you for a bit?
-Yes?
-Would you like some?
Japanese Sake. Koubou.
Really?
DAD
Father…
Go!
WRITE, SLEEP, EAT, CRY, TEASE SORA, WALK
"Eat."
-Yes?
-Mom, are you hungry?
Bingo! I'm so hungry!
-Uber?
-Uber Eats?
Yeah.
Mom wants to get some fresh air.
I'll go buy something.
Okay!
I see. You like her that much, huh?
Yeah. I do.
I really, really, like her.
I really do,
but I don't let that show.
I keep my feelings hidden.
What? Why?
Because I'd get dumped?
No way! You're so handsome.
Right. I'm pretty hot, right?
There are parts of myself I'm hiding,
but at first glance, I'm good-looking.
I understand the struggle
of handsome men entirely.
I totally get it.
You get me?
Well, now, drink up!
-That's my sake.
-Drink up!
Jadwiga is Blood type AB.
DOMINICA, TYPE O
And her mother, Dominica, is Type O.
And the father…
JADWIGA'S FATHER
Oh, weren't there rules on blood types
of parents and kids?
I can't just make it up.
"Blood type."
BLOOD TYPE COMBINATION OF PARENTS AND KIDS
MOTHER: TYPE O
CHILD: TYPE O, A OR B
What?
Thank you for dinner and the sake.
-It was a lot of fun.
-Come again, Watt!
No, it's Hikaru!
SORA MINASE
-Hello? It's Sora.
-Yeah.
Are you free to talk?
Yeah, I can talk.
-I was drawing the manga.
-Yeah.
I thought maybe Jadwiga's a Type B.
Okay.
But then, I wondered what blood type
her mom Dominica would be.
You know blood type combinations?
What blood type you can get
based on your parents' types.
OPEN
I saw that you can't get AB children
from a Type O parent.
I just googled it.
No matter the father's blood type,
you can't have an AB child
from an O mother.
-That's true.
-That's weird, right?
My mom's Type O, and I'm Type AB.
I had the same thought the other day.
Maybe you remembered
your blood type wrong, Minase.
Oh…
How did you learn your blood type?
From your mom?
No, it wasn't that.
In high school, I went with a friend
to donate blood.
It said "Type AB" in the corner of
the card.
Maybe you remembered wrong.
I'm not sure about that.
Maybe Mom remembered
her own blood type wrong.
That's possible, from her personality.
That's totally possible.
ABECHAN STEWED BEEF OFFAL
Will you come to
Sarashina Toyoda? I'm craving soba.
I'M GOING TO STAY HOME AND DRAW MANGA,
I'M ON A ROLL.
CAN YOU GET THE OMELET
AND THE SOBA SUSHI AS TAKEOUT?
JAPAN PASSPORT
Blood type…
It's not here.
It's the maternity handbook from when
Mom was born.
BLOOD TYPE O
Type O…
RISSEI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
Hey! I was just drunk!
She was so drunk the other day.
That's not true.
Her eyes were like this.
Huh? What is it?
I need Irino.
What is it?
Look, he's already standing up.
He's so enthusiastic to talk to her!
She was Type O.
Mom was Type O.
I see.
I'm going to test
what my blood type is now.
I'm going to go confirm that the Type AB
that I tested from the blood drive
that lured me in with
coffee milk was correct.
You don't have to make me laugh now.
Which part was funny?
The coffee milk.
You laugh too easily, Irino.
I'm not laughing, but…
I don't know, maybe you were trying
to make me laugh.
The position of my maternity handbook
that I always put in here changed!
It's always under the passport.
And my drawer keys
should be in this glass, but it was
in the glass next to it.
Why do you just
leave these out where anyone can see?
Sora never touched these things before.
Oh boy…
Oh, it's Dad. He got worried, so he came.
What about Odaya?
What are you worried about at such a time?
It's open, Dad!
MEIJI GENERAL HOSPITAL
You know…
What?
Maybe we should attend the Keynes seminar.
Professor Satonaka's strict
about attendance.
It's fine. It's just once.
If you don't feel like going to
the hospital,
we can go somewhere else. I'll join you.
Like where?
Anywhere you want.
The movies, or Disneyland.
We're not going to Disneyland right now.
Then, we could go bowling.
With Jadwiga,
we added the ears, right?
Yeah.
Wouldn't it be cool if those ears
can get bigger so she can fly?
That's a great idea!
Ow.
No way.
Ouch.
Not really.
Killing time.
What?
This is what killing time is, right?
When I didn't want to go home,
when I was little,
I was always killing time by myself,
like this.
Me too.
Now, it's the two of us.
Yeah.
The other day, Hikaru…
Sora's college friend.
Hikaru came, and asked you
about Aoi's blood type, right?
-Yeah.
-That time he did.
I exchanged phone numbers with him.
-Then let's call and explain…
-Wait a minute.
You're Type O. Sora's type AB.
Does Sora know this?
Yeah.
I knew it since she was three-months-old.
So I tried to prevent her
from doing blood type tests, but…
But then, when she was a freshman
in high school,
maybe it was eighth grade,
she went to a blood drive with a friend.
She said, "Mom, I'm Type AB."
How did she find out you're Type O?
-From magazine interview profile pages.
-Oh…
And then?
Oh, right.
But she didn't realize that a Type O mom
-can't have a Type AB child.
-I see.
So I just left it like that!
You just left it, huh?
I knew a day like this would come one day,
but,
I thought maybe
I could play dumb.
Shunichiro.
Do you think I have to
tell her the truth?
-Hm?
-Wait, Aoi.
We're way past that stage.
Hikaru came to our place to ask about
you and Sora's blood types,
and your maternity handbook position
had shifted, right?
Sora already saw what your blood type was.
Please fill in the patient form.
Yes.
INCOMING CALL
TEST RESULT DESK
Yes, hello?
Hello, is this Hikaru?
I got your number from Shunichiro.
Yes, I'm with Sora now.
She's a bit far away now.
-Where are you?
-At the hospital.
She's testing her blood type?
Yes, she wants to know her blood type.
Did you tell her?
That Type O moms can't have AB kids.
No, that's not exactly right.
But when we were thinking of characters
for our manga,
we started talking about it.
I realized it was strange at first.
Stop her from taking the test!
How?
You're right. How?
I think she will do the test.
Even if I stopped her.
Ms. Aoi, I'm with her.
I might not be enough,
and I know I'm just a kid.
But I'm with her.
-Oh, she's coming back.
-Hikaru.
Please…
Please look after Sora.
Yes, ma'am.
Who was that? Your girlfriend again?
A new girlfriend?
Something like that.
I heard it's pretty common.
What?
People who mistakenly remember
their own blood type.
I see.
Miss Minase. Miss Sora Minase?
Yes!
I have to go do prep for dinnertime.
What should I do, Gon-chan?
Sora's leaving me. She's going away.
No way that would happen!
I was lying this whole time.
I kept it a secret.
She'll never forgive me!
What are you saying? It'll be okay.
It's over.
Everything's over.
Stop saying that, alright?
Nothing's ending.
I was Type AB.
TYPE AB+
No doubt about it.
I'm Type AB.
Yeah.
Thanks.
-I'll pay you back.
-It's fine.
Do you want to be left alone?
Oh, are you busy?
No.
Not in the slightest.
I made you come with me the whole day.
I just finished
my temporary part-time job so…
Where did you work?
I made banana omelets at a bread factory.
What is that?
You don't know?
They sell it at convenience stores.
They have a whole banana inside.
I roll that up with cream and cake.
That sounds good.
I was peeling the bananas
all day.
-No way!
-It's true! From morning to night!
It takes three or four times to peel
a banana, right?
I can do it in one go!
You're lying!
It's true! There's a trick.
Really?
Hey, don't you have your date
with Doctor Wataru today?
Yeah. It's at six today.
On a day like this?
I promised, so I have to go.
I don't feel like going home,
so it works out.
I see.
What time is it now?
It's…
It's 4:30.
I see.
I have more time.
Yeah.
Is that person a stranger?
What?
Because if we're not related by blood,
we're strangers, right?
Don't say it like that.
Your mom would be sad.
I don't know what went on with her, but…
Do you have any ideas?
I don't know what went on with her, but,
I'd probably thank her first.
She wasn't related by blood,
but she raised you.
Aoi Minase
loves Sora Minase very much.
That's how I see it.
Minase…
No…
What should I do?
I shouldn't have…
I shouldn't have tested my blood type!
-Minase…
-Why?
Why did it become like this?
-Minase.
-I love Mom a lot.
-What's happening to me?
-Minase!
Minase! Hold it together, alright?
I'm here. It'll be okay.
You're not alone.
I'm not alone?
Yeah. I'll be here. I won't go away.
I can't say things like I'll protect you.
I won't.
I can't be that cool,
or be that confident,
but I'll be here.
No matter what happens.
Don't forget I'm here,
okay?
Irino!
Irino.
This was my first time being hugged
by a boy.
It was like a weak grandma
leaning against an utility pole.
Far from romantic, but sincere.
Stay, Irino.
Honey!
Chili pepper.
Yuzu citrus.
Alright!
What!
Is this Iberian pork bacon?
You have such nice ingredients,
rich woman!
Call me anytime you want.
I'll answer within three rings.
Yes, hello?
You're right. That was one ring.
Don't get cocky just because you're cute!
Huh?
No, I'll work hard
so I can answer in half a ring
next time round!
Order up! Gon-chan's special soup.
I don't want it.
Don't say that! I made it for you.
-So good!
-Right? The secret ingredient is miso.
It's better to eat something.
You'll feel calmer.
Yeah.
Sora went on her date
with Doctor Wataru, right?
Yeah. I got a call from Hikaru just now.
Hikaru's a handsome boy,
and Doctor Wataru's
a good doctor. Sora's so popular!
A man on each arm.
Maybe she doesn't need you!
Hey, it was just a joke.
It just means Sora's grown up.
She'll understand.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
What will happen to us?
Listen, Aoi.
No matter what,
I'll protect the both of you.
I proposed to you and Sora here. Remember?
What?
Proposed? What do you mean?
Hey, you.
Hey.
If you need help,
I can raise her with you.
Hey, it's alright!
Nako helps me out too, so I'll be fine.
What? That was a marriage proposal?
I didn't get that at all!
I thought you were just offering to
come help me again tomorrow.
Back then, Sora cried so much at night.
She wouldn't let me sleep.
I was tired and hazy.
You have to explain to me,
"This is a marriage proposal!"
Like I'd ever say, "Please marry me!"
But you left the country
for years after that!
To heal my broken heart.
As if! You married Étoile immediately!
That's irrelevant.
-I decline your offer.
-What?
I respectfully decline your proposal.
I'm not proposing right now!
Just back then!
I'd never propose to you ever again!
I just felt bad for you back then.
It was out of pity, okay?
FRENCH BULLDOG
Oh.
I just noticed that you looked down today.
I do?
Did something happen?
That's good.
Oh.
I might have a slight fever.
What? In that case…
No. I don't need a treatment today.
I'm sorry.
I'm going home.
Yes!
SORA MINASE
Yeah.
Yeah, what's up?
I don't want to go home.
Oh, makes sense.
Can I come over?
What? Now?
Wait, my room right now…
Is really messy…
Where are you right now?
-You find it okay?
-Yeah.
-On Google Maps.
-Right. Come in.
Thank you.
-Hey, Miss Minase?
-Yeah?
Don't do these things to random men.
Certain men of a certain age might
want to do you.
You're doing me?
No! Not me, never!
I'm not so desperate for girls
that I'd need you!
But, you know,
if you do this to random men,
you don't know what they'll think!
I choose my men.
I was chosen! No, that's irrelevant.
I changed the sheets here.
I have water and food in the fridge.
Help yourself.
What about you?
Well, you know,
I'm of a certain age too.
I'll spend the night at a manga café.
It'll be fine! I'll answer your call
in three rings.
I did just now, right?
I jumped out of the shower.
Oh, right.
I'm going here.
Manga Café "Sea Turtle."
It's really close. I can come by
if anything happens.
Did you contact your mom?
Yeah.
I told her
I'm going out all night with a friend.
Okay.
SORA: I'LL BE OUT ALL NIGHT.
KEEP THE CHAIN UNLOCKED FOR ME.
AOI: GOT IT!
Sora's favorite drink.
The Limoncello.
ROOM 53 WITH RECLINING SEAT
-Excuse me?
-Yes?
You have a guest.
What?
Why are you here?
100 YEN
No!
I didn't want to be alone.
So I followed you here.
You're too unguarded all of a sudden.
Because you drew Jadwiga.
What?
Materializing what's in someone's heart
and turning it into a drawing is
the same thing as opening our hearts
to each other, right?
When did you think that?
I just made it up now.
Stop that.
Don't play with my emotions like that!
It's so strange.
When I'm with you, my heart is free.
I really want to cry.
And I don't know what to do.
But with you, I can find an escape route
for my heart.
I'm an escape route then?
But beyond that escape route,
I can see light.
Because my name's Hikaru?
Mom mentioned that.
"You both have pretty names
meaning light and sky,
so why don't you call each other
by first names?"
Whenever I call you Minase,
I see the sky.
I feel like a blue sky is
opening up in front of me.
Was that a joke?
No, I'm serious.
I'm tired.
Today was a tiring day.
I'm going to sleep.
Hey…
What do you mean, sleep?
She's really asleep.
Mom.
Thank you. I'm fine here.
Are you fine by yourself?
Yeah.
It's still three rings, right?
Of course. Buy me dinner next time, okay?
Yeah.
Yakisoba at Odaya? Taiyaki?
Oh.
-Huh?
-There's a gachapon.
CELLS AT WORK
THAT TIME I GOT REINCARNATED AS A SLIME
Do they have White Blood Cell?
Jadwiga will go in here one day!
Good idea.
The shiny glass ball.
You're right.
Your favorite.
My favorite.
If I get it, it's yours.
What?
This makes the city look upside down,
so it's interesting, right?
If you want to cry, look at the world
through this.
Will you get it, though?
Of course I will!
What?
Wow!
This will be my lucky charm.
Yeah!
I'm home.
I just woke up. I'm making coffee.
-Want some?
-Yeah.
Mom.
Yeah?
Am I
not your daughter?
PREVIEW OF NEXT EPISODE
I found this in the forest.
-That's just like the novel.
-This is an umbilical cord, right?
They might take away Sora…
Are bloodlines that important?
I'm worried that Sora's going to break.
Pushing a kid onto Mom, who's not family?
How irresponsible!
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION
Apologize to Suzu!
Subtitle translation by: Yukimi Ohashi