He took her?
He kidnapped her?
She's not coming back?
-No one said that!
-Oh, sorry.
I saw this letter.
"Hey Mom, I decided to travel a bit
with Fuga.
Be well. I'll call you."
This "Be well" seems to have
a deeper meaning.
Don't say things like that!
I don't know what to do
if she doesn't come home ever again.
He's a phony.
Or is he evil?
That Fuga Ichinose, he's a crafty one!
It'll be fine.
She'll most likely come back.
What do you mean, "most likely"?
Not "certainly"?
Say certainly!
Hello!
I knew you were here.
Hey, you!
I have a souvenir from Okinawa.
Okinawa?
You were in Okinawa, Sora?
Okinawa donuts and a shisa.
Mom, your souvenir is at home.
We're decorating now.
Decorating? Who is?
Looks pretty good.
MAIN TITLE
You were in Okinawa for all four days?
Yes. We rode a hot air balloon.
Ichinose said there was a place
we could ride it in Okinawa.
After that, we ate Okinawa soba.
Why didn't you call me?
I thought you'd tell me to come home.
Mom,
you're still mad
at Ichinose, right?
You were mad too.
But he's
a little fun to be with.
Welcome home.
We're home.
Not bad!
Right?
I don't really get it.
You'll start to get it.
The beauty of driftwood.
I'll be on my way, then.
I don't want to interrupt
quality family time.
-Where are you going?
-Home?
I found good lodgings.
A toy store? The one in the corner?
Across from the soba shop?
Yeah.
Do you know yo-yo?
Yo-yo? The toy?
He befriended Granny Obayashi with that.
You're so good!
Is this fine? It's not much.
It's very nice.
This is the ideal room.
Apparently, he was already
asked to do interiors for Taiyou-Do,
where Doctor Wataru works.
He was asked to decorate it
Asian style, with driftwood.
Wow!
This is very nice!
He even found a job.
This soccer ball?
-Oh, let me help.
-I'm sure his rent is super cheap.
It's 1,100 yen.
He's got great survival
and communication skills.
Yeah. And then,
he got permission to park his car
inside Hikawa Shrine.
He even sells driftwood there.
And people buy it!
I've never seen anyone like that.
Even in Okinawa, he got stuff
for free from people!
That's what you noticed?
He found a big job
to do the interiors
for a resort hotel there.
He's very skilled at living life.
I'm bad at stuff like that.
Most kids these days are.
You're a kid these days too!
Oh, that's true, I am.
I've never met
someone that's
quite like him.
I think I should keep observing him.
Not because he's your father?
The fact that he's my father
must have some meaning, right?
I just thought
you were very much Aoi Minase's daughter.
Well, not by blood.
What do you mean?
You have a unique perspective on things.
Is it strange?
No, it's a compliment.
I meant it as a compliment.
Hey, I'm really taking this to
Jump, alright?
Oh, in that case.
Should we submit this
to a new talent contest?
-New talent contest?
-It's this.
SUZURAN SHOPPING DISTRICT
MEN, WOMEN
Hello!
Aoi. Long time no see.
I couldn't write, so I came here
to feel refreshed.
It felt so nice!
Aoi.
Aoi Minase.
Won't you come up?
Ms. Minase!
Ms. Aoi!
Stop it!
Everyone's watching!
What? I can't hear.
Aoi!
OBAYASHI TOYS
So you came.
This is Ryugu Sake, from Okinawa.
You want some?
What do you want from us?
You chased us all the way here,
and then you stayed.
What do you want from us?
What do you think?
Hey, I made some
daikon radish and squid stew.
Please have some.
Wow, it looks good!
Here.
-Chopsticks for you, Aoi.
-Oh, no, I…
I heard you know each other.
Aoi used to be
our customer back in the day.
After that, it was Sora.
-Join us, Kanae.
-What?
I prefer to be alone.
I feel more relaxed that way.
I'll eat this on my own while watching TV.
But Aoi, having him here with me,
he's like a bodyguard. I feel so safe!
I'll protect you from anything.
Including the bad men?
Because you're so beautiful.
I didn't think my radishes
would buy all this flattery!
-It's true, you know!
-Alright.
Right?
The fact that Kanae of Obayashi Toys
is beautiful
has been said by everyone
in Suzuran District for many years.
You're beautiful too.
-It's good.
-Right?
This is
a very rare sake.
They rest unprocessed awamori sake
for 20 years to get this aged sake.
They're very hard to come by.
I'll have some of Kanae's radishes.
Good, right?
I'm going home soon.
Oh!
RYUGU
Want to play this?
Doing it alone is boring.
No, thank you.
If I play this and win,
will you go back to Ouse Island quickly?
I see.
Sure. I'm fine with that.
You promise?
Yes.
Let's play.
You're doing it again.
You try to take the risky one
in the middle.
You haven't changed.
I won.
I think I'll stay for a little longer.
Why?
Why did you lie about forgetting me?
Why did you lie?
I'm sorry.
When you came to see me…
Long time no see.
It's me, Aoi.
Sora's eyes
looked exactly like Suzu's.
It was like Suzu was standing
right in front of me.
I couldn't say that I remembered you.
So I lied.
Also,
I was hesitant because you came to see me
so suddenly.
To be honest, I was shocked.
I couldn't imagine
that it was reality.
I'm so sorry.
You supported Suzu.
And to think
that you
raised Suzu's child.
We became
best friends.
What?
Suzu and me.
Two women with the same scars.
We were two people
who couldn't forget you.
Yes, you were a terrible man.
You had many other women.
Maybe to others,
you were a worthless shithead.
Yes. I was a worthless shithead.
But you had a charm that
surpassed the bad parts.
Love can be like that, you know?
Like, "Why do I even like someone
like this?"
That's why
neither Suzu nor I
wanted to deny
falling in love with you.
That's why Suzu
decided to have Sora.
I never said this
to Suzu,
but I always thought,
"Why does Suzu get to have your child,
and I can't?"
It was frustrating.
That's how much
I loved you.
Of course, it's all in the past.
But even so, I'm crying.
It's very strange.
But…
Why?
Why weren't you with her?
Why didn't you stay with Suzu?
Don't you know how scary it is
for a woman to have a child all alone?
And she was sick!
Fuga!
Can I punch you?
Yes.
That is for Suzu.
Um…
I have a favor to ask.
You punched him?
More like a slap.
My hand still hurts.
Is Ichinose okay?
You're worried about him?
Nah. But Ichinose didn't know
that Suzu was pregnant
with his kid, right?
By kid, I mean me.
He didn't know.
So it's not his fault.
It is his fault!
It's his fault for abandoning
his girlfriends!
But he remembered.
Both you and Suzu, right?
He did remember.
I'm glad.
I'm glad he remembered my two moms.
Hey, you're too soft on Ichinose.
Did he brainwash you?
His handsomeness
reminds me of Itachi Uchiha from Naruto.
It's too powerful.
Mom.
I want to go again.
If you, Ichinose, and I
visited her all together,
I'm sure Mother Suzu would feel relieved
in heaven,
up in the sky.
HOSHINO FAMILY
The weather is nice.
It's cold.
Want to go warm up?
Want to go to a hot spring?
Where? Hakone?
No. Suzuran Hot Springs.
Good idea!
Hey.
That hits the spot!
"Hits the spot"?
You're like a grandma.
You want to say it too, Mom.
So just say it.
That hits the spot!
It feels nicer when you say that.
I feel like
I've finished an important job.
Bringing you and Fuga to that grave,
I think that was a major duty
that I was given.
I see.
Work is
a big duty one must do in life.
I see. I guess life has its duties.
Things we have to do…
Hello!
Should we get out soon?
You two beauties!
Yes!
We're about to get overheated.
Hey, you!
I wanted to try this once.
Conversing between the men's
and women's baths.
Alright.
Let's say, "cheers!"
Cheers!
LEMON PAGE, AOI MINASE'S NEW WORK,
MIDSUMMER SKIES ARE DREAMS
It's good!
Minase Sensei's new work,
Midsummer Skies are Dreams.
The illustration is nice too!
It's refreshing. Like a new wind
is blowing.
I'm happy with it too.
Now, we can relax a bit about Aoi Minase.
Looks like a lot's going on
in her family life, though.
But maybe that was all good inspiration.
And did you inspire her?
I didn't quite get there.
It's fine. You've done well.
Now, you can go to New York.
-What?
-It's a great honor.
You'll be transferred to
Saneisha New York.
Go sell some manga in New York, alright?
An international copyrighting business.
Well, that's just a front.
Mr. Yuzuru Yube
lives in New York right now.
Soseki took the blame for
Mr. Yuzuru Yube's
plagiarism incident,
got transferred from manga,
and became Mom's editor.
Mr. Yube
would only accept you.
He wants you to be his editor.
But…
NEW BOOKS 4.7 MILLION COPIES
Listen.
Mr. Yube's Isekai Wonder is
a big hit right now.
It might even surpass Jump.
That's what Shonen Up editors are saying.
I'm going back to the Manga Department?
I don't want you to go either.
Trust me.
Because you're cute.
That's a little gross.
Think rationally.
Saneisha's main business
is manga and anime.
And their best magazine
asked me for you.
So I have to.
Do your best, alright?
For our company.
I talked to Ichinose about you in Okinawa.
About me?
Yeah. Ichinose
wanted to know what kind of mom you are.
Yes.
I heard many funny stories.
Like Sora's middle school
graduation ceremony.
All the students were holding back tears,
and just when someone was about to cry,
they heard a loud sobbing from the back.
Right. You cried first, Mom.
Because of that, no one could cry!
I felt really bad about that.
Oh! I have another story!
Sora! You drank too much!
I can drink more.
Do you want to have more
at my room on the second floor
of Obayashi?
I want to buy the drink we bought
at Okinawa! The shikuwasa sake.
Oh. That's still in the car.
Let's go grab it!
You're really drunk, you know?
I've always wanted to try something
as a kid.
Mom on the left, Dad on the right.
We hold hands,
and you lift me up!
Want to try now?
What? Right now?
I'm already grown!
Let's try it!
Let's go!
Mom, you have to hold my hand harder!
One, two.
We did it!
We did it.
All three of them together?
Yeah. They looked like a real family.
Well, they are family.
So that's Fuga Ichinose, huh?
It should be in that wooden box.
This one?
Are these photos from Okinawa?
-Photos of the sky?
-Yes.
-"Sora"? Of you?
-No.
The sky.
The blue sky.
You take a photo of the sky every day?
Well…
Yes.
Huh?
This is the photo you took of me.
I'm bad at this!
It stopped on March 14th.
OBAYASHI TOYS
Why did you stop taking photos of the sky
after taking
a picture of me?
Because you didn't need to?
Because you met the real Sora?
Did you know about Sora?
Is that why you took those photos?
Every day,
so you didn't forget about her.
It wasn't so that I don't forget.
How could I forget?
About me?
Because my name means sky?
Could it be
that the whole bag was filled with
pictures of the sky?
No way. That's gross and creepy.
Sorry, Dad.
Wait, no. I take that back.
No way, Anguidae!
Otterly weird, get otter here!
No way, no way, Nile crocodile!
Hell, hell, snail shell!
-What are you saying?
-I have an appointment!
I'll be going now!
SUPER SPICY TANTANMEN
Alright!
SORA MINASE
Who is it?
-Hello?
-I…
I called him "Dad!"
I called Dad "Dad."
At least say hello.
You would've seen my name on the screen!
I don't just live for you, you know.
I'm not some innocent girl waiting
by my phone all day
waiting for you to call!
Enough about that!
I called him Dad!
Who?
Fuga Ichinose!
He was taking photos of the sky.
The sky, not of me.
He took them every day
all the years before meeting me.
That's very moving.
No.
But it felt a bit like
he was a stalker.
Without thinking,
I called him gross and creepy.
That's so mean!
And then, I said,
"Sorry, Dad!"
What's going on with my head?
That sounds plausible.
Maybe deep, deep down in your heart,
you were moved,
and wanted to call him Dad.
-Wrong!
-I'm wrong?
Generally, you may be right,
but I think you're a little off.
If I'm generally right,
then let me have this one!
If I'm only a little off, it's fine!
Hey, I'm about to have the
Super Spicy Tantanmen from Hell.
So I'm hanging up in one minute.
Instant noodles take
2 minutes, 47 seconds, right?
Right.
There's no compromising instant ramen
cooking times.
Please eat your
Super Spicy Tantanmen from Hell.
Right. But I have 50 more seconds.
Prepare some chopsticks and water.
Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
But Ichinose didn't know about you,
right, Sora?
What?
About your existence.
Oh! You're right.
He didn't know that
Suzu, my birth mother,
was pregnant
and had me.
Then why did he take photos of the sky?
The sky above.
I know.
It's weird, right?
Doesn't that mean
he knew that you existed?
He knew your name too.
What does that mean?
So you knew about Sora?
Did you take photos
of the sky every day,
since the day she was born?
Yes.
But
how did you know about Sora?
I received a letter from Suzu.
Twenty years ago.
After she had Sora.
To be more exact,
it was a reply to my letter.
I sent her a letter
asking if we could get back together.
Her response was no.
She wouldn't be getting back with me.
But, that she gave birth to a baby girl.
She is your child.
Her name is Sora, meaning sky.
She'll be with someone else.
That's what the letter said.
Someone else?
"I have someone I love.
I'll start a new family with this person."
The letter said,
"This person accepted
me and Sora."
There was no one like that.
That's why I believed
Suzu started a new family.
That's why
I was surprised when you came to me
with Sora.
Why would she lie?
Maybe to avoid a scandal?
Because you had just
landed a big role.
So maybe to protect you?
That means
you've been taking a photo
of the sky every day
since you received
the letter from Suzu?
It's creepy, huh?
But she…
She called you Dad.
A letter?
A letter from Mother Suzu?
What did you think about
on hearing that, Mom?
What do you mean?
How did you feel?
I just learned that
they had exchanged letters
without me knowing.
That's all.
I guess I'm a little sad.
But maybe Suzu
didn't want to tell me.
She probably thought
if she told you, you would go away.
What? Why?
Because he didn't write
a letter to you.
But he wrote to Suzu.
It means he loved Suzu more.
You hit me right where it hurts!
Sorry.
But maybe if she told you, you could've
gotten mad
or jealous,
and felt bad
and have gone away.
You might have told her to go and
be with Ichinose.
I probably would've said that.
I don't know about
jealousy or anger,
but I would've thought it's better
to be raised by your real mom and dad.
But Suzu didn't think so.
Rather than being raised by
the mysterious Ichinose with many women,
she thought it was better
if I was raised by you.
If she ever died.
She trusted me like that,
but was I able to raise you properly?
I'll prove it.
I'm a pretty good kid, aren't I?
Long time no see.
It's been a while.
What is it?
You look as if you've seen a ghost.
Look, I have legs.
Why did you
lie to me?
Hey.
That's the first thing you say to me?
I'm sorry.
I'm really…
sorry.
I lied?
Oh, about that?
I should be allowed to say
I have a new man, don't you think?
You really mistreated me, you know?
I told you I had Sora
because I wanted to be a good mom.
It was the pride of a woman.
"I left your child
in this world before I went."
It was my statement.
Why didn't you get back with me then?
Because I couldn't trust you.
But
I'm glad you're doing well.
You too, Suzu.
Hey.
I can't reach down from
up above the clouds very well.
Take care of stuff
in this world, alright?
Promise me.
ODAYA
What I'm saying is,
because Mom is too giving
and kind,
I'm worried that…
What is it?
Maybe Mom
gave up on marriage
for my sake.
Maybe she gave up on having
her own kids for me.
You don't get it, do you?
She's not the type!
Actually,
could she think like that?
Hey,
you left for France
a year after Sora was born.
I was observing Aoi from here
for all these years.
So let me say this.
Sora.
I'd say,
your concerns are groundless.
You're worried over nothing.
Aoi, with her beauty,
was always popular with boys.
And Sora, you were so cute too.
Aoi would tell them,
"If you marry me,
you get to be with
this very cute girl too!
It's like getting both
a diamond and an emerald!
Aren't you so lucky?"
She said that all the time.
She's strong!
Whether they were doctors or bureaucrats,
all the men
were after her.
Stories like that about Aoi
always piss me off!
Gon-chan, are we talking about that now?
We're talking about me.
Sorry.
There's nothing for you to be
concerned about, Sora.
Aoi just felt
more at home
staying with just the two of you,
Sora.
That's why she didn't marry.
That's all.
Can I ask you something else?
Hey, ask me something too.
One question remains.
Why did Mother Suzu,
Suzu, who passed away,
let Fuga Ichinose know
that I existed, in her letter?
If she didn't want to
be in the way of an up and coming star,
she should have kept quiet about me.
I think that Suzu, before she died,
wanted to leave you with
another person to depend on
in case something happened to Aoi.
It's much easier on children if they have
two parents instead of just one.
It's better to have more people
to protect you.
That's why I think
she told Fuga Ichinose
that he had a daughter.
That's my opinion.
He might be
some kind of help to you in the future
when you need him.
Please…
don't tell
Mom about that, okay?
Sora.
I'm sure Aoi knows.
We've received great feedback
for Midsummer Skies are Dreams.
The reader survey is good too.
Sure, the survey is fine.
Huh? What's wrong?
Why do you ask?
Your tone is gloomy.
It's very obvious.
Hold on. Could it be…?
I checked online.
I told you not to do that!
Stop Googling yourself!
You know, the thing is,
even after reading 100 good comments,
if I find one criticism,
that's all I think about!
What did it say?
That I'm behind the times.
Ms. Aoi.
At one time,
you released several
explosive hit books that sold over
a million copies.
Like The Scent of the Sky
and The Tears About to Fall.
That's true.
Ms. Aoi.
Only writers who survive
for an era and leave
a strong impression on the public
get to be "behind the times."
The only way you can tell if an author
is truly behind the times
is if she's able to continue writing
fresh work right now.
That's what I believe.
Ms. Aoi, you haven't retired,
and you still feel strongly.
And, you've got energy.
Watching you like that,
I start thinking that the times will
end up
being behind you.
I'm so glad you're my editor, Soseki.
-About that…
-Sorry!
A three-star restaurant just
opened a bakery in Suzuran District.
They serve fresh-baked cream bread
at five o'clock!
So, I gotta go!
Bread comes before me, huh?
UMBILICAL CORD, AOI MINASE
I see.
You went with Ichinose and your mother
to visit your birth mother's grave?
I'm glad we did it.
Hey.
I asked Ichinose
to do the Taiyou-Do interiors
on purpose.
So that Ichinose could
stay in Suzuran.
Why?
So that he could spend
more time with you.
I lost my parents
when I was young
and I had many regrets.
I've always wished I could
talk to them more.
So I thought
you would think the same thing
if Ichinose left.
You got a great opportunity.
So I wanted to give you more time
to be together.
Doctor Wataru…
Mana, you don't have a Switch!
Yeah.
You can't play if you don't have a Switch.
-You can't join us!
-Bye!
The Fourth World from the Right.
-For the title?
-Yeah.
It means the world I live in
is just one out of
many worlds.
It doesn't feel very Jump.
-That's true.
-Yeah.
-I got it. I'll think about it more.
-Okay.
Hey.
About this panel…
Your drawing sucks.
I have no idea what this is!
Sorry.
Hey, don't apologize!
Otherwise, I'm just a mean girl.
You're right.
Hey, to change the subject,
are you hungry?
-I am!
-Alright.
Ichinose!
Your timer was beeping so I turned it off.
Oh, thank you.
I was making rafute
with the awamori.
We were making Okinawa food together.
-Join us, Aoi.
-But I have this.
Oh, that's the popular bakery!
Next to Café Tomoshibi, right?
-Exactly!
-Wow!
Save that
for tomorrow's breakfast.
Did you hear that, Aoi? So come over!
So delicious!
I'm glad.
You were always a good cook.
You could only boil water.
How did you date a girl like me?
Even though I thought you forgot about me.
No.
You were like
a sunflower.
A sunflower in the summer.
I was always
a heavy and gloomy person.
I was the type to do
underground theater in Shimokita.
If I was an unpopular literary magazine
with a thick letterpress,
the one week I spent with you
is the color-print page of my life.
A color-printed pinup girl?
Exactly.
But you'd get tired if the whole book
was printed in color.
You can't relax.
Want to play Jenga?
Great idea!
What should we bet on?
Let me think.
The Scent
of the Sky.
We Can Meet Again.
Tomorrow.
What is it?
An Off-Handed Goodbye.
Crybaby
Evening.
I read
all of your books.
They were all beautiful.
I fell in love
with many people after that.
After we broke up.
But
I couldn't truly love anyone else.
On stage
you were so beautiful,
and off the stage
you were very loveable.
Now,
I'm just some driftwood seller.
But you haven't changed.
You're the only you
in this whole entire world.
I'll take the smaller one.
-Really?
-Yeah.
So good!
Hey.
-Drink it!
-I can't.
How nice!
You're doing it
later tonight, right?
Stop it!
Hey, she's pretty cute!
Let me touch you!
-Don't touch her!
-What the hell?
Hey, stop! Stop!
Shut up!
Hey!
-Hey!
-Stop it!
What are you guys doing!
I'll call the police.
Shit.
This is bad.
You okay?
-Are you alright?
-Yes.
They're just some brats that are
always loitering around here.
Go home!
This area isn't safe.
It's not like where you live.
My glasses.
Where are my glasses?
They're cracked. The frames too.
I'm really nearsighted.
I can't see without them.
I'll put these away. Do you have spares?
I have a spare pair at home.
I'll head home for now.
I'll walk you home.
So you don't fall.
Okay.
Hey.
What is it?
I thought only
boyfriends and girlfriends held hands.
It's because it's an emergency.
Your glasses are broken.
I see.
Hey, it's red.
I can see that.
It's just blurry.
You don't wear contacts?
I'm scared to put them in my eyes.
That's true.
It's snowing!
It's beautiful.
I wonder if Sora's seeing
this snow right now.
Aoi.
What if we…
got together again?
What?
Or rather,
start together again?
What are you doing?
The Scent of the Snow.
Oh, your mom's novel!
The Scent of the Sky.
It does smell like snow!
What kind of smell is it?
Doesn't it smell like mints?
It stings.
It's green. We can cross.
Even though no one's here.
One day…
One day, in the future.
We're sophomores in college now.
We'll become juniors in April.
We'll start looking for jobs.
And we won't draw manga.
Don't talk about that when we're about to
submit to Jump!
I know.
That's why
this is all theoretical.
A story about
the third world from the right.
Then, we'll graduate college,
we'll become adults,
and start working.
We won't draw manga,
and when something happens,
I won't call you
and ask you to help me.
That will all
go away.
That's not true.
Nothing will change.
It will change!
Not everything
will change.
What is it?
The Scent of Hikaru.
What the hell is that?
Do I stink? Am I okay?
You smell like grass.
Like my childhood.
How romantic!
I'll remember
this smell, always.
One day,
I'll remember this day,
I'll remember this moment,
and think back on it longingly.
That's what I think now.
Even after
the light turned green,
we couldn't start walking.
THE FINAL EPISODE
-Won't you go to New York with me?
-What?
I just cast a spell on you.
All the men want Mom!
She might go away.
Even if your mom goes to
Okinawa, I'm right here.
Get out! Get out of this town!
I'll decide where to go myself!
Subtitle translation by: