Ms. Aoi.
What if we….
got together again?
What?
DON'T FORGET ME BY AOI MINASE
FILM ADAPTATION!
Wow, this is
so great. Wonderful!
Si-Kni's Yuto will play the lead…
-Si-Kni?
-Silent Knife!
When we announced that Yuto
will play the lead
for the film adaptation of
Don't Forget Me,
DFM, or Don't Forget Me,
got 300,000 reprints!
Your past works
are also selling because of this.
Reprint after reprint!
Midsummer Skies are Dreams
is doing extremely well.
A good wind is blowing our way!
Let's ride this out!
Let's ride! It'll be a breeze!
Yes, thanks to you,
I'm getting more new jobs.
Hey, Mom. You got
an offer for a Unishiro commercial.
Oh, I see.
You're happy, even though
you don't wear them?
How did you know that?
It's obvious from your expression.
A bunch of people will
appear in the footage.
You're one of many.
-Oh, then please say no.
-Ryo.
What is "Ryo"?
Konishi, you're so old!
It's short for "ryokai," or roger!
I'm joking. I know that.
Right now, even "Ri" is old.
You're declining the Unishiro offer?
What a waste!
Maybe I can go on instead.
I'd appear solo.
As expected from Aoi Minase!
You'll only appear
in a Unishiro commercial solo.
I don't hate that big ego
of yours, you know.
What's with you?
I'm saying that the only one
who could be Aoi Minase's editor
other than Soseki, is me.
I see.
Soseki will be transferring
this coming April.
To Saneisha New York.
-What?
-Mr. Konishi.
Why did you tell them?
I wanted to tell them myself!
I'm sorry.
I tried to tell you many times
over the phone.
I know! You requested the transfer
because you didn't
want to deal with me!
How did you come to
such a pessimistic conclusion?
I mean, it's hard to deal with me.
So, you do know.
No, that was a joke.
No!
You're so carefree,
but you become a little girl sometimes.
I was always afraid
of being by myself when
walking to the science room,
or eating lunch.
That's why I acted bubbly and friendly!
And now, we're here.
I was asked by
Fuga Ichinose
if I would go with him to Okinawa.
If we could get back together.
He found a long-term driftwood job
in Okinawa.
Doing interiors for a luxury hotel.
He's going to be
working on the hotel's interiors
for three years.
He said we'd find a house to
live in very cheaply.
Are you going?
I'm still thinking.
What if you
go to New York with me instead?
What?
Isn't the moon a little plump today?
Maybe it should go on a diet!
Sora! You here?
You're too loud.
Can't you see that I'm here?
Listen.
I'm so popular with the men right now!
Where's Gon-chan?
He's at Suzuran Hot Springs,
then he's going to a dinner party.
So you're popular right now?
Let's have some beer to celebrate!
Yes, let's!
-That's good!
-Shunichiro.
I've been wanting to say this to you
for a long time.
What is it?
The way you wear a hoodie under
the kimono is so cool!
Oh, not at all.
You're the only one in
the world who can pull that off!
The world, huh? That's a big statement!
So what is this about you
being popular with the men?
Sora, you listen too.
Another bragging story from you?
No. Before, I was bragging about
how popular I was in the past.
But now, I'm popular in the present!
I got proposed to!
By Fuga Ichinose and Soseki.
I wish it happened during separate times!
I wish it was separate.
I don't want it all at once.
But my choices aren't that great.
An ex, and Soseki, who's just nearby.
Mom, be nice!
You should be grateful.
That's true. I am grateful.
So, Sora.
Fuga found a house for us in Okinawa.
This one.
And if we go to New York with Soseki,
you can study abroad.
There are a lot of colleges
that work with Rissei Gakuin.
What are you saying, Mom?
I won't be going. I have school.
So you can study abroad.
I won't do that.
Oh, right. I see.
Because of Hikaru?
Why is that relevant?
I take that back!
That was toxic of me.
Eventually, children will
leave their parents.
That's true.
But Gon-chan and Shunichiro live together.
That's possible too.
Mom might need care one day.
It's too early for that.
I won't be a burden to you.
That's why I bought that house.
Eventually, I'll sell it
and get into a luxury senior home.
What? You're not giving me that house?
You earn your own living, Sora!
You let me live that luxury lifestyle!
And now, this?
Calm down, you two.
Today, we have
bamboo shoots and rice!
I'd like some, please!
That was so refreshing!
I love that they have a sauna here.
I was wondering why you were
in such great shape.
Is it because of driftwood?
Yes, I pick it up
on the beach.
On the beach?
The one I left with you,
this is for
the chiropractor,
Taiyou-Do.
Do you lift the big ones too?
Sure do.
Some are three times my size.
How nice! You're so strong.
Around here, it's just skinny men
working in IT.
They're smart, right?
They have money, so they go to
an expensive gym and train
to be popular with young women!
But men should be about the sea,
and driftwood!
Each one is different.
These curves have their unique beauty.
I'm sure they'll look nice here.
Really? How nice.
Maybe I'll ask my husband.
Auntie.
Give me fruit milk too.
Make it a double.
What are you saying?
So whether it's Okinawa or New York,
I'd be leaving you, huh?
You have to pick one.
You can't go to both. That'd be bigamy.
Yeah.
Both sound fun.
With your job, you can work anywhere.
But I can't speak English.
But in Okinawa, they'd look at you funny
if you wore Saint Laurent.
They look at you funny
in Suzuran Shopping District too.
-Really?
-Yup.
I didn't notice at all.
Excuse me.
How long will you be here?
I'm going to Okinawa soon.
And you are?
I'm from Odaya.
I run the taiyaki shop right next door.
So you're Gon-chan.
Odaya's taiyaki is very popular.
I'm not good with sweets, you see.
But you're drinking fruit milk now.
You're supposed to have fruit milk
after a bath!
Is that so?
But you serve
different types of foods, right?
I heard from Kanae at Obayashi.
I'm not sure if we have anything
to your liking.
Just things like yakisoba and oden.
I love those!
When will you be leaving?
By next weekend.
Thank god!
What? Oh, no.
Don't you feel that way when you
look at this painting?
"Thank god!"
Anyways,
the moon and cheese.
Keynes is a romantic, right?
He's acting all cool,
but he looks like this.
The last report of the year
is due next class!
What?
It's already goodbye, huh?
-Minase!
-What?
Did you take notes?
I was focused on our manga name.
I forgot to take notes.
That's what I thought,
so I took very detailed notes!
The Scent of Hikaru.
I'll copy this and give it back.
Recently,
Mom's been popular with the guys.
Your mom is pretty, after all.
And she's young.
She got proposed to.
What? That's fast!
She might go away.
I'll be glad to be alone.
-Hello.
-Welcome!
Oh, I can step out.
We were just about to go out.
Sally, I got transferred to
Saneisha New York.
I see.
Be well.
Sorry about the other day.
Sally.
Be happy, alright?
You too.
It's nothing.
We'll be going, then.
You're going to New York?
Yes. That's why
I wanted oden from here before I left.
I'm sorry, Shunichiro.
About what?
I don't have any feelings
for Soseki anymore.
I see.
Do you doubt me?
Nope.
If that's what you say,
then it must be true.
I trust you.
You're so kind.
To be completely honest,
it can't be helped that
you don't get over the person
you used to love completely.
We're all human.
It's strange to be able to
cut them off completely.
You can bring
all that with you.
Shunichiro.
You know?
As long as you're laughing,
and not crying,
and
if you're happy, that's all I care about.
That's my greatest wish.
-I found it.
-What?
My happiness.
I found you!
-Good evening.
-Welcome!
Oh.
We met at the bath, didn't we?
What'll it be?
Right.
-I'll have a beer first.
-Coming up!
It's done.
OKINAWA WITH FUGA, NY WITH SOSEKI
DRINK
Roger that!
What if we…
got back together?
Do I really have to decide?
I wish I could
stay in this moment forever.
Why does life keep moving forward?
Why can't we go back?
I'd love to stay
in this present moment forever.
I want to stay in this moment forever.
What if you…
came to New York with me instead?
What if he was just teasing me?
Who is it?
Please give this to her.
Sorry, Sora's not here right now.
She's seeing Doctor Wataru today,
then working at Odaya.
It's fine. It's not like we had plans.
Just wanted to
return this ASAP.
What are you guys studying?
The moon and cheese?
Won't you come in? I can make tea.
Oh, it's alright!
I have to write a report.
Right. I see.
Thank you for this.
Um…
I heard you were leaving Tokyo.
You got proposed to?
What?
Oh no, Sora talks about that stuff?
Yes.
I hear you're popular with the guys now.
Right.
Once every four years.
Once in a blue moon. Like Halley's comet.
It all came crashing at once!
Sora looked lonely.
What?
Because you might be going somewhere.
Sora said she was lonely?
She didn't, but it's obvious.
You can see it in her face.
I see.
She doesn't show that to me.
She's someone
who can't say she's lonely.
What?
Because I always say it first.
And I'm not great at
picking up on people's emotions.
Sora
loves you a lot.
Here's your yakisoba.
This is delicious.
What is this?
It's just a chikuwa.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Truly.
It's fine.
I knew your heart wasn't
in it, and I pretended
not to notice.
Doctor…
Do you have
someone else you like?
What?
I don't know if I like them.
I don't really know anything about love.
I see.
There's no need to force a label
on your feelings or relationships.
What?
That's what I think.
Just let it be.
Let it be?
But
it's an important relationship, right?
And you don't want to lose it.
I don't want to
lose it.
Protect it, then.
Protect it?
Yeah. You have to protect
what you don't want to lose.
Doctor Wataru.
I'll never be called "Doctor Wataru"
with your cute voice again.
My voice isn't
that cute.
That was lame to say.
I'm sorry.
It's partially my fault
that I couldn't
create a relationship with you
that you didn't want to lose.
But even then,
I loved you a lot, Doctor Wataru.
Past tense…
I knew that,
and it made me feel happy.
I also
loved how direct
and honest you were, Sora.
I used the past tense too.
So we're even.
Good luck,
Sora.
Huh?
You may not be able to
meet someone like that ever again
in your life.
That relationship of yours.
Here's another.
-More hot sake for you.
-Thank you.
I heard Aoi
also comes here often.
What?
And Sora works here too, right?
Thank you
for taking care of them.
Why are you thanking me?
We've been close for many years.
I know that.
When are you going to Okinawa?
Maybe next week.
I see.
With Aoi too.
What?
I think Aoi will be joining me.
We had a little something in the past.
And now too.
Honestly, I don't hate it.
You know, old flames and all.
Aoi's not bad for her age too.
She's a pretty good woman.
It'd be a waste if she stayed single.
I was patient with you because
you're a customer! What are you saying?
Don't come crawling back
to a woman of your past!
Get out of this town!
Stop it, Gon!
-What's going on?
-Does that hurt?
Aoi was hurting
so much more!
Right here!
Abandoned by a man she loved.
And raising his woman's child!
-Stop! Don't listen!
-Please, Gon.
Don't you know how hard it is
to raise a child
all on your own?
What you did was evil! You're the devil!
You're not human!
Gon!
Don't go around
calling Aoi a good woman!
Don't look at her with those filthy eyes!
Are you jealous?
Stop it!
Don't you know how hard it was for Sora?
Learning Aoi wasn't her real mom!
It's all your fault!
What nerve you've got,
coming here like that. Get out.
Leave this town!
I'll do as I please.
Listen closely, bastard!
Calm down, Gon!
I won't give you
Aoi or Sora!
You abandoned them once.
How can they trust you?
They don't belong to you.
-Gon!
-Stop it, Gon-chan!
I'll protect them!
Aoi and Sora are
mine!
-Stop it, Gon-chan! He'll die!
-Let go!
-He'll die!
-Stop, Gon!
-He's laughing!
-Please…
He seems to be relieved
that you punched him.
Hey.
Who are you?
I'm nobody.
I just happened to pass by.
SANEISHA SOSEKI TACHIBANA
I thought it would be better
if I told you.
Don't you need to go to the hospital?
-I'll be alright.
-That really happened?
It might be better to let Sora
be on her own for a bit.
Is Ichinose alright?
Are you worried about him?
Well…
Sora's with him.
Ichinose's a grown man too.
That's right.
He's a grown man.
If I did this at Obayashi,
Kanae will worry.
Why were you laughing?
Even though you got beaten up.
I wasn't laughing.
I don't believe
that something like this will
relieve my sins,
but I felt relief at someone condemning me
for my wrongdoings.
I could've taken five more punches.
You'd have died.
Gon-chan used to be
a Crows Zero youth back in the day.
Do you wish
I had punched you?
I'm not sure about that.
You're a girl, after all.
Here.
It was in my pocket.
Should I put it on?
No.
I'll do it.
Hey, Dad?
What kind of girl
did you think
I would be
as you took
pictures of the sky
every day?
Maybe you felt
disappointed that I was like this.
You grew up
inside my mind
slowly, over the years.
I wasn't told when your birthday was,
so I couldn't celebrate it.
But you grew up
year by year,
inside my mind.
I never imagined
I could ever meet you.
Should I put this on?
Your mouth's cut up.
No.
I'm not going to use this.
I'll keep this with me.
Alright, all finished!
Now, we just need a title.
Right.
Hey.
I actually have an idea for a title.
What is it?
But it's so embarrassing!
-Come on!
-Ask me what it is.
What is it, then?
The World with You.
Hear me out.
In a dilapidated world with no stories,
Emil and Jadwiga meet.
No matter how terrible the world becomes,
for Emil, it's the world
where Jadwiga exists.
As long as Jadwiga doesn't die.
That's the most important thing to Emil.
The World with You.
That's really good!
The World with You is a really cool title!
What? No way!
But it's not very Jump, don't you think?
Maybe Jump won't like it. But I like it.
Is that more important?
Because it's our manga.
Right. Alright!
It's decided then!
Now, we just have to draw the cover
and send it off to Jump!
I'm so nervous!
Same here!
I've provided Konishi with
all the necessary documents.
I think you're in great hands, Ms. Aoi.
Yes. Thank you.
I'll be going now.
Hey, wait a minute.
Today's your last day, right?
Yes, that's right.
-You're going to New York, right?
-Yes.
So…
What about your offer the other day?
What offer?
Are you playing dumb?
In that case…
why don't you go to New York with me?
Were you teasing me?
No.
I was serious.
But
I don't have to ask to know the answer.
You don't intend on coming with me
to New York, do you?
Wait a minute. I was…
I was thinking of what to say.
I'm a writer, after all.
But,
in conclusion, you won't be
coming with me, right?
Remember when I said,
"Let's put a lid on it for three months."
Why don't we put a lid on it?
It hasn't been three months yet.
And I haven't changed.
But for you,
a lot of things have happened.
I didn't want to burden you
with rejecting me.
And I didn't want our last time together
to be emotional.
This is our last time together?
Yes.
I'll be leaving Japan
next Wednesday on the afternoon flight.
Which airport? Narita or Haneda?
Narita.
So you're really going.
Let me be emotional,
if this is our last time.
As expected of you, Ms. Aoi.
You're already talking with the assumption
that you'll say no.
Alright, then.
I'll ask again.
Will you
come to New York with me?
Soseki…
It feels real when I say it.
Even though the answer's no.
Soseki, I'm sorry.
I can't come with you.
You just wanted to say that, huh?
You wanted to reject me.
-No! I was getting to the important part!
-What?
When I met you,
I thought it was the end of me.
I thought I had already peaked.
That no one cared about my work.
But I'm not my work.
I'm a human being, with a heart.
And hearts move.
And words pour out.
Those words,
those stories,
may move someone else's heart.
I'm a human, so I'll keep writing.
You made me
realize that.
That time,
you,
Soseki,
told me that you got into this industry
to work with me.
And you cried for me.
Because of those tears,
I can continue to write.
I'll keep
cheering you on from afar.
I'm alwayson your side.
Don't forget me!
Remember when that happened?
They tried to change the whole story.
It was scary.
Soseki!
Don't forget me!
You're a pretty powerful character.
I couldn't forget you,
even if I wanted to.
Hey…
I'll remember you each time I look
at a 1,000 yen bill.
Ms. Aoi.
The 1,000 yen bill isn't Soseki Natsume
anymore.
It's Hideyo Noguchi.
Oh, right.
But even then,
I won't forget you.
I promise.
You don't need to
promise.
I respect you, Mom.
You rely on men, then cut them off.
You cry, begging them to not forget you,
but you don't go to New York.
As expected of
the Queen of Romance Novels.
A professional woman!
You make me sound so evil.
So?
What about Ichinose?
What are you going to do?
You man magnet! Tell me!
-Stop it!
-Hey, you!
How nice, to be wanted!
You're really going?
Yes, to Okinawa.
I'll send you Okinawa shallots.
It'll be lonely around here.
Oh?
A friend request? Who is it?
KURUMI SAWANO
Kurumi?
I brought you these.
Work hard, alright?
What? That's it?
I'm in the middle of making deliveries.
Gorgonzola flavor?
It's pretty good.
I've continued to write
what people call "romance novels,"
but in actuality,
I can't live for love
and I never will.
Even if my prince comes,
I can't get on a white horse that
will take me away somewhere.
I decide
where to go on my own.
I walk with my own two feet.
Or, I book my own business class ticket.
I'm no longer a woman that tags along
when she's invited.
For better or worse,
that's who I am.
I'm so annoying!
But,
this is my home base.
THE WORLD WITH YOU
BY: HIKARU IRINO - DRAWN BY: SORA MINASE
I think
Mom's getting carried away these days.
That'll happen to anyone
if they're that popular.
You think?
We should all get carried away
when we have the chance.
It rarely happens.
Life is hard, huh?
RECEPTION COUNTER
Please accept this!
Award us with an honorable mention!
Please give us first place!
Seriously?
I'm so nervous.
Even if your mom goes to Okinawa,
I'll be here.
I'll be in Tokyo.
Even if your mom goes to New York,
That offer's gone.
Well, even if she stays, I'll be in Tokyo.
What are you saying?
That's all.
I'm finished.
OBAYASHI TOYS
Ms. Aoi.
Perfect timing.
I smelled freshly-baked bread.
I have a good nose.
Gon-chan hit you?
Just a little.
You're all cleaned up here.
I didn't have much luggage to begin with.
-Tomorrow?
-Yes.
All you need to bring is yourself.
You can send your things later.
Of course,
you can join me in Okinawa later.
You have work, after all.
Hey.
No need to say anything.
It's tomorrow.
Please think about it carefully
until tomorrow.
Your heart can change very easily.
It's always been that way.
I just put
a spell on you.
A spell?
Maybe
Ichinose did it on purpose.
On purpose?
I won't give you Aoi or Sora!
Gon!
I'll protect them!
Aoi and Sora
are mine!
Maybe he went to Odaya on purpose
to say something to piss off Gon-chan,
and get hit.
Why?
So that you and Gon-chan
would get together.
What?
Gon-chan from the taiyaki shop?
I think it would be best
if Mom got together
with Gon-chan.
Gon-chan's her childhood friend.
He understands Mom the best.
He might not get
the more complicated parts,
but complicated parts are unnecessary,
don't you think?
That's an interesting opinion, Sora.
Mom needs Gon-chan.
He's like oxygen to her.
She thinks he'll always be there.
But if he goes away,
she'll be like a goldfish without air.
That's what I think.
Does your mom
like Gon?
I think so.
Maybe it's beyond the scope of romance.
But her first is always Gon-chan.
You said that to him?
I did.
Maybe Ichinose
tried to make Gon-chan realize.
Since Gon-chan always goes for
the young beauties.
"Aoi's the most important woman for you!"
He wanted him to realize.
He won't go for the young girls.
For Gon-chan, it's always been me.
Wow! How are you so confident?
Just because you're popular right now!
Women are so scary!
It's Ichinose's trap! It's a trick!
If my guess is right, that is.
Gon-chan tried to marry the young
and beautiful Aoba, remember!
Oh, you're right!
Now that you mention that,
there's no absolutes in life.
You never know what could happen.
But that's why
life is so fun!
You're so optimistic!
But for you, you think
I should be with Gon-chan?
What about the way I feel?
Mom.
Imagine that you're a three-year-old girl.
You walk along a thorny path.
You turn back.
Who's the person who always tags along
and smiles back at you?
ONE TIME, ONE MEETING
In front of me,
there's a three-year-old girl.
She's walking ahead of me.
I am worried
that she might trip.
No matter how old she is.
If it's a thorny path,
if life is a thorny path,
then I will always be worried.
I…
want to keep
watching over her for a little bit longer.
Just a little bit longer.
I want to watch over her.
I want to keep watching over her forever.
I don't want to be away from her.
I want to keep watching over her!
So you won't come with me?
I'm so sorry.
I see.
But…
It made me happy.
Thank you.
Sora told me.
You put on an act to
set off Gon-chan?
Did you do it on purpose
to make us realize what's most important
for us?
No.
I'm no saint.
You think?
Because of what you did,
I came to this conclusion.
It's because of you
I was able to realize
what's most important to me.
Maybe I had that thought
in the back of my mind.
I was wishing you'd get with Gon-chan.
I see.
So you weren't serious, huh?
You're wrong.
This is my last time with you.
Right?
So I'll tell you the truth.
Half of the truth is
what you just said.
But the other half…
is maybe a little more than that.
To be honest, more than half.
I made excuses for myself,
dreaming about how nice it would be
if I could get back
together with you.
And how nice it would be
to meet Sora frequently.
I was only thinking about myself.
I'm sorry that
we can't get back together.
No.
I'll always think back
on the time I spent here.
So I'll be happy going forward.
In the heavy letterpress
black-and-white literary magazine,
I have a new color-print page.
Mommy!
Mom!
Dad!
I'm gonna jump, so watch me!
She's a little kid right now.
I want to ask you something.
Please give me
those photos of the sky.
The photo album
with a picture of me at the very end.
Sure.
Can I take
a photo of you for
the last page?
Say cheese!
-Let's take one, all together!
-Yeah!
-Could you take a photo of us?
-Oh.
Sure.
Could you move in a little closer?
That's great.
How nice!
-Be well, you two.
-Yeah!
You too, Dad.
You too, Fuga.
Maguroyaki?
Yes, and make it this big!
That's impossible! How many kilograms
of bean paste would I need?
Wait…
Maybe it's possible.
-For weddings, instead of cake.
-Yes.
Right?
I have to outgrow my child.
Sora will go away one day.
-I'm not going anywhere.
-What?
People have all kinds of tastes, you know.
Some weirdos might start swarming
around you. Become a grandma already!
What the hell?
That's how you flirt with me?
I'm not flirting with you!
MINATO BOOK CENTER
Sorry for the wait!
Thank you.
ROOKIE AWARD RESULTS!
FIRST PLACE!
THE WORLD WITH YOU
-Cheers!
Can I tell you something?
What?
I don't actually have a girlfriend.
Huh? What about Kokoro?
Kokoro with the high hips?
That's Kokoro Hasegawa!
From Smile Down the Runway?
It's just your fantasy?
What?
-Hey!
-Watch out!
-We got a Best Effort Award!
-Kick!
Congratulations!
Congratulations, congratulations!
Thank you, thank you!
-Thank you, thank you!
-No, it's like this.
Like this.
Thank you, thank you!
SEASONAL FLAVOR
Scissors, shoot!
I did it!
-Mom wins!
-Hey!
Come back with that!
THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
WE WISH YOU A WONDERFUL TOMORROW!