Where is it?
MINATO-KU SUZURAN-CHO 2 AREA MAP
Where could it possibly be?
I believe love is like holding a sword.
It's a battle between a man and a woman.
Romance is where you learn
how far you can hurt someone.
Without holding the sword, you don't know
when someone starts to bleed.
You don't know how to heal.
Wow, that's so deep.
Even so, there's not even a sign
that anything's going on.
Kids these days aren't interested in love.
Same with my daughter.
She's never had a boyfriend in her life.
Even with your daughter?
I'm sure she's beautiful and pretty too.
Not as much as me.
-Please edit that out.
-Yes.
THE NEVERENDING LESSON
ADULT COMIC
Excuse me?
Oh, we're not suspicious.
We just had a question.
Okay.
Do you know a building called
Angel Forest Tower?
Sure.
-Cross here, turn right…
-So it is famous.
Well, I live there.
I had her quite young. She's already 20.
I want my daughter to experience love.
There are parts of you that can only grow
through romance.
Most of all, don't you think it's sad to
not know the feeling of being in love
after being born in this world?
THE SOUND OF DREAMS
You want and pursue someone,
you get hurt, you hurt them,
and you learn what it is to be human.
Those without that experience are weak.
Are you listening, Ms. Matsuyama?
Sorry, don't shoot from below.
The upper right is my best angle.
Yes, ma'am.
You don't know her?
Aoi Minase, the queen of romance novels.
I guess kids these days don't know her.
Like the Sound of Dreams or
Seeing You Tomorrow.
It took the world by storm back then.
How about now?
-Well, it's hard to say…
-Past its prime?
You're a straight talker!
You said turn right here…
I'm going to the convenience store.
I didn't think I'd be concerned
about this.
Ever since my daughter was young,
my concern was
what if she gets caught up
with the wrong guy?
But there hasn't been a single guy
pursuing her.
Now, I have the opposite concern.
What if she never gets a boyfriend, and…
Even though her mother's a
master of romance?
A master? Me?
You've written so many romance novels.
You must have so much experience,
and have been pursued by many men.
No, it's not like that.
Ms. Matsuyama is
my mother's editor of 20 years.
But because of the recession,
Saneisha asked for employees to
retire early,
and she volunteered.
Today is her last day.
It's been so long, Editor-in-Chief!
I'm sorry it's been so long, star writer!
As expected of
the queen of romance novels.
What a beautiful home you have.
What's wrong?
Is that a bean jelly from Tatsuya?
Oh, you don't like these?
I do, but that's an apology gift.
So observant… Don't worry about me.
Please continue your interview.
We'll talk later.
Ms. Minase, you say that,
but I'm sure you'd get
very lonely once your daughter
has a boyfriend.
No, I'm more worried about her
staying home and becoming
"a parasite single."
Do you know about those?
Yes, it's kids who don't marry
and stay home…
Exactly! What if she's still living here
when she turns 30, 40,
or even 50?
Without a boyfriend, without marrying…
How horrific!
But your marriage didn't last, either.
What did you say?
I'm home.
Welcome home. Say hello to everyone.
Welcome to Denny's.
That was otterly weird. Get otter here!
THIS IS A SMALL-CLAWED OTTER!
Oh? You're the girl from earlier.
He said you're past your prime.
No, that was you…
Welcome home, Sora.
Where were you today?
Your daughter was buying
pornographic comics
at Tokyo Big Sight.
A ton of them.
MAIN TITLE
All done!
Sanmayaki, with white bean paste.
Yay!
SUZURAN SHOPPING DISTRICT
The Suzuran Shopping District is
a historic site that has been thriving
for over 300 years
as a temple town since the Edo period.
In the center of
Suzuran Shopping District,
right in the middle of Tokyo,
is the bathhouse, Suzuran Hot Springs.
Next to that is the historical
taiyaki shop,
Odaya. Gon-chan is the fourth generation
shop owner.
This is Gon-chan.
How is it?
Another bite! Eat another bite!
This is Gon-chan's dad, Shunichiro.
-Excuse me?
-Yes, sir!
Odaya, struggling from the
recent tapioca boom,
started developing a new product.
That was the sanmayaki,
instead of the taiyaki.
Welcome, everyone!
We have some delicious taiyaki!
We have whole beans, crushed beans,
Indian beans, alien beans… Just kidding!
We have everything!
-Right?
-I know!
You're not eating that?
Our bean paste is really good!
Yes, of course it's good,
but there's just too much.
What?
That was a big shock to Gon-chan.
In his life, he never doubted the
universal good of stuffing taiyaki
with as much bean paste as possible,
to the tail.
With this experience, he invented
the sanmayaki, with less bean paste.
So this is the sanmayaki?
I'm not a fan of too much bean paste.
That's why Odaya made this for me.
-She's lying.
-If there's only a little bit of paste,
it looks like fish organs. Gross!
So they're testing a new recipe
with white bean paste. Right, Sora?
Roger that.
That's not how you use that word.
Can I eat some, too?
Roger that.
I'm sorry this is more bean paste, but…
Here you are.
Hey, Sora's right there!
Tatsuya's bean jelly,
kneaded with apologies.
The weight of the jelly represents
the guilt.
Red bean paste,
stewed and simmered apologies.
What are you saying?
I'm so scared!
What will he apologize to me about?
This is difficult for me to say…
Then don't say it!
Oh, sorry! I need to take this.
Hey, wassup?
You're in Nishiazabu? Sure.
Right now? Yeah, sure.
Yes. Ask them to open early.
You're a VIP, they'd do that!
And who are you?
Everything is so chaotic, I haven't
had the chance to introduce…
Not yet. Now's not the time.
Alright, got it!
I'll just deal with this quickly.
I'll be right over. Okay!
Oh, sorry about that.
Apologies, apologies.
You know, you might call me
a little outdated, but…
Ms. Aoi. I'm so sorry about this.
Wait, don't say it! Sora's here!
Hey, don't you have work?
After I eat this.
Your series at Raphael
will end next month.
Canceled.
No!
We're so sorry.
I guess I'm too out of touch
for this line of work…
Huh?
The series at Raphael is
Umbilical Cord, right?
You said we'd release season two,
serialize it, and make a movie…
See! It says Season One right here!
Season One is the end.
What the hell?
Well… This book…
It didn't sell. It really didn't sell.
Not at all.
Soften it.
Soften the blow! You're too frank!
We need a little frankness at times,
don't you think?
This proves Aoi Minase is
a romance writer after all.
Mystery wasn't your thing.
I used all my weak brain powers
to write this!
Season One didn't sell at all,
so the film company had second thoughts,
we couldn't find actors or directors.
Truly, no one.
So who will it be?
Huh?
Who's going to take over
my spot at Raphael?
We found someone really good!
Who?
The handsome TV star, Tomoro Nakagawa.
-You know him too, right, Sora?
-No.
She's an otaku. Only interested in 2D men.
She doesn't even know
how many members are in Arashi.
There are five.
So close! There are six!
Ms. Aoi, there are five.
Anyways, Tomoro Nakagawa is
the next Arashi.
He's also the one who just called me.
He said he had an idea for a new series.
He's in Nishiazabu…
-Wait.
-He's drinking at a bar.
-Wait!
-It sure is nice to be young.
"Wait, will you?" That's a Kimutaku quote.
Wait.
He's an actor, right? An actor!
This Nakagawa man.
Yes, he became popular in the
morning drama series "Glaring Sun".
An actor should act! He's just hot, right?
He probably can't write a sentence
to save his life!
Ms. Aoi.
The thing is…
He's a pretty good writer.
And he has fans,
so we can expect sales.
Alright then. I'll be off…
Oh, I almost forgot.
I totally forgot he was here.
Since Matsuyama will be retiring early,
he will be your editor from now on.
I'm Tachibana.
"Soseki Tachibana"?
Your name is Soseki?
Yes. My brother is "Ogai."
-You're kidding!
-No, it's true.
His father loves literature.
He's just a high school teacher, though.
You don't need to say "just."
You could get in trouble for that.
So you're my new editor?
Yes. No matter how hard I work,
a woman would never be promoted.
Instead of being bossed around
by stupid young men,
I'll be retiring early and start work
at an IKEA near me.
I'll be the manager there.
That was so much information.
But you know, Ms. Minase,
we really care about you.
That's why we got the hottest guy
to be your editor.
"Hot?"
You just have hair in your eyes.
These days, all young hot guys have
hair in their eyes, so I can't tell.
Like that famous guy…
Stop! That's a red card!
This is broadcast TV, not Hulu.
I think he's pretty hot.
Maybe you can tell once he's next to me.
Hey, cameraman? Don't come too close.
Pull back.
He's eight heads tall.
I'm four heads tall.
Konishi-kun, you've gotten fat!
Mom calls the editor-in-chief
"Konishi-kun"
because they're old friends.
I don't know the details, but apparently,
he was the one that discovered my mom.
Even after losing a job,
the sky is wide and beautiful.
TAIYAKI
-Come again!
-Thank you!
Thank you!
Did I mess up?
No one's buying the sanmayaki!
Maybe it's the design.
I already got ten molds made too.
It'll pick up.
You think?
Let's hope so…
The customers are gone, so
let's take a break when you're done.
-Yes, sir!
-Sure.
I think we should move.
I don't think we can pay the mortgage.
Is your mom struggling
that much for work?
She might start wanting to work here.
No way. We can't hire Aoi!
She's no good! She can't do anything!
She'd break all the plates.
She's so clumsy!
What? A love story?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm writing romance again?
You're Aoi Minase,
the queen of romance novels, after all.
But that wasn't going so well. That's why
I wrote mystery…
But that was even worse.
So if I write romance,
you'll publish the book for sure?
Yes. Saneisha will make sure that happens.
I think there are a lot of fans
awaiting your romance novel.
I can't any more.
I'm so far from romance…
I don't have anyone to do it with.
Come.
Ow…
I avoided the tender spots.
Thank you very much!
Aoi.
If you eat that fast,
you're going to choke.
Shunichiro…
Can you hire me for 5,000 yen an hour?
Even 50 yen an hour is too much.
Hey, Dad?
For Nagaiki Home across the street,
did they say they want
40 taiyaki for dessert…
-Ouch!
-What the hell?
-You were here?
-My eyes! I'm going blind!
You can't see my handsome face.
I'm off to deliver ten taiyaki
to Hana Café.
Good work!
Good work! Ow…
What's wrong?
Recently, I can't raise my right arm.
You've got frozen shoulder! You're so old!
Sora, you can clock out
when you're done with that delivery.
Okay! Oh, but my bike…
-Mom, can you take my bike home?
-Okay!
-What do you want to eat tonight?
-Um… Grilled meat?
Then Hamada?
Hamada! Good idea!
But the leftover curry…
I'll go home and freeze it.
Got it.
Don't forget to remove the potatoes.
Her bike saddle is too high for me.
I have to lower it. So much work.
You've got short legs.
Gon-chan. Can you lower the saddle?
What?
Alright!
TAIYAKI
This is rusty! You have to maintain it!
Okay.
Gon-chan and Mom are old childhood friends
who grew up together in Suzuran District.
A lot of things happened,
and they're both single.
Gon-chan is a bit older, but they both
went to the same calligraphy class.
A HOPEFUL SPRING
That was Gon-chan's greatest masterpiece.
The teacher was approaching.
He was certain he'd get praised.
What have you done?
Mom tried to pour the ink in the inkstone,
but her hand slipped, so the stone
hit Gon-chan's…
Ouch!
You can still see the inkstone scar
under Gon-chan's chin.
Ouch!
This won't work.
I heard you lost a job.
It's not going well these days.
It's the same with electronics.
If one goes bad, everything follows.
This might be the end for Aoi Minase.
You can marry me, then.
What? Really? You'll have me?
Wait, you're that desperate?
So much that you'd marry me?
-We don't have to have sex, right?
-Cut it out!
In that case, don't go to Hamada.
Eat your leftover curry.
Their salted beef tongue is 1,800 yen,
you know!
It's really good, though.
The mortgage will be tight.
You should move then.
-I can't do that.
-Why?
Sora, huh?
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
Not at all.
Can't believe a trendy café like this
eats taiyaki for snacks.
That's how it is, you know?
Oh, we have a new product.
Do you want one? A soy-ppucino
-Really?
-Sure.
SUGI BEE GARDEN
This café and the honey shop next door
used to be combined into a single home.
It was our home.
We used to be a traditional photo studio
called Minase Photo Studio.
Apparently, we've taken photos
of the imperial family.
But we were pressured to sell
and my mom's mom…
My grandma and grandpa sold
the photo gallery,
with no regrets at all.
VACANT PLOT
Because this was a prime location
in the middle of the city,
Grandpa and Grandma fulfilled their
lifelong dream of moving to Switzerland.
Now, they live there,
taking photos of mountains.
My mom, a young novelist
just starting out,
was kicked out of home,
but she found success.
To celebrate, she bought herself
a newly-built high rise
just across Suzuran Shopping District.
The title of Mom's novel
from back then was
"The Scent of the Sky."
Pretty, right?
What does the sky smell like?
Um…
Are you okay?
And thus, a fateful encounter…
It spilled, huh?
Here, have this. It's a soy latte.
-That's what you're worried about?
-Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm close to home. I can walk.
-I see.
-Yeah.
Okay. Bye, thanks.
-Wait.
-Huh?
Your glasses.
They're bent out of shape.
Huh?
Did they get damaged from the fall?
Maybe before that. Here. Try them now.
-Wow!
-Easy to see, right?
Do you work with glasses?
Not really.
SUZURAN HOT SPRINGS
MEDICAL HEALTH BATH OF THE DAY
Oh, that feels good!
We're in heaven! And the beer after this…
-…will be so good!
-Yeah!
Gon.
Are you not going to get married?
What?
-Why ask now?
-How about you and Aoi?
That'll never happen.
Never. Not in a million years.
Not for forever and ever?
Not even long long ago.
Didn't happen long ago,
won't happen in the future,
not once in this long life, huh?
So sad.
It's Aoi after all.
Why do we always overeat grilled meat?
I could eat grilled meat forever!
After loin, the short rib, and the rumen,
I didn't think
we'd do the salted tongue again, ya know?
-"Ya know?"
-It's a reference to Chibi Maruko.
We should've gotten cold noodles
or bibimbap too! Regrets!
This is bad.
Today's grilled meat was bad?
No, Hamada is always delicious, forever.
The best in Suzuran Shopping District!
-I know.
-No…
What's bad is not the grilled meat,
but our household budget.
Now's not the time to eat out.
Mom, when you're struggling with
a manuscript, you always run to food.
Hamada, Aroma Fresca, Au Mirador,
Calanques, Kokoro and Yomogi… Too much!
You were there too!
Listen up. Our food budget is about to
surpass our income.
Those clothes are Prada, right?
You shopped online again!
No, they're Gucci.
They're both expensive!
You too. That sweater's from Toga, right?
I saw Mei Nagano wear it
in the New Year's show.
-Oh, I remember now!
-What?
Today, on my way home from Comic Market,
I bought some Milk &amp; Violet ice cream.
Which flavor?
Limited edition, Amaou Strawberries
and Mascarpone Blend.
Nicknamed "Ama-Mas." I also got Matcha.
-The limited edition is mine!
-No!
That one's for me! Ama-Mas is mine!
I got it!
Hey, are you serious?
I got this myself!
-Are you a kid?
-I had to go to three stores!
-That makes me want it more!
-No.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Shoot! Shoot!
-Can I have a little?
-No.
-I want a little!
-Is it good?
-Very much.
You're so mean.
I'm training your sense of motherhood.
Parents should give to their children.
LIMITED EDITION
STRAWBERRY MASCARPONE
Mom, I'm going to say it again.
You have ice cream here.
Our budget is in a bad state!
Huh? Why is that there?
I've decided that today was the day.
Okay? Look at this.
Here's our income and our expenses.
BALANCE: -111,020 YEN
This. Look. Look.
We're a mother and a child household.
She was a soft and fluffy baby.
I decided that I'd raise her properly.
I'd do it my way. My own unique way.
She grew up into a wonderful girl
and became my right-hand-man.
I was busy with work, so she took on
the household tasks and eventually,
our budget.
She sometimes steals from me,
but we're a mother-daughter team.
She's my partner as we live through
this world.
Even though she only decorates photos
where she looks good.
You say something?
No. You must be hearing things.
Listen up, Mom. Our mortgage for
this place is not looking good.
I know I haven't paid a cent, but…
Of course you haven't. You're in college!
Hey, wanna quit college and work?
Just kidding!
It was tough to lose Kodansha,
Marukawa Books and Chugakukan.
Huh?
Why did they keep Kodansha?
Let's move. Mom, let's move!
Wait. Okay? Wait up. Mom has an idea.
What is it?
UMBILICAL CORD
I'll sell Umbilical Cord!
I'll find a publisher that will
serialize Season Two!
Then, I'll make it a bestseller,
like Harry Potter!
That'll show Saneisha, and Konishi
for abandoning me!
Wow…
RISSEI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
Really good! Can you look more this way?
Sure.
Wow, that's really good.
Are we done here?
He's a model for Men's Non-no.
Oh, really?
Hey, you!
He's kidding.
I bet you could model anywhere.
Can I get one more?
Sure! I'm nice to pretty girls!
Stop! You're making me blush!
Can we take one here?
Isn't that Irino?
It is!
He's being photographed!
Irino!
Hey, Irino!
You're going to the party tonight, right?
That was today?
I'll go. Of course I will.
I'm asking Irino.
What does that mean?
I don't feel like it…
Oh, look at him!
Those popular kids…
Members of the light tribe.
Seriously?
I'm the chief of the shadow tribe
in this party school.
I'm a completely different being.
A different being. Different being.
Say it three times, and it's a mantra.
I can reach enlightenment.
BANG!
CRASH!
You're going too, right?
The Cains Seminar party.
No, I'm…
The professor said attendance is
mandatory. Otherwise, you'd fail.
Isn't that what some would call coercion?
I'm just joking!
But it's true, everyone should attend.
I'm planning it. So come.
Seven, at Ikkyu. See ya!
-Konishi.
-Yeah?
About Ms. Minase…
Right. Did she call?
Any ideas for a romance novel?
No, not at all.
You think she's planning to escape?
From us. From Saneisha.
You're a hot guy for a reason, okay?
Don't let her escape.
Hey!
Hey…
Where are we going?
-Hey.
-Hello, sir.
I'm not running away!
Huh?
-You pervert!
-Not like that. Why are you here? Why?
I work here part-time.
For eye candy, I assume. Because I'm cute.
Yeah, you are, but…
I want to be by your side forever, Soseki.
That's not cute.
Yes… Yes. It's a little tough?
Come on, give me a chance!
I have ideas for what happens next.
Autumn will turn into winter.
And then… Huh?
Oh, you have a meeting?
Wait, what about Gen?
Gen, the editor-in-chief.
I've worked with him before…
Oh? He retired?
It's alright, then.
Goodbye…
AKIKAWA SHORIN BOOKS: SAKURA SUGIMOTO
NEW MAIL: ABOUT THE SERIES PROPOSAL
From Iwatani Books?
"Thank you for contacting us
about publishing your series."
"As for Umbilical Cord,"
"we've decided not to go forward
with publishing… "
It's no good. I'll go to bed.
BEDROOM
I had this many ideas…
I could've continued to Season Ten
if needed…
Canceled…
NOTEBOOK
Oh… Am I crying?
Hello?
Hello, it's Tachibana from Saneisha.
Ogai, right?
Your name is more impressive than you!
I'm Soseki. Ogai's my brother.
Then the same for your brother!
He won the Nobel Prize.
No way! Like Haruki Murakami?
I'm just kidding.
Also, Murakami has never won it.
Are you alright? Did something happen?
It's nothing.
Your nose sounds stuffy.
That's how I sound. Also, I have sinuses.
I see.
Do you have any ideas
for the romance novel?
-I'm still thinking!
-I see.
About Umbilical Cord…
Yeah?
You have two more spots for your series
on Raphael.
Konishi said to end it in two chapters.
I can write 40 more chapters if needed.
I have the plot and everything.
How stupid of me.
You're sincere and diligent, Ms. Minase.
Huh?
That's how I felt reading your novels.
You're serious about your work.
Okay. Two chapters, right?
I can end it.
"BUT THEN, OUR PLAN WOULD FAIL…"
I feel sick…
Hikaru, I invited Minase, too.
Who's Minase?
Oh, that gloomy girl?
She's always by herself.
Hey, Tanaka, look carefully.
She's actually got a pretty face.
But she's an otaku, right?
Or a Boys' Love fan-girl?
Ew…
Did she hear us?
Is there more beer?
What are you drinking?
It stinks!
-Good, right?
-You like this?
What? It's good!
-It's cilantro.
-I want to try!
It tastes bad. You shouldn't.
What are you drinking?
-Calpis.
-Calpis?
What? Why did you do that?
Don't make fun of me.
I just thought it was cute.
Huh? What are you saying?
I'll be going now. I need to see an anime.
BATHROOMS ARE THIS WAY
No one will come after me, of course.
UMBILICAL CORD
SEASON 2
I can't write.
I can't write a single word…
-Hey, today…
-Yeah?
Someone threw an edamame at me.
What the heck? Who?
A classmate.
-A girl?
-A girl.
That's cute. What did you do?
Nothing.
You didn't do anything,
but she threw an edamame at you?
-A confession of love, maybe?
-What the hell?
Are you staying over?
Can I?
You're welcome to.
APARTMENT FOR RENT
What's this?
I found this on the way home from school.
I think it's good.
Minamijujou? That's outside of Tokyo!
It's accessible to the center of Tokyo.
It's only one train ride to my school.
I didn't ask you to find a house!
It's just a pamphlet.
You don't believe in your mom?
Did Umbilical Cord sell to another
publisher then?
No, but…
Then why not? I'm sure they have
cheap onions and potatoes there.
But they don't have Hamada!
Keep saying that,
and we'll keep losing money!
It's your pride that keeps you in
Minato Ward.
Yeah, but…
Prada and Louis Vuitton,
it's all your pride.
This house is filled with your pride.
But without my Pradas and Vuittons,
I can feel myself ending.
It feels like the end of Aoi Minase!
All I know is to write.
How will I raise you?
I'm suffering here for you, you know?
What? Don't use me as an excuse
for your creative block.
What is that tone?
Is that how you talk to a parent?
If you went to a national school,
it would've been a little easier.
Sorry I'm not smart like you, Mom.
You think that I should've at least
gotten into a private school like Waseda.
What? I never thought that.
Of course you do!
You said you want me to go
because that's where you went!
I just recommended it because
it's a good school!
Anyways, I never asked you
to write for me.
You decided to write. You got famous.
I'm not a part of it.
What are you saying?
I'm the one who raised you!
Here it is. What a cliché line. So lame!
If you don't like it, leave!
This is my house!
I'm the one who bought this house! Leave!
No need to tell me.
If you want to be spoken to like a mother,
then act like a mother!
What does that mean?
-How many of my teachers can you name?
-What?
Any of my teachers from elementary school
to high school.
Mr. Hirano! Your teacher in middle school!
I can't take this!
ODAYA: OPEN
Hey Dad, about the sanmayaki…
-Kenta said custard cream might…
-Ow!
Ow, ouch…
I'm so sorry!
But I can't see you, you know?
Don't bury yourself like a cat…
Huh?
Are you crying?
I have to write.
Here you are.
ODAYA
It's so warm.
Sure.
Just like your mom.
You're so cheesy, Gon-chan.
Yup. I'm a cheesy man.
Hey, Gon-chan.
The only teacher that Mom remembered
was a hot teacher named Mr. Hirano.
She loves hot guys.
Hey.
Your mom doesn't sell that house
for you, Sora.
Me?
You can see Zojirushi from
your room, right?
That cute elephant? It's a good design.
When you were a kid,
your mom would pick you up when you cried
to show you the elephant.
Then you'd stop crying.
I've heard that story a lot.
She said Zojirushi's there
as a stand-in for Dad.
She said it's our guardian…
You like Zojirushi, right?
Yeah. It's even my wallpaper.
Seriously?
It still calms me down when I look at it.
Like in high school, when I didn't make
first chair in brass band,
or when I didn't get into
a national school for college.
I looked at that elephant.
It calms me down.
It's kinda lame so
I was keeping it a secret.
But your mom knew, huh?
That "A leopard can't change its spots."
It calms me.
It's your guardian, after all.
NEW PRODUCT: SANMAYAKI
Anything that's important for you, Sora,
is way more important for your mom.
She should just say it.
Hey, come on…
Even Aoi has some things she can't say.
You probably think she says everything
that's in her head, but…
Well, she does say most things.
But not the important stuff.
Your mom's always
cheering you on, Sora.
Gon-chan.
Do you have red bean soup for Mom?
Sure do!
Mom!
Mom, what's wrong?
Mom! Mom! Mom, what's wrong?
-What's wrong?
-I was looking at this.
Huh?
Me, you, and the elephant.
You must've been in kindergarten
when you drew this.
What is it?
In here… In this house,
three-year-old you, nine-year-old you,
they're all here.
What are you doing, Mom?
We're moving to Minamijujou, right?
For the memories.
-No, Mom!
-What?
Aoi Minase can't move to Minamijujou!
That would be the end! You'd stop
wearing Prada or Vuitton or Marni.
You'd shop at Unishiro!
Unishiro has up to XXXXL.
You'd lose your figure!
It's already slipping away!
Umbilical Cord's ending after
two chapters,
and I can't even write that.
I have to quit writing…
I was gone for a little bit,
and her morale is so low.
Hey, Mom. What will you do in Minamijujou?
I'll work at a supermarket.
Mom. A customer
bought something for 878 yen.
They paid 1003 yen. What's the change?
-Two hundred…
-See?
All you know is to write.
You were born to write.
So many people are waiting for your book.
But after finishing Umbilical Cord
in two chapters,
I have to write a romance novel.
Otherwise, I have no path.
What? A romance novel?
Yeah. Did I not mention?
They said they'd publish if I write
a romance novel.
But I can't write those anymore!
I don't know love.
-I'll help.
-How?
I'll find romance!
What?
I'll find love, and you can write
about that!
You? The otaku and Boys' Love fan?
Is an otaku Boys' Love fan falling in
love a bad story?
No, it might be really good.
More than anything, I'm so happy
you're interested in that!
I was so worried that you'd never
get a boyfriend
and keep reading bloody manga
and manga about men making out.
BL, you mean.
I was so worried about you!
That much?
I'll write a romance novel! I'll do it!
I'm so excited for you to find love!
Yay!
-Ouch!
-What's wrong?
I can't raise my right arm these days.
I have frozen shoulder…
Ow, ouch…
CHIROPRACTIC: TAIYOU-DO
But actually, if it's an otaku
main character, it'd be a light novel.
A light novel?
Yeah. It's what young people read.
That's not really what I write.
I see. I didn't know about light novels.
So really, I have to find love.
If I can remember that sparkle
in my heart, I can write again…
Ouch!
A sparkle is good and all,
but your shoulders are in terrible state.
I need backup.
I'll go call the other doctor.
The Director?
No, he retired the other day.
We have a new doctor.
Can you come here, sir?
Excuse me.
A young man?
Your scapula and humerus are
stuck together.
Yes, my scapula and humerus…
Excuse me for a sec.
Okay. Try getting up.
Raise your right arm.
Oh, okay.
Oh, it worked! I can raise my arm!
Wow!
A little more, like this…
It's all fixed.
Thank you.
If you have the time, please come again.
Yes!
-I'm sure you're busy, but…
-Huh?
I'm reading your series on Raphael.
Umbilical Cord.
I'm a big fan! I have all your books!
Ouch!
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-Be careful!
-Because you're so tall…
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Wow…
I was so nervous. So lame…
So…
So cute!
And this is how the battle
between mother and daughter began.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE BEHIND THE SCENES
OF DATE MY DAUGHTER!
START OF FILMING
PRACTICING MAKING TAIYAKI
MADE BY HAMABE
FIRST VERSION MADE BY SAWAMURA
PICTURES OF MOTHER AND DAUGHTER
FIRST DAY OF FILMING AT SANEI-SHA
CONGRATS TO ARITA
FOR BIRTH OF HIS FIRST DAUGHTER!
A MOTHER AND DAUGHTER
WHO ARE MORE LIKE FRIENDS…
HOW WILL THEIR ROMANCE TURN OUT?
I'm going to go find love right now!
-She's on a date!
-What?
So you're an otaku too?
It's a secret that I'm an otaku.
Want to go together?
-What's going on?
-Maybe no one sees me as a woman anymore.
-Ms. Aoi?
-Love might be a battle.
Subtitle translation by: