Doctor Wataru!
Nose hair.
Nose hair?
Yes. Nose hair.
That's quite the hurdle, nose hair.
I may not be able to jump it.
Did you enjoy your date?
I can only remember the nose hair.
Plans for the next date?
My mind was on the nose hair.
I didn't ask.
You couldn't point out the nose hair
to him?
I'm certain I could never say
such a thing.
Oh!
Was the small-clawed otter cute?
He was really cute.
Oh, he's adorable!
So cold!
When can I see you next?
-Let's see.
-Tomorrow?
-I have work.
-No way!
Oh, Hikaru!
Hey.
Oh, this is my cousin.
I tutored him back home,
in Kumamoto.
I see. Good evening.
So you go to school here?
-Yes.
-Where?
Rissei Gakuin University.
Wow, impressive!
No, it was unacceptable at his home.
I felt guilty as his tutor.
His brother went to Kyushu
University pre-med from La Salle.
His father's a Kyushu University
med school professor.
Your family's very educated.
Well, my family is.
Don't sulk like that!
Did you need anything?
No, well…
My parents sent some stuff from home.
They asked me to give this to you.
-I'll be going, then.
-Really?
Yes. Talk about memories from back home.
-No, I'll head back.
-It's fine.
We can see each other whenever.
We see each other too much.
We need to spend some time apart.
Hey!
I'm so drunk!
Your parents sent you this from home?
Flan from a convenience store?
It's my favorite.
You're a liar, Miwa.
Oh, what I said before?
Half is a lie, and half is the truth.
It's true that I was your tutor.
But a complete lie
that you're my cousin.
Let me tell you
a great technique for when you lie.
You mix in some truths.
Is he your top choice?
Well, not really. I'm assessing.
More like, browsing.
I'm trying him out.
So he's being returned?
I'm almost 30, you know?
You don't look it.
Maybe I don't look it,
but once I'm 30,
I want to get married.
I don't need love anymore.
I'm tired of working.
I just want to relax.
You want to relax?
I came to Tokyo,
worked hard, and wore myself out.
I'm emotionally tired.
You have a lot of girlfriends too,
right, Hikaru?
Yeah. Of course. Lots.
Right?
It's too much work to like
and love just one person.
Having fun with pretty girls
is all you need, right?
We have Gorgonzola Taiyaki!
We have sanmayaki with less paste,
great for those on a diet!
White bean, crushed bean,
Indian, Alien, Adrian! Just kidding.
Gon-chan, three sanmayaki.
Are you on a diet, Asu?
Oh, sorry. That's sexual harassment.
Asu, you've grown up into a beauty!
Really?
Can you really eat three?
It's for my family.
I see.
He's handsome, isn't he?
He really is handsome!
What a bummer. Only if I was younger.
If only I wasn't married, right?
And these girls over here.
What will you have?
Gon-chan. We're not here to eat today.
-What?
-We have a proposal for you.
No way. Is that what I think it is?
She's really pretty, alright?
A beauty! Right?
You just have to meet her.
Come on. At my age?
All you have to do is look.
Trust me, alright?
Hey, come on. No…
-How old?
-Twenty-six.
So young!
I'm home. Geez.
Mr. Toyoda from Sarashina Toyoda
talks too much.
His rants are as long as his soba noodles,
am I right?
Hey, sorry my husband talks too much!
Oh? You're here?
Oh, today was Suzuran Shopping District's
Board of Directors meeting.
Was my husband there?
Yes, he was. But he went out for drinks.
What?
Another arranged marriage date?
Right? Auntie Toyoda and Mrs. Kanbayashi
always bring photos, calling her a beauty,
but they never are!
They're all leftovers of the district,
divorced.
-Or from Suzuran Elementary…
-Hey!
This one's impressive.
She's… What was it? Miss Universal?
Universal's a theme park.
She's like Miss Universe!
I'll meet her.
I'll marry her!
What are you saying? It's for me.
-No, wait.
-What? Just show me.
Shunichiro's fine, too. He's single.
A May and December wedding.
Just like Cha Katō.
Peh!
She's all mine.
What are you saying?
You perverted old man!
It's for me!
Let go!
Oh!
Are you alright?
My back!
Are you okay?
Don't touch me!
My back hurts. Ouch!
She's so pretty!
CHIROPRACTIC: TAIYOU-DO
How is it?
It's just a bruise. No need to worry.
Alright. All finished.
Help me up.
Huh? What?
It doesn't hurt.
-I'm glad.
-Wow.
-What is this?
-Nose hair extensions.
-What? Nose hair extensions?
-Yes.
-No, these are eyelash extensions…
-It's nose hair.
Pretty, right?
Wow, she's really pretty!
So beautiful.
-Prettier than you, Mom.
-What does that mean?
You always want to fight
against pretty women.
You want to decide who wins and who loses.
Oh yeah, she does that!
She was sulky for placing second
in a beauty contest in middle school.
I've already lost to her by age.
She's 26, right?
Wait, why am I fighting?
Whatever.
So you came all this way
to show this off?
No way. I'm busy, you know?
But you're going to meet her.
It's not like you can marry her,
right, Gon?
-Yes, I can.
-Really?
-I'm 90% sure.
-How are you so sure?
Apparently, she saw me making my taiyaki.
It was, you know…
Love at first sight!
So she came by every day.
But she was too shy to order taiyaki.
That's why she asked Auntie Toyoda.
I'm here because
if I do marry her, you're a
celebrity of sorts so…
-Not "of sorts."
-Make a speech for us.
You came to say that?
He came to show her off.
But you know, Mom.
If Gon-chan gets married,
we can't go to Odaya like we do now.
-Huh?
-What?
What? I mean, it's true.
A new wife. And she's young.
I bet she's the jealous type.
-Hey.
-Oh, sorry. But pretty people are jealous.
If he gets such a pretty wife,
and if Mom, his childhood friend,
who's old but still pretty…
Sora. Just call me pretty
and get to the point.
I'm saying that if his childhood friend
came to Odaya
like it was her own living room,
eating yakisoba and taiyaki
and grilled mochi
and curling up in the kotatsu like a cat.
She can't do that anymore!
Your new wife would hate it.
-I see.
-She's right.
But, you know,
if you really do get married,
Nako would be so happy.
Nako in heaven would be proud of you.
You think?
I was a good-for-nothing son.
I didn't see her on her deathbed.
It's because
we didn't know where you were!
I was traveling the world.
I was training in France as a pastry chef.
-Is that even true?
-What?
You want to hear my French?
Azabu juban. Shippo made anko.
You're so dumb.
It's true. I was in Paris.
That's why we have the Gorgonzola Taiyaki
in Odaya.
That was made in France.
Gon-chan.
Gorgonzola is an Italian cheese.
Oopsies!
I was all over Europe. That's why.
I hope I can have kids. Loads of them.
You want a baseball team?
I'd be happy if they took over the shop.
Odaya is really good.
You can't lose that.
It's continued since the Meiji Era.
That's amazing!
I thought Kenta could take over.
But when I asked him, he said,
"I couldn't!
It's gone on for four generations!
That's too much pressure!"
-Kids these days.
-Right?
I'm going to go check my books
at the bookstore.
I have a get-together
for Suzuran District.
Don't get sad if your books aren't piled.
You mean stacked. See you.
Oh, your right arm can go up!
So it's healed?
Your fifties shoulder.
My forties shoulder!!
PLOT FOR NEW SERIES
I've taken a look.
How is it?
Are you serious about this?
Why? It's good, right?
She wakes up, she's late, she runs
while holding toast,
then she bumps into a hot guy.
"Oh no, I'm so clumsy!" she says.
Then she goes to class and finds
that the hot guy is her teacher.
A fateful reunion.
Is it good?
Of course not!
I don't think I'm cut out for this
anymore.
I hear your annual income is 12 million
yen. Let me propose something.
Will you marry me?
What are you saying? You punched me
in the stomach the other day.
And how do you know my income?
I can't write romance novels
through interviews.
I need to find my own love.
No signs of that?
-None.
-You could think back on your past.
It was so long ago. I can't remember.
Not since the chiropractor?
-Nose hair man…
-What?
That's a taboo subject.
Mom, what about that story?
-Which story?
-How we can't go to Odaya.
That's so sad!
That place was my living room!
I love their kotatsu.
Why can't you go there?
Mom's childhood friend is getting married.
That's really good!
What?
Go on a date with him.
Bob Dylan tickets?
Those are so hard to get!
How? Through the power of Saneisha?
No. I clicked about 1,500 times.
Wow! Let's go, Sora!
No, this will be given to you
only if you go on a date
with that childhood friend.
A two in one pack.
ODAYA
What should I get?
-Their taiyaki's good, right?
-That's true.
Just get me whatever you're getting.
-Got it.
-Where's the restroom?
-It's over there.
-Thank you.
What? Why?
Hey, there.
Here you are. Enjoy.
Did you stalk me here?
No.
We just came here
after watching a movie around here.
Oh, a date?
In a way, yes.
What else would you call it?
I see… You saw Until They Kiss.
Let's talk Chainsaw Man
until she comes back.
Stop it, will you?
Is this your home?
No way. I work here.
Work. I see.
Hey, waitress. Two taiyaki, please.
And hurry, will you?
How was your date?
Getting along with your boyfriend?
It's going really well.
That's great.
We're both happy then.
To celebrate the joy,
this is for you.
Cells at Work! It's White Blood Cell!
I could never get Platelet.
Only White Blood Cell.
Gachapon on a date to get your character?
No way. I did it by myself,
on the way there.
Nice. I happily accept.
Oh, and this.
Here you are.
I got that too.
-What about your girlfriend?
-She only likes authentic stuff.
Like brand names.
I'd get sad if she asks me
how many carats that is.
I see.
Hey, Soseki.
Soseki?
Where did he go? Geez.
He's always off doing perverted things.
EQUIPMENT ROOM
Why won't you believe me?
Yesterday,
you went from Yotsuya to Otemachi,
then stopped at Jimbocho.
Jimbocho?
You know the new big bookstore there?
I stopped by
to see where they sell our books.
You didn't meet a hot girl
at the bookstore?
No way. I swear.
Jimbocho only has ugly girls.
It's not Ginza.
I see.
Hey, I'm working.
I'll get fired if I keep doing this.
I'm…
-Am I getting in your way, Soseki?
-It's not like that.
I will set aside time for you, Sally.
-I always do, right?
-Why…?
Why do you always react
like you're a kid in trouble?
Like a kid who has to submit his homework.
I want you to say, of your own accord,
"I want to be with you more!"
"I want to see your face more!"
Things like that.
Things like, "I want you!"
We're at work.
It's not our home or a love hotel.
What do you want from me?
Alright! I wanted to go to this!
No. I'm not giving you two. Just one.
The other one is for me.
We're going together.
Why do I have to go on a date with you?
Just give me two. I'll go with Takashi
from the clock shop.
I can't.
I can't separate these two.
It's a two-in-one set.
What is she on about?
When is that? Show me.
This Friday?
You're not invited, Dad.
Kenta and I will take care of the shop.
-You should go.
-What?
Go on a date with Aoi.
Why?
Don't go see Bob Dylan with two dudes!
You'll make Dylan cry.
Shunichiro, what have you been doing?
A dating app.
SEARCHING FOR CONNECTIONS…
It's upside down.
The cars illuminated with tail lights
look like tropical fish in an aquarium.
The elementary school I went to.
The school closed down
due to a declining birthrate.
One, two, three…
Four!
FORMER SUZURAN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
DEMOLITION NOTICE
It's going away?
This school?
This place is cute, right?
Really?
MOM
Oh, sorry.
How's your asthma?
It's calmed down these days.
You're calling about
the family gathering, right?
I think I can make it the day before.
Oh, about that.
You don't need to come for that.
What? Why?
All our relatives will be there.
Like Brother Hideo and Yuko from Fukuoka.
Yeah, haven't seen them for years.
It's been five years.
They don't know where you went
for college.
We'd talk about those things
at these events.
Dad wouldn't like it.
Your brother Hitoshi
got into La Salle last year.
So it's just you.
Dad doesn't know
how to tell everyone that
you didn't go to pre-med.
You should just stop
writing those silly cartoons of yours…
Hello?
Sorry for hanging up.
It works out for me. I was busy anyway.
Mom.
Take care of yourself, alright?
He plays the young Chris Matsumura…
Come in.
What's wrong?
I'm going to sleep.
Sure, okay.
They're going to demolish
Suzuran Elementary?
They're building a condo.
Right. They closed that school
six years after you graduated.
I guess that
things you love
never stay in their original form
forever.
You loved your elementary school?
Well, that's good.
So, Mom.
Thank you.
Why?
Thanks for letting us live here
while Zojirushi is here.
That Zojirushi might
one day disappear too.
That's true.
Anything that exists will one day go away.
In that case,
I want to cherish them while I still can.
See them while I still can.
Touch them when I still can!
Hey, are you drunk?
You were watching Exit, right?
Want to watch? Kanechika's so cool!
Are you done with work?
Isn't your Little Beauty deadline
for Mom's Helper Magazine today?
Can't someone just give me money?
-I just want to have fun and live!
-Hey.
Mom.
Do you do work you don't like for me?
Writing looks like a hard job.
No, I don't.
I'm very grateful for you.
If you weren't here, I would've quit
this hard job
years ago.
A cocktail waitress, maybe?
I'd be bad at it.
I'm not attentive enough.
I would've just starved.
I'm so glad you're here.
I worked hard because of you.
Doing something for others,
doing something for someone,
is a happy and beautiful thing.
There's a limit to how hard
you can work for yourself.
That's what I think.
Mom.
That was really beautiful.
You could use that later.
Maybe you should write it down.
You're right. Notes app!
You went to Suzuran Elementary too, right?
Yup. I'm your senpai.
I see.
You were an elementary school kid too.
Such a time existed?
Of course it did!
Thinking about you in elementary school
kind of makes me cry.
You as a little girl!
Hey, you!
That's too much limoncello for you!
Mom. What kind of kid were you?
I was always forgetting things at home.
Ouch! Why did you do that?
ODAYA
It got cold.
Miss, your yakisoba will get cold too.
I'd love it if you ate it warm.
It tastes better that way.
I don't
actually want yakisoba.
I was just tracking his phone.
He got on the Namboku Line,
so maybe he'd get off here again.
I'm ambushing him.
But the GPS is acting funky.
Let me see.
Let's see.
Turn off the cellular data.
-Oh. Here it is.
-Wow!
He's all the way in Toda.
I came here for nothing.
It may have been nothing,
but eat up, okay?
Our yakisoba's really good.
ODAYA
-It's really good.
-Right?
The tempura bits especially.
They're from the tempura shop over there.
-I see.
-Yeah.
This place Odaya, it's famous, right?
I'm the third generation owner.
I came in here
to treat myself
after a sad day.
Oh? What happened?
This may be on the final exam.
Maybe, maybe not.
Which is it?
-Which do you want?
-We can pick?
No way.
In that case, let's study at my place.
-Good idea.
-Let's split the work up.
But no one took good notes.
-I did.
-Seriously?
You did! Impressive!
I don't even have a notebook.
You're the worst!
That's really bad, dude.
Really bad.
Excuse me.
What is it?
I want to apologize to you.
Sorry. I'll be back.
What's going on?
I'll be done in two seconds.
What is it?
Last night, finally,
we got in a fight about this GPS tracking.
We've been dating for two years now.
I see.
It's so yummy.
Perhaps you shouldn't
cry, eat, and talk at the same time.
Just pick one.
It might be easier.
You know,
I don't have anything.
I only have love to give.
I came to Tokyo from Aomori
to chase after a guy.
A Tsugaru accent?
But that man ran away from me.
Oh, I see.
After that,
Soseki took me in.
I didn't have anywhere to go.
That's why I turned into
this stalker.
If I could, I would follow him
around all day.
Do you have work?
I started a part-time job
just to follow him,
but I'm probably gonna get fired-dabyon.
"Dabyon?"
I don't even know
if I love him anymore.
I'm just obsessed with being
attached to him.
She's back in her Tokyo accent.
I really hate myself.
You want some kuzukiri?
Soseki Natsume said the best way
to cheer up women is with sweets.
Soseki!
Oh, no, you've got it wrong!
I'm talking about the writer!
Wait, he didn't say that.
Was it Osamu Dazai? No…
Some smart person said it, right?
I'm a menhera.
These are my meds.
They're called Lyricas. Do you know it?
No, I don't. "Menhera"?
Menmen?
Tantanmen? No, that's wrong.
I love dad jokes.
I guess
there are people
with no knowledge of menhera
or Lyricas in this world.
Even at that age.
Are you dissing me?
I'm not dissing you.
You know what "dissing" means?
You're inconsistent in your knowledge
of slang!
No, no.
I'll bring water for your medication.
-No need.
-What?
I feel calm
after talking to you.
Oh, really?
I was able to help?
Will you embrace me?
What?
Please be my anti-anxiety medication.
No.
-You don't want to?
-No.
Just a light one.
Okay.
I guess I could do a light one.
What the hell?
-A glass ball?
-Yes.
It rolled into a drain.
I couldn't reach it.
Which glass ball?
Oh, wait! I remember! The one I gave you
with White Blood Cell.
But you're so honest.
That was just a tiny thing.
I could see the city upside down.
It was fun.
Then pay for my drink here.
-Sure.
-Really?
I liked seeing the upside down city.
-It felt new.
-Alright!
How is it going with your boyfriend?
The date. It went well, right?
I lied.
Nose hair.
-Nose hair?
-His nose hair was out.
-And then?
-That's it.
-That's all. The end.
-No way!
-Isn't that too hasty?
-Because…
Romance is to desire beautiful things.
-Who said that? Shakespeare?
-Me.
You can write too?
-Can you write a manga story?
-I can't write! It's my mom.
Your mother?
What does your mom do?
She's a writer.
Could she be Aoi Minase?
You know her?
Everyone knows her! Seriously?
That's so cool.
My mom is. I'm nobody.
What does your dad do?
I don't know.
I don't have a dad.
My mom had me on her own.
That's so cool!
You're a bit strange.
You are too!
You end a romance over some nose hair?
You're too narrow-minded.
Maybe he looked in the mirror at home
and went, "I've really messed up!"
Right?
Or, he grew it out as a joke.
No way.
Love is more random than you think.
Anything can spark it.
Oh, I was plagiarizing Shakespeare there.
I see.
Maybe a random love could happen to Mom.
Your mom, huh?
Mom's on a date today.
She's seeing Bob Dylan
with a childhood friend.
-You want more coffee?
-Yes, please.
Who's Bob Dylan?
What? You know Aoi Minase
but not Bob Dylan?
Your knowledge is skewed?
What?
That's Bob Dylan.
Wow! You can sing it!
I could sing it in French too.
No need for that.
He was so good! Dylan!
Gon-chan!
You're drunk.
Where are you headed?
Let's get more drinks.
You have work tomorrow, right?
Let's go home then. This way.
-Gon-chan.
-Yeah?
-This way.
-What? Where are we going?
SLOW DOWN!
Wow, brings me back!
They're building condos here.
Sora told me the other day.
Seriously?
See, it's written here.
You're right.
They're starting demolition
on February 8th.
They're taking it down next week?
It's going to go away.
Our elementary school.
This way! Come!
We'll get in trouble!
We'll be fine.
We played
"Pineapple" here a lot.
Hey, Gon-chan.
You saved me here once, remember?
What?
I was being bullied by
an upperclassman girl.
She was blocking my way.
FIRE EXTINGUISHER
REMIND EACHOTHER TO WASH HANDS AND MOUTH
Hey!
Get out of the way.
The stew will get cold.
It's my favorite.
Don't bully her just because she's cute.
You're cuter than her, you know?
So cool!
Hey. Let's carry this.
-Let's speed it up!
-What?
Push!
Why are we running?
What? Look!
There's always been ghosts
behind the west exit bathroom!
The blue hand and the red hand!
I haven't played like that in a long time.
My box was always filled
with love letters.
On Valentine's Day, they wouldn't
even fit in my box.
On that day,
I would borrow my friend's box.
Valentine's was snack day!
When I went to Odaya,
there was so much chocolate.
My name started with O,
so my class number was usually three.
I'd be around here.
Class number three,
Gonji Oda. Nicknamed Gon-chan.
Yes?
Let's not become a wife.
Mom messed up her line
at the most crucial moment.
Let's not become a wife.
Mom messed up her line
at the most crucial moment.
Um, well…
Wait, you're not becoming a wife.
You're the one getting a wife.
Aoi.
Yeah?
I'm sorry.
Well, you know, I…
Gon-chan was ruthless.
In these situations,
the man should leave the space
for the woman to say
"Come on, it was just a joke!"
That's what a real man does.
But Gon-chan was
still an elementary school kid.
I already
met with Aoba.
So you already had the marriage date?
I already asked
Auntie Toyoda to move forward.
So…
I can't return your feelings. I'm sorry!
Through a strange turn of events,
it was as if Mom was rejected
beyond any doubt.
As if she confessed her long-lasting love
and was rejected.
The casual line uttered by Mom,
called upon by the sweet night breeze,
grew into an irreparable ordeal
of confessing one's feelings
and was returned ruthlessly
by the cliché line for lost love,
"I'm sorry."
And she fell
into a deep, deep, hole
reaching the mantle of the Earth.
Here's the coated paper.
Here's the mermaid paper.
Here's the leather-like paper.
These are a bit pricey.
I can't tell the difference.
One's glossy, one's rough,
and one's sizzling.
-Sizzling?
-Feel it.
Excuse me.
Sizzle, sizzle.
Anything's fine.
-Are you alright, Ms. Aoi?
-I'm not.
I got dumped.
I do feel a little responsible for that.
But I suffered for two hours
clicking the same button.
-All for those Bob Dylan tickets…
-Why?
Why, why, why, why?
Why do I have to get rejected
by that monkey?
-He's a monkey?
-Yes, he is!
He isn't bad-looking, of course.
He was the star of the local
basketball team since elementary school.
All the girls cheered him on
in the sports contests.
But inside that head, he's just a monkey.
I went to the same cram school as him.
Gon-chan cried because he didn't get
the crane-turtle math at all!
He would add a bunny to the mix!
No one would solve that!
A crane and a turtle is too much.
Now, a bunny?
I'm glad the new member
wasn't a centipede.
He got bored of multiplication
after the fives.
He should've kept at that.
He'd get Valentine's chocolates, right?
He'd invite all his guy friends over
and eat them all up as a group!
Can you believe it?
They don't have an ounce of sensitivity.
He'd invite boys over
who didn't get any chocolates.
He'd tell them, "Eat up!"
And they'd be like,
"Why are we getting leftovers?"
And get even sadder.
But they're kids after all,
so they give in to how good
the chocolates are.
Eventually they'd start eating
taiyaki and yakisoba.
And his mom would make so much!
Of course, I would be eating
with them, but…
What are you saying, Ms. Aoi?
I'm upset! I'm so upset!
I got rejected by a monkey!
We're back to the start.
I didn't say I liked him.
I didn't say that at all. Not even a hint!
I just said,
"What if you don't get married?"
Because then, I can't go to Odaya.
Odaya's our living room.
To be honest, I don't actually like this
magazine cover house that much!
I just copied Ira Ishida.
These white walls that wash away
any shadow! It's for photo shoots!
I don't even get that many interviews
these days…
This room exists only to hide my wrinkles!
Like laugh lines?
Yes, exactly!
You're knowledgeable for a boy!
Do you do anything to remove them?
I just put on Nivea cream.
What were we talking about?
Monkeys.
Right! So I just don't like
that I can't go to Odaya.
It's not like I ever liked him
in the slightest!
Is that true?
Maybe you said that
because you liked him a little bit.
Well, it was the night.
"Let the darkness of the night
set the stage for love
with its thick curtains."
Shakespeare, Midsummer Night's Dream.
Right. So it was night.
We're inside a soon-to-be-gone school.
We saw Bob Dylan.
We were a bit drunk.
How didn't you sleep with each other?
That's what would happen.
-Huh?
-What?
Cut that part out.
Soseki. Are you experienced with women?
Could it be, Ms. Aoi,
you're bad at love?
Well…
Maybe I am. I had been noticing that
for a while.
It's impressive that you wrote
romance novels then.
In novels, men act the way I want them to.
Right?
So that's how it is.
You decided on that guy, then?
Kind of, yeah.
So I don't think I should see you anymore.
We're not cousins, you know.
-Was that a joke?
-Not very funny, huh?
That guy was actually really rich.
He owns several condos in Tokyo.
I didn't know! I scored big time.
-You lucked out.
-Yeah.
So, that's that.
I'm older, so I'll pay.
It was a lot of fun.
Can you leave first?
I like watching men who I've dated
walk away from me.
Let me see you off.
You move fast.
Are you sad?
Nope. I was just jealous that
you're this lucky.
I can't even win the toy I want
from a gachapon.
Your time will come.
Bye, Hikaru.
In love, whoever says goodbye first
is the winner.
Mine wasn't romance though.
Here you are!
Sora.
-Will you take a pic?
-Sure.
Alright.
-What are you doing?
-Ta-dah! Extended nose hair.
Realistic, right?
I was going to text a pic to him.
That nose hair…
-Where did you get it?
-I bought it online.
Funny, right? You know that place,
Taiyou-Do?
The chiropractor there told me about this.
-You mean Doctor Wataru?
-Yeah.
What are you trying to get?
Platelet.
Sorry for keeping you.
Not at all.
We'll go with the coated paper.
-Glossy.
-Oh, right.
Oh, also I have some news.
-Bad news?
-Why?
It's good news.
Looks like Don't Forget Me
could be made into a movie.
That's from years ago!
It won't happen, like always!
I think it will.
Oh shoot, I forgot.
A famous musician
said he wanted to do this movie.
He's the main character of our
"Early Spring 100 Books Fair."
I totally forgot his name.
CHIROPRACTIC: TAIYOU-DO
Welcome!
Why did you
come with
nose hair extensions?
Why?
Why did you wear nose hair
on our date, on purpose?
Hey,
you already got Platelet.
Look there.
You see that shiny ball?
The glass ball. I want that.
See you.
Wait a minute.
What am I doing?
I'm so sorry.
Is this him?
Yes, it's him!
YUTO KUON
No way! It's Yuto from Silent Knife!
I'm a huge fan!
I have all his CDs and concert Blu-rays.
He said he wanted to meet you in person.
Yes! This is a big one!
This rocks! This rocks! The Ezo red fox!
EZO RED FOX
I'm going to find love with him.
That's how I'll get back
at that monkey!
What are you saying?
I'll get back at Gonzo
for marrying that Aoba girl!
I'll find love with Yuto!
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE BEHIND THE SCENES
OF DATE MY DAUGHTER!
My socks came off!
PUTTING ON THE NOSE HAIR
DON'T BREATHE TOO MUCH.
Where's the nose hair?
THE DATE IS WITH
A WEATHER FORECASTER FROM ZIP!
Why do you always react
like you're in trouble?
-Cut!
-It's a cut!
"TAYAMA" WAS CHOSEN IN AN AUDITION
Soseki!
HE'S FINALLY ON SCREEN!
Where did he go? Geez.
CELLS AT WORK!
PLATELET,
WHITE BLOOD CELL
PREVIEW OF NEXT EPISODE
A movie, huh?
Let's swap genders.
What?
Will you go on another date with me?
I want to stop playing
with people's feelings.
I'm outdated, alright?
-I'll protect you.
-Stupid.
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION WITH NO RELATION TO
ACTUAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR OBJECTS.
Subtitle translation by: Yukimi Ohashi