Mom fell in love in the most shallow way
possible.
Cute…
Her daughter, me,
also had a fateful encounter.
Are you okay?
And it was with the same person!
The end! That's everything that
happened in Episode One.
What the hell? That's it?
Mom, language. You're too old to swear.
Well, Miss Sora,
I felt that the explanation
was insufficient.
We only have one precious hour a week…
-Let's begin the next episode. Enjoy!
-Enjoy!
CHIROPRACTIC: TAIYOU-DO
I feel it.
Something's coming.
Huh? What's coming?
A storm? A hurricane?
It's the middle of winter.
A big snowstorm or something?
No, something more…
Something more powerful.
Alright. Good.
CLASS CANCELLATION
Hey, is Mom pretty?
What the hell…?
Isn't that too much makeup?
Much more than when
your stylist Arai does it.
Is it an interview? TV?
A book signing?
The chiropractor!
THE CHIROPRACTOR
The chiropractor?
Yes. Remember I have a frozen shoulder?
It's actually much better, but…
Huh? Is it too much?
Hello, it's Tachibana from Saneisha.
Soseki, right?
I'm honored you remember my name.
I doubt most people can forget that name.
For the Early Spring 100 Books Fair,
your novel The Perfect Date
will be featured.
-It's been decided.
-Well, that's good.
It used to be Aoi Minase's
100 Books Fair a few years ago.
Oh…
I'm sorry.
Hey! It's a joke!
I haven't written 100 books!
Also, Ms. Minase, about the new novel…
Stop right there!
I have it.
-An idea!
-Wow!
I'm going to go find love right now!
Is that the title?
No.
A woman in her forties is going to
fall in love with a chiropractor.
Well, I'll say she's in her forties,
but she doesn't look it.
She looks around 30, maybe.
A romance with a chiropractor?
Is that something like,
she got touched
and felt something, or…
Anyways, that's the proposal.
Tell Konishi that, okay?
"Unemployment develops, that is to say,
because people want the moon."
This is what Keynes said.
If people accept
that fresh cheese and the moon
are the same…
Keynes…
What are you saying exactly?
It makes no sense at all.
Fresh cheese represents fiat money.
If the loan is money,
and everyone wants a loan…
Oh.
What are you doing?
What were you drawing instead of listening
to my very interesting lecture?
The people desiring the moon.
-So good!
-Wow! Nice!
Well,
I'll be taking this.
-You can't, Professor!
-Huh?
Don't throw it away.
I can't throw this away?
It's fine. Go ahead.
It's just a doodle.
Then, can I have it?
Alright. We're finished.
Thank you so much.
Oh god!
For frozen shoulder,
women in their fifties risk
damaging their rotator cuffs,
so don't move it if it's painful.
-Huh…
-What?
-Fifties?
-Yes, indeed.
You need to maintain good blood flow.
So make sure your shoulder doesn't
get cold.
A hot bath might be good.
Doctor,
I'm actually in my forties.
Hm?
Not a woman in her fifties,
but in her forties.
Oh, your age? You're in your forties?
Yes.
-I'm in my forties.
-Oh, I see.
-And how old are you?
-Twenty-five.
ODAYA
Isn't that rude? Do I look like
I'm in my fifties?
For a 25-year-old,
40, 50… It's all the same.
You're an old woman.
Here you are! Sanmayaki
and mitsumame.
If you eat that much,
you'll get a stomachache.
She's stress-eating!
It was so short!
The romance only lasted three days.
That's not real romance.
Hey, listen to this.
I created a new recipe.
Gorgonzola-flavored taiyaki.
-You want one?
-Nope.
Minase?
RISSEI GAKUIN UNIVERSITY
ECONOMICS DEPARTMENT
Hey, wait! Wait for me!
-Wait up.
-I'm in a rush.
-I'll hurry too then.
-Hey, Irino!
-You're going to karaoke, right?
-Yeah.
-The usual spot, Karaoke Zanmai.
-Okay!
-We'll see you there.
-Got it.
Okay, bye!
I placed seventh
in a national track tournament
back in high school.
You can't outrun me.
A popular kid like you
shouldn't talk to a nerdy kid like me.
The whole school will laugh at you.
-Is this a prank?
-That's so sad.
Why are you so cold?
Did I do anything to make you hate me?
Oh, the drawing from class.
Here you are.
Oh, hey, what…
Why did you do that?
You threw edamame too. You're a thrower!
Hey! Wait! I need to talk to you!
It's important!
Oh! Ow!
What's with that guy?
A housewife in her forties
in love with a chiropractor?
Actually,
I don't think she said housewife.
A woman in her forties and a chiropractor?
Yes.
Would that be any good?
A Japanese Harlequin Romance story?
I thought it sounded pretty standard, but…
She told me to tell you
to push that proposal through.
Geez.
Is even the great Aoi Minase floundering?
I was the one who discovered her,
you know?
Her debut was when
she was still in college.
She got her big break with
The Scent of the Sky at 23.
Oh, I'm the one that opened
the character for scent.
"TO OPEN"
TURN A KANJI CHARACTER INTO HIRAGANA
Otherwise, it was like an ad for Resesh.
Resesh? The spray?
The air freshener?
Now that you mention it…
THE SCENT OF THE SKY
Those who get their break early struggle.
Because they have to stay relevant
for a long time.
Minase started selling in her early 20s.
In this world, where you can't
catch a weasel alive,
being able to continue writing
is as hard as
winning the lottery.
Excuse me, Konishi,
but it's "catch a weasel asleep."
I said that on purpose, Soseki.
You work hard too.
I let you join my team
despite your issues.
If you don't prove yourself,
you'll get transferred again.
Yes. I understand.
-Sit down.
-Welcome!
Here you are.
Order anything you like.
-I just got paid at my job.
-Welcome.
Okay.
-Everything on this page.
-Wait a minute!
Hot chocolate, please.
-I'll have a coffee.
-Coming right up.
They don't have Jump.
I wanted to read Chainsaw Man.
Demon Slayer is fine too.
But I'm really drawn to Chainsaw Man.
It didn't hook me in the beginning, but…
What? What did you just say?
It was good from Chapter One.
You haven't read Fire Punch?
The author's previous work. You should.
It was on Jump Plus.
Or do you only read on paper?
Chainsaw Man is so freaking good.
I can feel my brain exploding.
I love it.
You know,
I've seen you before.
What?
I see you every week
at the Keynes Seminar.
I'm just a background character.
You probably haven't noticed.
No, somewhere else.
Even though you threw edamame
at me at the restaurant the other day.
It's somewhere else.
-Somewhere else?
-Yeah.
Where?
-At Comic Market.
-What?
Wait. Me being at Comiket
is like a camel drinking water
in a desert oasis.
-What does that mean?
-It means it's obvious.
Oh, okay.
Why were you there?
So you're an otaku too?
Bingo! I disguise myself when I go.
I wear glasses, a wig, a plaid flannel,
and a vest with so many pockets.
You'd never recognize me.
You were wearing a cosplay of Shiki
from Edens Zero and had a huge suitcase.
Can we get a picture?
-So cool!
-That's dope!
So cool!
You look just like him!
-You saw me?
-I did.
-You saw what was in my suitcase?
-It's fine.
I'm open to all genres.
NL, BL, GL. I read everything!
I don't have a preference either way,
but I read everything.
The open-minded type, huh?
Please keep it a secret.
Oh, sure…
But why?
My public image is Hikaru Irino,
the social, nice, handsome guy.
I successfully self-branded in college.
I don't intend on throwing that away.
Why not?
Oh, so you can get with cute girls?
You get it.
You're the worst. Go to karaoke already.
-They were inviting you.
-I'm not going.
I don't want to only sing
Kenshi Yonezu or Hige Dan.
I only want to sing anime songs.
You're a real otaku.
Here you are!
-Hot chocolate.
-Thank you.
-Hot coffee.
-Thank you, sir.
Here's your check.
Enjoy!
Anyways.
This drawing is wonderful.
-It's just a doodle.
-No.
Your eye level is stable,
the stipples are cool,
and your perspective is good.
Let's make manga together.
-Huh?
-I'll write the story, you draw.
We'll become the kings of Jump!
No way!
He's gone crazy! This isn't Bakuman.
So, are you going to do it?
No way.
Our series would never be Number One
on Jump,
let alone have it made into an anime.
And anyways, I don't even know
how to draw manga!
But you've always been good at drawing.
That's not relevant.
If all good drawers
could get a series on Jump,
Jump magazines would be this thick!
Like a telephone book.
Probably more.
You should try.
What?
Ever since you were a kid,
you always gave up before you even tried.
When I said you could go to art school
because you're good at art,
you said there was no guarantee
you'd earn a living
because that only happens
to a small group of people.
So you went to a regular college.
What's wrong with that?
There's nothing wrong, but…
It's such a waste. You're so talented.
Not everyone
can become successful like you, Mom.
That's not what I'm saying.
Yes, it is!
Things worked out for you,
so you don't know
what it's like to be scared.
Hey, you're pushing it.
I'm not!
I have regrets about art school too,
you know.
-You do? In that case…
-I knew that's what you'd say!
The world isn't as easy
as you think it is, Mom!
Not everyone can live
a lighthearted life like you!
I'm heading out.
-Listen, Kenta.
-Yes.
You have to listen closely
to the sound of the beans.
What, really?
It's true!
If you listen closely…
Simmer, simmer…
Huh?
"Not yet. Not yet."
You can hear that, right?
I see.
MOM
TURNING, FIGHT
AOI MINASE
THE TRANSPARENT YOU
Oh.
AOI MINASE
It's nothing.
AN OFFHANDED GOODBYE
It's time for dinner.
What are you dancing?
Dance with me.
Why?
Your mom and I went to see her.
It's Janis Ian.
Right.
You've told me many times.
-At the Budokan, right?
-Yeah.
That was a great concert.
It's a vintage item at this point.
I like the needles.
The way you place them softly.
You really love Mom, don't you?
Even now.
When I listen to this song, I remember it
like it was yesterday.
Mom didn't have a great son,
but she had a great husband.
That's how it is.
The son isn't so bad either.
CARAMEL SOY-PPUCINO
The guy from the other day.
Are you okay?
I met him again!
You are…
From that time!
Your glasses?
Huh?
How are your glasses?
Oh, excuse me.
Ouch! I'm sorry.
Oh!
I'm so sorry.
I'm too tall for this place.
I bump into everything.
How tall are you?
I always lie and say 187 centimeters,
but I'm actually 190.
It's too tall, it's weird, right?
Not at all.
I'm short, so I'm jealous.
It's cute when girls are short.
What?
What were you reading?
Oh, this?
AN OFFHANDED GOODBYE
-B-ah!
-What?
That was otterly weird. Get otter here!
-What is that?
-You don't know?
-It's a manga reference.
-I don't know it.
Do they also say "B-ah!"
when they're surprised?
No, this is otaku talk…
No, I was imitating the call of a Pokémon,
beloved by everyone in Japan.
It was a fun play on words.
-You're funny.
-Not at all.
-Do you have any more?
-What?
Other than the otter.
-I do. There's a LINE stamp for it…
-No.
Your own version,
if possible.
Purple…Girdle…
Pig-nosed turtle.
PIG-NOSED TURTLE
Pig-nosed turtle, huh?
I liked the otter one more.
Otters are cute, aren't they?
I've never seen one.
Oh, did you know?
There's an Asian small-clawed otter baby
at Ueno Zoo.
Really? They have one at Ueno Zoo?
Want to go see it together?
What?
What's happening?
Hey, old lady.
Are you going in or not?
I'm not.
Welcome.
ODAYA
Hot! So good! The radish is so good!
That's good.
You eat a lot, don't you?
-I pay for my food!
-Scooch over.
A percentage of our sales are supported
by Aoi's appetite.
You're drinking?
Are you sad that your daughter
got the hot guy?
I don't care about that at all.
I was just really surprised.
Really, really surprised!
I think it's my first time
seeing her smile at a boy.
The last time was in preschool,
when she was playing
in the sandbox with Shuhei.
Is Sora okay?
She's really not.
She's an otaku, you know?
She reads Chainsaw Man,
a manga where a boy
wears his own intestines as a scarf.
I don't get it.
Are you afraid of losing your daughter
to a boy?
That's not it, Shunichiro!
I'm afraid she'll get dumped!
She's an otaku,
you know?
It's like… Oh, I know!
Like that one time at preschool
sports day, she started running
in the opposite direction.
I was watching from the parents' seat,
and didn't know what to do.
Everyone else finished except for her.
Obviously. Since she was running
the wrong way!
And then finally, she realized,
"I'm all by myself.
There's no one around me."
And she just stood there!
Just remembering makes me cry from pity!
How old was she back then?
She was in the Bunny Class, so… Three?
Oh, I felt bad for her then.
You were there, Dad?
Never mind. Check this out!
How nice! A plum and a bush warbler.
It's almost February, after all.
Japanese hanging scrolls must get ahead
of the season.
That was Nako's favorite.
I see.
Today's her monthly death anniversary.
Exactly. Good memory.
Plum and bush warbler, willow and swallow,
Japanese maple and deer, bamboo and tiger.
Oden and sake!
Nako is Gon-chan's mother.
Shunichro's wife.
She passed away seven years ago.
Mom was close to her as a neighbor…
No, Mom thought of her as her own mother.
Mom took care of Nako.
Because back then,
Gon-chan wasn't in Japan.
Gon-chan didn't get to see his mother
on her deathbed.
Alright. Now Nako's in a good mood,
along with her favorite scroll.
Let's drink, the three of us!
We danced to Janis Ian too.
What?
Let's drink, Aoi.
Yes!
I've already started though.
Mom!
Oh.
It's like the moon's about to fall!
You here, Mom?
Is that how you enter someone's home?
Excuse me.
-Huh? What is it?
-We're going home.
-What is it? I haven't had the tofu yet…
-What's wrong, Sora?
-Something has happened.
-What do you mean?
-Something cataclysmic!
-What happened?
It's a date.
-What?
-Huh?
We must strategize!
Gon-chan can help!
Hey, I know all about dates!
-Ask me!
-No, me.
No. I can't rely on old men
who can't get women.
What?
I'll ask my mother,
the queen of romance novels.
-Give up on your tofu.
-What?
Let's go.
It's imprinting.
She's been telling Sora from birth
that she gets all the men
and we don't get women.
That's true. Kids always think
the first adult they see is their parent.
Huh?
That's not exactly right, Dad.
It's close enough.
But, I'm sure that Aoi was
popular with the boys.
Not really.
Her personality was her downfall.
I'm sure she was popular.
You just didn't see.
You're mean, Shunichiro!
It's cold.
So cold!
You're just wearing
a puffer over your pajamas.
Yeah, I wasn't really thinking.
You went outside in that?
Suzuran Shopping District is my yard!
Odaya is our…
-Kitchen!
You stopped growing.
-We're about the same height.
-Really?
I'll grow more.
Is that true?
I thought you'd grow taller than me!
I'll grow more.
Oh, did you know?
There's surgery abroad to
increase your height.
I do. It's pretty popular,
they're being flooded with bookings.
But it's really expensive!
I guess we can't then.
I'm heading out.
-Good night.
Yes, hello?
Hello. Sorry to bother you,
it's Tachibana.
Oh, Soseki.
You're not bothering me,
but I already quit Saneisha.
I wanted to ask you about Ms. Minase.
Love between a woman in her forties
and a chiropractor?
Yes. She hasn't called
since proposing that.
Should I bug her about this?
Writers need time to solidify their ideas.
Leave her alone for a bit.
I read the ending of Umbilical.
How was it?
UMBILICAL CORD
CHAPTER 2, FINAL CHAPTER
Well… it did feel forced.
I felt a writer's pride, though.
Well, finishing in two chapters
was like playing in
Extra-Hard Mode.
Extra-Hard Mode?
What's that, young people talk?
Whatever.
I think she feels very weak
right now as a writer.
Because of stupid Konishi,
she's only seeing numbers.
I wanted to protect her.
Is that the reason
you quit Saneisha?
I'm a woman,
and I was too weak.
Soseki,
you climb to the top and protect Ms. Aoi.
Do I have to climb to the top to do that?
If you continue to be an employee,
then yes.
It'll be alright.
She fights hard when it's needed.
She's probably writing that new novel
as we speak.
You're right.
All done.
"A list to get men"?
Yes. It's Mom's secret technique.
Secret technique? Like Pokémon?
-Tech Machine Mom!
-Huh?
One: Pretend to get drunk
after one and a half drinks.
Exactly. Like this!
"Oh, I think I'm drunk!"
This is a person. A hot guy.
Two: Pretend the train is full.
-Rumble, rumble…
-No need to demonstrate.
-Pretend it's crowded, and lean on him.
-Exactly.
Tip Number Three:
Say, "I forgot my gloves,
my hands are cold!"
And put your hands into his pockets.
Barf. Do I not have my own pockets?
It doesn't matter!
Four: Don't cry, but pretend to cry.
-Mom, how many of these are there?
-Sixty-three.
I didn't write these,
but don't forget the basics.
If the boy says something,
"Wow! Really?
I can't believe it!"
Exaggerated reactions. And smile!
And if you get Italian,
get tiramisu for dessert.
Tiramisu and strawberries are
a cute girl's food!
What era are you in, Mom?
That's Showa. Not even Heisei.
So far from Reiwa.
You poor thing.
Did this help you get boys?
You cunning woman.
You asked what to do for a first date.
That's why I dug up my memories…
No, this is too much work!
If I was Suzu Hirose,
I would just have to stand there.
Too bad, you're not Suzu Hirose.
If I was Haruka Igawa, I'd just sit there.
Mom.
You're sitting like an old man.
Oh, god!
But would Doctor Wataru
like this sort of thing?
All men love cute girls. Did you know?
When they took a survey
to ask everybody's type,
girls' types changed with their age.
They looked for traits like nice, cool,
and reliable.
But all men, from preschool to
elementary to middle
to high school to college to
working men and old men,
they all answer, "A cute girl!"
-Are they stupid?
-In a way.
Oh, you just called him
"Doctor Wataru."
You're already on a first name basis?
What a development!
No. Wataru's his last name.
His name's Shuichi Wataru.
I see. That's why everyone calls him
Doctor Wataru.
Oh, he said to say hello.
I didn't know you went to
that chiropractic.
Yes, actually.
Did he mention me at all?
Just to say hello.
That's it?
Also, he was worried about
your fifties shoulder.
I'm in my forties!
Woohoo!
Alright. It's your professor's turn.
"Daitokai!"
-Alright!
-Professor, that's so old!
You have to learn about the old times.
-Where are you going?
-Bathroom.
Sora Minase?
Are you leaving?
You have to participate
in the seminar parties.
"Cherish harmony among people."
Trademarked by Prince Shōtoku!
-That was Confucius.
-Oh, really?
You're leaving?
I stayed for 30 minutes. I'm good.
I want to go home too!
-I'm bad at singing.
-You're right.
And they make you sing Kenshi Yonezu.
I want to sing anime songs!
Don't tell anyone I'm an otaku!
I'm not flirting with her.
Sure.
Apparently, when I'm with girls,
it looks like I'm trying to seduce them.
Maybe it's this hand. It's too close.
Oh.
Listen.
It's hard for me to talk
with those eyes.
What is it? I want to go home.
-To watch Kaguya-sama.
-Did you watch Chika Dance?
They say they drew 845 key frames!
The movements were insane!
The way her skirt flowed was
so smooth…
You're already done peeing?
It was all occupied.
Maybe something's happening inside.
Dang! That's totally possible.
Whatever. I'll sing one more song.
-Can you put in "USA" for me?
-Got it!
-I'll be going now.
-Thanks! Hey, wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
Look at this.
-What is it?
-It's the plot.
I wrote a story for a manga.
I said I'm not interested.
You're annoying me.
I like reading manga.
I don't want to draw it.
Did she really call me
annoying?
It's a story about a place
that's not here.
It's about a time that's not now.
It's about searching for
freedom in a place not here,
a time not now.
Please look at it.
A time, a place, a time period.
A fictional world.
But such a world once existed.
And the government issues
a story prohibition order.
-A story prohibition order?
-Yes.
Because stories can
tempt hearts,
and tempt people.
They can move human hearts
more than any speech or lecture,
and influence them.
And then?
A boy meets a girl,
and the two break the law
to start creating stories.
Because that is their dream.
STORY
THE TWO DID NOT YET REALIZE
THEY WERE CREATING A STORY
If you can write such beautiful stories,
why hide it?
Because only otakus write manga?
Why sing Kenshi Yonezu?
Sing "Japari Park" instead!
Because it's lame.
Aiming for a series on Jump,
and wanting to make it an anime?
They'd just laugh at me.
That's cringey.
It's not my character.
And if I fail, it would be so pathetic.
And I'll fail for sure.
So…
You're actually a coward.
What?
You're the same as me.
I'm sorry. I don't have the time
to draw manga.
I'm busy.
What are you busy about?
Like playing games, watching anime,
reading light novels?
-Oh, collecting merch?
-A date. I have a date.
No way.
You have a boyfriend?
I'm going to soon.
This one? Or this one?
That one's cute too. Which is better?
Let's see. Which one is better…
Oh, she's home!
She has to try it on herself.
Huh? Why is she ringing the doorbell?
Did she forget her keys?
Huh?
The Early Spring 100 Books Fair.
We have a mockup for
the new cover of The Perfect Date.
I emailed you to tell you I'd drop by.
You replied and said okay.
I forgot.
Oh, please don't bother.
-I have my own.
-This is for me.
Ms. Aoi, do you cook?
I can only boil water.
I brew coffee.
I wait two minutes and 47 seconds
for cup noodles.
That's the best time.
I didn't know that.
You want to try?
I have curry noodles.
I'll have some.
I thought you'd say no.
I didn't have time for lunch.
PAUSE, CANCEL
Oh?
Just now, you called me Ms. Aoi.
I'm sorry.
I was talking to Ms. Matsuyama
and she called you that.
It's fine.
"Ms. Minase" is kind of hard to say.
The 'miz' and 'se' is tricky to say.
Oh, you mentioned the other day….
Wait. Ten more seconds!
Alright.
-You're right. It's good.
-Right?
It's my original recipe.
Oh, Ms. Aoi.
The romance with the chiropractor
you mentioned…
-It's over.
-What?
It ended before it even started.
I'm not writing it.
I see. That was fast.
Unexpectedly.
-What is that?
-It's from Zozotown.
I'll return what I don't need.
Oh, it's not mine. It's for my daughter.
Oh, I see.
It did look a little young for you.
My daughter's going on her
first ever date.
Your otaku daughter?
Is it her imagination?
Not imaginary. It's real.
Excuse me.
Ouch.
Ms. Aoi?
Just checking. Yes, it's reality.
Her date is with
the chiropractor.
The one I thought was cute.
Oh, I see.
It's very sad.
Even if I love like back then,
I'm not the same me.
I've gotten older.
Not at all.
You're still very beautiful.
Wow, the model answer!
That's not what I…
It's because you work for me.
Just because you're my editor.
That's actually quite cruel, you know?
I want to hear your honest thoughts.
You know,
maybe…
Maybe no one sees me as a woman anymore.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say something
so pathetic.
And in front of you.
I'm sorry.
Tip Number Four: Pretending to cry.
Mom was testing to see
if she still possessed her divine powers.
If her romance tricks she honed back then
would still work on men.
Wait a minute!
What are you doing to someone else's man?
Who is this person?
She was loitering
in front of our building.
I asked her what she was doing,
and she said,
"I'm a stalker.
"I'm the best stalker there is.
I'm on my 24-hour shift.
I stalk Soseki Tachibana of Saneisha."
She was funny, so I let her in.
How is that funny?
So we stayed quiet and watched you guys.
We were watching closely. But…
-I couldn't just watch this happen!
-You've got it all wrong.
I was just testing what would happen
if I cried.
You were testing me?
You too, Soseki!
Why would you enter some woman's house?
Once you've entered,
any woman would fall in love with you!
That's not true at all.
Hey. You've got it all wrong!
Let me explain myself.
Mom, show them that thing!
The list with 63 tips.
That was Number Four.
Right. Wait a second.
Oh.
Here it is!
See? I was just trying this.
Sally, will you just trust me already?
-Sally?
I'm Saori, so it's Sally.
It's not some woman's house.
She's just a novelist.
This is the home of Ms. Minase.
I'm her editor.
I know.
I know that! But!
I was tracking your movements.
You took the Hanzomon Line,
transferred to the Namboku Line,
then you entered this building,
then you didn't move at all.
That's why I got worried!
Are you okay?
I can't…
-I can't breathe.
-She's hyperventilating.
Do you have a bag?
That's been proven to be a bad treatment.
Just relax.
Calm down.
Calm down. Breathe out.
Mom gets this sometimes.
Like when she can't write.
Calm down, okay?
AZUMA
FULL BLADE
I knew it. I'm bad.
I can't do it!
I can't see the stars in Tokyo.
So pretty.
Are you awake?
This has a relaxing effect.
I fell asleep?
Soseki said
you have medication you usually take.
You took it and got sleepy.
So you slept here.
I see.
I made some lemonade.
You want some?
Thank you.
It's delicious.
-Where's Soseki?
-Oh, Soseki?
Soseki had to work.
He's back at the office.
What?
Hey.
Soseki isn't the one that's making
you a mess.
Love is.
Has Soseki ever done
anything to hurt you?
I get worried for no reason.
We live together,
but even then.
I worry because I'm not with him
all the time.
I got hired at Saneisha.
Because I wanted to be near him longer.
Even then…
Just watching him talk and laugh with
female coworkers drives me mad.
It's like someone is
wringing my heart like a rag.
I'm so stupid!
Soseki said
he'd make your favorite stew tonight.
Really?
Yeah.
Sally's about the same age as me.
Honestly, it was moving.
Maybe romance is a war.
For me, it's an encounter with an unknown.
I'll work hard, Mr. Elephant!
Sora Minase is
taking her first adult step!
Wow. Perfect.
Your mom has great taste.
True. But I picked too.
We picked together.
You're the cutest you've ever been!
Now, and when you were born.
Don't say things like that, Mom.
I'm not a baby anymore.
Roger that.
I wish you the best of luck.
Thank you, ma'am.
Doctor Wataru!
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE BEHIND THE SCENES
OF DATE MY DAUGHTER!
Now.
What the hell? That's it?
Mom, language. You're too old to swear.
-What the hell? That's it?
-Mom, you're young.
MOM, YOU'RE YOUNG
-Thank you.
-I'm sorry.
THE NOODLES…
THE NOODLES WON'T COME APART
THE TRASH WON'T…
THE TRASH WON'T GO IN!
A FAIL
ANOTHER FAIL
SO CLOSE!
A SUCCESS!
Yay!
Did you enjoy your date?
-An arranged marriage date?
-He marries.
We can't go to Odaya.
Go on a date with that childhood friend.
I need my own love, or I can't write.
Love is more random.
Will that random love come true?
Let's not get married.
Subtitle translation by: Yukimi Ohashi