What's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
I'm sorry.
Why?
For waking you up.
No need to apologize for that.
I was awake anyway.
Have I told you why we gave
Pichan the nickname Pichan?
No, you haven't.
He's always ready to pick a fight,
but in a way he's a coward.
He always gets anxious
when we have a big fight
and gets an upset stomach.
So we call him Pichan,
because his stomach goes "pi…"
Although he shuts himself
in the toilet before a fight
his upset stomach is cured when the
fight starts. Every single time.
Is that so?
I guess…
The scariest part of a fight
is the time before it starts.
Before it starts?
You don't know who your opponent is
or how strong they are,
but you can only wait,
and everything is unknown.
This is the scariest part.
Let's try to take the initiative.
What? Initiative?
I'm not saying that we'll go punch them.
I mean, we know nothing.
Although we want to look for something,
we don't even know what it is.
Yeah.
Thank you!
Thank you…
Thank you for being born into this world.
Thank you for being born into this world…
How do you feel?
After joining the whole purification
ceremony for the first time.
My body…
was trembling.
Marvelous!
Your soul was cleansed
by the purification ceremony,
and it was quivering with delight.
MIKI TIRES
-I'm sorry, Mikki.
-It's all right.
There is nothing to apologize for.
It's our regular day off.
Is Kayo still at Tenten's place?
Yeah, he picked her up when he came
to deliver our clothes.
-Excuse me.
-Okay.
Hello, Segawa speaking.
Thanks for calling me.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry…
No, I'm not available today…
It's suspicious that we couldn't
find anything at all.
Why?
I mean…
We should at least find out
where her parents work,
or her friends' contact details.
There has to be something
if this is where she lives.
Well, you're right.
Did Tagawa take them away?
Or was there for some reason
never anything?
Do I have a mother?
I can't even find a photo of her.
And nothing in this house
belongs to my mother.
Keebou.
This is strange.
I don't remember them…
and I can't recall what they're like…
but I miss them.
Dad…
and Mom too.
Don't worry.
We'll find them soon.
Is it the one Kayo was listening to
the other day?
This looks quite old,
so I think it might be your mom's.
June 10, 2004?
It was ten years ago.
Maybe it's your birthday.
Birthday?
Even if it isn't,
it still has to be an important date.
It's making a sound.
It's shallow.
-What?
-Look.
Look, the bottom of the box
seems to be deeper than this.
Yes, indeed.
A key?
What is it for?
This looks like a key
to an apartment door.
What is this for?
HAYASHIDA LAUNDRY SHOP
There you go.
-They're the guys'.
-Oh, thanks.
We have to do it for free for the guys.
There was a stain
that didn't come off easily.
I think it was blood.
HAYASHIDA LAUNDRY SHOP
A bloodstain.
I see.
Noriaki, you came back
with an injury the other day…
I told you,
we got into a fight with some drunks.
But you got another fresh wound
very soon after that.
It was obvious.
Oh?
Where is Kayo?
Oh, no!
A full-time employee in the main office?
The Security Measures Department,
that means they want you
to join the department
that takes measures
to prevent shoplifting.
Good Lord, I don't get
our company's taste.
Why did they choose me?
It seems that the number of
shoplifting incidents in our branch
-is much smaller than the others.
-What?
You have to do an exam as a formality,
but they want you to go to Tokyo
right after you do that.
-Go and get everything sorted.
-Okay.
I guess he'd have been delighted, too.
The detective who referred you here.
Manager…
Thank you!
Mr. Tokui, congratulations!
I'm so jealous.
I'd like to go to Tokyo too!
What?
Never mind.
Saya.
You didn't buy anything today.
I don't have to buy anything
when I'm with you.
Is that so?
Pichan.
Why do you let me buy whatever I want?
Is it because…
you think that I'm lonely
and you feel bad for me?
Toru.
You…
You're often injured
when you come home late.
Yes?
Are you…?
Did someone bully you?
What? No!
If you have been bullied,
just remember that I will protect you.
Because I am your mother.
I will protect you.
Remember to keep an eye on her.
I will. I'm sorry.
See you.
-I'm sorry, Mikki.
-I'm very sorry.
She went outside
when I wasn't paying attention.
Don't feel guilty.
I should be the one to say sorry.
It's okay.
Let's go home.
Sorry, Keebou,
for not completing our search.
It's okay.
Let's go to Choco's karaoke bar tonight.
Oh, thanks.
I'll call Ponjara and the other two guys.
Sorry for causing you so much trouble.
See you later, Tenten.
Thank you, Chairwoman.
Take care.
Let's go.
Look at this, Keebou.
An armband?
Is it a newspaper company?
ARMBAND, NEWSPAPER, PHOTOS
Nichidoku Shimbun?
NICHIDOKU SHIMBUN, GOTO
KARAOKE BOX URARA
-A news reporter?
-Yeah.
Hikari's dad seems to be a reporter
who works for Nichidoku Shimbun.
Seriously?
-Yeah. Look.
-Wow.
Look at the armband.
Nichidoku Shimbun? Wow.
The main office building
is in Shinagawa, Tokyo.
Like… We'll go and have a look?
We've finally found a clue!
When are you going?
As soon as possible. Tomorrow.
I hope someone will come with us.
I mean, if something happens to me,
it will be dangerous for Hikari
to be on her own.
I've been thinking.
I think we'd better leave this
to the police.
Frankly,
I think so, too.
But Ponjara…
-Same here.
-You still say that?
You all know…
that even the police can't be trusted.
Too many people have died for it.
Mr. Akagi,
the yakuza guy who liked whistle candies…
Even the fake teacher.
Though her life was saved,
she was still shot.
This is not normal.
We've been playing by ear when we do this,
but it's too risky
to get further involved.
We really will be killed.
I agree.
It's not a problem we can solve
just by following the nature of
the course or our fighting spirit.
But I thought you wanted to see what
you got involved in through to its end.
We're saying
that we have to risk our lives,
Keebou. Do you get it?
We won't be killed!
I guess…
But we have been close to
being killed many times.
But we were not killed.
It's the same this time.
If they want to kill us,
they can do it any time.
You are right, Keebou.
They can kill us any time they want.
The gangsters, too,
should want to avoid taking risks
if possible.
I don't think
they would lightly kill
honest people nowadays.
But…
You can't be sure that
they will always stay that way.
No matter how you look at it,
we can't possibly win this battle.
But guys, you still went there
at that time.
You still went to a fight where there
were 100 people versus you five.
It was a fight between kids.
-They didn't take our lives.
-Then what about Hikari?
-She is on her own!
-We'll take her to the police…
I'm saying that we can't trust the police!
But that's not a reason
for us to get further involved!
I'm sorry, that was uncalled for.
It's okay.
But…
We still can't risk our lives.
Just for someone's child.
There is someone else
who I want to risk my life for.
Okay.
I can do it.
I can go to Tokyo with you.
There is no one for me.
There is nobody who I want
to risk my life for, like you.
Frankly, your life isn't that important.
Choco!
Text me the time and stuff.
Thanks, Choco.
Sorry for getting you guys involved.
Thanks for everything.
KADOMATSU INDUSTRIES
Yes.
We have found Mr. Yanagihara's body.
But the guy on that side…
seemed to have been gotten rid of
before us.
Okay, we will.
The time has finally come.
Did the main branch summon us?
If you want to drop out, do it now.
You could get shot if it doesn't go well.
You don't have to lose your life
for nothing.
Boss.
-Thanks for everything…
-Seriously?
We were just kidding, boss.
Idiots…
Boss, we have talked about this,
but shall we have one as well?
What do you mean?
You know, like, "Who Are You?"
-Like, "Who are you?"
-We've already talked about it.
TOMORROW 7 A.M. AT THE SOUTH GATE. THANKS!
CALLER: SHIHO
What?
Shuntaro,
thank you for everything.
I was happy.
What? What are you saying?
I am going to die soon.
What?
But I have to hear your voice
before I die.
Seriously, I hate it when you do this.
You said that it wasn't love…
But believe me, Shuntaro…
I do love you.
And I love only you.
Where are you now?
The phone you have dialed
has been switched off,
and cannot be reached.
Darn woman!
Gosh! Seriously, will you give me a break?
Shiho.
Shiho?
Shiho…
Hey! Shiho, hang in there!
Oh, Choco.
-What's the matter…?
-The owner cannot answer the phone…
CHOCO
Let's go.
Don't worry, I'm here with you.
Mr. Goto's daughter?
Yes.
What?
Why are you here?
Aren't you with your father?
With her father?
He was sent to work overseas
for a long time.
-Oh, Miya.
-Yes?
Mr. Goto is in Italy now, right?
Yes.
What? Is that true?
Of course, he reports his duties
by e-mail every day.
Does he?
I'm glad for you.
Who is this girl?
She says that she is Mr. Goto's daughter.
Oh.
But that's strange.
-Strange?
-Yeah.
I mean, Mr. Goto's daughter
is in Italy with him.
He attached a photo of her
in the e-mail yesterday.
What?
Here it is.
Look.
Well, she does look like this girl.
Hey, are you a reporter from somewhere?
No, I…
You even bring a child with you
to infiltrate our company…
-Which company do you work for?
-No, I…
Anyway, get out of here now!
-Just go…
-Please let me explain.
Listen…
Hikari.
Look, I'm Matsui.
I'm Uncle Keita.
What a relief! You're unharmed.
I have always felt
that something was wrong.
When I read the e-mails
sent by Mr. Goto from Italy,
I just felt that they were not
written by him.
Also,
in the photos of Hikari
that Mr. Goto sends from Italy,
none of them show Hikari's face properly.
So…
I thought perhaps this wasn't Hikari.
But who did this? And why did they do it?
It's possible that…
he got into some kind of trouble
because of that case.
But Mr. Goto never told anybody
in the company
about his investigation on the case.
He suspected that someone in the
company may be involved as well,
so I can't be careless
and say something I shouldn't.
That's why I put on an act just now.
What case was that?
It's about…
his wife's death.
This is my home.
His apartment is around the corner.
I have been there many times.
Could this be your mom?
She looks kind.
A CAR CAUGHT FIRE
DEAD BODY FOUND INSIDE
THE REMAINS OF A FEMALE DRIVER
WERE DISCOVERED IN THE BURNING CAR
DRIVER FOUND DEAD IN A CAR FIRE
BUMPED INTO A LAMPPOST.
WOMAN BURNT TO DEATH IN HER CAR
Mr. Goto…
suspected that his wife's death
wasn't an accident.
Hikari?
You said she has lost her memory,
even the fact that her mom passed away?
Yes.
I see.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Hikari.
Tell me.
Tell me, please.
All the details.
Mr. Goto…
has always suspected that
the accident was planned,
in other words, it was murder.
And behind this…
was a cult called the Glorious Ark.
The Glorious Ark…
MITSUTERU SAKAKI
THE GLORIOUS ARK RELIGIOUS ORGANIZATION,
WHAT IS THE GLORIOUS ARK?
PEOPLE ARE INTERESTED IN THE GLORIOUS ARK
SUSPICION OF LAND TRANSACTION
THE GLORIOUS ARK IS A FRAUD RING?
Hello.
The key you showed me just now…
I think…
it could be the key
to Mr. Goto's desk drawer.
I didn't realize until now
that desks at the Culture Department
are different from ours.
Okay. I'll bring it there at once.
See you in 20 minutes then.
I'll wait at the entrance.
If we know what this key is for,
there must be something we will find
in what is locked up.
We will surely find it.
He's late.
Call an ambulance! Now!
Are you okay? Any idea who he is?
Are you all right?
Someone, call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance now!
An ambulance! Now!
Hikari, we have to go.
What the heck?
What the heck is going on?
Hikari, it's okay.
Don't worry.
Keebou…
MIKKI
Please come in.
Thanks…
The loot is probably not here.
We turned the place inside out
looking for it.
Well,
just remember where the apartment is.
Excuse me, but what is the "loot"?
Seriously?
Nobody has told you
what we are looking for?
No…
We were only told to bring them the kid.
They all looked down on you,
because you're a rustic.
It is a cellphone.
The kid's dad's cellphone.
What is on the cellphone?
I can't tell you that much,
though, just that…
it has stored photos with things
that shouldn't be in them.
Anyway,
why didn't you kill them right away?
The guys who were clinging to the kid.
Well, I just think that it isn't necessary
if we've got the kid.
But you haven't got the kid!
And that's because those guys
are with her!
Go and kill them now.
I heard that other side has long
been given the green light.
Kill them all.
Before you become a disgrace.
What…?
What is this?
Keebou?
Let's get out of here
when it gets brighter.
-But where are we going?
-Wherever.
It's dangerous to stay here.
CHOCO
I'm really sorry. I'm very sorry.
It's okay. So is she okay?
She is okay.
In the end she didn't
take enough to kill her.
Yeah, she did it on purpose,
it was a sham suicide.
I've had enough.
How is it going there?
The apartment where Hikari used to live
was right next to the newspaper company.
You've gotten quite a long way.
I'll go there first thing
in the morning tomorrow, then.
No!
Why?
You don't have to come.
-Don't come here, Choco.
-Why?
You guys don't have to come.
I can manage this on my own.
-Bye.
-Keebou!
Keebou,
I'll go to the police.
What?
-I'll go to the police, then you…
-Don't say that now.
-I'm sorry, but…
-If you're going now…
Then why didn't you
go to the police at first?
You don't like the police, that's why I…
The guys and me…
We all did everything for you.
Isn't it too late to say that?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it was uncalled for.
I should be the one to say sorry.
But Hikari,
don't be defeated.
I won't be defeated either.
So…
please don't say that.
Hikari…
In the bathroom?
MIKKI, THANKS FOR HANGING OUT WITH ME.
TENTEN, THANKS FOR WATCHING OVER ME.
CHOCO, THANKS FOR BEING SO NICE TO ME.
PICHAN, THANKS FOR YOUR SMILE.
PONJARA, THANKS FOR CHEERING ME UP.
MELOS, THANKS FOR BRINGING ME TO THE GUYS.
Hikari!
Mr. Segawa?
Oh? Miss Mifumi? Why…?
I came to attend my hospital's
seminar in the neighborhood.
What are you here for?
Oh, no!
Over there…
-Oh, no!
-What is she doing?
This is horrible!
We need to do something!
She's going to jump off…
That's… Hikari?
Hikari!
What are you doing, Hikari? Come here.
Stop there!
It's fine.
-It's fine now.
-What is fine?
This is not fine at all!
Hikari.
Don't give up until you win.
What is "win"?
I work hard, so I won't be defeated.
Then what?
Hikari…
Nothing.
I have nothing!
My mom is dead.
Maybe even my dad, too…
You don't "have nothing".
You've got me!
-I think of you as my family…
-It's fine, Keebou.
It's not fine!
Don't be ridiculous.
If you're prepared to die,
then you can do anything
with the same desperation!
That's not true.
You're killing yourself because you
want to do nothing.
You don't want to know anything,
see anything,
or hear anything.
That's why you're killing yourself.
Lots of people died…
because of me.
-It's not your fault.
-It is my fault!
It's obvious, don't treat me
like an idiot.
If you stay with me
you will die, too.
I am sorry, Keebou…
-Hikari…
-I'm sorry…
that I was defeated.
-Wait…
-I'm sorry…
that I couldn't win.
Hikari!
You didn't win or lose, Hikari!
Guys…
The fight has not yet begun.
We have just been brushing off the
sparks that have flown our way.
That wasn't a fight.
It starts after you're prepared
to take it on.
I'm ready for it now.
FROM CHOCO. KEEBOU SOUNDS STRANGE.
I'M GOING TO TOKYO NOW.
Mikki.
Grandma.
What should I do?
Who…
are you?
I am…
myself.
I will take on the fight
to guard what I treasure.
I…
promised none other…
than Mr. Akagi.
You have to take the exam later?
You… The position is not always open!
You might not even get the job!
Then I have to give it up.
What?
-I have acted cool once.
-Yes?
If you have acted cool once,
you have to do it
for the rest of your life.
I have promised the person
I'm indebted to.
Let me…
act cool till this ends, Hikari.
I have a button that I want to click too.
Saya.
I love you very much,
so much that I married you.
I really love you,
so I want to be with you forever!
Pichan…
But…
My work often prevents me
from staying home.
That's why I let you buy things.
I want to tie you to me by doing this.
You can buy as many things as you wish,
because I'll work hard to earn the money.
But Saya…
there is a button that
I want to click now, too.
It's a giant one.
Please, let me click this button,
just once!
This is the button that
I click once in a lifetime!
Hikari.
I'm going to be a father soon.
I know.
One's own child is more important
than other people's.
But Momoyo…
if our children…
suddenly lose their memories
and got separated from us,
we would pray very hard, wouldn't we?
We'd pray that someone would help them.
We'd desperately hope that someone would.
We would.
I just…
want to be that someone.
Let me answer it,
Hikari.
Your father's prayer.
I want to grow up.
Hang on a second, Toru.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I might look like one,
but I don't want to be a kid.
I don't want to be protected.
I want to protect someone,
like the guys do.
The guys?
People grow up when they carry
something on their shoulders.
Please let me carry you.
So that I can grow up.
We are all prepared.
The fight has just started.
Hikari.
We will protect you till the end.
We're not doing this for you.
We do this because
we all want to be ourselves.
That's why we want to protect you.
I'm sorry, Hikari.
Sorry…
I'm sorry.
We made you carry this burden.
I said that we do this for you,
but actually…
I made myself your burden.
You're just ten years old.
There have been a lot of scary
things and sadness in your life.
They're too heavy for you to carry, right?
Your shoulders are so narrow.
In addition to that,
you have to carry me as a burden.
I didn't even realize this.
And I wanted…
to protect you alone.
Hey…
Please help me.
Keebou!
I can't do this alone.
I know this now.
Please.
Please fight the battle with me.
We've already told you
that we're all ready to do so.
You never listen to what other people say.
Hikari.
I want to protect you
together with the guys.
Hikari.
You don't have to win.
We will win.
You don't have to carry the burden.
The sky is blue.
The clouds are white.
Get down!
Are you okay?
Choco?
Choco!
-Choco!
Choco…
-Hey, Choco!
-Can you hear me?
-Choco!
-Hey!
Choco…
It's you.
You shot Choco.
Rainman is coming.
If you hand her over, it'll all end.
THIS DRAMA IS A FICTIONAL STORY