Hikari!
What are you doing, Hikari? Come here.
Stop there!
Lots of people have died…
because of me.
You must have been scared, Hikari.
I'm Matsui. Uncle Keita.
Hikari.
I want to protect you…
together with the guys.
Get down!
Choco!
Choco…
-Choco!
-Go away.
-Please call an ambulance.
-Choco…
Now!
Choco…
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
-Darn!
-Pi, we're in a hospital.
How dare they look down on us?
Why did they shoot Choco?
It could have been anyone.
If they wanted to kill us,
we'd all be dead.
So it was a warning…
Guys,
I was really happy when I heard
what you said.
-But if--
-We have all made up our minds.
The battle has started.
Mikki…
We can't… no, we won't quit
after what's happened.
We won't give up before we win.
Who are you?
Oh?
-Idiot, this isn't the right time.
-Don't be so dumb!
You don't say that now?
You have to spend three years
to get the gist of it.
Sit down.
Don't worry.
It will be all right.
Hikari, don't worry.
Choco once fell off a motorcycle
and got hit and sent flying
by a dump truck,
but he only got a few scratches
and was alive and kicking.
Even when we fight he has never
been hit in the vital parts.
Because he keeps dodging.
So…
He isn't going to die.
Keebou, you know…
Hikari.
There you go.
Don't worry. He'll live. I saw his wound.
I promise.
You will meet your father, too.
Miss Mifumi, thank you very much.
We did nothing but panic.
But I was surprised.
Why was Choco shot?
You were talking on the roof about
how you'd protect Hikari, right?
Does that mean someone is after Hikari?
Who is it? And why?
Do you not like hot cocoa, Hikari?
I'll have it.
Ouch!
Are you okay? Did you scald yourself?
Gosh, you wanted it, Hikari?
I'm sorry.
It was hot…
Keebou!
The operation was successful.
I think he is all right now.
It helped that the first aid was perfect.
He was lucky that a nurse was there.
ANESTHESIOLOGIST
He was shot?
What, it wasn't you?
I thought better of you because
I thought you did it right away.
That means the other side did it.
Good Lord, those guys are greedy.
Who was shot? Did the guy survive?
How do I know that?
You came here from Numazu? Sorry
for making you come a long way.
Sir.
I'm allergic to cats.
That is unfortunate.
Hey, Kizaki.
Sir.
Did you not serve tea to our guest?
What…? Guest?
Ouch.
You idiot!
You're all simpletons,
that's why I asked him
to take the trouble to come!
He came from Numazu, the place in
the faraway land of Suruga Province!
I am sorry!
Well, it's not that far away.
Choco!
Choco…
Are you okay, Choco?
I'm not okay,
no matter how you look at it.
Choco!
Idiot! It hurts!
You are the idiot.
You made us so worried.
What? I was the only one who was shot?
Of course! We all dodged, dunce!
Dodged? You're not in the Matrix.
-Now, swap.
-Swap?
-Oh, swap.
-Hikari.
Come here.
Sorry for making you worry.
But I'm glad that you're safe.
Don't die…
Don't die!
I won't die.
I don't want any of you to die!
Please don't die! Don't leave me alone!
Hikari, don't cry anymore.
No!
We are from the Shinagawa Minami
police station.
We'd like to talk to you.
INTERROGATION ROOM TWO
We still can't go yet?
I'm worried about them.
There're officers standing by
in front of the hospital room.
I know, but…
Hikari seems…
Please go inside.
Please have a seat.
-I will interview him.
-Yes?
Would you leave us alone for a while?
-But this is--
-Please.
I'm from the Metropolitan Police's
First Investigation Division.
I'm Oshima.
You're Kiichi Segawa, aren't you?
Yes.
You were an important witness to
Inspector Tatsuhiko Akagi's murder.
Oh, don't cry, Hikari.
I'm really all right.
But it was my fault that you were shot.
I'm sorry.
Hikari.
Look at me.
I'm not dead. It's okay.
But…
if one of us gets injured again,
or worse, if we die--
-No!
-Listen.
Remember this.
Even if that happens,
it is not your fault.
All of us…
are here with you because
we decided to do it for ourselves.
Got it?
So this isn't your fault at all.
Even Dad…
What?
Even Dad's death isn't my fault?
Hikari, do you remember what happened?
When?
When you were shot.
Choco!
-Hey, Choco!
-Can you hear me?
Choco!
Then I remembered…
Dad was shot.
He was shot dead.
I'll be frank with you.
I don't think that you killed
Inspector Akagi.
From the case,
I can see the shadow of
an organization that I'm after.
So…
What is that organization?
I can't tell you.
The Glorious Ark.
Is it?
Please! Tell me.
What is happening?
I'm now working to try
to get the whole picture.
I'd actually like you to tell me.
How did you find that out?
Would you tell me everything
that you have experienced?
What did Keebou and the guys say?
I haven't told them.
Why?
Because there is someone
who I don't trust.
The person is among us?
Who is that?
Miss Mifumi.
Please leave this to me.
Why?
There have been too many coincidences.
She moved next door to Keebou,
and ran into him in Tokyo.
I just find this strange.
Well, you're right.
She has overdone it a bit.
Keebou thought it was a miracle
and was delighted about it.
He's such an idiot.
Also, just now Miss Mifumi…
You will meet your father, too.
I didn't tell Miss Mifumi
that my mom is dead,
but she didn't say I'd meet my mom,
only my dad.
I see.
But I know Keebou will just think
that it's nonsense.
Well, I think you should tell him
once and for all.
If he doesn't listen to you even then…
What should we do?
What are you saying?
Of course it's impossible!
Really, you always do what we expect.
When you were shot Miss Mifumi
worked very hard to save your life.
That's not the point.
That is exactly the point.
How can you suspect someone
who has saved your life?
Do you remember how many times
we have been deceived?
Mr. Akagi, and the class teacher, too.
But Miss Mifumi is different.
Why?
What?
Why is Miss Mifumi different?
Because she's pretty and you like her?
What are you talking about, Hikari?
What's the matter with you?
I mean, Keebou, if you trust her,
that means you don't trust me.
No, that's not the case.
Then why?
It's my intuition.
She is not a wicked person.
Keebou!
It's fine, Choco.
I'll say it.
In front of everybody.
On that day Dad suddenly
came home from work and said
we were going on a road trip.
It was already evening,
so I thought something was wrong.
Bavarois!
Apple pie.
Pie…
Roasted sweet potato.
Roasted sweet potato!
Potato…
You can name any snack you want,
it doesn't have to be sweet. Right?
We'll be there soon.
Did you see the picture I sent you?
I encountered an unbelievably
good opportunity, so now…
Hello?
Hello? Izuka?
Izuka!
Glad to see that you are safe.
On my cellphone…
Izuka?
Please help us! Just now,
in the hut up the mountain…
Dad!
Go!
I think they ran that way.
Hikari.
Will you do me a favor?
Yes?
Take it,
and hide it in a safe place.
You can do it, right?
Get away from here after you can't
hear anything, okay?
What about you?
Don't worry about me. Listen.
Hide it straight after you leave here.
You can't keep it with you.
Call my company
when you've hidden the phone.
Ask for Uncle Keita's help.
Don't go to the police.
No, I can't do it. I'm scared.
Don't worry, you can do it.
You are a clever and strong girl.
Dad has faith in you.
Hikari.
Have faith in yourself.
No matter what happens,
no matter how hard
your life is going to be…
you are who you are.
Don't forget that. Overcome
the difficulties and move on.
Dad…
I'm here.
Dad!
Give me your cellphone!
I've lost it.
Where is the cellphone?
Tell me!
Where is it?
Say it!
It's here!
-Hikari!
-I have the phone!
-Stop there!
-No, Hikari!
Give us the phone!
No, that isn't the phone!
-Let go! Let go at once!
-No!
Dad!
Give us the phone!
Then they hunted me down to the cliff.
I slipped and fell down.
That's all I can remember.
I was walking on the mountain
before I noticed.
And I'd forgotten everything.
So I don't remember
where my dad's phone is.
It's okay.
It's fine, Hikari.
I'm impressed that you've
recalled it. Well done.
Go and rest, Hikari.
It's okay. I want to go and
look for my dad's phone.
You want to go now?
Okay. Let's go now, to Mount Nakane.
Maybe one of us should stay.
I don't want to leave Choco alone.
You don't have to.
-You, stay behind.
-No, I think very soon…
Shuntaro!
What…? Why…?
-So she is Shiho?
-What?
Your cellphone kept ringing,
so I answered it and told her
what happened.
Shuntaro!
-Shuntaro, don't die!
-Ow…
It really hurts, Shiho!
-I'm sorry.
So now I guess none of us
has to stay behind.
Hasn't she gone too far?
Shooting them in the business
district in the middle of Tokyo.
Just make people keep quiet
about this, too.
What is the purpose of your
existence if not for that?
But this time…
there were witnesses.
You can get as many as you want,
I mean, the gangsters who
will take care of business like this.
You mean, get a fake culprit
from among the gangsters?
This country does not need gangsters.
You say they are a necessary evil,
but to sum it up,
they are only pigs that are here
for us to feed rotten meat to.
Humans make the meat rot, that's why
pigs are needed to get rid of it.
So we will just prevent
the meat from rotting.
We'll do a thorough quality control
and create a world that doesn't need pigs.
A very beautiful world.
I'm sorry, Shuntaro.
I didn't know, besides doing that,
how to make you--
Don't talk about that now.
Kayo…
my friend's grandmother
told me in the past…
that when you're not feeling well,
or when you're hungry or sleepy,
it's better not to talk about
something difficult.
All three apply now.
Anyway, go home for now.
Let's talk about it properly
after I get back.
-But…
-You know…
when I learned that you killed yourself,
frankly, I didn't feel sad.
I just thought, "Gosh, seriously?"
I just felt disgusted.
Shiho.
That's the way I am.
-It's not here.
-Already?
You draw your conclusion too soon.
But it doesn't seem to
be here at a glance.
You just glanced at it?
You know this just by glancing
at the ground?
I don't get what you mean.
Just shut up and search.
Be careful.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Sorry for making you come with us.
No worries, I'd like to help, too.
Thank you.
Pi, what is that?
A metal detector.
Pichan, why have you got that?
-My wife just clicked "buy."
-Seriously?
Oh, it has finally made its appearance!
Wow, it has detected something!
Really?
Great! We have found something!
Okay, go.
I knew that this would happen,
so all my gear is waterproof!
-This one, too.
-Your wife bought all of those?
Life must be tough for Pichan.
It has to be here!
Wow…
Found you!
What the heck?
Is it a farce?
Let's pick it up anyway.
It's for the environment!
You're ridiculous.
It's not here.
That's why I said
it was important to glance.
Let's go to the south to look for it
in the afternoon.
Oh, it's a bird.
-Oh!
-What…?
Over there!
There you go, Melos.
Hurry up, Melos!
You're so heavy…
Can you reach it?
Got it!
-Did your wife buy that too?
-Yeah.
They are in the spotlight all at once.
Okay, let's switch it on.
Try again.
Ah! It's not working.
Well, it has been left exposed
in the wild for days.
I think we can extract the data
in a store.
Okay, let's go and do that.
Hikari?
I'm glad we found it.
Keebou!
Get down, Keebou!
Guys, are you okay?
Yeah.
Guys.
Thanks for your hard work.
Give me the cellphone.
Freeze!
I won't miss this time.
You are the person who shot Choco?
You…
Ponjara!
Four more shots.
19 shots.
Mr. Segawa…
give it to us.
If you do,
then everything will end here.
Thanks.
For encountering her.
What?
Because you know my younger sister,
the Hierarch picked out
the two of us to do this job.
Our job was easy.
Because you are an idiot.
Right, Mifumi?
It's improbable,
under normal circumstances,
that she moved in
next door to you by chance,
or ran into you in Tokyo.
This is not some comic book for girls.
Didn't I tell you so?
They made you do this, didn't they?
Right?
They made you, right?
If they didn't
you wouldn't have--
Why do you still insist that?
I did it willingly.
I wanted to do this.
To make myself useful to the Hierarch.
To purify my soul.
The Glorious Ark?
Yeah.
You can do wicked things
to purify your soul?
Do you seriously believe that?
I do.
Why?
I have…
nothing else that I can believe.
Come on. Give us the phone now.
Give it to them, Keebou.
But your father risked his life to--
It's fine.
Give it to them.
I don't want any more deaths.
You're such a good girl, Hikari.
You are the cleverest among them.
Hikari is right, Keebou.
If you give it to them,
it will end here.
-Am I right?
-Yeah.
-But--
-Keebou!
We win…
when we have protected Hikari,
not the phone.
Believe in yourself!
If you can't…
believe in anyone or anything,
believe in yourself.
I trusted you.
And I trusted myself…
who trusted you.
Enough with your lecture.
I am sorry.
Hikari, I…
Choco.
Sorry.
Mifumi really is…
What?
Hikari?
Choco?
Yeah, your plan went well.
Hikari didn't tell you everything.
I told her not to.
We did it to trap the nurse.
Trap her?
At that time…
Where is the cellphone?
Tell me!
MOVING FILES
Paul.
Where is it?
Over here!
-Hikari!
-I've got the phone!
Give me the phone!
Stop there! Give me the phone!
So now the data is…
Paul has it.
Sorry for not telling you.
I told her to do this.
I'm sorry for not telling you guys.
But now the spy is gone.
This will buy us some time.
Okay, let's go look for Paul.
But still, it's difficult to find him.
Oh, Pi, have you got anything
like a dog detector or something
from the stuff your wife bought?
No, that's not something you can find.
I've gathered quite a lot of information.
SHUNTARO: I'M LOOKING FOR A DOG!
I THINK I'VE SEEN A SIMILAR DOG!
I KNOW THAT DOG! I SAW A GIRL IN
THE NEIGHBORHOOD TAKING CARE OF HIM
Is he Paul?
No.
What time is it?
Paul?
Do… Do something…
Hello, Paul.
Hello.
Paul, don't bark…
Step back. He won't come out
if we are here.
-He is very cautious.
-Yes?
WATCH OUT FOR BEARS!
Paul?
Paul.
Paul!
Paul?
He is Paul!
Paul has been guarding it.
Thank you, Paul! Thank you!
Yes?
Oh, the Metropolitan Police's…
Okay.
Segawa.
It seems that
the matter is pretty serious.
Do you know something?
No, not yet.
But the case relating
to your friend being shot
is now under press control.
Press control?
Not press restraint,
it's press control.
In other words,
the media weren't even informed
about the gunshot.
So…
Tell me what you guys know.
If you work with me your safety
will be guaranteed by the police…
By me, with all my might.
Please trust me.
Okay.
I trust you.
Thank you.
I'll call you again tomorrow…
Oshima.
Are you investigating something secretly?
Oh? Hello?
Mr. Oshima?
What's wrong?
Keebou, who is that?
You said you trusted them?
Oh, he is the policeman
who came to the hospital.
Why? But the police--
He is not a threat.
And your proof is?
He sounds determined…
I just feel that I can trust him.
How many times do you want to be deceived?
You've just been deceived by
that woman, don't be stupid.
I still trust her.
I mean Miss Mifumi.
What?
Why?
She is not a wicked person.
There must be a reason.
But wasn't she a wicked person?
She was a wicked person!
Hikari…
Keebou…
why do you never trust me
and only trust Miss Mifumi?
That's not true.
I've only got you, and yet…
No… Don't do this.
Don't tell the police anything.
Don't say that you trust
Miss Mifumi. Don't say that, Keebou!
Hikari…
I trust what I trust.
You're an idiot, Keebou.
I hope she will die, she should!
Hikari!
People who say that someone should die…
I don't like them.
Hikari!
CHECKING CORE DATA
No data? That means the photo
isn't stored in it?
Someone has moved the data to an SD card.
The original data
was probably moved there.
Darn!
How dare they give me this crap?
Were you deceived?
Now!
Take it back now! We have no time.
-Yes, sir.
Rainman…
Rainman is coming…
CALLER: KEEBOU
I told you to go home.
Answer it, maybe it's urgent.
What's the matter, Keebou?
Choco, we've found the data.
Seriously?
Well done!
We'll take it back first… Oh.
Oh?
-Where is it?
-You're stepping on it, Keebou!
-It's over there.
-Where?
-There.
-Oh, I've found it.
Don't drop it! It's important!
Oh, put it here! You idiot!
-Thanks.
-Idiot! You're definitely an idiot!
You're a bunch of idiots.
Ow… It hurts!
-Shut up!
-What's wrong with that car?
Guys, what's going on?
-Who the heck are they?
-Keebou! Answer me!
Guys… Get down!
Keebou! Hey! Keebou!
Hikari!
Hurry!
Guys!
What the heck is going on?
Give us the data.
Lady, I hope you won't
steal a march on us.
Give that to us!
-Do it!
-Don't be ridiculous!
We found it first.
Mr. Segawa, please understand this.
If you give it to us,
everything will really end.
Hikari can live in safety, too.
Of course, all of you will, too.
No.
Hikari?
No!
No, I won't give it to you.
I won't give it to you… No!
Hikari.
Don't move!
Stupid kid, we'll kill you!
Please talk some sense into Hikari,
Mr. Segawa!
Please!
Give them the data, Hikari.
Keebou!
Miss Mifumi is right.
Everything will end
if you give them the data.
Why?
Why do you only listen to Miss Mifumi?
Just give it to them!
You don't even know what it is.
But my dad died for it!
My dad…
Do it now, or I'll kill you!
I'll shoot you!
Please, Mr. Segawa!
Dad asked me to…
That's enough, Hikari!
Don't get us involved any further
just because you want
to do what you please!
Come on, Hikari.
You don't want any more deaths, right?
Thank you, Mr. Segawa.
Now,
everyone put down their guns.
Okay, listen carefully.
From now on I've got this.
I am your target.
-What?
-Don't be ridiculous!
Of course I won't give it to you.
Hikari, her dad and Paul
risked their lives to guard this!
How can I give it to you?
Hikari.
From now on,
I will exceed your courage.
Jump.
I'll kill you, jerk!
Keebou!
Come with me!
NEXT EPISODE
THE TRUTH WILL BE REVEALED GRADUALLY
THE REAL CULPRIT
SHOCKING LAST SCENE
THIS DRAMA IS A FICTIONAL STORY