Hikari!
Go after him!
I will draw their attention to me.
Take Hikari with you
and run away while I do that.
-Dad, no!
-Don't worry, I won't be killed…
before the ceremony.
What is the ceremony about?
Look at the content of the data,
then you'll know everything.
But please don't ever let Hikari see it.
Okay.
One more day. Just protect her
for one more day.
Please don't let her fall into
their hands.
One more day…
Dad…
Hikari.
I'm sorry, it's your birthday
tomorrow, but…
Keebou and Hikari are late.
WHO ARE YOU
-Guys!
-Hikari.
-Hikari…
-Hikari!
-Are you okay? Good.
-Yeah.
Keebou.
They got both the data and the girl.
What is your excuse, Ryugasaki?
If the ritual is brought to light, we…
We can deal with it.
We will get the power to do that
soon enough.
For a long time our ancestors have been
supporting this country
and running the government
in the background.
And finally…
the back and front will change places.
The seven of us will be the
generation to accomplish this.
But if tomorrow's ritual fails…
The ritual will be carried out.
The new world that is designed to be
subject to order,
and regulation will begin.
The seven of us…
and the new Rainman will start this world.
Here it goes.
I'll play the videos first.
NAME
YOKO AMEMIYA. MAY 19, 1984
Yoko?
No! Don't do this!
What is this?
No!
Dad!
What the heck is this?
It's not a movie, is it?
I think this girl…
is Hikari's mom.
Hikari's mom?
She died in an accident, didn't she?
No, she is alive.
Hikari's mom is now…
SOYOKO AMEMIYA. OCTOBER 21, 1957
No… Don't do this!
Dad!
Don't make her do this!
Please, don't make my daughter do this!
The ritual.
Dad!
This is…
the whole process of the succession
ritual that will be carried out.
This ritual is…
Ritual…
I have met them.
Are they Rainman?
No, they aren't.
Rainman is…
Hikari's mom.
Why are you doing something so horrible?
It's the rite of passage.
So that she'll be aware of her fate
of having to live in the dark
and accept it.
Where there is light,
there is shadow.
Light can't be born without shadow.
The sun warms everything,
but if it doesn't rain,
the sunlight
will burn everything.
Is Rainman the shadow and the rain?
It's the seven people who make
the sky rain.
What I have is the ground of history only.
I'm nothing more than a symbol.
So…
A part of me thought
that maybe I could totally escape from it.
I left my home,
encountered you,
then I was blessed with Hikari.
I thought…
maybe I could live my whole life
as Yoko Goto.
However…
It wasn't possible.
The day my mother died,
they feigned an accident
and brought me here.
So that I would…
become the next Rainman.
Rainman is a post passed down on the
maternal side of the family,
from mother to daughter, and has
existed for several centuries.
On the daughter's 11th birthday,
she would kill her father herself
and perform the rite of passage
and get the title…
Kill her father?
The current Rainman is Hikari's mom,
right?
That means…
Hikari will be the next Rainman.
Hikari's 11th birthday is…
It's tomorrow.
Is that why Mr. Goto asked us
to protect Hikari for one more day?
What on earth is Rainman after all?
I don't really know, too, but…
There is one thing that I'm certain about…
I don't care what this ritual is about,
but I will never
let Hikari do something so insane.
Okay. We'll protect her.
I will not let her do something as
cruel as killing her own father.
Please.
Help Hikari.
She will never
be able to escape from this.
This is her destiny.
Because she was born as my daughter.
There you go.
Thank you.
Let's go to another place.
It's difficult to fight here.
We can't do anything if they besiege us.
Our old hangout in the union will do.
Good idea. The structure there
is complicated.
Tenten used to get lost inside, after all.
-Is the place still there?
-Yeah, Chancellor told me so.
He told us to move there
when this place was found.
He has suddenly become nice, hasn't he?
What are you saying, Melos?
He has always been nice.
-Keebou is amazing.
-You don't say.
Keebou has always been amazing.
There are two entrances,
one at the front and one at the back.
We'll divide into two groups
and fortify the defenses.
Keebou, you'll stay with Hikari…
in this room.
Why?
In case they break our defenses,
you will protect Hikari.
Okay.
Well, we'll never let them break
our defenses,
Hikari.
I can't tell you why,
but they will never harm you.
What?
So don't worry.
I'm not worried.
I think Miss Mifumi should go.
Maybe there is something that
she wants to settle, too.
INCOMING CALL
Hello?
Shuntaro?
You've finally answered my call.
Will I not see you again?
No.
I'll be on my own if you're not with me…
Be on your own, then, Shiho.
We'll separate from each other
properly for once.
If not…
We'll never be able to love anyone again.
I'll hang up now.
Shuntaro…
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
How long have you been there?
You actually can love someone, Choco.
Yes?
I mean, no matter how you think about it,
that was love.
It's love.
Don't look so cocky, idiot!
It is love.
-We can see them on the monitors!
-Keebou.
-Wow!
-Melos.
-It's mine?
-Yeah.
When did you make it?
This brings back a lot of memories,
and it has touched my heart,
but wearing this at this age is a bit…
Let's do it!
Wearing it gets me in high spirits!
-You're so cool!
-Check it out!
What are you doing, Keebou?
Get changed already!
Miki, you too?
WHO ARE YOU
Maybe…
it will sound stupid when I say it,
but I'm glad that you're here.
Today, until midnight,
when a new day begins,
we will die to protect Hikari.
They're here.
One, two…
It is no use putting up any resistance.
Surrender at once and release the girl!
Go!
In your face!
Idiots!
Hang on!
It will be dangerous if there is any
spark near the liquid.
Retreat! Fall back! Now!
One, two…
Go!
Now you see how powerful 398 crow
netting No.eight is!
Your wife has bought a wide range
of things!
Yeah.
In your face!
It is okay, Hikari.
Yeah.
I know.
After everything I've been through,
I'll fight with you, too.
CALLER UNKNOWN
-Hello?
-Are you Kiichi Segawa?
This is my last warning.
Listen to me and hand the girl over to us.
I'll spare your life if you do now.
Where did you get their cellphone number?
I've gotten hold of
all your personal information.
Why don't you give up?
You have no chance of winning.
It's obvious if you look at the situation.
We are still on our way
to claim our victory.
We won't be defeated.
I have faith in them.
You have faith?
How many times have you been
deceived and betrayed?
You never know when they're going to
betray you.
Even the people who seem to be
your ally now.
Trust is only an illusion.
Everybody knows that it does not exist.
That's why people sound each other out,
they hide things from, deceive,
and trick each other.
That is why they need to be controlled.
Whoever disrupts order will be
thoroughly eliminated,
and all personal information
will be made public
in our clean world.
Don't you think it's wonderful?
Betrayal cannot possibly happen.
What the heck? This is absurd.
Being betrayed is no big deal.
When you trust someone,
it includes the betrayal as well.
You don't trust someone because
you know they won't betray you.
Trust is when you accept it
if someone betrays you.
That is what trust is.
The person betrays you
because something forces them to.
The person who betrayed me
would suffer and feel the pain
more than me.
The guys and I all know that,
so I trust them wholeheartedly.
We do not need your world.
You can continue to follow this
naïve and foolish heroism.
That's the end of my warning.
Miki!
Come on, you're still wearing that?
Why didn't you wear yours?
You still have it, don't you?
Of course!
In your face!
Do you know…
that the riot squad is attacking
some good citizens who are unarmed.
Rainman probably put them up to it.
All of you are involved?
I have no right to say this,
because I was used as well,
and committed a serious crime.
That's exactly why I'd like to ask you.
Hey.
Why did you become a police officer?
For the power or money?
Because you want an umbrella, so
that you can get out of the rain?
It was because you wanted to
become a hero, wasn't it?
Is that what you want to say?
-This is stupid.
-I wanted to be a hero.
I wanted to be a knight in shining
armor! Hero!
Kick him out at once!
I believe that…
there are still heroes among us!
Like he trusted me from the bottom
of his heart,
I believe in the conscience
that you possess as a police officer!
You…
Please stop the Glorious Ark.
Please.
You're the only one who can do that.
I wonder why they can
sacrifice their lives.
Just for a child
who is not related to them.
They never think that
they will be defeated.
They have no chance of winning
no matter how you look at it.
Rainman is a devil
who would force a wailing girl
to kill her own father.
It's because they have faith in…
themselves and their friends
from the bottom of their hearts.
That's what your believers do, too.
They trust you from the bottom
of their hearts.
They want to be useful to you,
so they risk their lives
and fight for you.
They threw away everything
just for you.
Why…
do they do that?
That's because they love you!
They want your words of praise.
They want your love.
Because they think that…
it's okay for them to stay alive,
and they're people who are
worthy to stay alive
if they do so.
Go away.
You can kill me if you want!
-But please stop them!
-Just go!
What about him…
that makes you do this for him?
Both you and those people.
Mr. Segawa…
We only knew each other
for a short period of time,
but he trusted me wholeheartedly.
You should know
how happy…
this made me feel.
I'm so happy that…
I can risk my life to repay him.
You were also…
like Mr. Segawa.
The reason why people loved you
when you were a child
must be because
you were a very nice person.
Will you tell me one thing?
Am I…
God's messenger?
Or am I…
the devil's instrument?
You are…
Human.
And Mr. Segawa will say…
"You are…
who you are."
Keebou!
How do you explain that?
Ryugasaki!
I will go to the police now.
I have to tell them everything that
my sister had done,
and atone for our sins.
Thank you.
For trusting me.
And telling me…
to believe in myself.
When you come back,
I've something to tell you.
I'll be waiting for you.
Chancellor, thank you for your help.
I guess we're even now.
Yeah.
I'm tired now, Patrasche.
-What?
-It's A Dog of Flanders!
You've told me.
I'm quitting for real this time.
There's no way I'm doing it.
It's embarrassing.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-Yes, Boss…
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, HIKARI
Hikari, make a wish.
You have to do it before you
blow out the candles.
-That's a stylish tradition.
-A Western one?
-Okay, tell us your wish, Hikari.
-She has to say it?
Let us hear your wish, Hikari.
I was…
very scared
before I met Keebou.
I didn't remember anything,
and I didn't even know who I was.
But after I met Keebou,
I knew right away…
that I could trust him.
When I met the rest of you, too,
I knew that right away as well.
So I want to become someone like you guys.
I want to become someone who is
not just protected by someone,
but who can protect others as well.
Hikari,
the candles are melting.
Choco, too.
Blow the candles out with me, Choco.
-Why?
-Just do it.
How scary.
Do it now!
The wax will drop on to the cake.
Blow the candles now!
Choco, be more sensitive!
Fine.
Ready, go…
Choco.
I'm so happy.
It is the smell of happiness.
Oh? Is he crying?
-Yes, he is.
-Wow, Choco is crying!
-I'm not crying, idiots!
-You are crying!
Your eyes will swell this much again.
Gosh, Choco!
I knew it.
I knew that wasn't the end of this.
And he timed it perfectly.
I'll say it only once more.
Hand over the girl.
Of course we won't do that.
I see.
All of you have to be eliminated,
just as I thought.
To express it in the
vulgar terms that you use,
you are "incorrigible morons".
The game is over.
People will be there to get her here soon.
The number of people
is 100.
100 people?
They've got some very nasty weapons.
Miki, I'll go with you guys, too. Okay?
100 people, huh?
It's 100 people.
This is a clever arrangement.
We won't be defeated this time.
Of course we won't.
Keebou is here this time.
-And we have one more on our side.
-Yes!
Okay, let's go.
Hang on.
Keebou, didn't you tell me
that they would never harm me?
Put down your weapons.
If you fire, you could hit Hikari.
-You use a girl as your shield?
-Of course not!
We are her shield!
We won't let you
get even a step into this circle!
Hikari.
Close your eyes until we tell you
to open them.
Remove weapons.
30 more minutes!
You guys really are idiots.
Do you know that
in the world,
the nicer you are, the more stupid
people think you are.
I wonder why people look down on
those who are kindhearted.
Honest people are deceived,
and only hard working people
have to suffer.
Seize them!
Perhaps he is right.
The world is helpless, dull
and not interesting at all,
and you can't do anything easily!
So I'm so glad to have met you!
I'm so glad to have met you all!
Go.
20 more minutes!
Thank you, Hikari!
For bringing me to the guys again,
and for letting me meet Melos!
I should be the one…
I should be the one to say thank you!
Say it now, Melos!
Say it now!
Who are you?
I am…
Myself!
Ten more minutes!
I thought I couldn't fly anymore,
because the burden was too heavy.
Until you came back.
I know this now, Keebou.
If I can't put down the burden,
then I only have to make
my wings stronger!
On the contrary, mine is too light.
I was like floating in mid-air,
and I thought that was how much
I was worth.
Thank you, Keebou!
For letting me carry Hikari
on my shoulders.
My feet have touched the ground
for the first time.
What is this, the time to say
something cool?
-I can't come up with any!
-Same here!
But don't worry, Pon, you're quite cool.
You, too, Pi.
I had forgotten for a long time, Keebou,
that we were actually very cool!
It's easier to forget,
and get looked down on, do whatever
people say and laugh foolishly!
But Keebou, when I met you again,
I remembered this…
-Don't you dare look down on us!
-We are…
Very cool…
Three more minutes!
I'm having so much fun now!
I'll tell my children…
that there will be a lot of agonies
and sadness in their lives,
so they have to find their friends.
Find the best friends
who you can laugh with when going
through hell if you're with them!
One more minute!
Okay…
Until we win…
Don't be defeated!
Ten more seconds!
We will win!
Five, four, three, two…
Yes!
Hikari, you can open your eyes now.
Keebou.
Hikari!
No! You can kill me,
-but don't make Hikari…
-Shut up!
Rainman's succession ritual
will be performed as of now.
Get him!
Come here!
Give me back!
-I can't let Rainman end!
-Of course I won't give you back!
Have you thought about…
how much lazy and incapable
losers like you
have kept victors from succeeding?
In our ideal country…
What are the victors and victory
that you are talking about?
To me it doesn't look at all like
you have won!
He is right.
You lost the battle, Ryugasaki.
This is the end of the story.
I will be
the last Rainman.
You can't do that. If the rain stops,
-this country will…
-Rain stops.
But the sun doesn't disappear.
Even when it is raining,
it is shining above the clouds.
It will never be realized.
Because…
it is the sun that produces rain.
Sunlight,
flowers,
and a populated village.
That's what Hikari means.
I gave Hikari her name.
My name…
Yoko…
means the sun.
It is the name
that my mother gave me.
No mother would ever wish her daughter…
to live a life that is…
as awful as being exposed
to the cold rain.
Hikari will be all right.
Because she is exactly like
what her name means.
So…
Don't worry.
Thank you.
For giving her
hope…
and light.
Fua, Yua, this is Daddy.
Oh, Noriaki, you have to deliver
the clothes.
You don't want to separate from
Daddy, do you?
-You have to go, come on.
-Hang on…
She…
-What's the matter?
-Fua's eyes somehow look like Choco's!
Ouch! It hurts!
-They are your children!
-I'm sorry.
I was kidding.
-I'm sorry!
-No need to apologize.
I think I'm going to
wear this when we go to visit
Masayoshi in your summer holiday.
What do you think?
Why not? It really suits you.
Mom.
He called me Mom…
Bikini! A white one!
Mom!
-I'll click it, Saya.
-Wait, Pichan!
Buying a house online is a bit…
But it's on special offer, Saya,
-and it's got a garden!
-I know, but…
I'm happy enough to live here,
as long as you're with me.
This is so sweet, Saya!
THANK YOU FOR YOUR PURCHASE.
He just clicked the button.
Great! I will work my ass off, Saya!
Oh! Pichan, I love you!
You'll really do that?
There was a sharp rise in the amount
of shoplifting during your absence.
I have no idea why an idiot like you
can prevent so many crimes.
-Manager! Thank you!
-Hey…
I'm so happy for you, Teppei!
-Teppei?
-Hana!
-Hana?
-Oh…
Since when have you two…
Sorry that I didn't tell you, Big bro.
-Big bro!
-Shush!
Call me Manager in the supermarket!
You promised you'd pretend
we weren't related!
But your surnames…
I married into her family.
What?
Miki!
Long time no see.
Why are you here? You moved to Tokyo
when you got married, right?
I got divorced and I'm back.
What are you doing here?
How is everyone?
-How are Pichan and Tenten?
-Good.
Kayo! Long time no see!
Minny!
I'm so happy that you remember me!
Yes, I'm Minny!
You often treated me to
the curry you make.
You look so lovely!
I'm not lovely now, I've grown old!
How have you been?
We haven't met for a long time!
Your smile is still very bright.
Thank you.
I thought you said you were a housewife?
I was never married…
to begin with.
Then why did you lie to me?
Because…
A single and poor ordinary
middle-aged woman
wouldn't have interested you.
Well, I guess you're right.
I'm sorry.
When will your shift end today?
What?
Let's go and have dinner.
Come on, don't cry.
Why are you grinning on your own?
It's from Hikari!
Let me see!
Wow!
Keebou, Miki,
Choco, Ponjara,
Pichan, Tenten,
Melos.
I've found some friends, too.
I've found some friends with whom
I can be myself when I am around them.
Someday the little band of us
will go to see you together.
I guess the "you" means me.
Idiot, of course it's not!
It's Keebou she misses most.
We only play a minor role.
Brilliantly, though.
Well, Miki…
Something is bothering me.
What?
What is this key for?
Don't pursue that issue.
-Why?
-Well…
I sense more trouble coming.
Please help me!
You see?
I've lost my way.
Who are you?
THIS DRAMA IS A FICTIONAL STORY