Today, before dawn,
a fire broke out in a hotel
Narita City Airport, Chiba Prefecture.
The victims of the fire
seem to be 44-year-old Yukio Goto
and his daughter,
ten-year-old Hikari Goto.
The police are working to determine
the cause of the fire.
No way…
This isn't true…
You have to be kidding!
According to the fire service,
the cause of the fire was smoking in bed.
Sadly, the fire sprinkler in the Gotos'
room was the only one that didn't work.
METROPOLITAN POLICE SHINAGAWA
MINAMI POLICE STATION
Mr. Oshima.
Please let us see Hikari.
The state of the body
is pretty horrible, are you sure?
I want to see her.
I want to see Hikari.
Hikari…
Are you sure that this is Hikari?
We're hurrying to run a DNA test,
but the dental record matched hers.
I think the fire was not related to
the series of incidents.
Also, the flight they were supposed
to take yesterday
was canceled because of an engine failure,
so they had to stay in that room…
These incidents are also just
extremely coincidental.
It is difficult to tamper with the
fire sprinkler in advance,
and the SD card was inserted
into the laptop,
though it was so badly damaged that
it was impossible to analyze.
But it probably stored the data.
-Where is Paul?
-Yes?
He's the dog that Hikari has with her.
I haven't been told about that.
I'll check that as soon as I can.
Thank you.
Most of their belongings were burned,
but this was left in the bathroom.
Saeki, Tokui.
I'm very sorry.
I know apologizing isn't enough to
ask for your forgiveness…
I…
I thought you were as stupid
as the old people
who'd fall for the "it's me" scams.
Nobody falls for them.
But that's what parents are.
The stupid and unforgivable ones are
the people who used a parent's love
to deceive them.
Sorry for making you do something
so difficult. Thank you.
It's okay. I'll call you when
I get hold of any information.
But more importantly,
is Segawa okay?
He is not okay.
Of course,
he's not the only one. None of us is okay.
Mr. Oshima, he is a white Poodle.
Hikari's dog. There is a large bell
attached to his collar.
Okay.
-Thanks very much.
-Okay.
Darn!
I hate how this ended!
Hikari…
was smiling in the airport.
We had won…
That was what we thought.
Toru, stay at my place today.
Keebou, too.
Stay with Miki, Keebou.
No, I'll go home.
Just stay at Miki's place.
Or you can stay with me.
You can stay at mine, too.
I'll go home.
Maybe Hikari will come back.
Keebou!
Pull yourself together! Don't be stupid.
Of course she won't come back.
Hikari is dead.
I don't believe this.
This isn't about whether you
believe it or not.
This is the facts, Keebou!
-You have seen Hikari's…
-That wasn't Hikari!
-You…
-Don't say that, Keebou!
You would have hurt Hikari's feelings!
Hikari was…
our Hikari, wasn't she?
Keebou.
People die,
you know…
-Keebou!
-Let him go.
But…
At a time like this there is no use
saying anything.
Okay… I'll go to work now.
-Choco.
-Hm?
Is Paul a Poodle?
-No?
-Well…
-I don't know much about dogs.
-Same here.
But I can tell the difference
between black and white.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
I LOVE YOU, KEEBOU.
Thank you for helping me.
I love you, Keebou!
Hikari…
Hikari!
Mr. Segawa.
I'm shocked to learn about…
what happened to Hikari.
It didn't occur to me that
this would happen.
Miss Mifumi…
What about the Glorious Ark?
Please don't worry about that.
Futaba and the other two people
had betrayed them,
so I said I had purified them.
-What are you going to…
-I will…
live my own life.
So please…
return to your own life, too.
I wonder…
what my life really is about.
I remember you once said
that when you don't want to do anything,
see anything and hear anything,
that's when you want to kill yourself.
I know this now.
What that means.
Mr. Segawa…
We had protected her.
From gangsters,
a killer,
and even the police.
Why did a fire kill her?
Was I…
defeated?
Keebou isn't answering the phone?
-The number you've dialed has…
-He ignored it yesterday too.
Oh, I ordered soba noodles in soup, ma'am.
The tempura is on the house.
You look quite depressed.
Thank you.
Of course, I have heard about it as well.
The groundless slander and defamation
against the Glorious Ark.
Real righteousness has always
been persecuted throughout history,
-but eventually…
-That pig…
…real righteousness will change the world.
Again!
-One more time!
-Keebou!
Empty yourselves!
Hey.
You're the guy who was with…
What are you doing here?
I brought him here.
He has lost everything.
Then he realized
how foolish and weak he had been.
Please let me join you!
I have left nothing for myself.
I'm prepared to offer everything
to the Glorious Ark.
Regardless of their past
we accept everybody who seeks
salvation without question.
This is the spirit
of "Everything's all right", isn't it?
-But that's…
-She is right.
Hierarch…
Segawa.
If someone like you
would become one of us,
it would be very encouraging to us.
But still,
we have too much history.
If you say that you're not
our enemy anymore…
then can you provide us with some proof?
What should I do?
-There's no doubt about it.
-It's Keebou.
That's Keebou.
What is that idiot doing?
Has Keebou ever worn glasses?
I think it was the best disguise
that the idiot could come up with.
He didn't answer.
-Still no signal?
-No.
He wasn't at his home yesterday, too,
when I dropped by on my way home
after delivering the clothes.
Keebou hasn't seriously joined
the group, has he?
-No, of course that's impossible…
-It's hard to say.
You can never be certain about
what Keebou thinks.
-What?
-He is a very straightforward person.
Depending on where the arrow
is pointing to,
he would go straight to do something
ridiculous, too.
He is too consumed with grief.
It's either that, or he seriously
believes that Hikari is alive
and has charged into the enemy
to look for her.
-That's also possible.
-Yes, it is.
But either way he will get caught.
All the people there know who he is,
and it wasn't really a disguise.
-I really can't leave him alone!
-Let's go and see how he's doing.
Keebou really does make
everyone worry about him.
Don't come with us, Choco.
-Why?
-You still can't move freely,
and you made the hospital discharge
you to come here, didn't you?
-Okay.
-Yeah.
You're awfully obedient.
Takuya is having his operation
today, and it's already started.
-Is Takuya, Mr. Oshima's…
-Yeah.
-I'll go and visit him.
-Okay.
You should have a rest too,
or you'll get stupider.
-I'm okay now…
-I'll leave Keebou to you.
-Sure.
-Yeah.
-Choco.
-Yes?
Don't act recklessly.
What?
It's pretty important to us.
What is important?
Your life.
You say the most embarrassing
things, Miki.
No one has come to tell us
to settle old scores.
I told you, no one will.
-Maybe they are frightened.
-Listen to me!
And get away from me.
There is not enough oxygen.
Why are you dressed like that?
Listen, it was the president who
betrayed the gangs in Japan
and curried favor with Rainman.
It's the president who has to put on
a last spurt.
-We don't have to hide.
-Yes, Boss…
You're dismissed after this is settled.
Yes, Boss…
Hang on…
Boss, we're dismissed?
-Think about what you're going to do.
-But Boss…
Ouch! What the heck is this?
That barricade is pointless!
-Anyway, Boss, this is bad news!
-You're so noisy! What is it?
THE PRESIDENT OF THE GANGSTER
ORGANIZATION SENDAGI IS SHOT DEAD
IT HAS CAUSED A STIR AMONG THE EXECUTIVES…
-Bodyguard?
-Yes.
A bodyguard for someone of high rank who
even I don't get to meet.
There is a vacancy.
He died to protect the person.
Our role in the ideal country is the
secret police, and among us,
the bodyguard is one of the most
important job.
Offering your body and making it
useful for the greater purpose.
There is nothing more wonderful
than this, is there?
No, sir.
I'm solely responsible for
picking the candidates.
I sincerely hope that…
you'll take the test, too.
-Test?
-It is not difficult at all.
Just fight…
and the person who defeats
everyone else will pass.
Hold on… Melos.
I'm surprised to find no security guards.
Well, it is a normal religious body
in public.
Despite being a group of assassins.
Will we be killed if we're found?
The incident was settled for the
time being, so it should be okay.
There is no use thinking about it.
An idiot has already charged in there.
Toru, lend me your shoes.
-Why?
-Just do it.
Anyway, Pon,
-are you really sure about this?
-What?
If your wound opens up and your
brain shoots out,
I'll be really grossed out.
Don't get grossed out!
You have to help me.
Hey, Miki!
Gosh, Miki!
What are you doing?
What is this, Miki? Stress?
Or are you just naughty?
Oh, look…
It's fine. If Keebou is caught they
will take us to where he is.
It takes too much trouble to look for him!
He is so wild…
We have caught Segawa's friends.
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
-You're here!
-Sorry, I'm late.
It's okay. He'll be happy.
He kept talking about you.
Oh, the white poodle with a bell
attached to its collar.
When they checked in at the hotel,
a staff member saw Hikari holding it
in her arms. But now…
Mr. Oshima.
You're surprisingly careless
at the final stage.
Why?
I didn't think you'd fall for
such a stupid lie.
Hikari is actually alive, isn't she?
Did you kill the people whose bodies
were used as substitutes?
No.
Well, I guess the Glorious Ark
can get as many dead bodies as they want.
They got you involved in the end,
didn't they?
Are you out of your mind?
-If you fire here, people will…
-It will be hushed up.
There are people behind me who are
powerful enough to do that.
This is your answer, right?
Hikari is alive, isn't she?
Brilliant. He is good.
Brilliant. That was brilliant,
Kiichi Segawa.
You are the strongest.
But…
Frankly, I…
I still can't wipe out the fact that
you were once our enemy.
I'm not going to blame you
for your past, but…
I need some solid proof,
that will prove your loyalty
to not only me,
but also the people of high rank.
What should I do?
Walk quickly!
-Keebou!
-Keebou! Why?
-It's gone exactly as Miki planned.
Choose one
among these people.
You will purify him, Segawa.
Choose one…
and kill him here now.
That will be your final test.
Okay.
Shoot me.
They won't keep quiet if you kill me.
Then you can't do anything, and no
powerful people can hush it up.
You guys are so cool.
Don't look at me with eyes like that.
Your eyes are so pure and honest.
You don't know, do you?
My reflection looks so sly and dirty
in your open and honest eyes.
When I see it, I'm so embarrassed
that I want to die!
It feels awful when your eyes can't
reflect others in them!
It's not too late to do that.
You were a good policeman once.
-You can still go back for Takuya.
-No, I can't go back!
Why?
I shot the Sendagi Group's president dead.
In exchange for Takuya's operation.
I can't go back.
You were the one who killed the old man?
Hey…
What are you thinking, Keebou?
Is he serious?
Could Keebou be brainwashed for real?
What's wrong with you?
Wake up, Keebou!
-You're kidding…
-Miki!
I see.
Your eyes are dull.
There is a suicide note
in my breast pocket.
Please…
Tell Takuya for me…
that I love him with all of my heart.
Don't say anything sentimental.
You…
If Takuya knows his father killed
someone and then himself for him…
Are you trying to give him
such a heavy cross to bear?
If you love him, lie to him.
Never let him think
that you killed someone for him.
You'll say that you killed
Sendagi's president for justice.
Stick with your lie with all your might
until you die.
OPERATION IN PROGRESS
The operation went well.
Takuya.
Remember.
Stick to the lie.
-Miki!
-Miki…
He is dead.
Brilliant…
Wait.
Congratulations.
You've passed,
Kiichi Segawa.
No way!
Miki is…
dead.
Okay. I'll go now.
Come to my room.
Keebou! You son of a gun!
Keebou! Choco just texted me!
Hikari is alive!
Keebou!
You idiot! Idiot!
-Shut up!
-Keebou!
Keebou!
Hikari…
It is successfully unlocked
and we have moved the data here.
Nobody has…
seen the content, right?
No one in our science team
would transgress God's will.
You can go now.
-Dad!
-No!
-Please.
Please spare her!
Dad! No!
Dad…
Dad!
This is Segawa.
I'm…
I'm coming.
You've saved my life. Thanks.
I received a call,
from Mad Dog number one.
-Miki called you?
-Yeah.
He told me that you were trying to
do something
and asked me to check on you.
Since when have you become so close?
We're not close.
I owe him a favor.
-My car is here, fancy a ride?
-No, thanks.
And I'm sorry, but will you do me a favor?
Chancellor, it's a big job that has
to be done by someone like you.
What is it?
Shoot.
What's the matter?
You know…
I have believed for
a very long time that I was
God's messenger.
People love me for some reason.
Since my childhood.
Everybody admires and looks up to me.
I don't know why.
I thought that…
it was because I was blessed by God.
But…
Before I knew it
I've become something far from
God's blessing,
and I might have…
become the devil's instrument.
I don't know much about god and devil,
but…
if everybody loved you when you were
a child, then…
Yes?
I think…
you must have been a very nice person.
We will now perform
the purification process.
Traitor!
-Miki!
-I thought you were dead!
Are you a zombie?
Idiot, that feeble kick can't kill me.
-I'm so glad that you're alive!
-Okay…
Let's go!
You'll get out of here with us.
Paul…
Aww, you're so darn cute! Hey!
Good lord!
Keebou went without telling us!
He's treating us like strangers!
Exactly.
That idiot hasn't grown up a bit
in ten years.
WHO ARE YOU
I think he is trying to do all the
dirty work himself.
So that you won't get involved.
He also lied to me at the beginning
and pretended to have really joined
the group.
But he didn't have to tell me,
because I knew soon enough,
what Mr. Segawa's real intention is.
-Why?
-It was his eyes, right?
-Eyes?
-Yes, his eyes.
I could tell it when I saw his eyes.
Mr. Segawa believes in something
and his heart is honest.
They are waiting.
His eyes? They look totally crazy.
Keebou made the right decision
to pick Miki.
So I pretended to be defeated
because I knew you'd do something.
-Yes.
-But the old man checked Miki's pulse,
then why couldn't he tell that
he faked his death?
I pressed a point which makes
the pulse undetectable.
Oh, that's why!
-It hurt like hell.
-I'm impressed by the nurse.
Here he is.
The other guy who wants to
do all the dirty work.
Wow, this brings back memories!
It's still here!
Wow…
Oh? Where is Keebou?
Where is it?
Thank you. Please leave the room.
Rainman…
That's the name.
But this is not the truth.
What?
I will now…
take you to where Rainman is.
He will fill the vacancy.
He will join the bodyguards. Also…
We have successfully retrieved it.
What would you do with it?
Is that…
the ritual's…
Yes.
Well, it is not very important now.
You're right.
Because everything is ready.
Then I will handle this.
Sure.
Maybe she is your mom?
Hikari's…
You're Hikari's mom, aren't you?
You're alive! You're Rainman!
You can't talk to her like that!
That is rude!
Hikari…
-Where is Hikari?
-Don't look directly at her!
Please tell me!
Hikari is alive, right?
Before the ceremony is held,
we cannot let her die.
-Ceremony?
-So…
I am certain that she has not been killed.
What do you mean?
I have to talk to her!
He is going to such
a dangerous place alone?
WHO ARE YOU
Isn't it too risky for Keebou?
But we don't know where it is.
No matter how much we want to
go to rescue him.
Well, we have to trust Keebou, then.
-Rod.
-Rod, huh?
-It's rod.
-Yeah, rod.
Rod.
What rod?
Mr. Akagi,
I'm sorry, but I have no time!
I will use a rod.
You're in Rainman's presence.
Don't say anything unnecessary!
The "bou" in Keebou's name
doesn't mean "boy"?
Idiot, it means rod, as in what a
roaming dog may find in the proverb.
But… Right, look! It's written here!
That's the word
he wrote when he
made Mr. Akagi his promise,
so that he wouldn't forget it.
He will be too dangerous
if he has a rod in his hand.
So Keebou had sealed off his rod.
His nickname, Keebou, actually means
"dangerous rod".
What? Can I tweet about it?
Where is Hikari?
Tell me!
He won't tell you.
Even if you kill him.
Please tell me! Hikari…
There is not much light…
that can reach here.
You will regret it soon enough.
The self-absorbed and childish
sense of justice
that you're now addicted to.
Ryugasaki.
I wonder which one is stronger.
The rain, or the sun?
Flood and drought…
Which will make people suffer more
when they die in it?
We will show you
the answers to your questions very soon.
Hikari.
I'm very sorry that
this has happened to you.
I'm sorry.
Hikari.
Dad.
You can't cry now.
Because your heart will admit defeat.
You have to get up your courage.
As long as you don't admit defeat,
then you're just on your way
to claim your victory.
Don't be give up until you win.
Kiichi told you that?
Don't worry.
Because Keebou will surely come
to get us out of here.
Come here!
I know he is capable,
but he won't find this place.
He will come for us.
I'm sure Keebou will.
Very soon.
He will come very soon.
Hikari…
Listen.
Can you hear footsteps?
I can hear them.
Keebou will come for us.
He will.
He'll call my name.
Hikari!
You see? Dad.
Keebou!
Keebou…
I knew you would come to rescue us.
I knew you were alive.
FINAL EPISODE
THE FINAL SHOWDOWN WITH RAINMAN
Bye, Keebou.
FAREWELL, WILD HEROES