Hikari.
From now on I will absorb your courage.
Jump.
I'm going to kill you!
Keebou!
Come with me.
Hikari.
He will be all right.
-But he jumped from so high…
-It wasn't the first time.
-Keebou had jumped off there before.
-What?
-Had he?
-Yeah.
When Choco and I were
at about the same age as Hikari,
Choco had teased him.
He said we had jumped off the
year before to test our courage,
and dared Keebou to jump. And then…
Keebou didn't even hesitate…
That was when Keebou swam to
the shore and found the Villa.
The Villa?
-I hope it hasn't been torn down.
-It has been ten years, huh?
Oh, there it is!
Okay…
CAUTION
It's still the way we left it.
-It brings back so many memories.
-This is so cool!
-This place is…
-When we were in high school,
it was like a sanctuary for us.
When we had to
separate to run away from the police,
we always assembled here afterwards.
WHO ARE YOU
KEEBOU, MIKI
Don't worry. He is Keebou after all.
You guys go and look
over the opposite ridge.
-Yes, madam.
-Futaba.
-Do you know, Futaba…
-What?
Who is trying to get the data and why?
The person who really wants it
isn't the Hierarch, isn't it?
I am terribly sorry. I will
definitely get it back.
To realize the ideal country,
even if… I have to sacrifice…
I don't care about your life.
We're running out of time.
Get it back quickly.
PONJARA, PI, MELOS
Let's move this…
Somehow this place looks as if you'll
see things like ghosts at night.
-Keebou!
-Whoa, stop there…
I'm soaked. My clothes are dirty.
-You're late.
-How dare you tell me to jump?
I can't fly! I just fell down.
You look like you can fly though.
We've told you, you don't say that now!
Don't be an idiot!
Don't be an idiot…
-Transferred to another hospital?
-Yes, just now.
The doctor told him to do so after
his condition had stabilized
and he tried to stop him,
but he still wanted to go back home.
FILE FOLDER
CANNOT ACCESS FILE
Why? Is it corrupted?
I'll take it somewhere to
recover the data.
-No, it's too risky.
-Exactly, don't be stupid.
It is some important secret, it's the CIA.
-I'll ask Mr. Oshima to do it.
-You mean the police officer?
-I trust Mr. Oshima--
-We know.
Let's do that.
What?
You never listen to what we say anyway.
-Because you're an idiot.
-Just believe what you believe.
We will handle the rest.
Drop it? What are you saying, sir?
About 80,000 people go missing in
this country every year.
79,000 of them are found.
What do you think about the number?
-That is pretty excellent.
-You are right.
However, the remaining 1,000 people
are still missing.
What is your point?
We are already exposed…
You, me, the whole country…
To the ever-continuing…
rain.
Rain?
NUMAZU FIRST GENERAL HOSPITAL
-I'm sorry.
-Oh, Takuya.
You shouldn't play with it
in the corridor.
But it's boring only to
play with it in the room.
Well, you shouldn't.
If you do it again I'll confiscate it.
-No!
-I guess I'll take it.
Mr. Shuntaro Saeki.
I'll leave it here.
I will get him to his room.
-I like this smell.
-This? The candles?
Yeah, when you blow them.
I like it, too.
It makes me feel happy.
Yeah.
I'd talked about this here in the
past, and Choco said…
"That's because you are fortunate."
He said that it's because I connect
happy memories
like birthdays and Christmas
with the smell that candles make
when you blow them out.
But Choco doesn't?
Before he went to elementary school
his family died in an accident.
What?
He was living in a relative's home
when I first met him.
Maybe he didn't like it there,
so he was always wandering.
When he was in middle school,
he almost never went home.
He used to live quite a precarious life.
Even when he was alone he would
get in a fight picked by others,
or go for the opponent,
the more dangerous the quicker.
He is friendly with people and gets
along with everybody,
but he breaks off with them easily.
CONTACT HAS BEEN DELETED
He sometimes does not seem to
care about himself very much.
I can transfer you to another hospital.
I've just come here.
How brave you are.
Will you talk some sense into Mr. Segawa?
Ask him to give us the data.
Of course I won't, idiot.
If he doesn't, everybody, including
Mr. Segawa and you, will be killed.
This is not poison, is it?
Are you scared?
It is not too late now.
If you give us the data…
What does that data mean to you?
Let go.
Don't get carried away.
I don't die easily.
Make sure you remember this.
Choco and I are the same.
My dad and mom had also died.
On my birthday last year,
my dad went, "Oh, no! A stray dog
took away my present for you!
I'll catch it tomorrow."
What? This is stupid.
My dad was very busy with his work
as a reporter at that time.
I think he just couldn't go and buy it.
So I pretended I was taken in by that.
I told him I'd give it to the dog,
then Dad said he'd surely go
and catch the dog.
I really enjoyed the time with him.
Did you?
Keebou.
On Choco's next birthday,
let's get him candles
and let him blow them out.
Yeah, sure.
Blow it.
-Good night.
You idiot!
I'm sorry!
We will definitely find her this time!
We'll put our lives
in your hands and go all out…
-You're too old, Kizaki.
-Old?
-I don't need you.
-Don't need me? Boss!
-No, Boss! Give me another chance!
-Shut up!
-Tagawa will take over your duties.
-Yes?
I'm sorry. I asked you to come a
long way here from Numazu,
and you have to go back so soon.
Well, it's not that far away.
It's time to play that card.
-Card?
-Actually, Tagawa…
We hold a giant card.
A trump card that will make or break.
We don't accept failure.
Well…
It's when we play it that is important.
HAYASHIDA LAUNDRY SHOP
-This is so cool! I'll tweet it.
-Stop being an idiot and let's go!
Why is only Keebou allowed inside?
I'll put you on Twitter, pig!
-Where does that passion come from?
-You're interested in forensics?
-Of course! It's Mariko!
-Mariko?
It's Yasuko Sawaguchi!
Sorry for making you to come
a long way here from Tokyo.
It's okay, the Metropolitan Police
might interfere with the matter,
so I'm glad that we can do it here.
And it is also convenient for me.
Actually, my wife's old home is here,
so she'll come to meet me tonight
after a long time.
-After a long time?
-It's complicated.
I live separately from my wife
and child now.
-Again!
-Choco, you suck at this.
But I can't use this arm.
What has happened to it?
I was shot with a rifle.
-That's a lie.
-Then why are you here, Takuya?
They say that this doesn't move properly.
-I see…
-But I'll have surgery soon.
I've been waiting for
my turn for a long time.
I'm happy for you.
-You'll get better.
-Yeah.
After I'm discharged I'll go to school,
and I want to make lots of friends!
Do you? You will very soon.
You seem very nice.
Can you really make 100 friends?
I still haven't got any, because
I've always been in the hospital.
You have, I'm the first one.
-Wow!
-Come on.
Good.
Is that a VIP? He must be.
The Chief is late.
Why…
I will take over and analyze the data.
-Okay…
-Don't give it to him!
What?
Oshima, give me the data.
I won't.
You know what it means if
you refuse to do so.
Yes.
I see.
Do you have to point that at us,
Sir?
Now…
Give me the data.
Go now! Darn…
-Sir!
-Get that guy!
Don't attack them!
They're police officers!
Go, Segawa! The data is more important!
Don't let him go!
-Keebou!
-What is he doing?
Those are policemen!
Block all the entrances!
What the heck?
It's difficult to fight with the police.
-But we've promised to handle the rest.
-Mikki!
-I'm Melos!
-Hey!
Get lost!
You…
Don't move!
Keebou!
-Ouch!
-I'm sorry, Keebou.
Get lost!
Are you all right? Okay, let's go.
Stop there!
Go!
Get in now!
Stop being an idiot!
Freeze!
I'll shoot if you don't.
Get in.
The police are not allowed to fire
at citizens with no weapon.
Only warning shots.
Oshima!
Even if you do that
the rain still won't stop.
I won't go under your umbrella.
I choose to get soaked…
and walk with them.
HAYASHIDA LAUNDRY SHOP
I'm very sorry that I've made you…
Please don't say that.
Never mind us, will you be okay?
I'll be fine.
Not the whole police force
has been corrupted. I'll manage.
I'm more worried about you guys.
Will we be put on the wanted list?
No, you won't. The chaos this time
will probably be covered up.
-What a relief.
-No.
This is worse.
You could be secretly hunted down.
I'm terribly sorry!
To analyze this,
we have to find a specialized agency
that is trustworthy.
I will take it until we find one.
Then you'll be exposed to less danger.
No, Mr. Oshima, I'll keep it…
-But…
-I've promised…
That I will take this on.
Okay.
But be very careful.
I will.
Detective…
Will they go after our families?
I don't think they will
go after your families.
Their goal is not to
threaten you or give you a warning.
It is to eliminate you guys.
Eliminate?
But I can't deny that it's possible
that they'll get involved
when the police hunt you down.
I think we'd better leave
our families for now.
Keebou.
Can I…
Can I go home just once?
Of course! And you guys, too.
HAYASHIDA LAUNDRY SHOP
-Oh, Noriaki?
-Hey.
Aren't you supposed to be
delivering the clothes?
Well, yeah…
I'm going out soon, though.
What are you doing?
I've thought about our babies' names.
Break up the word "hope"
into the two kanjis,
so it'll be "Ki" and "Bou".
HOPE
How do you read them?
It's not going to be
"Ki" and "Bou", is it?
Of course not!
It's Nozomi.
-Which one?
-Both.
No… I don't get it. You mean both
babies will be called Nozomi?
Oh, that's what it will become!
I thought I had a great idea!
Gosh, get a grip, daddy.
It's okay, just take some time
to think about it.
We'll decide them after they're born.
Okay, Noriaki?
LIFE INSURANCE
I'm ready now, Pichan!
Have a seat… Okay.
Chappy loves Pichan very much!
The end.
-Tell me… How did I do?
-Saya…
Ventriloquists close their mouths
when they speak.
You can't speak with your mouth shut.
Well… Yeah, but…
-Pichan, show me, then.
-Saya.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
Pichan.
Thank you…
For letting me buy so many things.
Yes?
I've already got lots of things.
You have bought me everything I want.
So it's your turn now.
Saya…
From now on,
the button you want to click
is the button that I will click.
Pichan… Are you crying?
Don't cry. You'll make me cry, too.
-Toru.
-I'll stay at my friend's place.
Will you? You have made some good friends?
-I'm so happy for you.
-Listen.
-Yeah?
-Go to where Dad is.
-Yes?
-To Singapore.
Right…
I have a suggestion!
-Let's go on our summer vacation…
-Will you stop that?
Don't treat me like a kid.
You're so annoying, seriously!
Please, just go to where Dad is.
I really can't live with
a strange woman alone.
-A strange woman…
-We're not related, are we?
No matter how you think about it.
I don't even want to see you.
Just go! Get lost from now on!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
CARE HOME FOR THE ELDERLY, SUNNY SQUARE
We will take care of her
during her stay here.
-Thank you very much.
-It's our job.
Oh, right. After my grandmother
finishes half her meal,
she takes a break to
switch on the TV or fold origami,
but she starts eating again,
so please don't take her meal away.
Okay.
-And when my grandma sleeps…
-Mr. Miki.
Don't worry.
Please let us take care of her.
Okay.
Kayo, where are you going?
Grandma.
What's the matter?
I have to go and help Kosuke.
Because Kosuke
is fighting with the others again.
You will help him?
You know, the boy
is actually a real softie.
-You'll go on leave for a long time?
-Please let me do that!
Are you disrespecting your job?
You skipped your exam, and…
-I'm terribly sorry!
-That's enough! I'm firing you!
Hey, hang on…
FISH
-Miss Moriyama.
-Yes?
Thank you for everything.
-What's the matter?
-I…
I really loved you!
Yes?
When everything went wrong
and I felt very down,
and when everything seemed pointless,
I could cheer up again
just after having a glimpse of you.
That's what you were to me.
So thank you very much!
MORIYAMA
I don't think they will
go after your families,
but I can't deny that
they will get involved when the
police hunt you down.
Can I…
Can I go home just once?
Keebou!
-Hikari!
-Keebou!
Chancellor!
Why?
Do you think I don't know this place?
Don't worry, I haven't told anyone.
I've come alone.
For what?
Will we bring this to a conclusion?
I guess you guys are sick of it, too.
Aihara, give us the data.
I guess you know this as well,
that someone is competing
with us for that.
It's the Glorious Ark,
which appears to
be a religious organization,
but actually is a group of
psychotic killers.
If you give them the data,
there will be serious consequences.
-Serious consequences?
-But if we get it,
we can crush both the group
and the people who control them
all together.
Give us the data. I'll see that you
don't lose anything by it.
-If you do…
-How can I trust you?
I won't be deceived again.
I don't believe what you said.
If you give us the data
we'll release the hostage.
Hostage?
Dad!
What?
Hikari, are you all right?
I heard that you have lost
your memory, and I'm very worried.
I have…
really put you through a tough time.
I'm sorry, Hikari.
-Forgive me.
-What is this?
-I thought Hikari's dad was dead?
-He is alive.
He is staying at the main branch.
It's pointless to show you that
when her memory was lost.
I only heard about it yesterday as well.
Tonight at nine, bring the data
with you to our club.
You'll exchange it for the girl's dad.
I'll see that
you don't lose anything by it.
Trust me.
Keebou.
I'm sorry, your family is going
through a hard time and…
It's not your fault at all.
I should be the one to…
This is unusual. Maybe someone is here.
What are you doing?
Dad!
Takuya.
-What… Why?
-Why?
Isn't it fishy? No matter how
you think about it.
That means we'll side with
the gangsters, right?
Chancellor said we wouldn't lose
anything, and more importantly,
Hikari's father can come back.
Will you go?
Keebou.
We don't hate that part of you.
But…
Is that all right?
Hikari's dad did everything
to guard the data,
and you're giving it away.
Does her father really want us to do that?
And you're going alone, too.
-That's too reckless, Keebou.
-But…
What if he has deceived you?
They will get the data,
and both Hikari's dad and
you could still be killed!
Then what have we been guarding it for?
We've made the gangsters, a heresy group,
and even the police into our enemies,
and we have destroyed
everything important to us, too!
-Say something, Keebou!
-Melos.
Chancellor saved us
at that time, didn't he?
I trust Chancellor.
-But what if it was a lie?
-Then I have been deceived.
That's what trust is.
This isn't like you at all, Keebou.
Are you going there to be defeated?
Of course not! I'm going there to win.
How can we win this battle? Tell us.
What are we fighting for?
Hikari will…
just like every ordinary child,
she will be carefree and
can be happy every day.
I will fight for that.
That is our victory.
So…
I will go to meet Hikari's father.
Okay… Keebou.
Believe in whatever you believe in.
We won't let you go alone.
Hey, now is the time.
It's now.
Yeah.
Who are you?
I am myself!
Why have you transferred
to another hospital?
And you didn't even tell us.
Enough about me.
-She is back, just as I thought.
-Who is back?
-The nurse, Mifumi.
-What?
-We'll get out of here at once.
-Don't worry.
I'll be the bait, then maybe we can
get some information out of her.
-What nonsense are you saying?
-I won't be killed easily.
Anyway, I'll tell Mr. Oshima
about this first.
-Mr. Oshima.
-Yes?
Takuya's operation on his heart
in three days
will be canceled.
Canceled?
Why?
After looking at
all the results of the tests,
the hospital has reached this decision.
But he did all the tests ages ago
and there was no problem…
It's no use transferring
to another hospital.
None of the hospitals that can perform
such a high level heart operation,
no matter where you go in Japan,
will admit Takuya
You…
It's the Glorious Ark?
What on earth are you?
You have control over not only the police,
but even the medical service?
Why can you do this?
Mr. Oshima, I think you know that…
There is only one way to let the
operation be performed as scheduled.
Give me the data.
If you don't it will be too late.
Takuya's life…
Please save his life.
Sorry for making you take the trouble.
Where is Hikari's father?
Where is the data?
You have got it with you, right?
I knew it.
An excellent police officer like you
would be carrying the real data himself.
Bring him here.
Are you… Hikari's father?
Are you Kiichi Segawa?
Yes.
Thank you for protecting Hikari.
I haven't done this alone.
Then where is Hikari now?
My friends are protecting her.
Please don't worry.
There are still young people
like you guys…
You are the last hope of this country.
We're not that good. We're just stupid.
Hold on, young man.
Give me the data first.
Give me the data.
Don't give it to her!
Don't believe her lies.
Please! Give it back to me!
Give it back to me!
Can I give it to him?
It is better than
giving it to the Glorious Ark.
Because it's Rainman
who is controlling them.
Rainman?
Rainman has control over everything,
a fixer who is trying to make this
a country of statism.
-Anyone who disrupts order will be--
-Talk later.
Give me the data.
The Glorious Ark!
Give it back to me…
Give it back to me!
-Ponjara!
-Choco!
Takuya has taken a sudden turn for
the worse, please call the doctor!
Okay.
President! Why?
If you give Rainman the data,
the gangs will be destroyed in a second!
That's not called destroyed.
-It's cleansing.
-Cleansing?
When you wash a futon
covered in mites and dust,
you don't call it destruction, do you?
Exactly.
Everybody wants to sleep in a clean futon.
In a clean room,
where the air is conditioned.
They've got me…
Rainman's power has
even reached the underworld…
Ryugasaki, how is
the retrieval of the data going?
If the worst comes to the worst
our dream will be at risk.
Arisugawa,
Irori,
it's unusual for you to be so fearful.
There is no problem.
Everything is in order.
As long as you have
the sense of righteousness
and the strong power to achieve it.
Chancellor.
-Did you know that?
-Of course.
He is new.
A man who is suitable to
live in the new world.
-The new world?
-A clean futon, my boy.
A world where everything is clean.
A beautiful world designed using
order and regulation.
In the world,
nothing is outside the norm.
Gangs are a typical example. Of course,
uncivilized dunces like you
are not wanted as well.
You mean you'll kill us?
Chancellor.
I don't get what
these guys are talking about at all.
Do you understand them?
What's wrong with you?
They're nothing but a group of killers!
They have no justice nor humanity.
And yet you have joined them?
-Are you out of your mind?
-I've told you, Aihara.
-This is all I can do.
-Of course not! Have you forgotten?
You had led 100 daredevils!
It was 1000 if you count the union too.
-You--
-It's not a children's game.
I have to survive.
I have to do it for them, too.
What is the point of
surviving in such a world?
Is that a world you'll enjoy?
Answer me, Chancellor!
It's not about whether I like it or not!
It's life or death.
I know you're going to
say you'd rather die.
You're happy to go and stand in
the pouring rain, aren't you?
But I need an umbrella.
Aihara…
That's my caliber.
Tagawa.
You really are new.
Now, this is the beginning of
the new world.
Hang on!
I have used…
a complicated way to lock the data.
When you input the three passwords,
if you get even one wrong,
the data will disappear.
After all this time…
That's ridiculous!
If you want me to unlock it,
Let me see Hikari.
Please.
I hope you'll…
grant me my last wish.
Don't give up until you win!
Dad!
Hikari…
No…
-She is not Hikari.
-What?
She isn't Hikari… She isn't my daughter!
Where is Hikari?
Where have you hidden her?
How can that…
Who… are you?
Too bad. You found out.
Rainman will go that far?
Sorry it has to be this way.
Miki! Who are you?
THIS DRAMA IS A FICTIONAL STORY