[gentle guitar music plays]
[traffic sounds]
Q: IS THERE AN EASY WAY TO DIE?
A: JUMP OFF A BUILDING?
[breathes lightly]
[gentle guitar music fades out]
[breathing quickens]
-[breathing continues]
-[background silences]
[breathing softens]
[clacking, rolling sounds]
[breeze blows]
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
[boy] They're beautiful colors.
Um, I mean those, pencils.
Um, Faber-Castell pencils are great,
aren't they?
I wanted some,
but they're a bit expensive.
I heard Chagall or someone
like that used them too.
[girl] Gogh.
Huh?
Van Gogh used to use these pencils.
[boy chuckles nervously]
So, like, what are you drawing?
Heaven.
Heaven? Really?
[girl keeps drawing]
The place I'm going soon.
What about you? Why are you here?
Huh?
Were you going to jump off
from the railing?
No.
I was just, uh…
[girl giggles] I'm joking.
Did you come to visit someone?
Yeah. Yeah, a friend.
Hey, by the way,
I don't think that's funny.
-You shouldn't joke about going to heaven.
-It's true, though.
It is.
I'm going to die soon.
Six months from now.
I've got a rare illness
that only affects one in, mm,
like, several hundred thousand.
Something I was born with.
Oh I see.
-[gentle music plays]
-I see.
You're not even shocked?
Huh?
Mm.
[boy exhales]
So, hey, uh…
are you not afraid?
Of what?
Of dying.
You don't… look like you're afraid.
I'm not afraid.
I've known for a while
that I don't have a lot of time left.
Just imagine the view from all the way up.
It's gotta be nicer than down here,
being stuck in a hospital.
Heaven is nice.
Looking forward to it, I guess.
Q: WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF YOU KNEW
YOU WERE GOING TO DIE SOON?
[knock at door]
[girl] Akito!
You'll be late
if you don't hurry up and eat soon!
[sighs]
-[crunch]
-[grunts in pain]
[groans]
[sighs]
[girl chuckles] You don't have much luck,
do you?
I mean, you're a pro
at attracting bad luck.
[Akito's mom sighs] Natsumi…
If you need a new palette,
we can get you one.
[Akito] It's fine.
It'd be a waste of money.
Buy Natsumi that new lacrosse stick
she wanted instead.
[gasps] What! No way? The Crux Pro?
Right, then, everyone.
I think we've all nearly finished,
so let's go over the answers.
[uplifting music plays]
[Akito] A "pro at attracting bad luck."
She's right.
[teacher] Today we're gonna be using
this formula…
[uplifting music continues]
[art teacher] Hayasaka,
you should submit your art.
ART EXHIBITION
It'd be an achievement
if one of our students
got the Nika Newcomer's Award.
[inhales sharply] Got it.
And just like that,
entering the Nika Art Exhibition
became my greatest ambition.
Through the power of art,
I could pave my way to the future.
Or so I thought.
[uplifting music continues]
[grunts]
[groans]
[bike wheels whine]
[Akito] A malignant tumor?
[doctor] It's not very common
for tumors to form in the heart,
but they can.
On very rare occasions,
a tumor can grow on the heart.
-[Akito] They found a tumor in my heart.
-[doctor] Unfortunately…
-[Akito] And I was given a year.
-[doctor] You don't have long.
It depends whether it spreads or not,
but I'd say that you have
about a year left to live.
[melancholy music plays]
[Akito sighs]
[melancholy music continues]
[Akito] It was days, no, a week,
before I could wrap my head around it.
NIKA ART EXHIBITION
[girl] Heaven is nice.
I'm really looking forward to it.
[gentle music plays]
[Akito] How could she look forward to it?
I needed to find out.
[gentle music continues]
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
If only I could see her
one more time to ask,
I think I'd feel a bit better.
[elevator dings]
[joyful music plays]
[Akito] I'm afraid of dying.
But she's looking forward to it.
DRAWING CLOSER
[PA] Doctor Kikuchi
to the nurses' station.
Doctor Kikuchi to the nurses' station.
[girl] Come in.
HARUNA SAKURAI
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
[Haruna] Just what I needed,
I was looking for a model to draw.
[objects clatter]
I don't have any friends
that come and visit me.
[box opens]
So you are Haruna Sakurai? Am I right?
My parents chose it 'cause Haru
means spring, which is when I was born.
That's easy, right?
Uh, my name is Akito.
Akito Hayasaka.
It's Aki because I was born in the fall.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
-How old are you?
-Seventeen.
Oh wow, me too. [laughs]
What a coincidence.
Uh, you can sit over there.
Uh, okay.
So, Akito,
are you into drawing as well?
Huh?
Since, you know, Faber-Castell.
-I'm in Art Club.
-I knew it.
But I've been slacking a lot lately.
But you're hoping to go to art school.
What do you wanna do in the future?
To be an artist, right? [laughs]
Uh, sure, the future.
Yeah, your dreams, what you will become.
-Actually…
-Art school, amazing.
Yeah, I really wanted to go too.
And win an award
in the Nika Art Exhibition.
I wanna submit, I just…
won't be around long enough
to design something really great.
I know!
I'll leave it all to you.
How about you go to art school
and win the award?
[Akito] There's no way I could tell her.
Uh, is it okay to check this out?
Yeah, sure you can.
Oh wow, look at these.
Miss Sakurai, you're very good.
Did you take classes?
[Haruna] No.
I've never even been to a real art museum.
Seriously?
-Oh and you can just call me Haruna.
-Huh?
[chuckles]
So, then, Haruna…
how is it that you can… draw like this?
[Haruna inhales]
Well, it's 'cause
it's the one place I find freedom.
It's like time and space
are no longer these big obstacles
whenever I'm drawing.
It's amazing.
I can paint my illness away
and fly to wherever I wanna fly to.
If anything ever bothers you,
I can just paint all of it away for you.
[delicate piano music plays]
Oh is this school
with the Kinjiro statue Aoba Junior High?
Yeah, I went there.
Somehow I was hardly ever there.
I used to go past there on my bike a lot.
I think a student in my
art club went there as well.
Takada. Yeah.
Oh really?
Well, then, do you know
where the elementary school is
on the page before?
[Akito] You two look close.
Is this a friend of yours, right here?
[Haruna] Yeah, something like that.
That person was a friend, yeah.
"Was" a friend?
-[knock at door]
-[door opens]
[nurse] Haruna, it's time for you IV.
[Haruna inhales, sighs]
Okay.
Sorry about that.
-[Akito] It's fine.
-Is this a friend?
-[Haruna] Yeah.
-Don't get too many of those, huh?
Uh, I guess I'll just, uh, go, then.
[Haruna] Mm.
[Haruna inhales, exhales]
[Akito] By the way,
is it okay if I come again?
-Huh?
-I would love to--
To, um, see some more of your drawings.
[laughs]
Yeah, sure.
Your request is granted, you may visit.
[giggles]
But in exchange,
you've gotta bring a present.
A present?
Yeah, a motif to draw.
I'm tired of drawing the things here.
Okay, got it.
I guess I'll see ya later.
You have a good day.
Mm-hm. Yeah, bye.
-[gentle music plays]
-[Haruna laughs]
That's all for today.
I'd like the Culture Committee members
to come to the staff room after class.
-Got that?
-[class] Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
[gentle music continues]
Sorry.
Akito!
You're not going to Art Club today either?
Hmm… I think I'm done with Art Club.
I'm tired of it.
You're done? Wait, what?
What about the Nika Art Exhibition?
You were so excited.
Ah, yeah, Nika…
-Hm? How're you guys?
-Hey, what's going on?
Ever since your bike accident,
you're all different.
Oh no, no, no, no.
-Your knee's all better.
-Shota!
Get off! Ugh. And hey! What's going on?
I'm sorry. My bus is coming now.
[announcer] The next stop
is the Medical University Hospital.
The Medical University Hospital.
Get off here
for the Bel Fiore flower shop.
Bel Fiore flower shop.
-[florist] Thank you!
-[woman] Thank you.
[girl] Thank you.
[florist] Are you looking
for something in particular?
-Huh?
-[florist] A present for your girlfriend?
Uh, no.
[laughs] You look a little stressed.
I'm visiting a friend in the hospital.
I wouldn't recommend a potted plant.
They're considered unlucky
because their roots are said
to have a bit of disease.
Hey, how about,
uh, something like this?
Oh wow, yeah. They got a lot of color.
They look painted.
Those are Gerberas right there.
There's two thousand kinds of them.
Two thousand?
[florist] All have different meanings.
But it doesn't matter
which type you choose,
none of them have
any negative connotation.
It's quite a rare flower in that way.
And since they're so colorful,
they really brighten the mood.
They're great for hospital visits.
Um, okay, I'll do four, then.
Oh no! I'll do five please, yeah.
What color would you like?
Uh… let's go, um, pink, I guess.
Pink flowers signify appreciation.
Gratitude.
Is that okay?
Uh… okay, what does, uh, orange signify?
Tolerance and, uh, open-mindedness.
Uh, and the yellow one?
Well, yellow signifies beauty. [giggles]
White is purity and blue is…
And just so you know,
Gerberas in general signify hope.
-They all do.
-Oh yeah, yeah, that!
How about five, uh, different colors?
HARUNA SAKURAI
Uh, Miss Haruna?
Haruna, can I come in?
[places flowers]
[Haruna] Don't just come in
without permission.
Uh,
I'm sorry.
You're in a lady's room here,
don't you realize that?
Sorry. But if it helps,
I did, uh, bring you these.
Oh flowers?
-Huh.
-Gerberas.
[chuckles] Aw, thank you.
Gorgeous.
I love Gerberas, you know?
They're so pretty.
They're supposed to signify hope,
I was told.
The woman selling these recommended
that I get them.
"Hope," huh?
Uh, my bad.
I didn't mean it like that.
[laughs] It's okay. Don't worry.
I think that the word illness
is a truly magical word, really.
Anyone you don't like,
you just say the word illness
and they run away, just like that.
There's only one person
that the magic word didn't work on.
Yeah?
Mm-hm.
Wanna get something to drink
in the common room?
Mm-hm.
[Haruna] Oh uh…
Do you have a new friend here?
Uh, yeah. We met on the roof.
This is Akito.
He was born in the fall.
A future Nika award-winner over here.
I see.
Well, I'm sorry to bother you guys,
though Haruna needs to go
for her physical exam.
Oh yeah.
I'm sorry.
Mm. It's okay.
Can we get some drinks next time?
Mm-hm. I'll see ya.
Ah, hold on, uh,
if it's okay with you, then please,
come see us here again.
I will.
[gentle guitar music plays]
[gentle guitar music continues]
[Akito] I see.
Haruna can't just go out
and visit people like I can,
even if she wanted to.
The only thing she can do
is wait around for someone to show up.
WHO WAS UNAFFECTED BY THE MAGIC WORD?
That person was a friend, yeah.
ART CLUB
-Hayasaka?
-[Akito gasps]
I heard that you're gonna quit.
Uh, yeah. Mm-hm.
[Takada] Hmm…
So you're running away.
Well, whatever.
Hey, Takada,
you went to Aoba Junior High, right?
Yeah, why?
Do you remember Haruna Sakurai?
Uh…
I think that she was sick.
I don't really remember.
Was there anyone she was close to?
-Did she have friends, huh?
-Friends?
You know,
she wasn't really ever at school.
Ah, but I think
I did see her a few times
hanging out with that Miura chick.
Miura chick?
The one who's in class with me.
Miura, huh? You mean…
Hey, what do you want?
And who are you?
Hayasaka. I'm, uh,
from the class that is, uh…
Why are you such a weirdo?
Huh? Uh, but…
Not interested, dude.
I can't believe some guys
hit on girls like this.
-[girl 1] Let's go, Ayaka.
-[Ayaka] Yeah.
[Ayaka sighs]
Uh, that's not what this is.
I wanted to ask you something.
[Ayaka] Huh?
Um, so why didn't you start with that,
then?
Why do you keep acting
like some kind of weirdo? Ask already.
Do you happen to know Haruna Sakurai?
I heard that you two were close.
[Ayaka] Sorry. You guys go ahead
-[girl 1] Okay.
-[girl 2] Okay.
How do you know Haruna, huh?
Oh you know, uh…
she's just someone that-- that I know.
-Huh?
-Did you ever play on the swings with her?
Or find a kitten in a box with Haruna
when you were a little kid
growing up together?
I see. So she's in the hospital again.
Looks like she's been there
for quite a while this time.
But I seem to be the only person
who goes and visits her.
And I think she'd really love it
if someone else could visit her, you know?
[Ayaka] So you're trying to impress her.
[Akito] No, that's not it!
I just… wanna help.
[Ayaka] It's Akito, right?
I have no intention of visiting Haruna.
I haven't seen her at all
since I've been in high school.
And I wouldn't exactly call
us friends anymore.
I don't think she'd be too thrilled
to see me either.
[delicate piano music plays]
[Ayaka] This is the reason
you don't have friends!
[mouths words]
[delicate piano music continues]
[Haruna cries]
[door opens]
I'm back.
Yeah, good, you're home.
Where did you go off to?
Shopping.
I heard you're not gonna do Art Club.
Eri came by.
She's worried about you, you know?
Oh really?
[Akito's mom] Mm…
You should talk to her about it.
Talk to her about what?
You know, I'd feel better
if Eri were by your side right now.
-I'm sure you and--
-It's got nothing to do with her.
And I don't wanna bother her anyway.
Ooh, tell me! What happened?
Ah, Akito got rejected!
You don't, uh… have any worries, do you?
I'm jealous.
Don't just focus on lacrosse.
Make sure you study too.
[knock at door]
Akito, can we talk?
[Akito] Hm?
[Akito's dad] Uh…
Why don't we all go on a family trip
during the next school holiday?
-It's been a while. Yeah.
-A trip?
You said you'd like to go on a…
on a sketch trip of Japan
when you got your license.
Did I say that?
All of Japan may be a bit difficult,
but we can try.
Natsumi says she wants to go too.
We'll go together.
I'm good. You guys go.
I'm sure I'd just cause trouble
on the road.
You're never any trouble for us.
You can be selfish, as well.
You've put your heart
and soul into your art.
I'm sure there's so much more
you can do with--
There's not.
I won't be alive long enough
to remember anyway.
I'm sorry.
Are we done?
[Akito sits]
[exhales]
[Akito draws]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[contemplative music plays]
[Haruna draws]
You've visited me three weeks in a row.
That's a record. Well done.
[both chuckle]
Thanks a lot.
I really didn't think
you'd visit me this much.
And the flowers have really made
an impression.
Let's survive for a week this time,
all right?
[chuckles] You can do it.
-[girl 1] Mako!
-[girl 2] Mako!
How are you?
-Oh hey, girls.
-How's it going?
-[girl 1] Are you doing all right?
-[girl 2] Oh my goodness.
-[girl 3] How are you feeling?
-[girl 2] That looks painful.
[Mako] All because Yuna dropped me.
Would you like to just go back
to the room?
'Cause this chatter is a bit annoying.
Mm-hm.
Haruna, is there someone
you'd like to visit you?
[Haruna] Hm…
What about that girl you said
you were friends with before?
I'd like to see my
father, you know?
-Your father?
-Mm-hm.
He doesn't visit you?
Not in five years.
I'd like to apologize to him.
Apologize?
He always would… take time
out of his own schedule
to do whatever would make me the happiest.
When I was hospitalized,
no matter how much he had to finish,
my dad would rush over here
as soon as he was done.
[mellow piano music plays]
But, um, he's more
of an outdoor kinda guy.
He always hoped to have a kid
who could go camping with him
or go swimming at the beach.
But we couldn't really partake
in any fun together.
So I…
I wanna say sorry
for having this frail body I've got.
I wanna tell him sorry
that I couldn't be a healthier daughter.
Here.
[mellow piano music continues]
-[woman] Thank you.
-Yeah, sure.
Uh, excuse me.
You said you're the head nurse, right?
I was wondering about, uh, her family.
[head nurse] Her family?
Um, well, it's just
I've never seen them come visit Haruna.
Not sure why, really.
She's not able to see her father?
Not trying to be nosy here,
but could the hospital try
to contact Haruna's father?
Could you do that?
I mean…
it would be great even
to speak with her mother.
Would you be able to tell me
the next time she'll be here?
[head nurse] Her mother is here.
Huh?
You're looking at her.
I am Haruna's mom.
[Akito] I'm sorry.
I didn't know about that.
I'm so sorry.
I just try to stay disciplined,
make sure I focus on my work.
I'm actually so grateful
you're here again.
It makes me so happy,
I want to just give you a hug.
About her father…
I'm sorry.
Even if I wanted to,
I can't reach him.
Huh?
He died in an accident.
[melancholy piano music plays]
[Haruna's mom] That day,
the doctor gave us the green light…
A few more things.
[Haruna's mom] …and the two of them
set off for the beach.
-[Haruna's dad] Okay, all set.
-[Haruna's mom chuckles]
Okay.
-We're off.
-[Haruna's mom] Have a safe trip.
We will.
Okay, let's go.
-[melancholy piano music continues]
-[Haruna's mom] But Haruna…
[Haruna breathes quickly]
…hid the fact she felt ill,
for her father's sake.
[Haruna's dad] Haruna? Hey! Haruna!
Haruna! Hey!
Are you okay? Haruna! Hey!
[car honks]
[melancholy piano music continues]
-[EMT 1] Right, let's lift. Are you okay?
-[EMT 2] On the count of three.
[EMT 1] Can you hear me?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
[Haruna's mom] She believes
it's all her fault.
[melancholy piano music continues]
She feels bad that she survived
and wants to see her dad
again as soon as she can.
She's shut out the world for so long.
But you opened it again,
even if it's just a little while.
As long as it doesn't interfere
with your studies,
please do stay friends with her.
[melancholy piano music fades out]
CARDIAC ANGIOSARCOMA SURGERY
CASE 1:
PRIMARY CARDIAC ANGIOSARCOMA
Thank you.
[Akito's mom] I wonder if he'd be smiling
and
going about his day as normal… [sniffs]
…if he hadn't been told about it.
[Akito's mom sniffs]
Oh yeah, that's…
that's what I wonder, over and over.
There's no doubt
that he would've been happier
if he didn't know.
But I guess
at least he's prepared.
He can use the time he's got
because he knows.
[Akito's mom weeps]
The thing is, though,
that no one knows what the answer is.
[Akito's dad] You know?
FOR GAKUENTOSHI STATION
[bus pulls away]
[Shota] Ah!
My bus!
-Ah! Dang it!
-[Eri] Late for morning practice again?
Ah! Ah!
-Ah! What?
-[Eri] Morning.
Ah! Ah, man, I'm so dead.
I was supposed to be at morning practice.
-[Eri] Uh-huh.
-[Shota] Yeah. Oh… Oh well.
Ah, if it isn't Mister Gerbera.
Can I please have five more
of the same pretty flowers?
Wow, this is a special person
if you're gonna miss school
to go and see them.
Uh, no, um, it's not like that.
It's just someone that I know.
[Akito chuckles nervously]
Well, I recommend a sixth.
On me, okay?
-No, no, but…
-It's okay, don't worry.
With Gerberas, the meaning changes
depending on how many you have as well.
Six Gerberas together means…
that I am falling for you.
[gentle music plays]
Oh there's one more in here.
-Really?
-Huh?
Oh…
she gave me one extra,
a freebie, since I'm a regular.
[sighs, laughs]
Well, that's great.
I feel so lucky
to get such pretty flowers.
[gentle music continues]
If only I could freeze them
and keep them forever.
Oh yeah! Look.
My mom bought me something.
She got me this.
I didn't realize
that the head nurse was also your mother.
Yeah.
It sounds like she told you a lot.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I wanna start posting some photos online
when I get better at it.
Whatcha think? And be honest, for real.
I know it's not great.
You took a… you took a video, you know.
Huh?
Yeah, that's art right there.
What about the other pictures I took?
[chuckles] Is this a selfie?
Ah! Wait a minute,
please don't look at that!
Huh? [chuckles]
Uh,
I'll go and…
put these in a vase.
[Haruna] Mm.
WELCOME
Akito,
I'm happy you come to see me,
but don't you have anything else to do?
Huh?
Don't you have friends?
It's not like I don't have friends,
but I don't have a lot.
Is there anyone you like?
It's not that I don't like anyone,
more like I don't really care at all.
What does that mean?
Well,
what about a girlfriend?
Hmm. Not really.
There's Eri,
but she's just a childhood friend.
And there's Shota.
So is it one-sided?
Ah!
So that's why
you were on the roof that day.
How about you, Haruna?
Anyone you like?
Huh?
I mean, is there anyone that you've…
had a crush on or…
are in love with?
It's frightening.
Love with a time limit.
Huh?
Something you know is gonna end
before it even begins.
It sounds nice what you've got.
One-sided love or not,
you do have a future at least.
No, I don't.
I don't have a future at all.
I gotta tell you--
You have to live a long life
and never give up.
Don't you give up on love, ever.
I wanna watch you from heaven
and see what kind of old man you become,
what kind of family you have.
What kind of person you fall in love with.
Go live a long time.
Live a long and happy life.
[shutter clicks]
That's my wish.
Will you honor my wish?
[Akito] I decided not to tell her
about my diagnosis.
I'll come every day.
Huh?
Hm.
Fine, then.
Then I'll wait for you.
["Wakamono No Subete" by Fujifabric plays]
[Akito] What would you do
if you knew you were going to die soon?
My answer to that,
I would use the time I had left for her.
[phone chimes]
WHAT TIME ARE YOU COMING?
AFTER SIXTH PERIOD, I MAY JUST MAKE IT.
UGH.
[phone chimes]
MOM, BRING A BLANKET.
[text chirps]
-MOM, BRING A BLANKET.
-WRONG PERSON, LOL.
Akito!
I haven't seen you in so long!
God, you're so clingy, Shota.
You're such a child!
[Shota] What about Sunday?
Should we all go to a movie?
Whatever you say, huh?
Ooh… All right, then, let's do it. Yeah?
Okay. Okay.
My little sister can be such a brat.
She's always ragging on me saying
that I was born with bad luck.
Really?
Yeah, my friends Eri
and Shota tease me as well.
-[Haruna giggles]
-Eri's smart.
She's the student council rep
all the way through, um,
elementary school and junior high.
And, uh, Shota's a good soccer player,
really good.
Hello again.
-You doing all five?
-Please.
Uh, you know what?
How about we do, uh, do six?
["Wakamono No Subete" fades out]
It's almost summer vacation.
Anything special that you wanna do?
Being sick doesn't come
with a summer vacation.
I really wish I could go somewhere though.
I'm so sorry.
I…
-[Haruna laughs]
-[Akito chuckles awkwardly]
Oh!
What about all the fireworks!
What?
You can see the whole
firework festival from right here.
The first time I didn't know
there'd be fireworks.
There was a huge bang.
I was so afraid I hid under my covers.
Then I looked out a little,
saw fireworks all the way to the ocean.
It was amazing.
You really should've seen it.
The thing is, though,
watching it up here alone was kind of…
was a little bit scary.
Let's watch it together this year.
You want to?
Mm-hm.
Really?
'Kay.
Promise.
[Akito chuckles awkwardly]
Deal. [giggles]
Woah, hang on, hang on!
-Open your hand up.
-Why?
What are you doing?
-Hey!
-It's fine!
Ah, dammit. I need to go soon.
You got plans?
Mm-hm. Yeah, I do.
A movie. I got forced to go.
Well, is it with your friend from school?
Yeah.
Mm…
A… date?
That's nice.
-Oh no, no, no. It's not like that.
-[phone chimes]
[phone chimes]
You should get going then.
Say hi for me.
Mm-hm. I'll be back again soon, though.
Hey, the fireworks are August 20th.
[chuckles]
See ya.
[door closes]
-Are you one of those who likes the ads?
-Huh?
-No, I really do not.
-Ah, Akito! Over here!
-[Akito] Sorry guys.
-He came.
You're late.
-Popcorn's on you.
-[Akito] Wait, what?
And get the drink combo, man.
-[Eri laughs]
-[Shota laughs]
-Okay, fine.
-Aw, yay.
Oh? Ayaka Miura.
There's a rumor goin' around
that you asked her out.
Did not.
It's a joke.
Come on, let's go.
-[Ayaka] Diet soda, please.
-Okay.
-[Shota] Hey, Akito, let's go.
-[Ayaka] That one for me, please.
-[Shota] This way!
-[Eri] Okay.
-[phone chimes]
-[Shota] I wanna see an action movie next.
MESSAGE FROM: HARUNA
[grunts in pain]
-[background silences]
-[gasps]
[melancholy music plays]
[Haruna] Did you make it
to the movie in time?
I've already made a teru teru bōzu doll.
I hope we have nice
weather for the fireworks.
[melancholy music continues over silence]
-[man] Are you okay?
-[woman] Are you okay?
[concerned commotion]
Akito!
Akito!?
-Akito! Akito!
-Akito!
[Eri] Someone call an ambulance!
Akito!
[Haruna hums "Wakamono No Subete"
by Fujifabric]
[disturbing rattling noise]
[rattling noise crescendoes]
[machine beeps]
[Natsumi] Akito.
[gasps] Mom, I think Akito is…
Akito, can you hear me, sweetie?
-[groans]
-[Akito's mom] You need to rest.
You collapsed at the movie theater.
Eri brought you to the hospital.
You've been here for a week now.
What?
[Akito's mom] You collapsed 'cause
of an irregular heartbeat.
They did surgery
and they put a device into your heart.
They said your recovery
is gonna take a while.
At least through your summer vacation.
What day is it?
[Akito's mom] What?
Uh. What's the date today?
It's, uh, August 20th.
No way.
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
[Haruna] Hey, what's up?
You haven't read any of my messages.
I've made loads of teru teru bōzu dolls.
Has something happened?
Do you need some time apart?
Do you have plans with your friend?
[fireworks explode]
INCOMING CALL FROM: HARUNA
[phone rings]
[Haruna] Hi.
Hey, Haruna.
I broke our promise.
I'm not there. I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry I didn't text you back.
That's good to hear.
I was afraid you hated me now.
To tell you the truth,
there's a reason I didn't text you.
It's fine. It's Eri, right?
Huh?
[Haruna] I'm sure you guys are busy
during summer vacation.
I'm happy if it worked out.
As your friend, I'm happy for you.
Remember what I said?
The thing I look forward to most
is watching down on you from heaven
and seeing you happy.
The whole fireworks thing is nothing.
[melancholy piano music plays]
I'm sorry.
[fireworks continue]
[gasps]
Stay on the phone with me a little longer.
Don't get off the phone just yet.
I won't hang up.
Not till the fireworks are done.
I don't know if I'll see this again,
these beautiful fireworks.
[exhales] Don't you say that.
Your time's not up yet.
We're gonna watch again next year.
They told me I only had six months to live
quite a while ago now.
You can do this!
I looked it up,
and there are tons of people
who outlive their prognosis.
Some people live for over ten years.
I mean, it could even be a misdiagnosis.
So…
let's celebrate Christmas,
New Years!
Let's have a party for your 18th birthday.
It's in April, right?
Mm-hm.
Akito?
Actually…
you see, I, um…
To tell you the truth, uh…
I really do, um--
What? Did you say something?
[Haruna cries]
[Haruna] No.
It seems like…
[inhales, sighs]
…the fireworks are done.
[melancholy music fades out]
[Shota] Why didn't you tell us?
If I'd told you,
it would've felt like my own funeral.
I didn't want…
to put that on you.
To have you go through that.
[Shota] I mean, even if you had told us,
I know there's nothing we could've done.
Still, I…
I wish you'd told us.
That's what best friends are for.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Can you come back to school?
Yeah.
They said after the summer
I can go back, so next semester.
[Haruna's mom] Akito?
[Haruna's mom] This comes as a shock.
Please, can you…
Can you please not, um, not tell Haruna?
Being told that I didn't have long,
I-- I was afraid, but then
she gave me a reason to live.
She gave me something to hold onto.
[exhales]
I'm sorry that it's a… a selfish reason.
But I, uh, I want her
to enjoy her time now, instead of…
of looking forward to--
To heaven.
I just wanted us to enjoy living…
living as normal teenagers.
[hopeful music plays]
[sighs] Yeah, me too.
I could be in denial as well.
Huh?
It's really just an escape,
my working here as a nurse.
I, too,
need to face reality.
[Akito's mom] Have you forgotten anything?
-[Akito] Mm-mm.
-[Akito's mom] Okay.
[Akito] I have to face reality.
So Haruna can enjoy the present.
Ugh, I don't ever wanna go
to school again.
Me neither.
Ayaka, oh my gosh, those nails are a lot.
You think? Yeah?
-Girl… for real, yeah.
-Uh, yeah, I'd say so.
-I'm shook.
-You're right.
But I met with my career counselor.
She thinks I should become
a nail technician.
-Then I'll be your first customer.
-Oh!
Oh yeah, and I'll be your second one.
[all laugh]
[girl] Huh?
Huh? Is that…
Uh… What?
[Akito] Let's go and see Haruna.
Uh… Huh? Wait!
What?
[Ayaka] Hey! Hey!
Ugh! Let go of me!
Uh, hey, man! Are you insane? Let me go!
Akito, you are seriously crazy right now!
Are you into Haruna or what?
'Cause if you are,
she's not into psychopaths, seriously.
Listen to me.
She doesn't have very long.
She has three months.
If she even has that long.
[knock at door]
[door opens]
Wow, you're here.
Yes, and I'm sorry.
I don't have an excuse,
and I know being sorry won't cut it.
I know it doesn't excuse anything,
but I've brought
someone else with me today.
Aya.
It's been a while.
[Haruna] I'm sorry.
I am, really.
[delicate music plays]
[Ayaka] No.
It's me who's sorry.
Oh God, I'm sorry it…
it took so long to visit.
I'm sorry, Haruna.
I said some horrible things.
[Ayaka] No.
I did.
It's not true, is it?
You can't die.
I won't let you.
[quietly] I'm sorry.
[Ayaka] Even if you apologize,
I won't forgive you.
Ever.
[Ayaka] I'm not thanking you.
[Akito] Hm.
Haruna and I became friends
when we were in the second grade.
[little girl laughs]
You're never gonna get me!
[Ayaka] Everyone would say,
"That girl's sick,"
and would stay away from her.
[young Ayaka] Don't you wanna play
over there?
I'm not allowed to run around.
[young Ayaka] Hm…
Let's see who can go the highest
on the swing!
Go!
[giggles] Hey, Haruna, you swing too.
[delicate piano music plays]
[Ayaka] I wasn't scared at all,
so I just straight up asked her
about her illness.
It's strange, but we clicked instantly.
[silent background]
I was her best friend,
and she was mine.
[young Ayaka] It's so cute.
[young Haruna] You can be her new mommy!
Aw!
-[background silences]
-[delicate piano music continues]
[Ayaka] But when we started junior high,
she was still missing a lot of school.
[dramatic piano music plays]
We started drifting apart
without realizing it.
The nail in the coffin was graduation day.
She wasn't able to go
to her own graduation.
Ta-da!
[dramatic piano music continues]
What do you think? I made you a diploma.
CONGRATS! LET'S STAY FRIENDS!
Don't give up, Haruna.
Let's go to high school together.
They have remote-learning programs too,
you know.
[sniffs]
Is this some kind of a joke?
What's wrong? Don't you like it, Haruna?
A handmade certificate?
You really thought I'd want that?
God. Seriously, are you my teacher now?
No, what? Why would you say that?
I didn't even go to my club's
group graduation to make you this.
We're friends. I wanna graduate with you--
We are not friends.
Ever since we were little,
I never considered me
and you to be friends.
I just, uh…
[Haruna sniffs]
…I simply wanted to be you.
But it's impossible.
I can't be you.
I don't even wanna be you anymore.
I think it's also time for us…
Mm…
to graduate from each other.
Don't come here again.
What are you saying?
[weeps]
I thought that we were best friends.
This is the reason you don't have friends!
Fine! Bye-bye!
And that was it.
Maybe she was just trying her best
to let go of you.
Like she knew she didn't have long
and didn't wanna drag you through it.
[delicate piano music plays]
CONGRATS HARUNA!
[Haruna weeps]
Bye, bye.
[Akito] I understand wanting
to distance yourself from your friends.
Uh, it's just
what I think.
-[knock at door]
-[door opens]
-[Akito's dad] Akito, got a minute?
-[closes door]
I wanted to talk to you
about something important
before school resumes.
Well, so that critical surgery
that I told you about, you remember?
Well, Doctor Kikuchi searched everywhere
and found an excellent doctor
that he'll refer you to.
SURVIVING INCURABLE HEART TUMORS
[Akito] I see, but he said
it only prolongs my life a little, right?
But, Akito, don't you think
it's worth a shot anyway?
Because if the surgery's successful,
you could do the Nika Art Exhibition.
You'll have to stay out of school
for three months though.
Three months?
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
I can't do the surgery.
Okay.
I'm sorry for pushing it on you.
Maybe this was actually
more for me than it was for you anyway.
[opens door]
[closes door]
[PA] Paging Doctor Tanaka,
please report to the nurses' station.
[knock at door]
[Haruna] Come in.
You're alone?
Uh, thank God.
Huh. Don't let me disturb you.
-[whimsical music plays]
-[clears throat]
And you're here… again!
You have been here every day, haven't you?
Look who's talking!
You're being an absolute creeper.
You're no different.
So, if you're gonna be here,
at least try to be entertaining.
You overanalyze everything.
Who are you, Rodin?
[Ayaka] Haruna loves me being here.
At least I'm not here to just constantly
bother Haruna like you do.
[Akito] I'm not bothering her.
Yeah, well I think
that you guys are a perfect pair.
-Huh?
[Ayaka] Are you kidding?
I'm not into goofy nerds like him.
Seriously, ugh.
She doesn't have a boyfriend,
you know, Akito.
Haruna!
[Akito laughs] What?
Yeah, I'm on a little dating hiatus,
because men are the worst, lemme tell ya.
[Akito laughs]
Yeah? What are you laughing at, Akito?
Why don't you date
one of your cartoon characters?
I'm not too focused on love right now.
This is nice.
I guess this is what school's like.
[whimsical music fades out]
Oh uh… here.
SEIMEI HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL SHOW
Tickets to the school festival, two.
What?
Yeah, our class is, uh…
We're doing a hip version of Snow White.
Well, I had the idea.
Take a hint, man!
There's two here so you can take Haruna!
I didn't really wanna ask you anyway,
but I want Haruna to have
some experience of being young.
SNOW WHITE
For our school play in elementary school…
we performed Snow White.
I was the prince,
and Haruna was Snow White.
But just before the show started,
she collapsed.
She wasn't able to perform
or watch the show.
So that's why.
Hm.
I'll take Haruna to it.
For sure.
[Haruna] School festival?
[Akito] Yeah, let's go together.
I've asked your mom,
and we'll get permission from the doctor.
Ayaka said she can't wait.
Hm.
I'll go.
I'd love to.
Yeah, let's do it.
[joyful piano music plays]
YEAR 2, CLASS B
[phone chimes]
[Haruna] Look, I made a few more dolls.
I might just be a genius.
How's prep going on your end?
It's a shame we can't see each other,
but that makes me even more excited
for the festival.
[breathes heavily]
[Haruna's mom] Are you all right?
[joyful piano music fades out]
This will relieve the pain,
so hang in there.
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
If it's for the school festival,
I'm doing it.
[uplifting music plays]
[boy] Well, hello there.
How are you doing, pretty lady?
[Akito] Wow.
[girl] We have two guests coming in.
[Eri] Ah, Akito! [giggles]
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Hi.
-[Eri] I hope you enjoy our festival.
-Thanks.
[Shota] Oh!
-Come on! Just stop it.
-Oh?
-Akito?
-Hey! Yeah.
-Come in, this way.
-Oh?
-Oh? Ow! Ow!
-[Eri] Enough.
Wait a sec. Is that Eri?
Yeah.
Hmm.
She looks really nice.
-[Akito] You think?
-Well, yeah, I do.
Ooh! Look at this one.
It's nice, don't you think?
Yeah, I get what you're saying.
It's like they're
in their own little world.
Don't you wish it was you?
[both shout]
[Akito] Zombies!
Okay, both of us, then.
[girl] Okay, say cheese!
[shutter clicks repeatedly]
[girl] One more. You look so cute.
[uplifting music fades out]
Sorry.
I just need to rest a little.
Are you okay?
I'm having a ton of fun. It hurts.
You want some water?
Please.
[phone vibrates]
[phone keeps vibrating]
Mom, hi.
Haruna?
It's time to come back,
so could you start making your way
back to the hospital?
You must be tired too.
No, I'm okay.
Just a little longer.
You can go again next time, okay?
I'm not here much longer.
It's your mother, huh?
It's me, Akito.
I'll make sure she gets back okay.
Can we please stay just a bit longer?
As the head nurse,
I want you to bring her back right away.
However…
[inhales deeply]
[exhales] …however, as her mom…
I won't say a word.
Thank you very much.
[audience cheers]
SNOW WHITE
[dance club music plays]
[audience claps in time to music]
[music stops]
[audience cheers]
[cheerful music plays]
If you wash your face every day,
then apply some lotion,
and, of course, sunscreen after washing,
you become a--!
[Shota] You're ruining the vibe!
[thunderclaps]
-Slasher!
-Ah!
-[Takada] Ah!
[Takada breathes deeply]
[Takada] Snow… White.
[audience laughs]
Ah!
[heart beats]
[audience] Whoo!
[cheerful music fades out]
[Takada] Snow White, are you all right?
[Ayaka] Prince!
[gasps] You saved me.
Thank you!
[gentle piano music plays]
[silent background]
[applause]
Ah! Haruna! [laughs]
[Haruna] Ah! [chuckles]
[Ayaka] You made it.
You really came to see it.
Thank you for this, Aya.
You looked really gorgeous on that stage.
No, thank you.
I was dancing as if you were right there
with me on that stage.
[girl 1] Okay, everyone,
let's take a photo.
Gather around.
-[Ayaka] See you after, okay?
-Mm.
-[girl 2] Where did Aya go?
-Ayaka in the middle. Okay, Aya here!
Okay, Ayaka's in the middle.
-Let's group together, what're you doing?
-[Shota] I'm gonna be here
[Ayaka] Huh? Where's Takada?
Where's Takada? Seriously.
[Haruna] Thank you.
You really made
one of my dreams come true today.
We'll go, uh, to the beach next time.
You wanna go to that place that you,
uh, drew in your sketchbook, right?
I hope there is a next time, Akito.
That place I drew?
That's where I was going
that day with my dad.
We never made it, though.
SATURDAY, NOVEMBER 16TH
[breathes deeply]
[rings stop]
We're getting off! Please let us off here.
[hopeful piano music plays]
-I'll push you.
-Mm.
[Akito] Thank you.
[Akito] Get on my back.
[Akito grunts]
[waves crash]
[Akito] We made it.
Thank you.
Hey.
If I were to die…
would you give me a kiss
to save this lonely soul?
I also wanted to fall in love.
Even just once.
I wanted to really love somebody.
[delicate piano music plays]
To give myself over to someone…
for them to do the same,
to make each other happy.
That was always my biggest wish.
I'm sorry…
that I… wasn't able…
wasn't able to do anything for you.
Akito, what's wrong?
[Akito sniffs]
Are you sad, Akito?
I'm sorry. I was joking about the kiss.
Did I upset you?
It was a joke. Don't cry.
[Akito sniffs]
I…
I've, uh… I've been hiding something
from the very start.
I felt like it was better
not to say anything.
So…
Don't say it.
I wanna just hear nice things
and sweet things right now.
Let's be here, nowhere else.
Let's maybe leave it alone for today.
[delicate piano music fades out]
[Haruna's mom] Haruna…
doesn't have much longer.
Cherish the time
you have left together.
What are you… drawing?
It's a secret.
Let me see it.
No way.
Why not?
I'd like to see…
what you've been working on.
Huh?
It's not fair. You get to see mine.
Hey.
Can you draw me?
I'd like you to.
I want you to draw me.
[clock ticking]
You're beautiful, Haruna.
Thank you very much, Aya.
I feel like I'm being made up
for my funeral.
I was thinking more like bride
on her wedding day. [chuckles]
Voilà!
Thank you, Aya
[Akito draws]
Sitting in the same position for so long
is really quite tiring.
I feel almost like I'm the Mona Lisa.
[giggles]
[Akito chuckles]
You can lie down if you like.
Hey.
Do you remember the day that we first met?
Why did you… start talking to me
on that certain day?
Uh…
I was in a bad place
and then someone saved me.
An angel.
Huh?
[clacking, rolling sounds]
[gentle piano music plays]
[Akito] You might laugh,
but that day, after all my bad luck,
it was as if an angel appeared before me.
So, yeah.
[gentle piano music continues]
That girl that I saw…
she only had six months to live,
but she wasn't afraid.
I thought that was incredible.
Really, really, incredible.
No.
That was the day that I
found out I had six months left.
It was earlier that day.
It was something I already knew.
But when it actually came down to it,
I was so afraid.
[drawing rapidly]
[sighing]
[pencil falls, rolls]
KINKI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
[Akito] They're beautiful colors.
[gentle piano music continues]
Um, I-- I mean those, pencils, um…
[Haruna] You started talking to me and
it was as if a hero swooped down.
[gentle piano music continues]
I said
I wanted to die soon, right?
At that time, I really thought that I did.
I feel differently now.
I don't wanna die yet.
I just wanna live.
I wanna…
I wanna be with you…
and also with Aya.
I don't need…
ten years, or twenty years…
Even just one day…
one minute, one second more.
I wanna live longer.
I decided that after being
with both of you.
So from now on,
I will fight this illness every day.
If I don't die today, it's my win.
Akito…
even if something's troubling you…
you've got to keep on fighting too.
Hm.
[quietly] Your drawing.
Let's see it.
[sniffs]
[gentle piano music crescendoes]
[Haruna] It's beautiful.
You're a great artist.
So, uh…
would you please…
let me get the surgery?
I know it'll be hard to… to pay for it,
and even under perfect conditions,
there's a low success rate,
especially given the luck I've got.
But I still wanna do it.
Is that okay?
[hopeful music plays]
Yeah.
Of course it is.
[Akito] And…
you were right telling me the truth
on how long I had left.
The diagnosis has made me realize
what's most important.
[Akito's mom cries]
And Natsumi?
Thank you for being
the best little sister.
Thank you.
In our family, you know,
you're the lucky one, Akito.
Yeah.
[hopeful music continues]
[rolling, banging sounds]
-[nurse] Her blood pressure is dropping.
-[doctor] Let's intubate her immediately.
[Haruna's mom] Haru! Hang in there!
[anxious piano music plays]
[background silences]
[drops sketchbook]
[anxious piano music continues]
HARUNA'S TAKEN A TURN.
GOT IT. HEADED OVER NOW.
[types on phone]
[Akito] Haruna, come on, wake up.
[silent background]
[phone chirps]
There's something I wanna tell you
when you wake up.
[gentle piano music plays]
[silent background]
So…
[no dialogue]
…please wake up.
Wake up, Haruna.
[cries] Wake up.
[silent background]
[cries]
[dramatic string music plays]
[slaps chest]
[groans]
[gasps desperately]
[nurse 1] Can you hear me?
Sir, can you hear me?
-Bring a defibrillator.
-[nurse 2] Okay.
[dramatic string music continues]
[background silences]
[Haruna echoes] Akito.
[cheerful piano music plays]
[cheerful piano music fades out]
[Ayaka] Why…
Why weren't you there?
Haruna fought so hard.
She woke up right before the end.
She was calling for you.
She called out your name.
[Ayaka stands]
[Ayaka stomps off]
[Haruna's mom] Here.
I want you to have this.
It's the last drawing she made.
Uh, uh, but…
Just trust me.
You really deserve to have it, Akito.
You know, drawing was a way for her…
to escape reality.
A way she could take refuge
in a world of her own.
[sniffs] But when you started to visit…
she wanted to show you her drawings.
That's the reason she drew.
[Akito] I…
I wanted to tell her something.
But I couldn't.
I wasn't even by her side at the end.
I couldn't do anything.
[Haruna] Dear Akito…
this room,
where we spent so much time,
is heaven to me now.
[uplifting piano music plays]
You turned this place,
filled with nothing but pain,
into
a warm and bright place.
I think
that I've laughed for a lifetime here.
[silent background]
But also,
I've cried for a lifetime here too.
I thought I wanted to hurry up and die…
but now I want to live for longer,
even if only for a day.
Thanks to you…
I was really happy.
So, Akito…
I want you to live a long
and a happy life for me…
and draw even more beautiful pictures,
okay?
[Akito] So, like,
what are you drawing?
It's a secret.
I look forward to meeting you again
someday when you're old
and have lived a full life…
on the other side of the sky.
And on that day,
when I see you again…
can I call you
my best friend?
And lastly…
for all of the flowers you gave me,
I'll give you some flowers too.
[sniffs]
[upbeat music plays]
[doctor] You'll start to feel tired,
Mr. Hayasaka.
Okay.
[strained breathing]
[therapist] Okay, now turn slowly.
Well done.
Thank you.
-You really killed it!
-[Akito chuckles]
Will you be okay?
Yeah.
This bag is so heavy.
[silent background]
UNIVERSITY EXAM RESULT: ACCEPTED
[Natsumi sings]
[Akito's dad] Oh you're good!
On the way back,
can we go to a hot spring?
-Huh?
-Oh what did you say?
-A hot spring?
-Please, guys!
-There you go.
-Thanks.
-Can I have it?
-[Akito's mom] Mm!
Akito, here.
Ah, thank you.
[Ayaka] Are you alive, Akito?
[phone chimes]
[Akito] I'm hanging in there,
but I'm in the hospital again.
Man, again?
[florist] Ah, if it isn't Miss Gerbera.
Is your boyfriend sick again?
Akito is not my boyfriend, we're rivals.
-[florist laughs]
-[Ayaka chuckles]
-You want five again today?
-Mm.
Or
should I make it six?
[Ayaka snickers]
Oh five's great.
Hm…
that's a shame.
If you did six,
it might look a little
like this over here.
[Ayaka] Hm.
Is this…?
Hm? Ah, this?
I arranged the flowers,
but someone else uploaded the photos.
They took some beautiful photos of them,
so I thought I'd show you.
[PA] Doctor Tanaka to the emergency room.
Doctor Tanaka.
[Ayaka] Akito!
What's that? What are you painting?
My last painting ever.
No…
The first picture
of the second life that Haruna's given me.
How're you feeling?
They say it has spread.
Oh no.
The cancer's spread to my spine,
so… that's the last I was told.
That's really bad, isn't it?
Yeah, I believe so.
Not really bad, extremely bad.
Yeah, it is.
But…
Well, anyway…
uh,
look what I saw.
[Akito] Are these… the flowers
I gave Haruna?
[Haruna]
I wanna start posting some photos online
when I get better at it.
She posted it, all right.
There haven't been any updates
since December.
But before that… look.
There's a private link.
[Akito] "To the boy born
in the fall."
But you can't view it without a password.
ENTER PASSWORD
PASSWORD: INCORRECT
So it's not her birthday.
-[incorrect password buzz]
-[Akito inhales]
Gerbera.
PASSWORD INCORRECT
ENTER PASSWORD
[phone clicks]
[Haruna] The story of how the girl
with six months to live
met the boy with one year to live.
Huh?
[Haruna] To the boy born in the fall…
[shutter clicks]
…I decided to write down
all of my thoughts
together with a photo of the Gerberas
you gave me.
[joyful music plays]
You were the first person
my magic word didn't work on.
[joyful music continues]
I couldn't believe it.
When we first met on the roof,
it surprised me that despite my illness,
you were unafraid
and didn't look at me with pity.
From that moment on,
[joyful music continues]
I wanted to see you again
and I searched the hospital every day
looking for you.
Every day, I'd wait in the hallway
for you to come and visit…
-[gasps]
-…and when I saw you…
I'd hyperventilate and jump into bed.
When I realized you really would come
and visit me every day,
I was so happy I couldn't breathe!
Uh, Miss Haruna?
[joyful music continues]
At the beginning of the fall,
I found out about your secret.
He's in cardiology?
Not much time left?
Akito too?
[joyful music continues]
So she knew.
[Haruna] But you kept quiet about it
and supported me
with what I was dealing with.
[sniffs]
You didn't have much time left.
But what you did have, you used on me.
I'm sorry.
[joyful music continues]
So to repay you for your kindness,
I pretended not to know.
I just wanted things to be normal.
Because to us,
normal is the most precious
and the most irreplaceable thing
in the world.
[joyful music continues]
These past six months,
I have been the happiest I've ever been.
[joyful music continues]
You know,
us meeting like we did
wasn't a coincidence.
It was inevitable.
[joyful music continues]
I'm certain we were born
just so we could meet each other.
And that thought
made it possible for me to endure
my inescapable pain.
[joyful music continues]
Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
Akito, please don't be afraid.
I will help you. I will carry your pain.
[joyful music continues]
When I'm gone,
I will watch over you from above,
making sure you are okay.
[joyful music continues]
Also, thank you for everything with Aya.
Try and get along with her, will you?
You're saying Akito and I?
-[Haruna] I've told her to do the same.
-No way.
Hm? Are you sure?
Aya looks tough, but she's soft at heart.
It'd be good for you.
-I do worry about her.
-Huh?
[joyful music continues]
[Haruna] If you could support each other
for me,
that would make me so happy.
[joyful music continues]
I won't tell you what I wanted to say
on the night of the fireworks.
Actually…
you see, I, um…
[joyful music continues]
To tell you the truth, uh…
I really do love--
But I'd like to believe
that one way or another,
you would've already realized what it was.
How I felt.
And that would be my last gift…
[joyful music continues]
…from a god that has been so cruel to me
for so long.
[joyful music continues]
I'm sure you knew what six Gerberas meant
when you gave them to me, didn't you?
Being in a hospital for so long,
you come to learn the meanings
of different sympathy flowers.
I believe you know their meanings too.
I'm sure you do.
That's why I decided to draw
three Gerberas for you.
[joyful music continues]
[florist] Three Gerberas
means I love you.
[joyful music continues]
I usually don't recommend three
just because it feels lonely,
but the meaning is so beautiful.
-[joyful music continues]
-[Akito sobs]
THREE GERBERAS MEAN "I LOVE YOU"
[sniffs]
[joyful music fades out]
[Ayaka] You and Haruna are amazing.
To experience such pure love
in such a limited amount of time.
Your love always had an expiration date.
All I've had
is love that expires after a month.
But now…
now that I'm visiting you like this… hm…
I feel like I know what love truly means.
Hey, Haruna…
how do you think he'll react
when he wakes up?
Angry?
Annoyed?
Or do you think it'll make him
laugh just a little?
Akito passed away
three and a half years
after he was given his diagnosis.
[gentle piano music plays]
You know, Haruna,
for someone with such bad luck,
he sure was persistent.
Do you use any hand cream or anything?
[woman] Not really.
Oh really?
They're a little dry…
And it's really quite something
that the anniversary of your death
is the same day.
[gentle guitar music continues]
TO THE BOY BORN IN AUTUMN.
[Ayaka] Whoa, what?
This reply…
Akito?
[Akito] Haruna, how are you?
[gentle music plays]
I'm probably going to be joining you soon.
Part of me is scared,
but part of me is looking forward to it.
Thanks to you,
I've continued to challenge
life right until the very end.
This dark, monochromatic world
has become a colorful one.
It's almost blinding.
And thank you for everything with Ayaka.
She comes to visit me often,
and she's actually been really helpful.
Once I'm gone, Ayaka will be free,
and I'm sure she'll be glad
to be done with all this.
P. S.
I woke up just now and looked at my hand,
and there were three Gerberas
painted on my nails.
It must have been Ayaka.
She probably doesn't know the meaning,
so I'm gonna tease her about it
the next time I see her.
I do know. Come on, silly.
["Wakamono No Subete" plays]
NIKA ART EXHIBITION SELECTION
AKITO HAYASAKA &amp; HARUNA SAKURAI
"OUR SKY"
THE COLOR OF LOVE PROVIDES THE MEANING
OF LIFE AND ART - MARC CHAGALL