Hello, sorry to call you so late.
I'm at Maribu-kun's apartment
right now.
Why? Because...
I can't reach him.
I'm worried.
Here they come.
- Make way!
- Make way.
Tonight at 9:00 P.M. in Mitaka
City, Nakano-Suginami districts,
police arrested the 29-year old
manager of a red-light bar
based on reports of threatening
and blackmailing customers;
disturbing the peace with
intimidating customer-barking;
alleged criminal activities of
fraud and extortion;
along with two cronies associated
with the red-light establishment,
he was arrested on charges of
obstruction of public duties.
What? The immigration bureau?
Who is this Yuka?
Huh?
You mean Bin Rin?
Fu Bin Rin.
It's uncertain if
this is even her real name.
Tourist visa.
It's expired.
She also gave birth, didn't she?
When a foreigner gives birth in
Japan, within 30 days, they must
apply for a residence permit with
the immigration bureau
and report the birth
to their country of origin
via the embassy or consulate.
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
Welcome.
Oh.
Sorry, I know today's
your day off.
Anyway, what's going on?
It's Maribu.
Right now he's...
being detained at the Suginami
Police Station.
I'm not allowed to see him so I'm
not clear on what happened.
But it seems they'd run a
sting operation on his bar.
You're under arrest.
He's not involved anymore; he'd
gone clean. He's a gardener now.
There was trouble at work.
He skipped out and left.
Then unfortunately, he got
caught by the police.
His pub has a history of
victim complaints,
and undercover agents had been
onto them for quite awhile now.
What's going to happen to him?
For intimidation...
he'll get 2 years.
And for attempted extortion, he'll
get under 10 years imprisonment.
What?
He just happened to be there.
It seems the paperwork reflected
him to be the bar manager.
Can the charges be dropped?
Only an attorney
can answer that.
Attorney...
Attorney, eh...
And his wife and child?
Yamaji-san will
care for them...
Yuka-san had "overstayed."
Then, the attorney...
We have to find one fast.
I'm on it already.
Who is it?
I've found one, I've found one.
Shut up, for crying out loud...
"Shut up"?
By the way, though the
timing is odd...
I heard you're getting married,
congratulations.
Congratulations.
Nothing's happened yet...
Akane-chan was elated; she said
she's a chairman's wife.
So, your older brother
is becoming a farmer?
- Shut up, for crying out loud.
- "Shut up"?
"Maternity Handbook"
- We've got good news of our own.
Which means...
The 6th generation heir will still
be my older brother.
Midori-san is the wife of the
chairman...
it seems.
I'm just his supporter.
I see.
Do you want to reconsider quit-
ting, and go back to work?
Why?
Why? Because...
I'm not marrying you because you
might become a chairman.
If you're going to support your
brother, then your supporter
will be your wife's role.
I quit my job because I found some-
thing better than work. That's all.
Can I take this frying pan?
It's light and easy to use.
Just buy a new one.
No, I want this one.
All right then, go ahead.
You can have it.
I dunno, that's kinda cute.
She is kinda cute.
She said she was having
marriage "pink."
It'll eventually turn blue...
We'll both be unemployed
starting next month.
Too bad you can't be chairman.
Aso-san is late.
Our meeting is at 3:00.
Maybe he's already here.
Huh? The attorney?
Huh?
There and the major contractor
Hayama Steel?
Your companies have a close
business relationship, don't you?
Therefore...
Crap, crap, he's coming.
There's nothing the police
can do. Ice coffee.
Yes.
Seriously...
Howdy.
I overslept, so...
Evidence that can't be presented
is not evidence.
Seriously.
What? What?
So he is... is he?
Oh, yes.
He is my son...
I told you didn't I?
He's an attorney.
What?
Did you get a tan,
Masanobu-kun?
Riding the waves?
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
I only have 4 minutes to spare.
Please make it brief.
First, I need a retainer
of 300,000 yen.
For winning the case, I will
expect another 300,000 yen.
Of course, expenses are
charged separately.
Wait a second. You're asking his
brother to defend him?
It'll depend on the
agreement.
You were late to the appointment,
which lowers my opinion of you.
I mean, seriously.
You haven't called in ages, and
suddenly this is the call I get?
What kind of father are you?
Please...
When's the last time
I saw you?
It's not funny.
The time...
to...
Seat for 4 people.
expose my darkness
has come.
Here? That's a problem.
Go do that in the booth.
When Masanobu
was four...
after I had a big affair...
I married for the second time.
And...
that was... to Hitomi.
She's Maribu's mother.
Huh?
He wouldn't remember anything
if he was only four.
The child wouldn't, but...
the mother would ponder.
A step-child and her own
child are utterly different.
She tried to raise them equally,
without favouritism...
and that's what got her stressed.
For example, in a running race at
the school sports event,
Masanobu came in 2nd place.
As his mother she wanted
Maribu to also come in 2nd place.
Or 1st place,
and simultaneously, she rued her
ego for having wished that.
Yet, 3rd place would
have been unacceptable.
3rd place is no fun.
So only 2nd place for both would've
satisfied her sense of equality.
Therefore when he came in 2nd,
she would say in relief...
"I'm so glad."
"Masanobu, Maribu, both of
you did great."
And because of those words...
Masanobu was deeply hurt.
- Why?
- Refill.
One highball coming up.
Because he was equally praised
when the situation wasn't equal.
"Masanobu you did great!
Maribu you did great too."
That would've been fine.
But to say Masanobu and Maribu
both did great, is not.
How confusing.
Huh? What?
You see...
what took away that
confusion was...
Millennial education.
Exactly.
"Only one"
instead of "number one."
That's right. You can't tell who's
1st in those school races anyway.
Teachers with flags run along
with them to mix it all up.
I wish millennial education had
been applied much sooner.
What? What is it?
I was thinking I'd met
your wife somewhere.
This.
-You mind?
-Go ahead.
What?
That's Aso Hitomi.
Right?
Ah, my secret has been revealed.
She's a "Tama Beauty."
I've been a subscriber.
I get a free poster
every year.
So Aso is...
the same "Aso" as Aso Hitomi.
I'm humbled
to say, yes.
She used the name instead
of her maiden name.
To not vex her kids.
Gosh I was a fan.
She debuted as a heroine
in a morning drama.
That was "Kappore-chan."
Right, "Kappore-chan"!
You know your stuff.
But just when her career was
taking off, she got married
to some bubble-refugee flim-flam
real-estate jerk.
I should punch
you for that.
Hey Nakamori-kun.
When was that posted?
I dunno; I think
it's always been there.
As I thought.
He's been coming here
to see his mother.
Maribu-kun.
Here.
And the older brother
began to bully his little brother...
because he was envious
of him.
He played the part of the kind older
brother in front of their mother...
but behind her back,
he bullied Maribu.
She didn't notice it.
This so-called
"Tama Beauty."
It seems she pretended not
to see what she saw.
"It seems"?
What were you doing, then?
You're the father you know.
Masanobu had...
started law school at the
public university...
And Maribu was getting
his own life started...
Um... My...
How do I say it...
My adultery got found out...
What are you thinking?
Tama Beauty went
crazy with rage.
She had a lot of
pride to begin with.
She always condemned my
character after that.
You reaped what you'd sowed.
- You know, Yamaji-san...
- Yeah?
I...
"you reaped what you've
sowed" is...
of all the many phrases, the one
I hate the most.
- Sorry.
- The most, without question.
2nd is: "legal compensation,"
3rd is: "alimony."
- But the fact is...
- I reaped what I'd sowed.
I admit that, of course I do.
I'll live the rest of my life
reaping what I've sowed.
So don't remind me.
You know, don't mention it.
Don't mention it on the side.
Give it to me as a big conclusion.
A big conclusion.
Or...
tell me after I'm dead.
Because I know...
my death won't be dignified any way.
You laughed, didn't you?
After the divorce Masanobu became
estranged to me.
He had no obligation
to live with me,
so he left home and pursued
to become a lawyer.
Maribu was touted as a prodigy, but
at that time, his grades plummeted.
That was because the diffused
attention he had been receiving
from his mom suddenly
honed in on him and him alone.
"I didn't marry to put a stranger's
child through college."
"Your turn has finally come."
"You must boldly aim for the top."
"What do you think you're doing?"
"I can't take this anymore."
"If you don't win. My life..."
"can be considered a huge failure!"
Number 127, you have a visitor.
I was assigned the case
by Michigami Iwao.
I am Michigami of Law Office
of Michigami.
You are Michigami Maribu?
That's right.
Have you submitted to
questionings cooperatively?
Regarding how we
will proceed,
do you require a
consultation?
I'm going to trial.
But I don't want a lawyer.
It's a waste of money.
And I wouldn't want
you as my defender.
I'll bow out myself,
you jerk!
Now you're talking,
bastard!
What's going on here?
Who do you think
you are, bastard?
What's the prodigy doing in here?
Look how you've fallen!
Oh no...
It's partly your fault!
Shut up, you're
an embarassment!
I hope you get convicted!
Okay, that's enough now.
Enough. Please stop, you two.
Please stop!
Please stop! What's
happening here?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
No can do,
out of the question.
I'm turning it down.
Please reconsider, so he
may return to society.
Impossible.
He's not legit.
He tricked your sister into working
at his pub, didn't he?
He's scum.
What does "legit" mean?
- Huh?
- Who decides what's "legit"?
Who is the standard
of measure?
Society and the law.
In that case he must be scum.
But he's always been legit.
Ever since I've met him.
What's your connection to him?
I'm a victim of his extortion.
He took 120,000 yen from me.
You a twerp or something?
Oh!
What's your problem?
I'm gonna bash you up.
I told him I'll erase his tab if he
came to my shop 100 times.
Then he really came.
A full 100 times.
He sure did, come to think of it.
Maribu-kun
always made sense.
It's amazing.
He attended a university that
would have him,
he works at a company that would
have him, and hasn't quit.
It's like repeating the same stage
in a game without leveling up.
Even though you could
easily clear the stage.
Also...
the chest thing.
So in other words,
isn't it about chest?
But he was praising Sakama-kun
the other day.
He bumps into many things,
breaks dishes...
gets scolded by a part-time worker,
washes sauce and salt in the sink.
Nobody's like that.
He's not cut out for it.
That doesn't sound
like praise at all.
But he said you're a fighter.
He said you're awesome.
He said he needed to get himself
together too; and became a gardener.
He's not legit at all.
That's because society
is not legit.
That's why he, who is legit, gets
treated like a freak.
Sorry, that was arrogant.
Anyway, now,
the only person who can save
Maribu-kun is you.
Please.
Where's my father during all this?
He's a victim.
Victim, huh? Even when the real
victims are being so kind.
Um...
he's here.
The vibes at work are already
deeply set; they're bad vibes.
And at work,...
I want to get out of that "power-
harassed" image, and yet...
I haven't found a new image yet!
You know...
this image thing...
do you really need to choose one?
If you just be yourself...
isn't it already wonderful enough?
He does make a good
listener at least...
But as a father, well...
Okay.
You should hire movers
to help you move.
That won't be romantic for
newlyweds.
Midori-san rode in the truck
here too, you know.
She had loaded a white dresser,
like a young girl's.
I'm throwing that dresser
away now.
I'm not a little girl anymore.
- I'm home, give me a hand.
- Here he comes.
No, no, no...
you stay seated.
Gosh it's hot.
I want cold barley tea.
I cleared out upstairs.
Use it any way you like.
Thank you very much.
Mother.
I look forward to
living with you.
Oh my, how formal...
same here as well...
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, let's carry the stuff out,
Masakazu.
Let's take a break!
No, it's a lot in the truck.
She's industrious, isn't she?
A call for you,
Yamaji-sensei.
Oh, okay.
Hello, this is Yamaji speaking.
It's Shizuma.
Is there a teacher called
Maruyama where you work?
Yes, he's two desks away from mine.
"What is going on?"
Oh my...
What happened?
Nothing.
So that's how it is...
my battle with you is
now on hiatus.
I'm not battling
in the first place.
You shaking salt to your enemy?
It's "sending salt," not
"shaking."
But really...
He asked for my phone number.
Who did?
What am I going to do?
I need to apologize to you about
something, sensei.
Huh?
It's about my career path.
Oh...
I decided...
to become a teacher afterall.
What?
I'm sorry.
I know I said
I was burned out, but...
I always think about...
the view from the
teaching platform;
the faculty room;
I wonder why?
Maybe I left something behind...
in the 4th grade, class-2 classroom.
Precious memories with
a precious person.
Are you okay?
Hey you! Hey!
Oh, I'm fine.
Sorry to bother you,
I have to go now.
So I'm going to get a
teaching license,
and take the hiring test...
Good job.
Maruyama-sensei,
got a minute?
What the...
That's not me.
That's me.
What's your relationship?
With Ecchan?
Yeah.
We normally play online games...
we sometimes have tea together,
go to karaoke while we talk....
I know your charade. You act all
cute at first as you approach her...
and you nonchalantly touch her; I,
won't allow it, fashionable virgin.
- Wait a second.
- I want to laugh it off,
but I can't and I had to live
with it till today.
My libido and I are in
daily conflict!
What's going on?
I'm a virgin, you're a virgin, but
we're fundamentally different.
Wait a second!
You're assuming that
I'm a virgin, but...
I'm not a virgin.
I've known women, in spite of
how I look.
I lost my virginity when I was 16.
It was with a girl who
was my senior.
I apologize.
Apology my foot.
I'm sorry.
You're a couple of fools.
Sakama-san and Yamaji-san
requested me to be here...
Sit down.
Aren't you settling this out
of court, professor?
What did you...
do to the gardener called
Kitazawa?
Stop it!
Kitazawa-san...
is pressing charges for assault.
You're in double jeopardy.
He rejected
out-of-court settlement.
I'm going to have to fight so you
don't get prosecuted.
Who's paying?
It better not be
Sakama and Yama-chan.
I can't take money from your
victims, you idiot.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
A delivery of Saga-bred steaks came
from my father back home.
What? Oh my!
This is amazing.
This is Yutori.
I saw the news about you.
I know that I'm
in no position to say anything
that could comfort you, but...
I'm writing anyway,
about home,
and recent events.
A new bride has joined the
Sakama family.
It's Akane-san.
She's very fun.
She's radiant like the sun.
She has brought light
into our home.
My bro is working hard too.
My little brother
Masakazu here
will officially be working here, on
occasion of his marriage.
You all know who I am.
I'll draw from my experience
as an office worker,
and mainly support my brother
in business management.
Looking forward to
working with you.
The wedding is planned
for October,
to be held at a Shinto shrine.
I never thought it'd happen, but
Miyashita-kun is retiring.
She's getting married.
Let's congratulate him even
if we don't mean it.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Thanks. Thanks.
This is Aoyama-kun.
She's taking over your Sendai-
branch project job
soon as you leave.
I've always looked up to you,
Miyashita-senpai; it's an
honor to work in your post.
I will do my best.
Oh, sure, knock yourself out.
Sure will.
Oh yeah...
the blueprint arrived...
This is where the elevator
got placed...
Which means the position
of the branch would be...
- What are you doing?
- You scared me.
What? What do you want?
Yutori.
Let's wrestle.
I'm not wrestling.
Come on, let's play.
I'm bored.
- Ding!
- Not "ding."
Come here, come here.
Come on.
Okay.
If any of this fits you,
you want it?
- You sure?
- Yeah. I don't need them.
But they're brand new.
The tags are still on!
The shoes might not fit...
What's your shoe size?
- Akane-san...
- Hm?
You cried in your interview,
didn't you?
- What?
- My bro told me.
I didn't cry.
Masakazu cried during
employee training, though.
He did?
They were split into pairs.
The partners would pinpoint each
others' weaknesses.
It was a self-improvement thing,
at 6:00 A.M. no less.
He must've been hungry
and irritable.
So I told him:
"You're not as cool
as you think."
"Nor are you smart."
"You're a dufus. So you
must improve yourself;"
"otherwise you won't succeed."
Then Masakazu started to cry
while eating breakfast.
You made him cry, Akane-san?
Who knew I'd marry him?
I worked 7.5 years in the office.
It was fun though.
No regrets.
-You're working at a travel agency?
-Yes.
I bet the employee training
will be tough.
But it also looks fun. You can go
to all kinds of places.
Oh, yeah.
You should plan a wine
distillery tour.
Make it super cheap.
With hot springs to boot.
What do you say?
Let's submit the idea!
Oh well.
I'm taking a bath.
Come to think of it,
I've never told you
about the origin of my name.
It actually has nothing to do
with the
millennial generation
(yutori).
Which-will-I-choose?
When I was still in my
mother's womb,
my two older brothers
were thinking about
what to name
their new baby sibling.
"Yutori...
... of God."
"Yutori of God"? What
does that mean?
Mom.
Masakazu said,
the name will be
"Yutori of God."
And that is how...
I became "Yutori."
Is that true?
That's why I'm eternally
thankful to my big brother.
Because if we left it up to God...
I would have been called "Kaba"
or "Baka" instead.
Cut the crap.
Why does she need a passport
to make the birth report?
Maribu, I have it.
You talk about rules.
You'd actually deport a
mother with a newborn baby?
And you call yourself
a Japanese?
My passport isn't fake.
It's real.
It is?
In that case you should've...
shown it right away, dummy.
Children can't choose
their parents.
They can't choose their
names either.
That's why we just have to
believing in...
our parents who had
given us life...
and given us our names.
The same is true of
millennials.
They're the grownups who
gave us life and our names.
So they should take
proper care of us.
Isn't that so?
And soon, it'll be our turn
to shape society.
It'll be our turn to give life
and give names.
Isn't that so?
What the heck...
She's grown up before me.
You're released on bail,
number 127.
What? What?
I'm not getting indicted?
Maribu.
It wasn't me.
Your mother paid the bail.
The case wasn't dropped
due to my inability.
Where is the
immigration bureau?
The report of birth has
been submitted?
At that point she should
have applied
for a staying visa.
She would've received
special permission to stay...
I don't get this whole "special
permission to stay" thing.
When an illegal immigrant
gives birth to a Japanese
child and is raising it,
she could receive a special
permit to stay.
That is, if she had applied
for the permission.
In other words...
she doesn't need to keep
running from the law?
I never heard of such a system.
Nobody taught me that in school
and prep-school.
- Can you contact her?
- I can't.
She doesn't have a cell phone.
I tried buying her one, but
she couldn't get a contract.
They wanted to see her
stay visa.
Or her passport,
and all that.
Stop it, Maribu.
You're out on bail.
Anyway...
all we can do is put out a police
search, or wait till she shows up.
She's not going to show up!
You idiot!
She's on the run!
Maribu, stop that.
Listen to me.
You were at fault too, you know?
You reaped what you sow...
Sorry.
What did you apologize for?
Because I don't have the
right to speak to you that way.
I no longer
count, you see.
Then who else would
speak to me like that?
To me?
You're the only one I've got.
Get your act together,
old man.
Stop that.
It's a civil matter.
Don't give me a
cheap apology.
You can't apologize and get away
with what you have done.
I would've changed you if
you were on rental.
But I can't change you,
so it's maddening!
Because you're the
only one I've got.
You're my father, so speak
to me like a father.
It's your personal issues
that don't count!
You're my father, so act like it.
Because I didn't get choose.
I had no choice!
Yes.
Not "yes." Say it.
Who's at fault here?
It's your fault!
You reaped what you've sowed!
Dad...
You got no right to speak to
me like that, you jerk!
Hey...
Then...
what am I supposed to do, huh?
Is this how you behave
toward your father?
- Help! Somebody help!
- It's a civil matter.
You fool! Fool!
"Due to a party reservation, we will
open at 19:00 today."
What's this party reservation thing?
Oh...
you don't want to go in looking
like that anyway, do you?
I'll go home first.
You can eat yakitori anywhere,
you know.
No, it has to be here.
I promised myself to eat yakitori
here after I got out.
Maribu-kun.
Well. Thanks for your hard work.
Sit, sit.
Store manager, today I'll...
Don't worry about it, it's to
celebrate his release.
Is beer okay for you?
You've done all this...
for my son...
It's not for him.
It's for me and him.
Oh, of course!
Since he's out on bail,
the trial comes next?
Yes. But it's promising since
this was his first offense.
I'm glad.
I was scared of asking
the big brother here...
that maybe it might backfire.
But I'm a professional.
In the realm of the law, that is.
So he says, but you know...
he was visiting every day...
Shut up already.
You're distracting Sakama.
Don't look at me so much.
But this is the last time we'll
see you work here.
The salt didn't sprinkle on it.
Most of it fell to the floor.
What a shame he's quitting; he
had gotten so skilled.
Maybe you can work
here part time.
He's got time, right?
He's got time because it's not
busy right now, that's all.
Wine making gets busy
starting Autumn.
Here you go.
Here.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you.
Tab.
The beer just came.
I shouldn't stay long.
See ya.
Thank you very much.
Listen, senpai...
are you really quitting?
I'm quitting. Why?
Well...
I need a good reason.
It's too vague, I dunno.
You should talk.
That's right.
"kneel down to me" you said
and raised all that fuss.
I can speak my mind too.
If he quits now...
then senpai will just be a
millennial after all.
Some people are
already saying that.
I've gotten my satisfaction.
For 7.5 years...
though I'm just a small fry,
I did the best I could.
I had a taste of hell now and
then too.
I had precious experiences.
I met the best partner ever.
So I've gotten my satisfaction.
From now on, with my wife,
and my big brother,
who's a smaller fry than me,
I'm going to run the small company
to make sure it doesn't
get any smaller.
That's how I'll live out my days.
I don't get it.
Okay.
Since you can't report me for
power harassment...
I'm going to say what I want to
say, once and for all.
Yamagishi.
Yes.
You...
are not as...
cool as you think, nor smart as you
think; you're a dufus.
Stop being such a flake.
Make an effort to
improve on yourself.
Or else you'll never succeed.
Masakazu...
That's all.
Oh!
He's crying.
Yamagishi is crying.
Sir. Would that be considered
power harassment?
"Three months later"
- Of Sakama Wine Distillery,
Sakama Munetaka...
Sakama Masakazu...
will hereby
as sacred distillers,
will with radiant, pure,
sincere hearts...
Wait up!
You're fast!
Yamaji!
Okay, Yamaji is here!
What's all the commotion?
Mori-kun and Muto-kun
sexually harassed Nomura-san.
Se-, se-, sexual harassment?
He said, "say what
size cup is your bra."
No-Nomura-san. You wear a bra?
Yamaji made her cry!
What were you thinking?
It's not too soon for a
4th grader to wear
a bra in 2nd semester.
I'm sorry.
Some will begin menstruation.
You must be extra sensitive.
Letter.
You better assign the
dates.
Otherwise Yamaji-sensei won't
be able to get serious.
No, no, don't bother.
So, the health and physical
fitness class of 4th grade is...
But Yamaji-sensei is still a...
Virgin.
It'll be during the 4th hour,
on Friday.
So, that'll be set for...
October 14.
Okay.
"To Mr. Yamaji Kazutoyo"
Sorry about that.
I didn't know your address,
so I sent it to school.
It'll be on October...
the 15th, is that so?
Right; it's an auspicious day
plus a day off.
Can you come?
- I'm going.
- As the emcee too?
The emcee? Me?
Didn't Akane-chan tell you?
She never did.
But why me?
Why? Well...
I can't ask Aso-san.
Yeah, but...
These are going to be tough
consecutive events...
But I must say,
you haven't changed.
- Same old Yama-chan.
- You think so?
But Sakama-kun, you
have somewhat...
become wild.
You were searching for a nice
word, weren't you?
Oh yeah.
This is from Akane-chan.
Oh, thanks.
Masakazu.
What's the order and inventory
status of the micro-brew beer?
I think my brother was in
charge of that.
Okay.
No, you were.
I'm too busy with the
new wine distillation.
Who's in charge?
But I have to go make
my rounds.
I have the new wine...
But I...
It doesn't matter who's
in charge.
Just make a decision. Now.
Can you run a business without
checking the inventory? What if
we run out of stock?
Then...
I'll be in charge.
And Sakama-san.
Yes?
- "Yes"?
- "Sakama-san"?
- What?
- Yes?
That's from...
being an area manager.
That's right. She's a stay-at-home
area manager.
How's Maribu-kun?
Haven't seen him. He hasn't
replied to my letters either.
Hmm...
How did the trial go?
I couldn't attend
because of work.
Shall we go see him?
I think he still lives in the
same apartment.
No, not today.
I have to go get an order.
Or else my better half...
will gripe at me.
Better half, eh?
You again?
We're not buying.
I brought you bottles of
"Tears of the Demon Bride."
I don't want it.
Welcome.
No, no.
Then can you buy our T-shirts?
We made some.
We don't even want your wine.
Why would we want
your T-shirts?
Get out!
Here, let me help you.
Get out.
"Searching"
- She's a Chinese lady
with baby. I'm searching for her.
Thank you very much.
Please contact me
if you see them.
Please help.
She's a Chinese lady...
Thank you very much.
- She's a Chinese lady...
- Please help.
I'm looking for my baby.
You scared me.
My brother used to sit
there to drink.
I was looking at Facebook.
Whose?
Nobody in particular.
Just wondering how
everybody's doing.
Yamagishi's posts are nothing but
lies, as usual.
We're getting married, aren't we?
We are. Why?
It just doesn't feel real.
You don't want to marry?
I want to. I do, but...
then again...
I felt if I did, I might
become empty.
The moment I feel happiness...
it might end right there.
You won't become empty,
Akane-chan.
You think so?
That's right.
When you become happy...
you will try to become even
happier; that's how you are.
Because you're greedy.
That's why I want to marry you.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
All I ever thought for
7.5 years is work.
I've never known any other
sense of fulfillment.
In that case...
think of it as work.
To become happy.
That is your job.
You can think of it like that.
I am so happy right now.
I'm happy too.
Yikes!
I'm sorry.
What?
What's the matter,
Akane-chan?
What're you doing,
Punch me, then.
Seriously?
Making excuses,
crying...
blaming others...
grownups make
mistakes too.
Sorry. I can't go in the
presence of God like this.
- Masakazu!
- I can't do it right now!
Masakazu!