Yesterday at the opening of an
event in the city,
30 visitors reported nausea after
eating catered bento.
They were taken to a nearby
hospital.
The salmonella bacteria was
detected in the patients.
The cause was expired frozen meat
used by the bento packager...
Hayakawa-san.
You're alone? Where's Yamagishi?
I haven't been able to reach him.
Figures; millennials
just don't grow up.
Take the badge off.
- Is Nogami-san at his office?
- Yeah.
Oh! Hey!
If somebody dies we're both
done for; do you realize that?
I'm sorry.
We couldn't find the person
in charge, so the former...
Did Min Min market frozen meat
and side dishes only this month?
There's also flavor-flakes...
We're talking about the
food poisoning case;
so flavor-flakes don't count.
The issue here is, was the cause...
your company's shumai
or Min Min's chicken wings?
Both were supposedly included
in the bento yesterday.
Chicken wings?
If so, those were used before
the expiration date.
Huh? What are you saying, then?
You're saying it was our shumai?
This is what happened,
Sakama-san...
they didn't all fit in the freezer,
so they naturally thawed out.
- Huh?
- I'm sorry.
We ordered too much, double
the amount of food.
How long's this been going on?
I don't know, let's see...
Hey!
Get your act together old man!
Why did you sell food that didn't
fit in the freezer?
Because I couldn't sever ties
with either company.
Ai Ai and Min Min are both
faithful companies...
You were getting
buttered up.
I heard Min Min would take you to
"naughty" places.
Well, there's no point in raising a
fuss. What's done is done.
Let's talk about the future instead.
First we must make public apology,
explain how it happened,
and respond to the media.
So far it's clear that the cause was
careless food maintenance.
The media will be all over that.
Your relationship to Min Min
goes back quite a long way.
Yes. It goes back to the
inception of the business, so...
it's been 23 years.
Our company's relationship to
you is short in comparison.
My relationship with you
started just this year;
I heard you forced
a contract on us.
We are merely newcomers.
What is it you're trying to say?
To be clear...
our request to you is to not
mention the name of our company.
He's direct.
Excuse me, but we're a
major business.
We have an image to protect.
Of course, I'm not asking you
to do us this favor for free.
Nogami-san.
How much do you currently
owe us?
How much? Well... I haven't
even made a single payment yet.
Approximately 3 million yen.
Our company will not bill you
a penny of it.
Your lawsuit and compensations
to victims will be quite heavy.
It's best if you cut as many
corners as you can.
Shouldn't we find out first if the
culprit was the wing or shumai?
It wasn't us!
We didn't deliver a supply.
Oh man...
this is so soothing...
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
"What are you going to do?"
he asked. That young punk!
He jumped ship real fast.
3 million must be a drop in the
bucket for a major corporation.
How much were we owed?
-Let's see...
- It doesn't matter!
We can't afford to
waive debts owed to us.
I'm sorry.
Come with me.
Yes.
All right, all right.
Come and get it.
Okay.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey! There!
Argh!
Don't mess with me!
I'm sorry.
- Don't mess with me!
- Okay, I'm sorry.
Okay.
Don't mess with me.
Damn it!
I feel better now.
Really?
Of course not!
I'm sorry.
That Nogami-san...
what'll he do after
losing his connections?
Under normal circumstances he'd
take the blame and get fired.
Huh?
The penalty is severe on
the mishandling of food.
His excuse was the supply thawed
because it didn't fit the freezer.
Sounds like my wife.
I sort of...
feel responsible.
That time...
had I listened to Yamagishi
and pulled us out...
"...this wouldn't have happened";
is that what you're saying?
I didn't want to let them
usurp our business...
and I, personally...
wanted a feather in my cap before
returning to business management.
Then my girlfriend got transferred,
There were so many things
happening...
I panicked and did things
I'd usually never do.
As a result I've hurt not only
Nogami-san, but also our
company's name.
Let's go the opposite direction.
Opposite direction?
You have trusted us...
no, no, no...
at this time...
although you had entrusted
in our company...
no, no... we were the grateful
recipients of your trust...
trust... uh... trust...
Our trusting customers...
we have betrayed them.
And of that we deeply express
our apology.
We are very...
very sorry.
Very...
We are paying a portion of the
lawsuit and compensation fees.
But we needn't.
We weren't in the wrong.
Paying though we weren't in the
wrong will improve our image.
Truly. This will guarantee an
exclusive contract with us alone.
Because Ai Ai Foods is
out the picture now.
But still ...
it's a sinking ship.
Nogami is in a desperate situation.
That's why we rescue him, and he
becomes indebted to us.
This isn't goodwill.
It's business. We need him
to recover or it's a bust.
Sakama! Keep a close
watch on Nogami.
His back's against the wall...
There's no telling what he'll do.
And about Yamagishi...
when you reach him, tell him
to write a letter of apology.
Awesome.
I've never seen Hayakawa-san
in-action before.
He's a legendary businessman
in spite of how he looks.
Compared to him I'm just...
slow witted...
all I ever do is
exercise hindsight...
At least you self-reflect, which
can't be said of Yamagishi.
Why is this the only
way I can talk?
What?
Oh, nothing.
What shall we do about my dad?
I am Miyashita Akane's father.
You haven't told him
we've broken up?
He wouldn't have come
if I had told him.
Can I bring him to the
restaurant at 7:00?
Yes.
Ouch!
Don't sigh!
Here's the special skewered
assortment of poultry.
- This is quite a good restaurant.
- Thank you very much.
Maybe they're still going out.
Who's the superior, the area
manager or the store manager?
Of course that would be
Miyashita-san.
In that case, area manager...
may I buy the store manager
another drink?
You don't have to ask my
permission.
Ah yes.
Go on, have a seat.
We don't have a glass. Hey...
He sat down.
He can't escape now.
Why does he speak to you
using polite ceremony?
Why does he call you
"Miyashita-san"?
I'm his superior. He can't call
me "Akane-chan", can he?
He has to use the honorific
"-san" even after marriage?
That's pathetic.
He kept grinning like a fool.
I have no idea what he's thinking.
You want to put on sweats?
It's Masakazu's but...
You lived together?
No. He lives far away, he stayed
when he missed the last train.
What the heck is that?
I don't like the way he
responds to my questions.
Are you the second son,
Masakazu-kun?
That is so. So, so, so.
"So, so, so, so."
Was he telling me to die?
He wasn't making a
pun about death.
He was nervous.
And then...
he fiddled with his cell phone
during our conversation.
If I have to be in Yurakucho at 10,
I should leave the apartment at 9.
A friend from my townhall days will
be at the local-products exhibit...
Get on the train to Ikebukuro
at 9:28,
then change to the JR at
Tokyo Station.
Oh, sure.
Wait, the Yurakucho Line from
Akasaka-mitsuke is 2 minutes faster.
Please board the rearmost car.
Wait, the Ginza Line comes
a minute later...
Wait, if you got off at Hibiya and
walked at 15km per hour...
I can't walk at 15km per hour.
Dad, are you lonesome,
on your own?
Me?
You talk a lot.
Don't you have friends to talk
to in Saga?
Of course I do.
Kazushi comes home
on weekends too.
Anyway...
no matter what you do...
it won't last long.
Sleep on the futon.
I have to drive the school
bus in the morning.
What? You're still
doing that?
You better quit.
It's dangerous.
Voicing your concern?
The elderly are sensitively aware of
when they're being treated as old.
Young people wouldn't understand.
We elderly get treated like so.
So all we ever say are
elderly stuff.
What are you doing there?
Oh...
"Grave of Tanoguchi household"
I called Tanoguchi-san.
I told her you might be going
there, so I asked her to call me.
She said she's thinking of
moving soon...
since the forty-nine days of
mourning have passed.
I see.
Time passed so fast.
I watched the press
conference on TV.
You should've been there
in person.
She scolded me.
I don't want you coming
here all the time.
Sure, I think of you like
a son, but...
you're not my son.
I'm sorry.
The way you habitually pout like
that, you're just like Hiroyuki.
You really should...
openly display your
shortcomings...
entrust yourself to the
people at the office.
The fish!
Well...
I really can't do that. I've already
given them an initial impression.
You disappeared twice on them,
think about it.
For you kids, "you can do it
if you try" is a myth.
You kids "can't do it
if you don't try."
So...
why didn't I say that...
to my son?
Um...
Can I have grated daikon
radish with this?
Thick-skinned.
Here.
Thank you.
I don't know why I can't
be normal.
I'm either up or I'm down.
It's one or the other.
You just need more
humbling experiences.
You and me, both.
The logogram of 'shame' is comp-
osed of 'ear' and 'heart'...
Yes?
'Ear' and...
'heart.'
So?
Well...
I thought I'd think
of something, but...
nothing at all came to mind.
Very!
Very sorry!
I'm sorry!
Oh no... Masa-kun
hasn't done anything wrong,
yet he's bowing in apology.
The number one cause is
- said to be the ingredients of...
- Is that okay?
That necktie...
Look.
The number of victims has
risen to 41...
Oh my.
What...
This is where you start,
Nogami-san.
You have no choice but to
claw your way up.
Yes.
First, daycare facilities and pre-
schools on the client list...
you must go to schools and bus-
inesses, and endure the clamor.
Yamagishi will go with you.
We'll estimate the renumerations
to victim households...
fortunately there were no critically
cases; we must act swiftly.
Yes.
Don't get gloomy on me...
old man.
Show some excitement!
Like when you sang the Matsuyama
Chiaki song at karaoke.
- Yamagishi.
- It's all right.
I'm actually grateful.
But...
why are you so caring to me?
A guy like me. Just a...
bento caterering company's...
soon-to-retire site manager.
Because we accept you
for the man that you are.
That's why...
we're going to give
you the loan.
Thank you.
I'm grateful!
Damn it!
Would you have preferred
a better hotel?
Or would you have preferred that
it wasn't a hotel at all?
Why do you ask?
Because you're so quiet.
My brother doesn't know
a thing about this.
But now that I've gotten hired...
I've been thinking of telling
him about us.
Now you're quiet.
No...
I've been thinking the same.
It's only right.
Next year about now, we'll be
worker and college student.
I've finally landed a job at an
office that would hire me.
I can't ask for more.
Bathroom.
"Rental Man: 1,000 yen per hour"
"Which rental man will
you play with?"
What?
I never thought I'd see you again.
Neither did I.
It's been a month since
I've been going out with him.
I thought things would be more
exciting after I got hired.
But they haven't been?
The proprietor's ideas are novel;
they're beyond dispute, but...
when I think about him, I see he's
just a college student on hiatus.
So we're just a college student and
hiatus-student couple.
Your older brother though,
he's stable.
Yes... huh?
Did I ever tell you I had
an older brother?
No... no, you see. Because
you're like a cute little sister.
So I thought you probably had
an older brother...
Amazing.
Because you see, Aso-san...
- My brother and Maribu are friends.
- What?
There's something thrilling
about that.
And if there was adultery involved,
it'd really get exciting.
Adultery?
Are you okay?
The meeting day...
Huh?
The meeting day. The second
Saturday of every month.
I don't think he'll come, but...
it's meeting day. What am
I going to do?
Meeting day... oh boy.
The father of the boy with
learning disability...
is in denial about the facts.
"It's impossible to be
born with it."
And that's why he's divorcing?
- No, it was because of adultery.
- I see.
Anyway, his coming is going to
test my mettle as a teacher.
He's not interested in
contrary opinions.
Does he even have the right?
He's an adulterer who
abandoned his wife and child.
I knew you'd get it wrong.
What? What's so funny?
The adulterer...
Huh?
...was the wife.
Oh, I see.
Not to mention,
her illicit partner was...
What? What?
What's so funny?
...was the previous school's
homeroom teacher.
I see.
I was serious.
You might think of me
as unfaithful, but...
he became a father-figure
to my son.
My husband and I were
already on the outs, so...
But he was young,
he was passionate...
I gave him my all.
In other words, Nanae
has a track record.
She doesn't regret having been in an
illicit relationship with a teacher.
She's outrageously naughty.
Naughtiness personified.
Yamaji-san, everyone
can hear you.
Anyway, what's it all about?
I've scored zero this
past 29 years.
So why does it suddenly go from
number 1 to number 2?
What do you mean by
"number 2"?
Yamaji-sensei.
It's too fast.
I am Harashima Daigo's father.
That was my old name.
This is Yamaji-sensei,
the homeroom teacher.
You're young.
Twenties?
Yes. I'm 29.
The homeroom teacher at the
former school was no good.
Because my son is fully capable
when he tries.
I'm counting on you, sensei.
Right?
Yes.
I will see you in class.
Do your best.
Are you going to be okay?
Maybe you should change the
study topic.
Good grief...
It's father's observation day. We
couldn't have told him not to come.
He's going to sit in on the
math class, of all things.
Actually, it was Daigo-kun
himself who told him to
come during math.
Isn't that so, Yamaji-sensei?
S-sorry...
my ears are ringing...
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Okay then, Mori-kun.
Yay. Yes.
Me! Me! Me!
All right, Tadokoro-kun.
All right.
Next, Tsutsui-san.
And Nozawa-san.
One more to go.
Me! Me! Me!
Okay then. Daigo-kun.
Yes.
Okay.
Don't sweat it, Daigo. What do you
do when you don't know the step?
You go in order, from 1.
And go on dividing like that.
Right?
And then? Subtraction.
You can do it.
You can do it, Daigo!
Daigo, you can do it!
D-a-i-go.
Wrong!
It's "6".
Dad...
Don't go easy on him.
This is a waste of time.
Please stop.
Look Daigo, watch carefully.
You can't.
But the chime will go off.
And if it does, fine.
Okay, Daigo.
Let's multiply one more time.
D-a-i-go.
He was a locally prominent
government employee.
He totally aged after
my mother died.
The problem is...
he can't come to terms with it.
The light's turning, let's go back.
He was hired as a school-bus driver
after retirement.
But he got in an accident
last year.
It happened after dropping
off the kids.
It wasn't a serious accident but...
Ever since then...
he's been down in the dumps,
reflecting on the chasm between
how he views himself...
and his actual decrepitude.
That's worrisome.
He needs to openly embrace
his faults.
Like that, you know...
the learning disability boy.
You mean Daigo?
Like Daigo-kun.
Because after all...
he got everyone to accept him
even with his inabilities.
I think he has
tremendous courage.
That's true.
Huh?
Your thinking you can get popular
with ladies using kickbacks...
that's what makes me think
you're just an insignificant man.
- I'm sorry.
- When are you guys breaking up?
- Store manager?
- What can I cook for you?
My daughter...
has a boyfriend...
you know, that Insta...
- Instant... Instantmental...
- Instagram, you mean?
Turnips and...
Turnips and
when are you breaking up?
And also... cartilage.
With salt or with sauce?
She's not a foreigner, you know.
There were pics of her
hugging a man.
She posts them one
after another.
When are you guys breaking up?
- With salt.
- Oh, salt. Sometime this week?
- With salt, sometime this week.
- Huh?
And if that's the fruit of my
40 years of labor...
with the sweat of my brow...
it made me feel pathetic.
So I...
just wanted to cut loose.
- Understand?
- I don't understand.
My daughter too...
has fallen for a man.
Hey. Who are you?
Don't butt in.
Father, here is your shochu
with hot water.
"Father"?
- I am Miyashita Akane's father.
- What?
You are?
I better keep my trap shut.
Hey.
But Miyashita-san...
- Hasn't broken up!
- Welcome.
Let me ask you something...
to you guys...
the millennials generation,
our hard-nosed generation is...
repellent?
Excuse me, but I didn't
understand that last part.
Geezers like us that don't know
Wikipedia and gigabytes...
are we repellent?
All I know is "Wikipedia"
and "gigabytes".
We're repellent.
In other words, we're repulsive.
Hey.
You from Kyushu?
Yeah, from Kurume.
Wow.
I'm from Tosu of Saga.
We're neighbors.
Really?
Saga, huh?
What do you want to drink?
I'll get you shochu.
Potato liquor.
Delicious potato.
- Chest...
- That's enough.
Hey.
What's the idea?
This is a public place.
Yelling out loud...
"chest, chest"...
There are those who have
issues with that.
There are those who
are bothered by that.
Sorry.
I'm losing it...
I'm done for today.
Huh?
Okay.
Good job today.
They're here.
Mother.
Hurry, hurry.
Well, well.
Thank you for coming
such long distance.
I am the father of
Miyashita Akane.
I am Sakama Masakazu's
mother.
I am Sakama...
- Masakazu's older brother.
- Please come in.
- Thank you.
- This way please.
This way.
Man, I overslept.
When were they coming?
Idiot.
That's my younger sister,
Yutori.
I didn't put on makeup yet,
I'm sorry.
"Condolences: Miyashita"
Oh my. I was holding my breath.
I know I shouldn't
be so tense.
How silly of me.
Are the older brother and wife
- in charge of the distillery now?
- Yes.
Not even half a year has
gone by since we took charge.
We're very busy.
The distillery...
is always the busiest
from October to March.
My husband was meticulous.
He thoroughly trained the
workers
to distill new wine.
And after that was done...
he passed away in March.
I see.
Yes.
Oh no. Silence again.
We should talk about
cheerful things.
I know. Why don't you
show him the storage room?
Oh yes.
A social science class is coming
at noon for a tour...
I didn't come here on a social-
science tour.
Dad. You're being rude.
My youngest daughter Yutori
from next year is...
I didn't come here for
frivolous banter either.
I apologize. This is
how he talks.
I think it was...
in January the year before last.
She told me she was
seeing a man she was
intending to marry.
It's been two-and-a-half
years since then.
She's of good age now
to get married, and yet...
she's been too busy with work,
and nothing further developed.
I was never introduced to him.
I'm from the old world.
Therefore I believe that
girls, when they marry,
I mean, "women"...
should become
part of a household.
This has nothing to do with job
superiors and subordinates.
Nothing to do with wages
being higher or lower.
Those are separate issues.
A man must shoulder
responsibility.
I hope Masakazu-kun
has the will to do so.
Well of course.
Isn't that so?
That's his intention.
Bro's ears are bright red.
Yutori-chan.
I'm not expecting
an immediate reply.
- Missus.
- Yes?
May I borrow a
brush-pen?
A brush-pen?
Brush-pen... brush-pen...
What are you up to?
Oh, I bought this
gift yesterday
at a department store.
It's a little too soon...
What do you mean?
It's not too soon.
Because, like you said...
he hasn't given
you a reply yet.
Oh yeah.
I'll take the brush-pen,
and write this and that
in the registry.
You can think about
it while I do that.
- Brush-pen.
- Yes.
Oh no, I gave it to him.
Hey, just a second.
Relax, dad.
You're jumping the gun.
Besides, the situation is
reversed to begin with.
The groom's family is
supposed to make the preparation.
- What?
- Yes.
This is all because you're
uncommitted...
That's right, Masakazu.
What are your thoughts?
Say something.
I do love...
Akane-san.
However...
I hate her father.
Idiot!
Because he...
barges in all of a sudden...
He asks about my family,
he asks about my siblings,
he asks about my work; but he
asks nothing about me.
What kind of person am I?
What are my thoughts? Those
things don't matter at all to you?
I'm the one getting married here.
My family, siblings, work,
my surroundings got
nothing to do with it.
Furthermore...
you don't ask about your
daughter's feelings...
what are her concerns?
Yet you tell her to choose work or
marriage, just because she's of age.
I don't get it.
But that, you see...
unless the both of you
get fully committed...
things won't move forward.
Of course it won't move forward.
Because we're not a couple.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
We have broken up.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
What?
In that case...
what are we doing here?
We're no longer a couple
so I'll go ahead and say it...
Miyashita-san was given a
promotion and transfer.
She was at a loss because
I'm the way I am.
- That's not true.
- Let me talk.
I got to hate myself
eventually...
I severed my Achilles' heel...
and finally we decided to
break up for now.
Wrong. Totally wrong.
I didn't want to break up.
What are we doing here?
I wanted to marry you.
Whether I become a homemaker,
or choose to continue
my career...
I was putting the decision off
till later.
I wanted to marry first,
and become happy.
I wanted to become happy,
and...
"Oh no, we're broke.
Who'll go to work?"
That would have been
fine for me.
It's not that simple.
Why?
It's okay for us, but...
what about our surroundings?
I told you I don't care
about our surroundings.
But...
That's why...
that's what I'm talking about.
Forget it.
- Akane.
- Idiot!
Wow...
I had no idea this distillery
has such a reputable history.
Outstanding, outstanding.
When I was kid,
we'd play hide and seek here.
My dad yelled at us for that.
What a nice smell it has.
It could make you tipsy.
Um...
you have come such a long way...
Oh.
It's my fault;
I jumped the gun.
But anyway...
my daughter sure
is strong willed.
I wonder who she took after?
I was hoping she'd look after me
in my senior days...
but it doesn't seem likely.
My life span will shrink.
Oh well...
I'll be going back alone.
I will accompany you
to the station.
Don't bother,
that's all right.
I'd feel awkward,
just you and me.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Masakazu-kun.
When you young folks see
old fogies like me,
do you think to yourselves:
"We've won"?
Huh?
You must feel superior to us.
Whenever we fogies see
young folks, we think
without rhyme or reason:
"We've lost"!
Although I know
you folks don't think in terms
of winning, but...
we, of our own accord...
feel inferior to you folks.
You folks don't know anything yet.
You don't fear what you
don't know either.
Fear...
it's a menacing thing.
We elderly folk call you
the millennial generation...
we make sweeping
generalizations
because we fear you;
we can't look you
straight in the face.
The logogram of
'shame' is...
written with 'ear'
and 'heart'.
Back in there...
when you were
expressing your ire to me...
I felt shame and anger.
My ears turned bright red.
But since I'm young, I have to
experience humbling things;
I have to turn my ears and heart
bright red, more and more.
I have to. Isn't that so?
Hm?
No, never mind.
In appointment of Ms.
Miyashita Akane
on the last day of June, 2016...
has been relieved of her
duties
of branch-management in the
Setagaya district...
and has been appointed
the leader of the project
of development of
the new Sendai branch.
- Thank you very much.
- Do your best.
In appointment of Mr.
Sakama Masakazu,
he has been relieved of
duties
of store manager
at "Tori no Tami"
and has been appointed
the general area manager of all
branches in the Setagaya district.
- I'm area manager?
- That's right.
Our business will revive.
Thank you very much.
Oh. Go to Koenji now.
Everybody from the main office
is a store manager.
But I don't know if I'll
call you that or not...
In any case, whenever we use
the term "store manager"...
we're actually making fun of them.
I look forward to working
with you.
I'm interviewing a part-timer at
4:00, so I'll train you till then.
Yes.
Isn't that your friend,
Yamaji-sensei?
Excuse me! Excuse me!
No, first you ask the customer:
"Are you hurt?"
Are you hurt?
What's the point of asking me?
Never mind. Help
with the orders.
Yes.
Hey, Sakama, Sakama.
Sorry I can't right now.
Nakamori-kun, please
arrange the skewered assortment.
One order of skewered
assortment coming up.
- Store manager.
- Yeah.
Um, the real store manager.
Who cut the turnips?
I did.
The turnips are cut
to 2.5 cm.
Longer, shorter...
shorter, longer...
super longer!
Do it over.
- Yes.
- Hey, hey.
Has Maribu-kun been
around lately?
Come to think of it, he hasn't
been here once this whole week.
Hey, newbie.
- Keep a firm grip on the ladder.
- I'm sorry.
You have a weird
first name too, guy.
Sorry about that.
- Gardener?
- He's an apprentice or something.
Maribu? You got
to be kidding.
He's not kidding!
He said he's going legit...
he abandoned the
bar and all...
he's not there anymore!
What's he talking about?
Excuse me!
Excuse us.
Huh?
I just heard a girl's voice.
She's the new part-timer.
What? Wait a sec...
What? What is this?
I figured I would see you
if I worked here...
and I'd get paid hourly
wages for it.
Store manager, will you
move out of the way?
Excuse me...
Really, though...
what's going on here?
And also, starting July,
I'm the area manager.
So I'm telling you...
I chose work over marriage
this time, but...
it's not that I've
given up on marriage.
I'm an eligible date,
believe it or not.
Sure, sure, I understand.
Think of it as adding to your
marriage endeavors, then.
What?
Going to Sendai?
Not a bad way to look at it.
Like Date Masamune
or something.
Oh boy...
my head...
isn't banging all pistons...
but still...
such was my timing...
to sever the rotten relationship.
Sure.
You know...
he got promoted to
area manager...
it's like he's got me
to thank for it.
That's how it is.
Yeah.
You know...
Yes, thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
Excuse us.
You know...
Woops... huh?
Am I drunk, or...
am I trying to get drunk?
I'm totally confused.
Totally confused.
Maybe you should
have a glass of water.
Appreciate it.
Excuse me. One
glass of water please.
Um, Hayakawa-san.
Don't tell me...
What is it?
I'm sorry.
Hayakawa-san, are you feeling
like it right now?
I'm sort of feeling like it.
Well, me too.
If you want to pretend it was
a joke, I can go along with it.
Now's the last chance.
Now.
I'm fine.
At times like this...
what am I supposed to say?
A clinching one-liner?
I know.
"Let's take a little break here."
You're the last, so drain the tub
after you're done.
What if...
Huh?
I were to get married...
and manage the
distillery the with you...
What do you think?
Never mind.
If you're reluctant to
continue the heritage...
I'd rather shut it down.
Who cars about this
booze warehouse?
Good morning,
Miyashita-kun.
division chief.
There are some things virgins
know more about.
Maribu-san!
What happened?
I'm quitting my job
and getting married.