Welcome.
What? Yutori?
Born in 1987...
and 29 years old?
It is usually referred to as
the first pressure-free generation.
I thought for sure that it would be
my younger sister's generation.
Starting from the 2003
high school fresh admissions,
an amendment to the curriculum
guideline was applied.
- The schools were...
- Public schools.
- Right.
- Five day week?
Right.
That is pressure-free indeed.
(Yutori).
Has anyone said that about you?
Yes.
Just in case, I had attached
and sent the G-Map link...
Even so, on a first visit,
you should meet at the station,
and you should reach
10 minutes earlier. Seriously...
It hurts.
That's why you are called a Yutori!
I thought it meant that I
looked younger than my real age,
and was happy about it.
Since this is the first time, let me
take notes during our conversation.
Second year in the company,...
What was his again?
Yamagishi.
But...
if I'm also a Yutori...
the story is different.
I didn't know the way,
so I took a taxi from the station.
- Didn't I send the map via G-Map?
- I was too busy to check my mail.
Next time, please use LINE.
Good day.
I am sorry to have kept you waiting.
I am sorry, Mr Nogami,
he is the new person in charge...
I am Yamagishi.
Just putting this forward, I am the
type who grows with compliments.
I see.
Although my real
ambition lies in marketing,
being in sales...
and getting a feel from the ground;
from a long term perspective,
it's not bad.
I thought that, for sure,
was a pressure-free person.
Am I included too?
Well...
If your companion is late,
you should go ahead first
to explain the situation.
Indeed, it was hard to tell
who was late.
Sorry.
I'm acting like
a difficult superior.
No, you're not.
- He is not that difficult.
- Really?
Maybe it wasn't a good idea
to refuse the invitation.
- Why did you refuse?
- If I go, I might get told off.
- Really?
- Ah, but...
Yamagishi is even worse than me.
- Is it compulsory?
- Eh?
Do we have to
join the drinking party?
It is not compulsory but...
- Then I shall not attend.
- May I know the reason?
- I feel sluggish.
- Your body?
- What?
- Because they will ask me,
"what happened to Yamagishi".
Sluggish is referring to your body?
Well then, yes, that is the reason.
Yes. Hello.
This is Yamagishi, who
grows with your compliments.
So I pass on the message
as it is and then...
that line pops up again.
That's why you are called a Yutori!
I couldn't stand it any more
so I went home quickly.
I want to do something about these
pent up frustrations,
lately things have not been
going well my girlfriend.
My friends are getting busy too.
Just as I thought
of watching AV at home...
"Rental Uncle"
- What are you doing?
- Sorry.
I got a shock.
All are good.
Malibu beach.
I like it.
Recently...
I have not ridden on it.
The waves.
So this was your deciding move?
Well, I thought that
it was foolish of me.
- You got all out of your chest?
- Well, yes.
Instead, now I'm the one who's
feeling the pent up stress...
We're just getting
to the main story.
- Unfortunately, the time is up.
- What?
2000 yen for 2 hours,
plus 1550 yen for the coffee latte
and BLT sandwich.
The transportation fee is 2000 yen.
- That is expensive.
- Because I came from Kamakura.
May I extend the time?
My next customer is already here...
I have done all I can, so...
He didn't...
He didn't have to say it like that,
right?
Please calm down.
Do you need some water?
But the vice principal...
...told me to prioritize their
training for the sports competition.
The guardians...
...told me that their
study is behind schedule.
The children...
- Do not even listen to me.
- Well...
I do not know who is listening,
so please calm...
If they lose in the relay,
they'll say
it is the fault of the teacher.
Saying that is alright not to be
the number 1,
but the bashing if they lose...
- Isn't that weird?
- That is weird.
Eh, you are still here?
Sorry, I did not
feel like going home.
I got all out of my chest.
- Eh?
- It is just about time.
No, but nothing has been solved.
You can split the transportation fee
with Mr Sakama.
- Work hard.
- Thank you.
Well,
that guy...
only needs someone
to listen to him.
Thank you.
Wait! Oh, sorry!
Wait! Wait!
Does this bus
go to the train station?
The next bus
is heading to the station.
Then I will get off.
Sorry.
The door is closing.
Eight minutes.
- Just now... You first.
- You first. What is it?
Well... Just now...
sorry for showing you
something unsightly.
No, I am the one who was disturbing.
- Do you often use this service?
- The rental uncle?
- Yes.
- Yes, once in a while.
- Was that your first time?
- Yes.
It is better than going
to my company drinking party.
- It was my farewell party though...
- Eh?
I will be working in the shop
from tomorrow.
I was transferred
because my results were not good.
Project, promotion and sales...
I have been rolling from
department to department.
I lied that it was the 49th day
after my dad's death,
and ignored the party.
Are you kidding?
Last month...
...my father passed away.
Sorry! I spoiled the mood.
Not at all.
Oh yes, this is my business card.
This doesn't mean anything, so...
Here.
- I know this.
- Torinotami, the shop at Kouenshi.
Two Yakitori per drink.
100 sheets here
so you can have 200 Yakitori.
- This is too much...
- I planned to throw it anyway.
Do you have any plans after this?
If you are OK,
let's go to that farewell party...
You seem to have plans.
- No, I don't have any.
- But...
Ah, this is...
I've been trying to call my
girlfriend from just now, but...
The number you have dialed...
...is current out of service.
- It's strange.
- Maybe...
...she has changed her number?
Sorry.
What will you do?
I still have tomorrow...
so I am going home for the day.
Could you be...
a Yutori?
Yes, I'm a Yutori...
is there a problem?
WE'RE MILLENIALS.
GOT A PROBLEM?
Masa, get Yutori.
Yutori! Wake up!
- Ah, ouch!
- Sorry, sorry.
You are late.
I told you.
I'll be store keeping from today.
- Need a ride to the station?
- Yes, please.
It stinks.
Ma-Chan, get Yutori.
That kid is having an interview.
Okay.
Yutori!
- What are you doing, wake up!
- I am awake.
Stop calling me Yutori.
Good morning.
Yutori, your resume!
Thank you. I am leaving now.
Ah... wait!
(Torinotami)
Good morning.
- I am Sakama from the head office.
- You came in a suit.
- Ah, sorry.
- Over there.
Everyone from the head
office will be the shop manager.
But I do not know
if you will be called so...
Wait!
In other words,
four weeks starting from today.
Sakura sensei
will be your teacher.
- How about Yamaji?
- I will be watching from behind.
Eh? You're making things difficult!
Yes!
Okay, listen.
Listen to Yamaji's words.
Yamaji is responsible
for teaching Sakura sensei
the method for teaching.
- Thank you for your guidance.
- No,
I am a new comer too.
Be quiet.
Where should you put your hands?
Yes, on your knees.
Then, close your eyes.
Flip the study switch...
on!
Stick the meat and making it bigger
from the bottom towards the end.
Do you know why?
- No.
- Using perspective,
they will all look to be about
the same size.
Petty, right?
Hey, who made this?
- Me.
- Anything wrong?
Nakamori.
How many millimeter is the length of
spring onion for making Negima?
- Well...
- 25 mm.
Long. Short. Short.
Long, Super long! Redo it!
Shop manager, I will
introduce to you the area manager.
How is the inventory?
Eh?
This is my first day here, so...
I am talking about
today's inventory.
Did I say anything about yesterday?
I see. Well...
- I will do that from now.
- How about the sales report?
- Today's report?
- We have not even opened yet.
Of course I mean yesterday's report.
Because I was not here...
So you do not care about the
sales on days you are not here?
No.
Knowing the status of the shop,
solving problems
and bringing results,
these are your duties for sure.
If you cannot do this,
then it is meaningless to
send the staff to the shop.
Sakama is good at sales, right?
I'm not good,
but yes, I am from sales.
The sales department is directly
connected to the end shops.
The result of sales will be
reflected from the end shops.
If the result of end shops are bad,
it is the responsibility of sales.
I got it.
How about in the field
of the internet?
I have some confidence in it.
- Like Facebook?
- Yes.
You have a lot
of internship experiences.
Yes, about ten companies.
- Mass communications?
- And advertisement-related.
- How about publication companies?
- Yes, I have been there.
- The time is up.
- Thank you.
Excuse me.
She values herself too highly.
It was so obvious that
she speaking herself highly.
The way she speak
is also irritating.
There's not an interesting person.
In the past, there was an idiot who
broke roof tiles with his head.
But well,
that is because she is a Yutori.
In contrary, Shimoyama,
although she is not the type
that could answer smartly,
she listens to the lecture
well and could comprehend it.
I see.
It's important to call out
and correct kids,
like Nomura and Mori,
who make simple mistakes
in tests and handouts.
That too, I see.
Only correcting the mistake
they made...
would not make the kids grow.
It is also boring
to teach like this, right?
What could the teacher feel from
the wrong answer?
What could he learn?
You might call it a thrill,
or what makes it worth doing,
therefore...
I see...
- Eh?
- Sorry.
- Eh? Eh?
- No, no.
- Sakura sensei?
Well, no,
Why did I become like this?
What happened?
Yamaji sensei, what have you done?
No, not me...
Was that because of me?
I am fine.
Somehow, I felt so overwhelm.
I could not carrying out
the class according to my plan.
Just when I was feeling all pent up,
Yamaji sensei suddenly told me
so many things...
Did I say that much?
- Did I that that much to you?
- Isn't that it?
Isn't this power harassment?
(Torinotami)
- Welcome.
Hey, Nakamori!
How are the six Negima?
Ah, it burned.
- The sauce...
- That should be salt, all of them!
- Look at it properly, Nakamori!
- Sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry...
- I will change the sauce to salt.
- I beg you not to do anything.
The jumbo tsukune looks tasty.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Yes.
- Thank you.
- Pass this.
Sorry, at this crowded moment.
It is fine.
Don't you feel cold?
Can you turn down the air-con?
- And then, the yakitori...
- Let's order a lot of them.
Because today is
Yamaji sensei's treat.
It's nothing,
because I have vouchers.
Then, I will consolidate the order.
Who wants the jumbo tsukune?
- Here.
Then it will be everyone.
It will be two
sticks per sheet, right?
Sorry. Here.
- That's only for the first drink.
- Is that so?
Of course!
We will be in deficit if we gave
2 sticks for additional drinks.
- Did you say anything, Nakamori?
- Sorry!
Also, the jumbo tsukune is
not included in the voucher.
- Sorry. And the air-con...
- No way.
The temperature has been pre-fixed.
- I see.
- In short,
there is a nation-wide experiment.
No cramming.
No indiscriminate memorizing.
Is 3 okay for Pi?
The learning ability of the kids
decrease when it was applied.
Experiment failed.
Withdraw!
Right, vice principal?
Does that mean that we
were part of an experiment?
Hey!
- Sorry!
- Sorry.
- In the first place, Sakura,
- Yes.
- You,
have never been
scolded before, right?
Of course I have.
Yamaji sensei
made you cried today, didn't he?
- Eh?
- I feel cold.
The air-con is too strong.
Tell your friend.
Yes.
Because I am hated by Yamaji sensei.
There is no such thing.
It is fine. I am not honest,
and I cannot comprehend well too.
- Did you say that?
- No...!
I might became a bit too emotional.
But that is,
because it's my first time
mentoring.
- I don't hate you at all, really.
- Then, do you like her?
Like... like?
- So, you dislike me.
- No, no...
Sorry!
The discounted portion from
the group just now,
the wasted food,
the broken mug and plates.
There you go,
20,000 Yen.
Sorry, this sounds
like we conned you.
That is the regulation
of the company,
is that right, Nakamori?
Please lock the door.
Thank you for your hard work.
Sakama.
Are you alright?
Well... somehow...
It is was really cheap.
It is definitely weird if the meal
of six persons is under 20,000 yen.
Can you stand up?
Me too.
I am just like that
female college student.
I have never been scolded before.
- Do you want to stand up?
- Ah.
You saw that right?
The part-time work leader.
Even though I had failed,
he only scolded the young man.
Even though they were my mistakes.
No,
because you are
transferred from the head office.
In the first place,
nothing was expected
from me and I was not needed.
That's why I'm looked down on...
It is better not to stand up.
There's no way a human who
has never been scolded,
could scold his subordinates.
Here, sorry.
In the past,
I did fairly well
in study and sports.
The teacher was stuck working on
the kids who could not do as well.
Also, my parents kept saying,
"you have it easier than your elder
brother and younger sister".
That was dangerous. Are you alright?
- Hey...
- Yes.
Just now,
I was giving a self-introduction
in a casual manner.
But by generation,
there's that right?
Starting from the third year of
junior high,
there was the 5 day week,
- 5 level assessment and ranking...
- I'm pressure-free person!
Me too.
Though I was not conscious
of it at all.
Me too. I still went to
tuition on weekends.
You went there.
But I am in the common
ranking at the tuition center.
We were told that we are defective
items from the Ministry of Education
Wow, are you alright?
Got into a college,
I thought I would find a good job.
- Salaryman shock.
- Salaryman shock!
It became ice age suddenly!
What was that about!
I have never felt the life
of a pressure-free person.
Sakama!
This is dangerous.
Sorry, can I have some water?
You can't drink.
My body does not allow me to drink.
- Eh?
- Let's go to one more shop!
- Get a lady?
- Let's go home.
Isn't now the time to find a lady?
This time is my turn
to get accompanied.
Have you ever listened to my story?
They told me it is
alright not to get number one.
You listened to that willfully.
Indeed.
If compared with my friends who got
there in the same year with me,
Yamaji.
Let's go to get a lady of
pressure-free generation.
Please leave me alone.
Eh.
Yama... Am I wrong?
You are really Yama.
I am Kobayashi from Fukushima.
Kobayashi of Kooriyama,
do you remember me?
Although we were
not in the same class,
Yama for sure,
joined the skiing club, right?
- Is that so?
- Yes, three years in junior high.
Ah, the one at the ski lodging...
Now you remember?
- I miss that time.
- It was a long time...
That is enough.
No way, I cannot
take Yama to such a place.
V I... V I...
That is alright.
Remember my face.
Turn at that corner, go to
the sixth floor of the building.
I shall go up there first,
I will be waiting for you.
Really?
Make yourself look good!
Yama!
You are from Fukushima, Yama.
Yes, until 18 years old.
After the teaching license exam,
there was an earthquake.
I went there too.
A food manufacturing
factory at Miyagi.
To support the reconstruction.
But at my second
year in that company,
I didn't perform well.
I felt sorry for myself.
During the recession,
the 3.11 incident happened
we were just about
to enter the work force.
Your friend is late.
It is 2 am already.
Seems that he is not my friend.
I confirmed with
my local friend via LINE.
Who is that?
Kobayashi? I do not know him.
That is dangerous.
This is super suspicious!
What is this! Eh?
But you have hugged him
like you miss him so much.
Sorry, he called me with
my name in junior high, so...
The words match at that time.
We are deceived!
How much do you have?
Are you going to pay?
But it costs 120,000 Yen for
one beer and jasmine tea.
If we cause trouble here,
the school might know.
Stop messing around, Yama.
You were the one kept
saying about getting lady.
No way, it is not enough at all.
Only this much?
Ah, the receipt?
Idiot...
Akane!
Wait for me, Akane.
Akane, wait for me!
Hey.
Where is your friend?
He will stay at the comic
coffee shop,
he is a primary school teacher.
By the way,
why did you change the number?
Hah? You should apologize first.
- Sorry.
- For what?
Eh, well...
I will reimburse you on
the day of receiving salary.
Recently I am thinking what if
we are not the same company.
Only meet when we want to,
and hide
when we do not want to.
quarrel about the job,
half of that is a lie.
But, it is alright because
it is the matter of other persons.
Somehow we cannot
take the same day off.
Like a normal couple.
I feel suffocated.
I want to stop.
I should be the one to call it off.
- Why?
- Because...
you have been promoted
to area manager.
You have big expectation and duty.
What is that? Opinion
from whose perspective?
Sorry.
I got promoted
and got to a higher level
in the company.
It has shaken our relationship,
and I don't like that.
Sorry. Sorry.
Because I like you.
So I do not want to
get immersed into job and love.
If that is the case...
- What?
- Eh?
Wait.
- I know what you want to say.
- Me?
If that is the case,
I really dislike that.
That is not the case.
Let's get married.
- That is what I mean.
- Seriously?
Why now?
At a time like this?
I don't get it...
I know.
We are hurt anyway,
so you propose desperately,
even though you are rejected.
Do you know who
or why are you hurt?
That is not the case.
Well.
Indeed, today I am exhausted.
I am not happy even
you have propose me.
I see.
He is not coming?
Of course we are exchanging mail.
Though we also received
the sample of the new products.
But only that.
Afterwards, he did not even
ask about how things are.
Yamagiwa?
Is he into this job?
He is Yamagishi.
Not even once
after I hand over to him?
Yes. Sakama comes even though
you have nothing in need.
- I like the fried chicken rice box.
- Well, you have been helping me.
Do you want some?
Yes, I want.
- Glad you want some. Here you go.
- Thank you.
We are a small company
and we cannot order as much.
I can't say you are trying
to please the customers.
But,
remember the faces.
You take the time to have meal
and chat with us.
If that is the case,
do you want to buy some?
Is that what sales does?
This kind of thought,
maybe old-fashioned.
There is strength that does not
match with the face.
In reverse, the one who contact
frequently, and fawn,
giving strong feeling of
his wish to complete quota,
is pathetic, and people's
impression on him will turn worse.
But, they do not even
remember your name.
Hey, seriously,
I send
sales email to them every day.
That was an email for all, right?
If you type the mail one by one, you
will not have time for your own.
Please leave me alone.
But having so, you will
not win other companies.
Perhaps I should say,
I do not want to do useless job.
Eh? What?
Although it is useless, keep
going back to the customers,
it is a useless job, right?
You do not need to fawn if you have
confidence on your own products.
Having time for the seniority,
how about leap in?
Isn't that good to
open up new rules bravely?
- May be that is right. But...
- What do you come here for?
If you are
concerned with my problem,
I am grateful. But somehow,
it feels like you are
doing private inquiry.
I feel bad.
You said private inquiry.
It is hard, right?
If you do too much preaching.
It will be power harassment,
or moral harassment in this era.
The pressure-free persons who think
like this are spoil by Heisei-born.
- If you were me...
- Welcome.
The usual.
How about my position that has been
away from that useless job.
It appears.
He updated
Facebook during our talk.
"From a gentle senior,
I receive words
that make me grateful.
I am awakened. Thank you.
That was lunch time
at Harajuku."
Welcome home.
I am back.
Do you think I am crying?
Eh?
I am eating Yakisoba.
At this hour?
- Where is elder brother?
- He's ou.
The invitation for sample testing.
There are so many memos of absence.
There is nothing we can do.
- It just past 49 days.
- That is not the case.
After all, they were all
your father's customers.
The network which your
father had built in his own.
Talking about the craftsman,
although that comes to Munetaka,
without the backing called as
father, how will things turn into?
How about you?
You have not talked
about your work recently.
I will tell you when
things become clearer.
You and your temper.
A lot of things happened.
I am in a vortex
of a big company.
I will eat.
I will eat...
Sorry.
It tastes good?
I could not find
Yamagishi, so I call you.
I ordered last week.
170 kg of frozen chicken
leg for fried chicken.
It has not been delivered yet.
Is that so? I am sorry.
No, you have no
responsibility on this.
- This happened frequently.
- I see.
This is not the first time for him.
Who wrote this?
- Good morning.
- We are Torinotami.
- What is this? Toriminzoku.
- I am sorry.
- Correct that.
- Ok.
I will report this
to the head office. Yes.
What are you doing?
It seems to be a mistake
of order at the head office.
Now seems that someone
is coming to collect this.
Wait, not that we
have the spare ones.
Who is the person in charge?
Give me a break.
Sorry, what's your name?
Sales department at
head office, Yamagishi.
May I?
Senior, I did it.
Mistake in taking order.
Lucky that I realized it early.
The delivery truck
will return to collect it.
Eh? What is that?
You should come and collect it.
Eh.
No, impossible.
I also have my arrangement...
Fine, just come.
- Eh, where is that?
- Kouenji
- You must be kidding.
- Your way of speaking!
Things become like this
because of your mistake.
Sorry!
- Sorry.
- It should not be sorry.
Take this, and come with me.
I will let you do the useless job.
- Come over here!
- Yes!
Too bad, it is already too late.
The menu has been changed.
I am sorry.
That's why,
you should come by train.
- It melts, right?
- Sorry.
Two of these cannot be used.
The remaining ones
will be deliver by freezer truck.
- Why are you crying?
- Sorry.
Because of my fault.
My...!
Don't kneel, it is meaningless.
If you make the floor dirty,
it will be the problem of hygiene.
Well, in this case...
Put on this.
I am sorry.
Like you said, maybe we can catch
the time with arrangement via phone.
What are you saying?
I am happy that you come.
Factory like this, people like this,
doing rice-box like this.
For the elders who stay alone, for
caregiving institution,
or for nursery.
You will not understand
without seeing this directly.
The severity of your mistake,
you will never know
this via phone or email.
Yamagishi,
starting from now,
show up more often.
Senior.
Today.
Thank you.
I...
...have just entered
this company for 2 years.
This is the first time
I am properly scolded.
That's why you are
a pressure-free person.
In short, it is not about
talking or scolding.
It is about the heart.
Because power harassment is scary,
you cannot do staff training.
Because he is not an idiot,
you can run into emotion,
- and deliver this feeling directly.
- This is too much.
- Your pace is too fast.
- You want ice with it?
Yama, you have an annoying vibe.
- Eh?
- And you are grinning.
Something I should ask?
Someone confessed her feeling to me.
I have not even asked.
Through this internship,
I realize about my feeling.
Of course, as a teacher,
I should be firm...
I also...
- like you.
- That is not good.
That is not good?
Are you going to
date a college student?
The formality will remain
until the end of the internship.
What is this becoming?
You are nasty.
Deterioration of education.
I want more ice.
- Ice.
- OK...
Sakama, you also get
your girlfriend back.
No, now is the delicate period
of time.
Sorry.
I am getting irritated.
I want to hit someone.
Rather than that,
I am a feminist.
In the first place,
before the public,
what do you
mean by yelling "lady", "lady?
If there is someone
getting irritated,
there will also
be someone getting angry.
The angry one will
not come from Kouenji.
Idiot! That's why you
are a pressure-free person.
What's up?
What are you looking at?
Any problem?
Money...
- Yes?
- Please give our money back.
Please give our money back.
The 120,000 Yen.
Money, 120,000 Yen.
Don't get so loud.
Sorry.
I only introduced the shop to you.
You are the one who paid the money.
Isn't that your own responsibility?
You are not kid anyway.
What is it?
Why do you stand there?
I will beat you up.
I...
Please come to my shop.
Because I have
gone to your shop too.
100 sheets of voucher.
Please come until you spend it all.
I will forget the 120,000 Yen.
Sakama.
I can't, I can't hit him.
We have tried hard.
Yutori, Masakazu,
I will take you to the station.
Good morning.
Masa, your tie?
It is fine to be like this in shop.
- Yutori, breakfast?
- I have no time.
- Midori, can you make some onigiri.
- OK.
Do it yourself.
Midori is not your maid.
I wrote down some points
regarding the lecture yesterday.
You specially did that for
me after you went home?
- It is my job.
- I am happy.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
I am leaving.
Sorry, I am on my brother's car.
Good morning, what happened?
Yamagishi at sales department
was Sakama's subordinate, right?
Yes, when I was still
in sales department.
He seemed to have
a problem with Sakama yesterday.
Not a problem...
Does he make mistake again?
He has resigned from the company.
He sent a message to all superiors
and colleagues this morning.
Did you get it?
I will resign.
I will die. I better die rather than
working with that superior.
Somehow.
This is the first time
I am scolded properly.
Are you kidding, Yamagishi?
Attention please
all passengers.
Right now, as there is an incident
at Musashikokubunji Station...
Seems to be a salaryman who
jumped to the rail.
Give me a break.
Jump. suicide?
Male, in his early twenty.
Yamagishi is dead.
- What?
- Really?
I am sorry.
Listen.
I am here.
We are here for you.
Maribu.
Your friend.
No, we are not...