I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Huh?
What's the matter, Akane-chan?
We've never had
drama between us.
We started work at the same time,
and 7.5 years dragged on as we
got closer, then further, and so on.
What?
I think couples like that may
surprisingly not tie the knot.
What are you talking about?
What's wrong? This isn't
like you, Akane-chan.
You're always so decisive.
And how about you, how can you
be so sure of yourself?
I'm not, really...
It's not like at work; I can't make
a firm decision on personal matters.
We don't have income, you know?
I was prepared for that, but...
In this family business we must sell
a bottle at a time, or we'll starve.
That's why it's fun.
Results are direct, unlike
big businesses.
They reflect our abilities, as well
as our responsibilities.
There are no guarantees, but
it's well worth the effort.
For you only?
Akane-chan.
You want to go back
to work, don't you?
Then you should get
a job at Min Min.
That'll help us out too.
I know you can get rehired.
Or I can ask Hayakawa-san...
You can't do that.
You can't. Besides, I
wouldn't want to do that.
I can't.
Did something happen?
With Hayakawa-san?
You have good intuition at
the wrong time.
I knew something was weird.
He's not coming to the wedding.
Hayakawasa-san was nonchalant
when you quit too.
Hold on. I'll tell you.
I know why he didn't try
to change my mind...
but now I know why he didn't try to
change your mind about quitting.
Just be quiet and listen.
It was as you think.
Excuse me, a glass of water.
I see.
So that's how it was.
What?
Masakazu, it's late, you'll
wake everybody up.
No! No way!
No! No! No!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm not apologizing about
what I did...
well, of course I am, but the
timing for it is off...
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
I'm not mad.
Not completely not-mad, but...
It happened only once, right?
And you were drunk, right?
It was the part of our rocky
relationship when we were separated.
So you didn't belong
to anybody at that time.
"Belong"?
Not "belong," I know you're not
a possession. Sorry about that.
But it was only one time, right?
I didn't do anything, though.
I could have, that would've been
fine, but I didn't do anything!
Are you thinking?
Thinking?
Me?
About what?
About the kind of attitude you
must take as a man.
I don't have that ability.
I mean, really.
What is this?
What were you thinking?
Why have you kept quiet
about it till now?
Akane-chan, what happened?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
I heard sirens or something.
Is there a fire?
Masakazu?
Hey, Masakazu.
Hayakawa-kawa-kawa!
Damn you!
"Hayakawa"? Who's that?
A mystery?
Hey, how dare you show your face
around here!
Huh?
Hey, Maribu!
I'm taking a break.
Get me coffee.
Yes.
Even ex-convicts need to eat.
Yeah, but...
I'm his boss.
Go work elsewhere if
you don't like it.
It's work. Work.
I'll be on a business trip
that day. Sorry.
Is that so?
Since you were our direct superior,
Hayakawa-san,
we wanted you to give a speech
at a our wedding.
Everything okay?
My wife?
No, you.
"My wife" sounds odd.
She's been wanting to
come back to work.
Even while anticipating
the prospect of homemaking,
she seems to be rejecting it.
I see...
So that's what you wanted
to talk about.
Can you lend us your help,
Hayakawa-san,
so that she can get re-hired?
She's so competent...
she could get hired anywhere.
It doesn't have to be us.
I could introduce her somewhere
as an intermediary...
Is that because there is some
shady issue involved?
Shady?
Ouch!
Me?
That's ridiculous.
Is that what she said?
Either way, that's insulting.
Sorry, grandma is in town,
I can't make it today.
No, that's not it...
Did you pay?
I paid. 9,000 yen.
It was an upfront payment.
I didn't know that.
No, no, this isn't good.
Because you said, sensei,
it's where we can be alone.
No, I meant a place where
there are no people.
In terms of a general meaning,
sure, but, I, you see...
I have to say...
the name of the parts
out loud, so...
That's...
Mother?
I'm not your "mother."
Yamaji-kun.
I'm sorry.
I guess apologizing
isn't right either.
I suddenly see the faces of
the kids in class...
I can't do this.
I imagine them asking me
questions in my head.
From Mori-kun, Kato-kun,
Inoue-san; it sounds like an excuse,
but I hear...
"Yamaji. How are babies made?"
They ask me innocently.
You're a good teacher.
Huh?
Um...
what just happened...
About what I had said...
You don't have to become
a good teacher.
Become a good human being.
Was what you said an
"answer song" kind of rebuke?
In other words,
you're saying that I'm
not a good human being?
When is your class?
Oh, the health class?
At the end of the week.
I wish you all the best.
Ouch!
Excuse me.
Hey, Yamaji.
Akane-chan.
What are you saying? What are
you doing, Akane-chan?
Truly...
I can say anything to you. So I
should've confessed it to you.
Well, instead of the main
person in concern...
But still...
it was only once, right?
Here we go.
You too, Yama?
Why do men obsess over the
number of times?
Would "one time" be okay? No.
Once is once. It's not zero.
If once is okay, what if it was once
with a hundred different men?
Excuse me.
Excuse you is right.
It's not a light burden.
The weight of the burden...
even to me, is quite intense.
I had thought I could handle
work and love at the same time.
But I ruined everything
at the very end.
What have I done?
I'm an idiot.
I don't deserve to be happy.
I want to die.
I should be judged in hell.
Akane-chan. Akane-chan.
"We will, we will..."
not "rock you," Akane-chan.
Are you acting this way on purpose,
so I could tell Sakama-kun
that you're down in the dumps?
Because if you are...
you're doing the wrong thing.
You have to tell him yourself.
Then punch me.
Punch me in Masakazu's
stead.
Huh?
Because if he were to punch me...
I'd be so sad I'd die.
- Get out, what'd you take me for?
- A friend.
Oh, yeah. That's true.
Unless I get hurt too,
we can't strike a balance.
I don't want Masakazu to
suffer anymore.
So I thought about it.
How I could get hurt,
without him having to get hurt.
I've been thinking for a while...
Ouch... What was that for?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Was that too soon?
That was too soon. The gong
hadn't gone off yet.
But I got a deep understanding
of your sentiment.
I don't know anymore...
I don't want any more of this.
Are you all right?
I saw that.
That was inexcusable.
That was disgusting!
No, no, no...
What? What's going on?
Oh crap. Did you assault her?
Ice! Bring ice!
- Call the police first.
- No, you got it all wrong.
What's wrong with you?
The wedding is day
after tomorrow!
Oh man...
How could you?
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
It's no good.
I think I'm a no-good human being.
Come on, relax.
Even if she asked me to...
even still...
how could I hit a woman?
This virgin domestic-violence
bastard is going to teach sex-ed?
That's totally crazy.
Aren't knowledge and experience
are irrelevant in teaching
sex-education in elementary school.
Aso-san...
I don't want to get pampered
by you, Aso-san!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I don't need that from you!
I wanted to actually do it,
with the pretext of it being a
reference for sex-education.
I'm a beast.
I wanted to do it.
Okay, shut up. Shut up.
Okay everyone,
take your seats.
So far...
in the health class,
we've learned about our
growing bodies.
Do you all remember
what you've learned?
As to how and when
we begin to develop...
It's different for
each and every one of us.
Okay. How do you read that?
- "Omoharuki."
- Wrong.
I know. It reads: "Choshinki."
Wrong again. The correct
reading is:
"Shi-..."
"shun-..."
"ki."
"Shishunki" (puberty). That's how
this is read.
We will now study about the
respective changes
boys and girls go through
during puberty.
I'm sorry.
It's not that I've forgotten
we're in mourning.
Look.
This was my mother's.
Don't tell Midori-san.
When you reach puberty,
with respect to appearance and
what's inside...
girls grow to become more womanly.
Mother?
I need to go to the restroom.
Oh. Sure.
Okay.
Ouch!
Ouch.
And boys grow to
become more manly.
Chairman. Thank you for
everything today.
Thank you very much.
Um, uh...
this is a wedding, isn't it?
Where are the candles? The cake?
- Where's the champagne tower?
- For generations now,
we have done orthodox Japanese
Shinto ceremonies.
I never heard about this.
What is this, a Yakuza
naming ceremony?
Oh. Miyashita-san.
A Yakuza!
This is Akane-san's father.
This is...
the master of ceremony
for today, Yamaji-san.
How do you do?
This is my oldest son, Kazushige.
It was only till yesterday...
boys and girls rolled in mud...
and played together.
But the man and woman
start becoming aware
of each other,
as a person from the opposite
gender.
That's what puberty is.
It is a very natural thing.
And for the purpose of growing,
it is a necessary thing.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Sorry.
I can't go to the divine
sanctum like this.
Boys become more manly.
Girls become more womanly.
Each follows his or her
respective path...
and becomes a grownup.
Because...
Akane-chan was the only one
that got hurt.
But I'm hurt even worse.
I don't want to pretend to have
the upper hand
over something that stupid.
I don't want Akane-chan to feel
bad over that.
Sorry...
In any case, I can't do this now.
- Bro.
- Masakazu, stop!
Masakazu!
Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for waiting.
Here is your chilled sake.
Thank you.
I'm not lying.
I'm getting ready to leave
for the business trip.
I didn't know how to get here,
I took a cab from the station.
- Hanakawa-san!
- Yes.
For 7.5 years at work,
I had always looked up to you.
Your rational judgment,
your passion for work.
Sometimes you were gentle,
sometimes you were harsh.
I am sincerely grateful
- for your mentorship.
- Yes.
Therefore...
- Let me punch you once.
- Yes. Huh?
Thank you very much!
Wait.
Wait!
Wait, Sakama-kun!
He ran away?
- This is the pamphelet...
- What is that?
- Was it Akane-chan?
- No, it wasn't.
It was Masakazu.
Hey, Aso-san, you're here too.
What? What's going on?
Sakama-san...
got cold feet.
Wait!
Seriously...
Wait up!
- Welcome.
Thank you for waiting.
Welcome. May I take
your order?
Rice wine...
please.
What? What's going on?
Who knows! He suddenly dashed
off toward the station.
Huh?
Brides getting cold feet,
is something I've seen
in movies and what not...
but I've never heard of
grooms ditching.
What are we going to do?
The exchange of vows is
at 1:00 o'clock, isn't it?
Will it be canceled?
Of course, she can't get
married alone. Where's her dad?
Midori is distracting him right now,
it'll be a big fuss if he came here.
Madam. Hasn't the taxi
arrived yet?
Oh, sure. It should be
here soon, I think.
Ouch.
My stomach hurts.
Your stomach?
I have to go to the bathroom.
Akane-san!
Akane-chan!
What are you doing?
I'm doing it. I'm going to exchange
vows by myself.
You can't do it without a groom!
I can't give up
until I do it.
Give up?
I can be the groom's stand-in. I've
done it 4 times. I have experience.
Akane-chan!
Don't give up!
I will go find him and drag
him here!
Let's go!
During puberty,
hormones from the brain affect the
body to make various changes.
Okay, okay.
Women... become rounder.
And eventually, they begin
menstruation.
Thank you for waiting. Here
is your chilled sake.
Ouch!
Sorry.
It is a preparation for having and
raising a baby.
Two drafts...
- Excuse me, one chilled sake.
- One chilled sake.
The probability of new life
being born is...
approximately one in
one-hundred million.
In other words, birth is mostly a
random event.
Hey customer. That is
a small plate.
Sorry. Sorry.
You have no manners for a
Japanese person.
Welcome.
And if that random
event didn't happen...
One draft.
An order of beef platter.
Everybody here...
would not exist in this world.
One beef platter. 330 yen.
Yuka-san.
You're Yuka-san.
I'm Sakama.
Maribu-kun's friend.
I'm Yoshida. Yoshida Yoshie,
a vocational student.
No, wait a second.
Let go! Power harassment!
No, no. I'm Maribu's...
- Store manager!
- This is not how it looks!
Yuka-chan!
Maribu!
The baby just fell asleep.
Sorry. I explained it, but...
I don't understand what
he's saying.
This guy is awkward.
Yuka-chan, why did you run away?
Because if you got arrested,
I would get arrested too.
Because I've overstayed.
But it's okay. We submitted a
birth report.
As long as we did that, you can get
a special staying permit.
In other words, you wouldn't
be sent back to China.
- Even if we're not married?
- Even if we're not married.
What in the world?
Japan is lenient.
I thought I'd feel better
if I punched him.
That superior at work.
But I felt even more powerless
after that.
First of all, that's the first time
I'd ever punched anybody.
It still hurts. Maybe I broke
a bone.
It's not broken.
At the same time, a part
of me feels turned off.
I've been thinking it through,
just like Akane-chan said.
As to what kind of attitude
I ought to take...
- Go hail a taxi.
- Huh?
Continue.
Anyway, I...
don't know how to
face Akane-chan right now.
Hey, what the...
Uh... we're passed the time, but...
please wait just a little longer.
What is this?
The groom isn't here...
there are very few friends...
the master of ceremonies
is a virgin...
Who else is coming?
Huh?
Hey.
It's you?
This is inexcusable.
My sister is a laughingstock!
I think Sakama-san
has backed out.
What? What the heck?
That's something I would do.
I am very sorry.
My family and workers
are looking for him as we speak.
We have not come here from Saga
to get shamed.
Madam. I had thought
the boy had character.
I had thought he speaks frankly,
in spite of how he looks.
However, my judgment
was an over-estimation.
Anyway, I am taking my
daughter home.
So... are we canceling?
Um, perhaps I should
tell everyone...
Sorry to bother you, but
something's going on.
The bride is receiving her
congratulatory wine.
Akane-chan?
The groom's not here,
what are you doing?
Knock it off, for crying out loud.
We heard everything you said.
So now...
we shall begin the
wedding ceremony...
of the Sakama and
Miyashita households.
Um... as the representative
of both families,
Father of the bride, Mr. Miyashita
Shigezo will address us.
On second thought, maybe he
shouldn't. The mother...
as you can see...
the groom, Masakuzu-kun,
is currently not
where he should be.
However,
do not worry! He will definitely
show up; for sure!
He's not, you know...
an irresponsible man.
Let's have a drink for now.
Then I will leave the
drinking lead up to Nogami-san.
All right, Nogami!
Draw it out.
Draw it out as long as you can.
Sure, sure.
That's a tall order.
Well...
the skirts of women,
and speeches...
ought to be short; so they say,
so cheers.
Cheers.
Maribu. Seriously.
What the...
Store manager!
Long time no see!
The groom has arrived!
Masakazu! How could you
be so foolish?
Hey, all of you.
Leave the hall for now!
What is this?
You dare crash my daughter's
precious wedding?
It's her precious wedding, that's
why I'm telling you to step out.
The two of them need to talk.
Hurry up! Don't just sit there,
scoot!
Or maybe the two of them
should step outside.
Yama-chan.
You're smart.
- Okay ugly, step outside.
- You mustn't say 'ugly,' Maribu.
I...
I want to marry Masakazu-san!
I have never been
more embarassed...
more sad...
more angry...
more forlorn...
in my entire life.
And yet,
I didn't...
I didn't leave my spot,
I endured, because...
I want to be...
Masakazu's...
the Sakama family's...
bride.
Don't cry, ugly.
- Your makeup will run.
- Maribu-kun.
I was taking marriage lightly.
I don't ever want to
feel like this again.
If I cannot marry Masakazu...
I vow to be single the
rest of my life.
I don't ever want to go
through this ever again.
If it weren't you, Akane-chan...
I could've never come this far.
I wouldn't have done it.
Me too...
I vow that I will never marry
anyone but you.
My legs are cramped.
Get this thing off me!
Erm...
The sealing kiss! Wait that's
a different kind of ceremony.
The exchanging of rings.
The rings...
Congratulations!
So...
is there such thing as a
perfect grownup?
I wonder about that.
For example, I am turning
thirty next year.
To all of you, thirty years old
sounds like a real grownup's age.
However,
twenty years from now...
Twenty years from now,
for all of you...
When you all turn
thirty years old,
you will surely
think the this:
"I am still such a child."
"So this is how Yamaji was?"
"I have no girlfriend."
"I hate my job. I'm still a virgin.
I'm like Yamaji!"
Yamaji has gone berserk.
Now all of your moms
and dads...
are they perfect grownups?
They oversleep sometimes,
don't they?
They get drunk and argue, don't
they? They rip farts, don't they?
Different from the body...
the puberty of one's mind...
will continue as long
as you live.
Therefore...
grownups make mistakes too.
They get lazy. They run away.
They lose their way.
It's a dead end, isn't it?
This place is
totally confusing.
They make excuses.
They blame others.
They fall in love with people
they shouldn't fall in love with.
It's all because of puberty.
Okay!
Here goes.
I'm here now.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I got lost
along the way.
Hey there...
You're here, Sakama-san!
Never mind that, just get
into the picture.
Please.
I see.
- Sorry about that.
- Okay, here goes.
Okay.
Grownups make mistakes too.
They can't help it.
So...
please become a grownup
who can forgive others' mistakes.
That said,
we conclude the
sex-education class.
Rise.
Bow.
Let's play, Yamaji.
Let's play.
The mackerel is cooked.
Okay.
Mackerel...
Akane-chan, please go
wake Yutori up.
Okay.
Yutori-chan.
Get up.
You're starting work
next month, aren't you?
Okay.
Good morning.
Good morning. How are you?
- Good morning.
Akane-chan, tie my tie for me,
I can't remember how.
I haven't seen you in a
suit in a long time.
Start.
All right, I got this.
- I know all of it!
- Be seated!
Okay.
Business manager... eh?
I brought my company's
newest product today.
Could you add this to the
inventory in all the
Tori-no-tami store across
the country?
"Millennial People"?
You added one character and
made it look like a collaboration!
Are you talking about an
exclusive contract?
Is that so?
Yes.
Please give it a try.
What is this... this is a
little too aggressive.
Yamagishi.
I shall test it out.
Okay.
I have written it.
And this one too, please.
Why is it me? I mean I can, but...
Thank you very much.
Even if our wedding anniversaries
are the same...
we're still not friends.
I'm a witness he said that.
Can this guy do it?
- He's a virgin, isn't he?
- That shouldn't matter.
Anybody want a refill?
The ever popular "Millennial People"
is available at a bargain price.
Yay, this is our sake. For
millennials only.
I can't drink anymore.
I will.
Oh yeah, look at this.
"Certificate of passing law exam:
law dept., Michigami Maribu"
It took me eleven years,
and I can only go to a university
that would actually let me in.
So you're a college student starting
spring, in spite of how you look.
I'll be job hunting soon enough.
How's your sister?
Yeah.
She's doing fine.
When you talk of Maui,
you're talking sunsets.
A nice offshore breeze was blowing
the last time I went there,
and the northshore and sideshore
were both totally attractive.
Lots of temptations.
So this one here, it's
"Four Seasons"?
I'm sorry.
I don't understand a
word you're saying.
Guess who came for the teaching
internship this year?
After all the bad attitude he'd
shown...
what the cheek!
But he acts as if nothing
had happened.
Looking very forward.
He's a true millennial.
I tried to focus more energy
on my business, so
I gave a hiring tests, but...
Don't tell me...
So your hobby is wine tasting.
Yes, my dream is to go to
wineries in all 47 prefectures.
Is the baby coming,
Midori-san?
- I think it's coming.
- What?
- I'll go get my brother.
- I'll call an ambulance.
- Ouch.
- I am...
a feminist, so...
That's a true millennial.
So, did your sister
have her baby?
It's a boy. He's so cute!
Sorry to bother you,
- but we're closing shop.
- How much do we owe?
I'll pay.
- Come on, witness to the wedding.
- No, really.
I only have 3,000 yen.
- Then let's split the bill...
- The tab has already been paid!
Good night! Let's
drink together again.
What the heck...
show off.
Thank you for waiting.
Um... I'm going home.
Really?
- Excuse me.
- Is that so?
Be happy.
- You too.
- I will.
See you.
Let's get going.
Let's help out with the washing.
- Here.
I'll hold that.
This too?
Take this too?
Alright.
"We're Millennials. Got a Problem?
'Millennial People'"
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.