Yamagishi from Sales Dept. was
Mr. Sakama's subordinate, right?
He said he's going to resign.
- "Suicide?"
- "Male in his early 20's."
"Oh, he's alive!"
Big bro! Big bro!
- I'm sorry about that.
- What's wrong?
Hey, Bro!
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Due to an accident involving
human casualties
the operation
is currently suspended.
(Notice)
Excuse me, where's
the man who jumped off?
- Do you know each other?
- He's my subordinate.
No, I mean there's a possiblity.
He was taken to the hospital.
(We're Millennials, Got A Problem)
"I'm going to resign
from the company."
"Thank you very much. Seriously!"
"I'll die! Working with such
superior will put me to death."
Hey! Where's Yamagishi's table?
It's here.
The computer provided by
the company was left in the office.
The data inside was erased.
But why use LINE out of all?
For argument's sake,
he could have sent email or--
No! There was not even an email!
(Surgery in progress)
Are you a relative?
Well...
What is it?
Were you able to identify?
No, not yet. The person over here...
I have not been able to contact
my subordinate since this morning.
Please go inside and verify.
No.
- Come on. Don't say "no."
- No, I can't do it. I'm sorry.
Doc.
Were you able to identify?
Here's a family of the deceased.
It's the mother.
Unfortunately, just a while ago...
Please go inside and verify.
Finally, I'm able to reach you!
Is it okay to talk to you now?
Huh?
Are you crying?
Yamaji is dead.
What should I do?
What? Who?
My subordinate in the company.
The guy in his second year.
I mentioned about him last time.
The guy you gave sermon
for the first time?
That's right.
Yamagishi from the Sales Dept.
He jumped in front of a train
and died just now at the hospital.
What? Sorry, hold on a second.
Sorry about that. Come again?
Was it on the news?
That's right. That's Yamagishi
from our company.
Oh no, what should I do?
Are you sure?
He's dead. If he were alive
they wouldn't say
"Are you a family of the deceased?"
That's not what I mean.
Could it be someone else?
It's Yamaji!
Really? Did you verify it?
Someone who looked like his
mother is verifying now though.
It must be Yamaji
'cause he's a salaried man
in his early 20's.
I can't even reach his mobile phone.
'Cause it was quite out of his
character to do such a thing.
Yamagishi, what should I do?
- What?
- Yamaji.
What did I just say?
Well, sometimes you said
"Yamagishi." Sometimes "Yamaji."
I'm sorry.
It's okay. Yeah, I thought
you were confused.
Why didn't you say that, Yama...
Yamaji.
You kow what, let's calm down.
Well... We still don't know
if it's Yamaji--
I mean we don't know yet
if it's really Yamagishi or not.
- Sorry, I've got an incoming call.
- What?
We found Yamagishi.
What?
He updated his Facebook account
just a while ago.
It says that he's at an aquarium
watching the arowana cozily.
- Shall we "like" it?
- What?
Excuse me. He's an office mate
of your son.
- No, I mean--
- I'm sorry.
Hiroyuki has caused so much trouble.
No. Well... Actually, Im--
He used to say that he
enjoyed his work so much.
He said that to have no day off
was proof that he was needed
in the company.
Come to think about it,
he didn't want us, his parents,
to worry about him.
He was such a loving son.
- Madam.
- Are you his mother?
I'm Hidaka from
Sunshine Trading Company.
With regards to your son,
please accept
our sincere condolences.
Likewise, I'm Eguchi,
Promotion Division Manager.
This is Attorney Takahashi,
our corporate lawyer
and the person in charge of
your son's insurance--
I'm Ishibashi from Sontoku Japan.
My condolences.
The incident this time is truly...
I felt sorry...
for the mother.
She hasn't sorted out her feelings,
yet people came one after another.
I guess there's a manual...
on how to handle matters when
an employee commits suicide.
It was super sweatshop.
But good for you
it wasn't Yamagishi.
I'm sorry. That was inappropriate.
Same here. Sorry for calling you
by the wrong name.
Honestly speaking, I felt relieved.
Since we're not related,
all the more I was able to be
objective. How should I put it?
It was like watching a play
titled...
"If your subordinate
commits suicide."
We'd like to start inquiring
immediately into the matter
whether there were any demand for
harsh labor, excessive instructions
and power harassment.
Then, we shall report
the result to you.
After that...
I think the guy named Goto who was
standing absent-mindedly
and gave me his name card
is his direct superior.
Well, I think it was someone who
was in my position for Yamagishi.
The reason why I thought
that way was because...
he was the only one...
crying.
If you think about it, the big shots
and lawyers who were bowing
don't know anything about
the guy who committed suicide.
That's why they could talk about
money in a businesslike manner.
Anyway...
when I imagined that
it could have been my role
I'm really glad that the one
who died was not Yamagishi.
Having felt that...
I was relieved, but...
I also felt a sense of guilt.
Somehow it was unbearable.
By the way,
did you call this morning?
Oh yeah, that's right.
I came across that guy.
The pimp in Koenji.
The pimp who lures you
to get ladies?
That's right. Believe it or not...
Who do you think he was with?
You mean he also uses
Uncle-For-Rent?
Is there such a coincidence?
Well, our case was
a coincidence though.
Then, I thought about it.
The pimp who calls himself Kobayashi
called me "Yama," right?
Yama, as far as I can remember.
You were at a ski club, right?
The high school you graduated from
and ski lessons you took
are personal information, right?
I wonder where such
information leaked out.
And the person that came to mind
was...
Mr. Aso.
Weren't you asked to fill out
your profile at your first meeting?
Yes, I was asked to fill it out.
I also talked about my addiction to
ski during my high school years.
I remember Mr. Aso was taking notes.
Hold on a second.
You mean the two are accomplice?
Or...
they buy and sell information
for certain purposes.
That's impossible!
I can't think of anything else.
It's true, I didn't tell anyone,
not even my co-teachers.
No matter how you think about it,
there's no one else, but him.
A lady for you, Mister.
Don't you want a lady tonight?
Oh dear, this way goes to the ladies
Would you like to get one?
Bro! Bro!
There you go!
I'm terribly sorry!
No, no, no.
- What? Parent and child?
- It can't be true.
Well...
When he entered senior high school,
I got a divorce.
Since then, I haven't
lived with him.
He only comes to me
for allowance sometimes.
You mean he sneaked a look at my
personal information on his way?
Most probably. Well...
When we met last time, in fact...
he was there.
Once they lose in a relay,
they'd say it's my fault
even if they said it's okay
not to be number one.
Since you're a regular customer,
Mr. Yamaji,
when you had a near miss
with my son...
How should I put it? He thought
it'd be easy to deceive you.
And so I think he had an eye on you.
I'm terribly sorry!
Please accept this.
Please tell us more in details.
About my son?
About yourself too, Mr. Aso.
- Is that so?
- Are you fooling around?
No, of course not.
Well...
first of all...
Aso is...
a fake name.
My real name is Michigami.
Originally, I run
a real estate business.
During the heyday of
the bubble economy when I was 30,
I put up the company.
Now...
by using that experience,
I'm registered as "Uncle-For-Rent"
on top of my normal job
as a freelance corporate advisor.
You're comfortably free
from worldly cares, huh?
- Not really.
- What about your son?
Maribu Michigami, just like you two,
was born in 1987.
He's a first generation millennial.
When he was in high school,
he was called a prodigy.
He passed first on the list
on the entrance exam
at a prestigious private school.
It's just that ever since
the divorce,
my wife's unreasonable expectation
had caused too much pressure on him.
Is he the only child?
Yes. No. Yes.
Is it yes or no?
It's such a shame,
but I got married again.
That's young.
Yes, he was only two years old.
I was referring to your wife.
Ah, this one.
As I've expected,
she was born in 1987...
- A millennial.
- First generation.
I decided to name my son Maui.
It was the place...
where I first met my wife.
It was a memorable place.
Anyway...
this one.
Please don't say anything
and just accept it.
It's illogical to ask the parent to
make up for the mistake of his son.
Besides, he's not a kid anymore.
I'll settle this matter on my own.
Please give me your son's contact.
I can't disclose
such personal information.
Are you still protecting that guy?
If you're the parent, why don't you
give that scum a good scolding?
- Mr. Sakama.
- He's scum, right?
Myself, Yama and your son too!
No, 'cause...
But everyone is different.
We're all scum, but each of us
are different scums.
Don't use the one word
"millennials" to refer to all.
If you have time to earn extra money
by giving advice to young people
and feel that you understand them,
why don't you at least
scold your son properly?
Excuse me,
I've got other things to do.
You're late!
I'm sorry.
- You wouldn't mind a coffee, right?
- It's fine.
Was it your first time to receive
a wrong order yesterday?
No.
There were several times
before that.
It's for recording purposes.
Please continue.
Everyone makes mistakes.
The thing I found questionable
was...
Yamagishi's attitude as a salesman.
I don't want to do dirty work.
Huh? Dirty what? Come again?
To make rounds of customers for
the hell of it is dirty work, right?
That's terrible.
Here you go.
The problem is...
no one tries to call his attention.
I mean, no one educate
nor can educate him.
I thought that such mood
is not good for him.
Do you really think so?
Didn't you unilaterally
attack on impulse?
Watch your mouth!
Because of your mistakes,
this is happening!
At that time...
Yes.
But I thought...
he wouldn't notice the seriousness
of the matter unless it's enforced.
Bow your head together.
It feels like I was scolded
properly for the first time.
Then, "I'll resign from the company"
"Jekyll and Hyde".
Then, on LINE he said "Working with
such supeior will put me to death."
We're also millennials...
but there were still scary seniors
who guided us strictly.
Our generation is on the borderline.
But in their case,
they've never been scolded.
I mean they only learned
ways not to be scolded.
That's why it's the end
once they get scolded.
Is that a bash against
the next generation?
No, that's not what I mean.
You say it's because they were
born in Heisei period or
they're millennials and put
all blame on the generation.
Isn't that a mentality of
denying individuality?
No, it's not!
You were severely bashed
by the older generation
and you're going to repeat it to
the younger generation as well?
Well, well...
Anyway, Sakuma,
can you go on leave for a week?
What?
You're suspended.
Why me?
It's just a formality.
So the company won't be criticized
for not doing anything.
It was sent from my hometown.
It's Saga Beef sirloin steak.
Wow! Amazing!
How would you like your steak done?
Rare? Medium?
Hey, Martin.
It doesn't matter.
Oh yeah! There'll be a three-day
weekend, right?
Shall we go somewhere using our paid
leave? To hot spring, perhaps?
Or would you like to
check out a property?
There was a nice one
in Kichijoji. 2LDK.
Stop dwelling on it. Hey!
What do you mean
"It doesn't matter?"
This is my house.
Now is our time together.
There's nothing more important
than the doneness of meat!
What do you think
I should have done?
If you were in my shoes,
what would you do...
if you received complaints
from a regular customer
because of mistakes
made by your junior...
who doesn't take his work seriously.
It wasn't right to yell at him.
Besides, it didn't do anything good.
There's no right answer.
Just leave him alone.
If he keeps on making mistakes
and gets the contract terminated,
it's his mistake.
It's the company that
will suffer the loss.
- I thought he died.
- Huh?
Yamagishi.
I thought he jumped
in front of a train.
I regretted it at once.
After scolding a junior
for the first time,
he died the following day.
It wasn't him though.
But people die just like that.
Then, the one who killed...
I didn't kill him, but...
I'll keep on living...
while dwelling on it.
Then, people will console you
that it wasn't your fault.
And eventually,
you'll feel that way.
When you thought that
everything will be fine,
somehow you'll get scared.
- Akane.
- Huh?
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
- What?
- Well...
I just remembered I had a classmate
back in senior high school who died.
We were not particularly close,
but at the funeral,
I was pissed off with the people
who wailed in sorrow.
The guys who actually bullied him
didn't even show up.
Watching such funeral full of
unrelated people crying...
I though, I didn't want to die.
I don't know what else
I wanted to say.
You'll be fine, Martin.
You're the kind of guy who cries
even if you're not related.
What do you mean?
I'll have my steak medium.
Hello?
Sir...
you gave away discount coupons
again, didn't you?
Somehow a strange person
lingerd around.
He said, "I won't order
until Sakama arrives."
Martin, the bike key. Here you go.
Thank you.
(Discount Coupon)
Thank you very much.
(Store Manager)
(Sakuma)
What's that sense of intimidation?
Are they yakuza?
- You idiot!
- Ouch!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Check, please.
- That's it?
- That's it.
I also thought he'd beat me up.
Don't tell me...
he intends to use up
all the 100 yen coupons.
So that's why he came
the following day too.
- Draft beer.
- One draft beer!
One draft beer!
You're suspended, right?
I heard you're currently suspended.
- Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Table number three is ready.
Okay!
Check, please.
(1,000 yen)
- Draft beer.
- One draft beer!
One draft beer!
I'll have a draft beer also.
Buy your own drinks! Come on!
Hey, Nakamori!
After all, I didn't confine
myself at home.
I go everyday to grill two sticks of
yakitori only. What about you?
I'm sorry. Excuse me,
but I heard my son has been
disturbing your restaurant.
We just finished talking about that.
What?
By the way,
what do you intend to do?
At that point when your son
took the personal information
you're no longer convincing
as Uncle-For-Rent.
I'm really sorry.
Certainly, it was easier to vent out
to a complete stranger.
If that's the case...
why don't you just request
for someone else?
- Well then, please change.
- No! Could you please consider it?
I really regret what I've done.
I don't feel like asking for advice
from someone who's soul-searching.
- Welcome to our cafe.
- Thank you.
The usual, please.
I'll do it though.
What is it about?
The trainee in question?
I also...
like you.
- What?
- You're in love with each other.
Yeah!
After the training, I intend to
officially ask her to go out with me
- Yeah!
- Yesterday...
she walked pass me like this.
Maybe she felt cold.
No, she was avoiding me
'cause she went like this.
- Did you see it?
- Of course not!
Before I could,
she covered up like this.
Maybe you tried to look at it?
What the hell. Don't interrupt.
Maybe she got too conscious
and things got weird.
I'm not sure 'cause
- I have no experience.
- No experience?
If she's trying to avoid me,
I should give up, right?
Did you say you have no experience?
Never mind that. Just casually
ignore it. What do you think?
In the first place, she was the one
who confessed her feelings.
What? You have no experience?
- Darn it! It was almost ignored!
- Does it mean
you've never dated a woman before?
Well, yes.
It wasn't particularly necessary.
Instead of wasting time on
a relationship,
I'd rather spend it for myself
like reading books for my knowledge.
Got a problem with that?
- I see.
- You were about to say asexual.
I can tell by the movement
of your mouth.
Don't summarize it
in such a cheap word.
Yamaji! Yamaji!
By the way, you were about to say
"virgin" earlier, weren't you?
Oh no.
Well, well, Mr. Yamaji.
I don't mind at all.
I happen to reach this age while
thinking I could do it anytime.
Got a problem with that?
(Muneyasu)
You'll catch a cold. Get inside.
Here.
Try it.
As I've said, liquor is...
(Honki Shibori Beer)
Local beer?
We've asked a consigner to make it.
After all, it's beer for the summer.
Does Mom know about this?
Nevermind that. Just drink!
If I do the same thing Dad did,
we can't make the company grow.
If you like it, serve it in
your restaurant as well.
Right?
What do you mean "right?"
What the hell is this?
I give up.
How many times was this brewed?
Even if you spill a 10 times-brewed
beer and wipe it off with a cloth
then wring out the beer,
it won't taste like this.
That's all?
We can't just make this much,
you idiot!
(Honki Shibori Beer)
What have you done?
Say it yourself.
Bro, look. I passed the interview.
I'll tell her about it tomorrow.
I thought I'd fail 'cause I was late
but I shrugged it off and
was able to express my true self.
You passed? The interview
was for an internship, right?
There were seniors who got hired
officially after the internship.
Let me take a look at it.
- Hold on a second.
- What?
Why do you have to bring
the socks Bro took off?
'Cause I just turned on
the washing machine.
Do it yourself.
She's not a housekeeper.
Hey!
- I'm sorry about that.
- It's really no big deal.
I'm doing mine anyway.
- I'm really sorry. It's okay.
- 'Cause it'll get stretched.
- No, no. Please.
- Don't worry.
What's going on?
They were talking about
being a housekeeper.
Mom, why do you only say
bits and pieces of things?
What does it mean?
It's okay.
Midori is not a housekeeper.
I didn't say that.
Then, who said she's a housekeeper?
I said that she's not a housekeeper.
Well then, shall we
decide by majority?
Why?
It's okay.
Whether I'm a housekeeper or not
I'll be the one to decide.
"Since it's what the children says
I don't intend to believe
everything,
but please keep in mind to
be careful and responsible
of one's language and behavior."
It says.
I'm sorry.
It's not uncommon for
a class teacher and a trainee
to be talked about.
It's a seasonal tradition.
It's still okay while the children
are making noise.
But once it reaches
the parents, this happens.
"What's written here is not a fact."
Is it okay if we reply that way?
Yes, of course.
Is there anything wrong?
Ms. Sakura didn't say
anything like that though.
What?
On the contrary, she asked me for
advice since she was having trouble
'cause Mr. Yamaji approaches
her aggressively.
- What?
- Well, that's what...
You mean I aggressively
approached her?
Did you know that the two are
from the same batch when
they entered the company?
The store manager and Akane,
the area manager?
Seriously?
Oh no! That's heartrending.
I'm sorry for interrupting,
but I need to go now.
Thank you for the delicious meal.
- Thank you.
- A friend?
No.
Anyway,
it looks like a younger employee
aroused issues of irresponsibility
and declared threateningly
that he'll officially
make a direct plea
to the labor union.
Yamagishi? Seriously?
Yes, it looks like he hired
a lawyer as well.
Well, I'll insist that you're not
accountable for it,
but expect for an interrogation
very soon.
See you tomorrow.
Thank you for your hard work.
Excuse me, Sir, your friend...
He's not my friend!
Forgot this.
No way! Definitely not!
I'm not saying anything yet.
Once a crime is uncovered,
teachers get fired.
In the first place,
the 120,000 yen is our money.
You saw inside?
That's why I asked you
to come here, Yama.
Me?
Please. Go ahead.
Just give it a thought and
you'll know right away.
What about the cash?
A little less than 10,000 yen.
Everything in 1,000 yen bills.
There's a driver's license.
The address is on it.
(Maribu Michigami)
- What? You'll bring it yourself?
- I haven't said anything yet.
After all, it looks like
this is the place.
Of course not. It's a typo.
- No, it's correct.
- Really?
No, I mean...
Papa.
Are you looking for Maribu?
He's here.
- What?
Maribu! Your friends are here!
No, we're not friends.
(Takaoka Clinic)
You came all the way here
to deliver it.
I appreciate it.
Don't just stand there.
Come inside and have a seat.
- Well, but...
- What? The house dust bothers you?
No, I mean sorry for coming
this late at night.
Well then, stay outside.
No, Madam. Don't.
- Wife?
- What?
How did you know?
- I can't think of anything else.
- I panicked.
This is my wife, Yuka
and my daughter, Serebu.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
- Excuse me,
but we're the same age, right?
I was born in 1987. Why?
That book. There's a difficult book.
'Cause I'm a student taking
an entrance exam.
- What?
- Haven't you heard from my father?
I failed the college entrance exam.
I heard about that. What?
We're the same age, right?
You're also a first generation
millennial, right? We're the same.
Don't count! I failed 11 times!
I've been busy lately.
Besides, I've got a child now.
I only took
the National Center test.
Do you know?
From this year,
physical science is divided into
physical science and basic physics.
You can now choose three subjects
from the eight science subjects.
During your time, it used to be
Integrated Science A, right?
- I don't remember.
- Have a seat.
Somehow...
I misunderstood various things.
Since when did you start
using honorific language?
Why are you so particular
about college?
I'm not particular about it.
Besides, that old battle-axe...
is telling me to go to
a national university.
I'm referring to my mother.
There's only one college
I want to go.
Since it's a prestigious school
it'd take me about 10 years.
- But...
- I told you, have a seat.
If you three remain standing
while I sit alone
people would think that
I'm the one who's wrong.
It's not three against one,
but four against one.
Even if you enter college from now
by the time you find work,
you'll be 33 years old, right?
I'm not going to find work.
Why do I have to be pushed around
by someone who's dumber than myself?
What?
If that's the case, I could either
be a doctor or a lawyer.
Got it.
I just have to stand instead, right?
Then, let me ask you.
How did you choose your university?
A college where I'll
likely pass the exam.
What about the company?
A company where I'll likely
get an official job offer.
Amazing!
He went to college where he'll
likely pass the entrance exam.
He got into a company where
he'll likely be accepted.
He hasn't resigned and
continue to work until now.
Isn't that amazing?
Sorry if I've put you
in a bad mood. Sorry,
I'm seriously impressed.
'Cause you know what,
if it were a game, you're doing
the same thing over and over
without going to the next level
which is supposedly easy to clear.
It's impossible.
I don't have skills like that.
That's why I live like this.
- Here's the money.
- No, it's okay.
No, I shouldn't keep this.
I misunderstood it.
I thought you were more
of an ambitious person.
- Take it. I said take it!
- No, really...
Having yakitori everyday
is also hard for me.
- Really! It's okay!
- Why?
Really! It's okay!
Please go home soon!
It's time I breastfeed my baby!
Does it mean this is my grandchild?
The father is currently preparing to
take the university entrance exam.
I know.
Anyway, I wonder how Maribu...
named Serebu and how it's written.
Papa, look!
Ah, Maui!
Amazing!
I'm sorry to bother you.
You came all the way
to Kamakura,
but I couldn't tour you around
'cause it's family day today.
No problem.
I mean...
it's not uncommon for someone
my age to have children.
Beside, Mr. Sakama has a girlfriend.
I'm the only one somehow...
feeling cold.
What? Didn't you say...
it wasn't necessary?
Yes, I did, but...
I'm not at an age to say
such things anymore.
I feel cold.
- Here you go.
- That's not what I mean.
I know.
Is that so?
You went to the hospital and
found out it was someone else.
I'm sorry. It was hard
to tell you that time.
How young are you?
Since it's his second year
in the company
I guess he's 23 or 24 years old.
That's not what I mean. I'm asking
your age, Mr. Sakama.
Me? I'm 29 years old.
Are you the eldest son?
Are your parents in good health?
No, my father passed away.
My family runs a small sake brewery
and my elder brother
is the 6th generation.
My younger sister is
a student looking for a job,
She's busy attending job fairs
and internships on holidays.
Since she's a confident person
who's ignorant of the world
I'm worried whether
she's qualified to work.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Since I use Mac at home,
I'm not familiar with Windows.
Could someone assist her?
The intern is having trouble.
I'm sorry to bother you
while you're at work.
I'm sorry for talking
so much about myself.
It's okay.
Oh dear, it's beautiful. Excuse me.
You haven't had lunch yet, right?
No, please don't bother.
Please have lunch. I don't feel
like cooking whenever I'm alone.
I know it's hard for you to ask
so let me just talk.
When he was a child,
he was affectionate.
Since my husband passed away,
he became a whole new person.
He became cheerful.
He participated in
local festivals and--
Please help me with this.
Okay.
He participated in
volunteer activities
and everyone liked him.
Come to think about it, I guess
he was concerned of me
that he didn't want me to worry.
Are there any reasons?
I really can't think of anything.
Please take a look at his
computer browsing history.
Right?
On the night before, he was
giving advices to strangers
on their personal problems.
He showed me he was
chosen as "The best answer."
See! Do you think a person who plans
to commit suicide would do this?
Will you answer earnestly
to the sexual problem of
a high school student?
But you know what...
according to Mr. Goto...
Ah, Mr. Goto. Yes.
- I'm terribly sorry!
- Hiroyuki...
accepted a job that was
too much to handle alone.
Eventually, he cried to Mr. Goto
and asked for help from him
two to three times.
It's okay.
Since then, Mr. Goto
asked him whether he's okay
and offered to help.
It looks like Mr. Goto was
quite worried about him.
Here you go.
(Patience)
But...
he was transferred last April.
If only he was by his side,
he could have noticed it.
He said it's frustrating.
Oh dear, I...
What am I making?
I thought...
I was making yakisoba.
Yakisoba?
Did I say that?
No, you didn't,
but from what you've been doing
I somehow figured it out.
There's no noodles.
What?
I've got udon though.
Udon...
Let's have yakiudon!
- Sure.
- Right.
It's the first time I was able
to talk about Hiroshi without crying
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Sometimes, when it crosses your mind
could you pass by?
What? You mean me?
People from his office
also come to visit,
but I can't tell them the truth.
That's because I'm not
related to him, right?
Yes.
What the hell. Darn it.
After all, I cry.
What a shame.
What? You're alone?
What about the female
college student?
I told you I don't think she
will come. I invited her though.
Well, then, I guess I'll go home.
No, please.
You came all the way here.
That's right.
I'll have lunch then.
- What?
- What? Well...
- Ah.
Why do you eat alone?
It's very you, Yamaji.
Mr. Sakama,
what do you know about me?
He's this kind of person.
Well, this is Akane Miyashita.
Ah, no. It's for her.
We met last time at the rip-off bar.
That's right.
I'm terribly sorry for that time.
- What?
I'm here.
- Ah!
- Did you just hit it?
- I didn't see it.
- What?
Oh no!
- I think I'm winning at this point.
- You're kidding me!
I don't want to lose.
I'm sorry about what
happened last time
- at the faculty room.
- Huh?
No, it's okay.
I don't really care about it.
The vice principal pressed me
for an answer
and I had no choice
but to say such things.
I thought so. I understand.
Well, it's a seasonal tradition.
Akane, do you want something
to drink?
Yes, soft drinks! Afterall, it's...
Yamagishi.
Yamagishi?
The talked-about Yamagishi?
Ms. Sakura, would you like to try?
- What? Me too?
- Of course.
Hold on. I'll put this here.
What was the name
of your subordinate again?
It's Yamagishi.
I don't know what kind of
a person Mr.Yamagishi is,
whether he's a good or bad person.
If you happen to meet him again,
be kind to him.
But...
Yamagishi and your son,
they are different.
It's the same thing 'cause they
both have parents, right?
You too.
Yes.
(Patience)
Here you go.
There's nothing good
if you get emotional.
I don't want to see you suffer...
like what happened to Mr. Goto.
Shall we go home?
I'm sorry.
Come on, Mom and Mune.
Please talk to each other.
Good morning.
Why did you keep silent about it?
What?
Zokin Shibori?
Hey! It's "Honki Shibori!"
What a waste of money!
First, you just have to
take over Dad's position.
He died leaving you
the connection and skill.
What about Yutori? She has
internship today as well, right?
She wouldn't wake up.
Looks like it didn't go very well.
What are you doing?
It's not good for an intern
to be late.
I'm not going.
Why?
I thought it was a company
that was more creative and open.
It was nearly sweatshop.
Besides, the employees are
unfriendly. The canteen is super--
- Then, don't get a job.
- Why not?
The company you like
is nowhere to find.
And no company will like you either.
How mean.
That's not what it's like to
step out into the world,
not working and receive salary!
Look at your brother!
I finally got into a company,
but due to my poor performance,
I'm sent around.
At last, a subordinate sued me
for power harassment.
Seriously?
After compensating for
the mistakes of a subordinate
and working for seven years,
I thought I'd finally made
contribution to the company.
And now this power harassment issue!
I've never imagined this life as
a full-fledged member of society.
But your brother will do it.
I make rounds of customers
and bow my head. Grill yakitori
and get pushed around by a part-time
worker who's elder than me.
Be laughed at by the juniors.
By all means, I won't quit!
If I quit now,
there's nothing I'll gain.
Until I get a return, I won't quit.
That's why you cannot quit!
Until you get a return, don't quit.
Thank you.
Somehow I feel much better now.
What?
Hey, Bro! Send me to the station!
Hold on a second!
Yutori! Rice balls!
Eat it in the car. Here you go.
- Thank you, Sis.
- Take care.
See you later.
- See you later!
Don't get emotional.
Don't get provoked.
Maintain your presence of mind.
Yes.
(Patience)
Over here, please.
Well then, shall we start?
I came as the representative
of the labor union.
I'm Aoki. And this is
Yamagishi's legal advisor.
I'm Asakura.
Please allow me to record it
for documentation.
Before that, you apologize.
Hey! Apologize first!
You middle-aged man!
Come on, Mr. Yamagishi. Calm down.
Kneel down on the floor.
First, it should start from that!
Hey! Do I have to teach you how?
Stop it!
You too, bastard! Apologize!
Area manager!
I'll upload.
I'll upload this on the internet.
(Patience)
Trial court?
That's a millennial monster.
Thank you for your hard work.
If he calls now,
she'll likely be proposed.
I thought you were under
suspension and feeling down.
I was worried for nothing.
- We'll divide it into--
- We're not friends.