What?
Good job today.
- What is it?
- Nothing!
- I'm going.
- Have a nice day.
- Isn't Yutori in a good mood?
- What?
- You think so?
- She got to the second interview...
at the travel agency she applied to.
Hey, Midori.
What is it?
Wrap this.
I'm thinking of eating it tonight.
Then you've just said so:
"Wrap this for me."
I hear the ferility situation
isn't going smoothly.
Say...
Is that all?
Is that all you know about
Yutori's good mood?
- You know something I don't?
- Well, no.
But you know...
she came home late last
night too.
- Maybe she has a boyfriend.
- What?
I know you're concerned
as her older brother, ...
but don't worry.
After all, she's already 21.
If it could be a trigger
for her to get hired,
even if not by a first-rate
company; it would be great.
I wonder what kind of man he is?
What? Does she really have
a boyfriend?
I don't know. Oh,
I'm going out tonight,
to Korokke's dinner show.
So if you want to talk behind
my back, tonight's your chance.
Whoopsy-daisy.
Okay.
- You want to stop?
- What, why?
I dunno, you know.
Maybe you've reached the goal
of your climb for today.
- It's okay if you want to leave.
- But going back...
just because we were
seen together is also...
- Huh?
- Ouch!
-Stop it.
-What?
You're misunderstanding me.
You misunderstood me,
I said.
I didn't... Okay...
Akane-chan...
You win, Akane-chan.
Oh, store manager.
I was just speaking with someone
from the main office.
I heard that you and the area
manager...
We've already broken up!
I was going to say, "are peers
from the same year".
Welcome, I'll show
you to your table.
Of course I want to see her.
But her contact number
was deleted...
right before me by her
younger boyfriend.
I have it.
- Etsuko-sensei's? Seriously?
- Yeah, we exchanged numbers.
That was when we went to
Ma-chin's home.
- Here.
- Erm...
It's okay.
- Then shall I text on your behalf?
-No, no.
No.
- Then I'll send her your LINE ID.
- No, seriously.
Please don't bother yourself.
I'll just...
take her number down for now.
Of course, I'm not going
to call her.
It's just that I won't recognize
the number if it's not saved.
Welcome.
- Draft.
- Coming right up.
You're getting the hang of it,
store manager.
- You think so?
- Your preparations are perfect.
You skewer the meat exactly
2 seconds prior...
to the customers
taking their seats.
But actually, you're
not supposed to.
- We grill after taking their order.
- I'm sorry.
I'm just saying you've got talent.
How many months has it been?
It'll be 2 months soon.
You've got talent.
- He's got it, right, Sujimori?
- I'm Nakamori.
We even have each other's
business phone numbers.
It's because of the superior
and subordinate thing.
Even if we broke up, my cellphone
will simple convert from
private to business-only.
- Are you breaking up with him?
- If I did, do you want to go out?
Oh, don't go all quiet on me.
I'm not interested in
virgins anyway.
That new place on the
name card you gave me...
I've was thinking
of going there...
You've got numbers in here of
people you'll never see again.
That's true.
You guys hold on to these
meaningless connections...
that's why you feel no
sense of danger.
That's true.
I've been saying "That's true"
quite a lot, haven't I?
Why did I suddenly
become effeminate?
- What, you're 38?
- Right.
You don't look it.
You look no older than 36.
Let's not go there today.
Why is that?
Um... there's a lot of traffic
out there...
It's kind of far from here.
Besides, it's not that much fun.
- Alright, let's go.
- No, forget it.
The address book should have a
function of automatically
deleting all contacts of men who
have no will to marry.
You want to get married?
Who said I didn't want to?
- Sorry.
- Look, look!
I got a call!
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
That's amazing.
Your virgin spirit has
evoked a response.
What am I going to do?
What do I do?
You have to answer it,
"Yamamichi"!
I don't wanna.
Okay, I'll answer.
"Etsuko-sensei"
Don't you dare answer
calls from her.
Idiot. "Yamamichi".
Virgin idiot.
- I'm sorry.
- What?
You thought it was Etsuko calling,
didn't you?
Too bad! Because
she is...
taking a bath right now.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're a teacher, aren't you?
Don't you have any
common sense? Virgin.
Yes...
What happened?
She's taking a bath.
I heard she's taking
a bath.
A bath?
- I'm home.
- You're late!
It's not midnight yet.
Is midnight your curfew?
I don't have a curfew.
Wait a second.
- What were you doing out so late?
- Visiting alumni members.
Alumni?
Y-you've been drinking!
- Kidding. It was a drinking party.
- Then say so in the first place.
- Mom said it was okay.
- Is that so? Is that so?
She told me to let loose once in
a while; she gave me 5,000 yen.
That's what I've heard.
But... but still...
Right, bro?
- Sit down.
- Sit!
Yutori.
It's been 3 months since
father died.
Mother is putting up a
cheerful front, but...
I think the last 3 months
were tough on her.
She looks young,
but she's over 60.
- She's a senior citizen now.
- What's this about?
- Be quiet and listen.
- You need to grow up.
Each and every one of us.
Our Sakama family now...
no longer has a navigator,
who was our father.
And yet we must plunge into
a chaotic world.
Yutori, your difficulty
in finding work.
Midori, your difficulty in
gaining fertility.
And Masakazu's...
just... chaos.
- What is this about?
- Be quiet and listen.
You guys, ...
just because I'm the oldest,
you all simply assumed...
that I'd automatically
become the heir.
We've never even
discussed it.
Are you sure you want me
to be father's successor?
I'll be the heir, sure...
The second oldest can be heir
too. But I'll do it though...
You could at least offer
to take my place.
- Although I won't let you.
- It's bedtime.
Hey, wait a second.
Masakazu...
So, in the end I have to
turn to the Rental Uncle.
- You're pretty.
- Stop it.
I see.
I can't discuss it with my family,
my girlfriend, my friends...
but I could with you, Aso-san.
Because I pay you,
you're not related,
and you give me a response.
Like I'm playing catch
by myself against a wall.
I get calm when I talk to you.
Your sister...
she works at my son's
bar, doesn't she?
So you and I are not
completely unrelated.
He takes my money, he
gets involved with your sister...
- "Gets involved with?"
- Oh, he didn't?
Huh?
"I love you"
- What?
- I dunno...
I feel guilty for having peeked
at my sister's cellphone.
I loathe myself for suspecting,
but also for hitting the mark.
but more corncerning yet,
are my sister's actions...
Oh, yeah...
- you must be worried.
- Yes.
Do you want me to check the
situation out for you?
- No, no...
- She doesn't know me.
Of course, it'll be a secret,
that you and I have met.
Sometimes I do receive
and accept such request.
To do detective work.
So describe her to me.
My sister?
I dunno... well...
She has a gloomy look.
- Gloomy?
- She's actually not gloomy.
I don't have a pic...
Well, there's a texting emoji
that looks like her, though.
Should I send it to you?
- Does she look like that?
- No, not like that.
Welcome. Welcome.
Where can I sit?
Welcome.
Good evening.
- You're Moe-chan?
- I'm Moe.
- You're cute.
- Thank you.
Oh, pardon me.
Good evening.
- I can explain our system, right?
- "Right"?
The 2,000 yen drink-all-you-want
course is for 40 minutes.
It's 1,000 yen for every 15 minute
time extension.
But it's better value than ordering
a glass at a time. Is that okay?
- Well, let me see...
- What drink would you like first?
A drink? Let's see, what
should I have...
I already opened a beer.
So is it curry flavored garbage,
or garbage flavored curry.
Isn't that the same thing?
Then how about...
garbage flavored garbage?
Then that would be...
nothing but garbage.
I've never gotten along well
with older people...
but I could totally get along
with you, Aso-san.
Oh, how cute. You're blushing!
Why are you smirking like that?
How was my sister doing?
Well, her shift is twice a week.
She works from opening till
10:30 for 1,200 yen per hour.
And her nickname is...
here it is.
It's "Milla".
I wonder if it's Milla,
as in Milla Jovovich.
Why...
What made her so sad?
"Milla"
Sad enough to work at a
place like that?
About that...
It seems, it was her
own wish to do so.
In this world, there are people who
die unnoticed...
There are lots of
things you can't do,
places you can't go,
people you can't meet.
You and I are in the same boat.
We have infinite choices, but we
chose to be here at this time.
That is why I want to take
pride and
responsibility for the
choices I made.
I want to take pride and
responsibility
in working for a company I chose;
a company that in turn chose me.
I don't want clients who chose that
company to have regrets either.
Out of the many travel agencies...
I want them to be glad
they chose us,
and to make it a trip
they'd never forget.
I did it! Mother!
I passed the second interview!
I'm so glad. I'm so glad.
Let's go tell your father.
We must inform him.
Hurry.
That's awesome.
Congrats.
Huh?
I'm not doing anything special.
I have you to thank,
store manager.
That's why...
to congratulate me,
please go out on a date with me.
What?
Me?
Yes. I feel that if you did, I'd be
energized for my final interview.
Well...
Is that okay?
I think it's okay.
Then, tell you what.
Only after you talk
to your brother,
and tell him you're
working at my bar.
I see him every day, you know.
But I just can't bring myself
to tell him.
- He's here. I'll tell him now.
- Seriously?
- Who was that?
- Just a friend.
I'm taking a bath.
Wakayama Daigo-kun.
He has moved here because of
his mother's job.
Starting today,
he will be studying with all of you.
Be a friend to him.
Applause.
I want him to take classes in
the same classroom as his peers.
Well...
if he did that...
it would help to clear the kids'
misunderstandings
on learning disabilities, but...
How was he at the
previous school?
Yes.
He couldn't keep up with his
classmates in math.
So he received private lessons
in a separate classroom.
However, it made him
feel alienated.
He became slightly adverse
on attending school...
Our textbooks are different!
No kidding.
Let me see.
Wow! It's completely
different!
I understand.
In that case, he should
study along with the class.
I'm glad.
Well, we makes arrangements
to help him keep up,
like giving him extra lessons.
Thank you very much.
It is nice to meet you.
When did the cancel notice
come in?
Friday last week.
- It was Wednesday.
- Which was it?
It was Wednesday.
Which ever the case, you
should've reported immediately!
Why didn't you
tell me till now?
Something told me...
that the timing wasn't right.
I don't care about timing! Do you
know how much reception costs?
Oh, senpai.
Are you power
harassing?
No, no. Please,
give me a break.
Oh, senpai.
I can relate now to how
you must feel.
I have no idea what these
entitled monsters are thinking.
If only I had confirmed...
You think crying will solve
the problem?
That works only in the first year.
Hey. Hey.
I think you have gotten the hang
of working at the shop.
Yes, thanks to your support.
I hear sales have gone up.
You were fit for the task.
Nah.
Well, it would be nice for you
to come back to the office and
apply your energies here, but...
can you wait just a
little while longer?
Um...
Yes.
Are you disappointed?
No, no.
I'm so sorry, but Suginami,
Setagaya is starting to take off.
You know, the area manager
is going to change too so...
- What?
- Huh?
Didn't she tell you? Miyashita-kun
will probably get moved.
Sorry about that.
Oh, as your peer, she
probably found it hard to tell you.
Um...
There's a plan underway
to install a branch
at the giant shopping mall
in Sendai.
And Miyashita-kun has
been picked for a post
to be in-charge of the development.
They wanted to integrate women's
perspectives;
she'll be supervisor of the
Sendai branch.
It's definitely a promotion.
- Where's Daigo?
- In the school infirmary.
He raised his hand to answer a
division problem, so I picked him.
Then he slumped down in
front of the blackboard.
I see. I'm sorry
for the trouble.
It's okay.
I hope I didn't
overwhelm him.
Let's hurry.
Don't walk...
- The shoes..
- Oh no, I mean, don't run.
4... 9...
Could the answer be 6?
Think carefully.
Okay...
try it again on this paper.
Take your time.
Do your best.
So close!
Don't tell him.
Daigo-kun, you can do it!
Do your best!
Okay...
you answered every
question correctly.
You did it!
Congratulations!
That's amazing!
Well done!
Oh no, please...
- His mom comes to school daily?
- Not daily.
Only for math class.
Learning disability, eh?
Did kids have that when we
were in school?
Nobody noticed, that's all.
It's an educational awareness
of the millennial generation.
People realized that effort
alone is sometimes not enough.
It's not bad being a
millennial, I must say.
And...
is she pretty, his mother?
Huh? What's that got to
do with anything?
Because Daigo-kun is all you've
talked about today.
You know...
she's a single mother, right?
Sounds perfect.
Come on...
I'm not a teacher so I
can find marriage prospects.
We've got parents from college
students to more senior guardians.
- A broad range is good.
- Don't be silly.
You're late, Akane-chan.
- Aren't you working?
- I here to try it out.
Hey.
Hey, hey, you can't just
crawl your way up there.
That's right.
You have to follow
the colors.
If you choose green, you
keep following the green.
Follow the color!
- Which one?
- To your right.
- Which one? This one?
- On the right.
You were warned.
Welcome.
What?
Store manager?
- I'm all right, I'm all right.
- You're not all right.
He tore his Achilles' heel.
It's not torn. Not torn completely.
If it were, it'd be far worse.
I'll be fully recovered in a month.
Store manager,
what are you doing?
Here's your first order.
With sauce, right?
Oh.
Here's your salted order,
thank you for waiting.
Okay, one order of skins.
One order of skins.
And rice vinegar too.
- Hey, Nakamori-kun.
- Yes.
Clear table 2's pitcher and
take their refill order.
- Yes.
- Amazing, not a waste a moment.
Same order, okay.
I've got skewers too for
table 5.
All right.
The area manager is a
charimatic worker.
It's ready to go, Nakamori.
Okay, sorry.
Please take a seated at
the back table.
Welcome.
- Good job.
What are you doing?
What do you want to do?
I'm sorry.
I told you, there's nothing going on
with me and Yama-chan.
We're friends.
We climb, come down, talk.
That's all we do.
- That's a lot of things.
- You think so?
Don't you go 3 or 4 times a week?
Is it so much fun, this
- Ro-ro-ro....
- Rock climbing.
Rock climbing.
You don't even look at me
when I talk to you.
Because we're at the workplace.
But you go immediately after work
to that ro-ro-ro...
- Ro-ro-ro-....
- Rock climbing
- I can do it too!
- And you got injured, remember?
Even I have things I want to
talk to you about!
- What about?
- Never mind.
That's the part about you...
about people going out...
a presumptuousness?
I don't need that in my
life right now.
You got things you want to talk
about? Then talk!
"Never mind"?
What are you, a child?
You should've realized before
you tore your Achilles' heel.
That kind of...
egocentrical hubris.
Yama-chan isn't like way.
He's my friend. I can talk to him
about anything, with ease.
But look at you.
You're less than a lover. Less than
a friend. Just a subordinate.
I heard you got hurt.
Sorry. I should've let you know
I was coming.
It's fine, fine.
We're almost done.
Wait outside.
Hey...
Did the main office
call you in today?
- What?
- You're going to the Sendai branch.
That's awesome. You're going
higher up the corporate ladder.
Which pushes our marriage
further and further away.
I've been quiet because
I'm still uncertain.
What about Yamaji?
I told him.
Because we're friends.
I'm sorry,
but I'm going to be frank.
I would've gone to Sendai
if I weren't seeing you.
In fact, I want to go.
It's my chance to
test my abilities.
But I also think it's time for me
to draw a line.
and I also wonder if I'm too
dedicated to the job.
Also, it's going to get harder
and harder to quit it.
Not to mention my parents...
never mind that part.
Anyway, if there's a reason
why I wouldn't go...
it's could only be you.
In that case...
Just a sec.
I think I already know
what you're going to say, but...
Go ahead.
Should we break up?
So that was it.
Huh?
Sure.
Okay.
Understood.
Let's break up.
Oh well.
Everything is finished.
You mustn't break up,
Masakazu-kun.
Definitely not.
- You keep saying that.
- I don't break up relationships.
Go outside for a while.
I can't, the baby will cry.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Maybe she wanted...
me to ask her to marry me.
Maybe she was just
feeling pent up.
She's moving to another job.
She talks as if I'm an obstacle
to her promotion.
She didn't say it
like that to me.
Maybe the baby is hungry.
Baby just ate.
She said it was her work...
that was the obstacle to
marriage.
Which is it?
Both are truth.
Don't interrupt.
All the men
are mistaken.
Women do not want
men to make all decisions.
Marriage, work: she will
make her own decisions.
Men do not
need to decide for her.
Men must make women
happy, that is all.
When she puts it like that,
I have no choice but to be quiet.
She's talking about a
global standard.
How long has missus
lived in Japan?
She's Japanese.
No, seriously.
Her name is Yuka.
In other words, if I am
unsure I can make her happy,
I should not ask
her to marry me?
That goes...
without saying.
You pronounced that wrong.
This guy is preying on your sister.
-Wh-what did she say?
-I dunno.
He is preying on your sister,
so be careful.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes.
Like I said, ask me anytime.
It'll cost over 10,000 yen
to ride a taxi home.
The first train
will depart shortly.
Okay then.
You know... I know
the timing is weird, but...
how's your sister?
Why?
Just wondering.
Why doesn't he tell me?
Oh... nothing.
Please take good
care of her as usual.
Miyashita-san says she
can talk to you about anything.
Like I said, you can't.
Please. Climb the rocks,
come down, and talk.
That's all you have to do.
All right.
Hey, are you going
to be okay?
Masakazu-kun.
But I'm not capable of making
Akane-chan happy.
Because the person able
to make her happy is...
Excuse me, sir.
Please don't disturb
the other customers.
I'm sorry.
Sir. Sir.
Um... what is
the matter?
I'm sorry.
I'll take a taxi home.
This might sound strange, but...
thanks to Daigo-kun,
the class has become
unified as one.
That would be nice.
So you needn't
worry about him anymore.
What?
Am I a bother?
No, absolutely not.
I'm glad you're here.
I thought you had to work.
I work at night, so
it's all right.
I see.
By night, I mean...
something perhaps a little different
from what you are imagining.
Somebody is coming.
Yikes.
Etsuko-sensei!
She was an internship teacher.
She's so popular.
I missed you all,
so I dropped in.
Is everybody doing great?
Yes!
Oh yes, the DVD.
"The Wizard of Oz".
I burned a copy for you.
One moment please.
Sure.
He went away.
Murai-san, check please.
- Thank you very much.
- Table number 4 please.
Did I say 'sauce'?
I meant 'salt'.
- Just a second, it's almost done.
- I appreciate it.
- Did they break up?
- Were they really going out?
It's unclear, so it makes
things awkward.
Welcome.
I'm taking the place of an
injured subordinate.
- Have you been well?
- Yes, thanks for asking.
I'm sorry you always have
to dress up so strangely.
- Huh?
- At the bar.
- Not at all.
- Where shall we go eat?
Anything other than yakitori.
All right!
Oh yeah.
Here. Thanks.
It's been washed, too.
I see that.
We did it.
- You sure did.
- We sure did.
That was so funny.
It was funny.
I'll take the empty glasses.
This one's so cute.
This one wearing the root.
Thanks.
Muto-kun is so good.
I think I'm not going to
be a teacher anymore.
I'll get my certificate, but I'm not
taking the employment exam.
I wanted to tell you the truth,
Yamaji-sensei.
Even though you had counseled
me well. I am sorry.
- Why?
- My one-month internship...
was very meaningful.
Every day was fun, laughing
and crying with the kids.
However...
it's true that it was also tough.
I slept less so I could study.
But it still didn't go well. So I
cried. Self-reflected.
I didn't know what was
correct anymore.
I thought to myself: Will it
go on like this the rest of my life?
When I thought that
I came to realize...
that I couldn't do it.
Thank you very much.
It doesn't excite me anymore.
I think I burned out.
An unreachable place...
As your teacher, I...
don't think I was very good...
I broke up with my boyfriend.
He raised such a fuss, but he
cheated on me without a hitch.
That wasn't the only reason,
though.
He was younger
and he was childish.
I've been doing all the talking.
I'm sorry.
Here.
Thank you very much.
I don't get excited either.
What?
About what you were saying.
Every day I think I can't
do it anymore.
There are students I like,
and students I don't.
There are obnoxious colleagues
and parents, I can tell you.
There are people I'd rather not see.
But I still go on teaching.
Even a guy like me.
I spent 4 hours doing division
with Daigo-kun,
the learning-disability boy.
I get so frustrated I want to cry.
A lifetime of it is impossible.
A single day a best.
But I still go on.
Why are you so quiet?
Why don't you fight back?
You fought back, remember?
When you were interning. When I
disagreed, you cried and left.
Gosh you were goofy.
- I'm sorry.
- It's not a matter of sorry.
Uh...
I too am sorry.
I'm drunk.
But I sure wanted you to become a
good teacher, Etsuko-sensei.
Please don't call me 'sensei'.
I'm no longer a sensei.
Nope, you're sensei. I call
you that even if you quit.
The rest of my life...
Along with all the children...
I felt like I was one of your
students too.
They all said today:
"Etsuko-sensei!"
I wanted to run toward you too,
with the children.
I wanted to embrace you.
You can.
That's not what I mean.
What I meant was...
And? Did you hug her?
Of course I did...
No you didn't.
I was watching. I stopped the
ventilator and watched.
After all that hesitation...
He shook her hand.
And then patted her head.
That's gross, Yamamichi.
Gross.
I could tell you're a virgin
even through the ventilator.
Hey, don't talk that way to a
customer. And how did you know?
The youth today are a joke.
"Burned out" after a
one-month internship?
What a joke!
I agree. But there
are many like her.
A teaching certificate is
advantageous to finding employment.
But the one teaching
is doing it seriously.
Even the kids...
want their teachers to become
good teachers.
I dunno...
I just couldn't keep quiet.
You weren't wrong.
Store manager, can you stop
the ventilator now?
Oh, you can't reach it?
What's the matter?
Maribu-kun.
He didn't come today.
When's it coming off?
- Huh?
- The cast.
I was told one month.
Hey, um...
What?
M-R Grand Prix Buffet's
Kotoge had an electrifying wedding.
Seriously?
Don't, we're watching.
His partner, a regular woman,
according to a blog,
is four-months with child.
Many congratulatory comments
were made.
Midori-san, this tofu is delicious.
I love it.
It's the one we always
buy at the co-op.
Munetaka. What happened to...
you know, the bank thing...
I'm done eating.
Why don't you just act normal?
You make her self-conscious.
Ridiculous. They talk of
some regular woman,
but everybody knows she's
not a regular woman.
You can't fool the public.
You make me sick!
- Yutori!
- You're the worst!
I'll kill you if you touch my
cellphone ever again!
- You stop right there, Yutori!
- What's the matter?
She confessed. Finally confessed!
She has a part-time job!
A part-time job? Where?
- Well...
- What kind of part-time job?
Well, I don't know the details.
- What are you talking about?
- But that's not all!
- She's... with a guy at the job...
- Are they dating?
I don't know the details, but...
She's not a child. She can do
what she wants.
- But she's job hunting...
- She's getting inspired.
That's why she passed
the interview.
Don't spoil my morning with
with such petty concerns.
Okay... okay...
Sorry, I haven't had the
time lately.
I forgot to tell you. I severed
half my Achilles' heel.
It's healing well, I was told
it won't take a month.
I went...
I went to...
see him.
What, Aso-san?
- Stop it.
- Did Sakama send you here
to snoop on me? Huh?
- No, that's not it.
- Hey!
Because if that's the case,
you're too late.
Wh-what do you mean?
She quit.
Yutori-chan.
And I fired her.
I see.
I'm glad.
She's my woman...
I'd never let her work
at a place like that.
What?
We're seeing each other.
I know he's my son, but...
I'm ashamed of him.
- Wait just a second.
- I'm sorry.
Does my sister...
know...
That he has a baby?
Well, if you, Sakama-san...
He's having an illicit relationship!
I am truly sorry!
It's not for you to apologize,
Aso-san.
I want to punch him!
My leg... No, but...
- I want to punch him!
- Yes, yes. I understand.
You punch him for me. You're
his father, aren't you?
You got no business telling
me what to do.
Please let go.
- Please let go. Ouch. Ouch.
- I'm related to you, aren't I?
- Wow.
- What's up?
Exactly one-hundred
service tickets.
They're Maribu's.
He used exactly one-hundred
tickets.
Maybe he won't ever
come back.
You see...
I divorced my former wife...
because of my
illicit relationships.
It was when my son was studying
for college entrance exams.
His family had already fallen
apart on him once before.
My ex-wife also...
because he's our only son...
- put a lot of pressure on me...
- No, no, no.
No, that's irrelevant!
That is absolutely irrelevant
to my sister.
That's your problem, not mine.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-I can't handle this.
- I'm sorry.
- Why did she trust a guy like that?
I'm sorry.
- Was it me?
- No, no, no.
- Is it my fault this happened?
- No, it wasn't.
How noisy. Who is it?
- I'm sorry.
- Oh. Sakama.
Maribu is not home yet.
I see.
Um, sorry to visit at such
a late hour.
Did that guy do something?
- No, well...
- Is it a woman?
- It's a woman, isn't it?
- No, well...
It's a woman, right?
He did it again, that idiot!
I have not introduced
myself, I am...
He must be just like
his father.
A pathetic man!
I hear his father
is a womanizer.
That is why he is also
that way.
But I told you, Sakama.
- To be careful.
- You told me that?
"He is preying on your sister."
"He is preying on your sister,
so be careful."
So that's what you were saying.
I didn't know.
Welcome home.
Welcome.
What? What do you know
about common sense?
I just want to protect my sister.
There are some millennials
who are like that.
I thought being a millennial
teacher is a fine idea.
- Spent the night?
- Yeah.
- I am Miyashita Akane's father.
- What?