I'm uploading this to the internet.
Yamagishi-san, calm down.
Calm down.
Mr. Yamagishi wants to apply
for worker's compensation.
You're aware of the
approval criteria?
He is experiencing a
psychological disorder.
He experienced psychological
duress from 6 months at work.
Um ... is something wrong with him?
Depression. It's depression.
You doubt me?
We have surmised that his case
falls in the power-harassment
category;
the case is summarized in the
paperwork, have a look.
The first here, as you know, is the
usage of the expression "gruntwork."
- "As we know"?
- You can do the gruntwork!
- But I ...
- He said it!
You said it, didn't you?
There were plenty others who
heard you say it.
I'm not denying it. I was just...
responding to his words:
"I don't want to do gruntwork."
He was then forcefully
taken to a client,
and compelled to make an apology.
I am sorry!
No, no, no.
He erred in receiving an
order, he had to apologize.
We shall hear your
counterarguments later.
As the situation settled, he
recounted his error...
I feel I was reprimanded fairly.
You snorted and made fun of him.
That's the reason why
you're a Yutori.
No, no, no...
Huh?
I was just masking my
embarassment.
I'm also a Yutori,
so I used that term with affection.
We must also mentioned forced
unpaid overtime.
Making pesky invitations to attend
a drinking party, against his will.
Oh, the drinking party!
They made me oversee it, even though
I'm only in my first year here.
I've saved the back-and-forth texts
regarding that situation.
What happens if his worker's
comp gets approved?
I wonder...
A trial will be expensive,
I propose a settlement.
Let's take it to court.
I'm confident to go all the way.
Going to court will be
more expensive than a settlement.
This isn't a matter of money,
it's about me!
I've been hurt because of this guy.
- Enough is enough!
- Wow, scary!
Did you see that? This person
pointed her finger at me.
Scary.
What do you say, Sakama-san?
It'll be in no one's interest to
make matters worse.
As the wrongdoer, you should admit
to power-harassment...
Wrongdoer?
I'm the wrongdoer?
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm the victim of your wrongdoing.
If I weren't as tough as I am, I
would've committed suicide by now.
But I truly don't believe I did
anything wrong.
I found them. I found the texts.
"Did you reserve a spot?"
"I did."
"It's a party of 40 people."
"I'm sorry."
"It's the day after tomorrow."
"Yes, it's set."
"It's today, you know."
"Forget about it."
"I'm sorry."
Normal stuff.
What did you just say?
His attitude at work...
was definitely lacking seriousness.
His handling of our clients was
also unsatisfactory.
I figured I should warn him for his
own sake...
and I gave him guidance.
I did nothing excessive.
Well?
- Was I wrong?
- I don't know.
He's trying to increase the
settlement money.
You could say he's self-indulgent.
To him it's a matter of expression.
He revels in the idea of
him suing the company.
Doesn't he realize the more fuss he
raises, the harder it'll be to stay?
Oh, but I guess he's quitting so he
doesn't care.
Huh?
What makes you think
I'm going to quit?
But you said you were quitting,
on LINE.
No, I have to work. The trial is
going to be expensive.
I have to make up for
the time I've lost.
He's expecting allowances
to be made?
We were able to have another
discussion the day after.
His attitude was completely
different; like a victim.
Some how...
During my previous statement...
I had gotten overly emotional...
Does that mean you're recalling
the lawsuit?
- I'm suing.
- What?
- Huh?
However, he must've figured
a settlement would be better.
No, no, no... It should be at least
this much.
- A hundred-thousand?
- One million, you jerk!
Don't lowball me.
He's an allowances-monster.
If I were to write a formal
letter of apology
and pay his settlement, the issue
would be peaceably settled.
Would you be satisfied with that?
You wouldn't be, right?
Afterall, ...
you did nothing wrong.
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
You can't leave too much fat
on the skin either.
And why is that?
Because if the fat catches fire
the whole thing burns.
And yet, too little fat
isn't good either.
And why is that?
You listening?
No, I'm sorry.
Master, six skins,
eight leeks please.
Was that an instance of
power harassment?
Huh?
People talking from the front and
back; that was irritating.
I wonder if I can sue you for
power harassment.
Remember very clearly.
Where was the store in the Asagaya
Pearl Center?
What was it selling?
Please make sure to color
them separately.
That's not correct.
Ellen-chan, where's your color pen?
You're supposed to use different
colors for different shops.
Did you forget to bring
your color pens?
I won't know if how to help
if you just keep quiet.
You can borrow mine.
Bullying?
Shimoyama Ellen is
getting bullied?
I don't know about that...
Inoue Ayaka let her borrow
her pen.
It's because she's the culprit.
"Culprit"?
Wait a sec...
It was tossed into the
janitor's trash bin.
Are you aware...
that there is a Inoue sect and
Saotome sect among the girls?
No... yes. No.
When those two became conducting
candidates at the singing contest,
Shimoyama Ellen
didn't enter a vote for either girl.
Is that so?
She's become the classroom
reject ever since.
Because she doesn't belong
to either sect? I see.
May I contact her parents?
Huh? What, out of the blue?
Whose parents are you calling?
The parents of both of them.
You should talk to the kids first.
I think information should be
shared with the parents.
Why?
Because those children will
continue bullying.
Parents and teachers need to
cooperate and watch over them.
Why for?
Because this is an urgent matter.
Why do you think that?
Because I read something like
this on the internet.
There's a website where parents
and teachers give advice,
based on their own experiences of
having been bullied.
Um...
That's not what I meant when
I asked you "why".
I meant, why are you so sure
that Inoue Ayaka
stole Shimoyama Ellen's pen?
What? I just told you didn't I...
Right, there's sectarian
partisanship.
But it could be Saotome's fault, or
it could be someone else's prank.
Maybe these color pens
aren't even Shimoyama's,
to begin with.
Before you rely on the internet, you
should investigate on your own.
Let's talk in the hall.
It's too late. What's going on?
Well you see, in class...
Uh...
All right.
- Maruyama-sensei, please excuse us.
- What for?
Sakura-sensei.
I was being too opinionated.
I apologize.
It's okay.
Women know how women
feel better than men do.
Let's hear what the students have
to say, tomorrow.
Oh!
- Oh!
- Oh, hi.
- You rock climb?
- Yes, but I'm just a beginner.
I do this occasionally...
but it's my first on this wall.
Is that so?
I like it here, it's not crowded.
And the wall's quite high too.
You're right.
I'm here alone. By myself.
Man, "Suzume"...
What the heck is "Hansuzume"?
I'm not repentant.
You can't do that, Yamaji-kun;
you overstepped your bounds.
Women know how women
feel better than men do.
You've implied that her mentality
is like an elementary schooler's.
I don't think she'd interpret
it that way.
Tough girls like her must be treated
and spoken to as an adult.
Then...
every now and then, you have to be
sweet to her too.
I know, but it's all a
matter of timing.
The timing's hard to discern.
- Because you're a virgin.
- That's got nothing to do with it.
Wait a second, how did you know?
Um...
How could you tell?
- Get out of my way.
- Sorry.
Please don't say a thing
about that to her.
Really.
I've passed the threshold of being
sweet-talked to like a girl.
What?
How about Sakama-kun?
Not at all.
Relatives, colleagues, everybody
comes to me for advice.
They think I'm their mother.
Mom. Where's the ink pad?
In the third drawer of
your father's drawer.
Mom, can I have Yakisoba?
Which drawer is his?
- It must be this.
- Oh, I see.
Mom. Make me Yakisoba.
Mom, what day is it tomorrow?
Oh, the calendar.
Mom, you put Masakazu's underwear
in my drawer again.
Well, it wasn't me.
Mom, what's the date tomorrow?
I can't take it anymore.
Mom, where's my Yakisoba?
You're not getting married?
-No way, not a chance.
-Oh.
- Are you trying to say something?
- No.
You're not going to?
I don't know you well enough
for starters.
I'll probably marry eventually.
- But he treats marriage lightly.
- Huh?
He's obviously using marriage as
some kind of pretext.
Some kind?
That's not it.
I just want to get marriage.
Hear what I'm saying?
Yeah.
A marriage without extra baggage, a
marriage without pretexts.
Ah.
It's like all a virgin wants
is to have sex.
Maybe you better not tell him that.
Yama-chan, what's your first name?
Oh, it's Kazutoyo: 'Kazu' and
'Ho' of 'Hosaku'.
What's that?
- They should've named you Hosaku.
- No, they shouldn't.
And your first name is...
- It's Akane.
- Akane-chan?
Say, Akane-chan...
are you going to tell Sakama-kun
that you and I talked today?
I won't.
-Why?
-Well, you know...
It might be more meaningful
if you don't.
Huh?
What? What?
No, no, it's not like that.
- Nevermind.
- I won't say a word either.
I won't say it, not a word.
Ouch!
Virgin!
- Don't say that!
- Virgin!
Too loud!
- Yikes!
- I wasn't surprising you.
- I know you weren't.
But why were you standing
behind me so quietly?
Because I didn't want to
be downstairs.
Hey...
you shouldn't smoke. It'll
affect your fertility.
I smoke off and on.
It's not about fertility.
It's about perseverance.
Perseverance.
I know that,
but this can't be helped.
It's okay by me.
Masakau is always here,
and even Yutori will
get married someday.
It's just that...
she's rueful her dad never
saw his grandchildren.
It makes her weep.
- Midori cries about it?
- It pressures me.
Just moments ago,
she just up and walked away.
Even I feel it.
I should never pressure her.
This is terrible.
I was once a young bride...
now I'm a mother-in-law.
So please, take action fast.
I'm working on it.
I'm not galavanting
or anything...
I'm planning things out.
Do it instead of planning
on doing it.
You're forty years old,
aren't you?
My business has to run
smoothly first.
That failed beer idea
got you in debt.
Don't call it a "failed" idea!
Everyone, put the color
pens on your desks.
Everybody has pens except
Shimoyama-san, right?
Which must mean, then...
these color pens belong to
Shimoyama-san.
Yes.
You were worried because
you had no pens.
You know what that means?
That means somebody here is
being a bully.
- If that's the case, our class...
- Okay, everybody.
Let's close our eyes.
All eyes closed?
No cheating now.
If you want to respond, please
raise your hand.
"I threw Shimoyama-san's
color pens...
"...into the trash bin."
We promise not to scold
you for being honest.
I know you want to apologize.
Go on.
To be honest, I wanted to be
the conductor too.
But before I could announce
my candidacy...
Inoue-san and Saotome-san both
asked me to vote for them.
You didn't want to choose one
over the other?
That's why I decided not to
choose one over another.
That's why both of them
gave you the silent treatment?
No. Saotome-san and I go home
together after school.
We're good friends as
we've ever been.
But things were awkard
with Inoue-san.
I like them. I wanted to reconcile
with her, and...
I thought the only chance I had
was during sociology.
You threw your own
pens into the trash bin?
But...
I didn't have the courage to
ask to borrow hers...
Is all this true? You're not
covering up for anybody?
Why did you throw your
own pens away?
I'm sorry.
You had us worried, we thought
you were getting bullied.
I didn't notice at all though.
I'm sorry. Etsuko-sensei,
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, we'd like to order.
One moment please.
Hmm, well...
this would be a standard
formal letter of apology, but...
Sakama-san.
The harasser and victim
legally can't work together.
If the worker's comp is on
and the accusation stands,
as long as Yamagishi is here,
it means you can't
work here anymore.
It means your life
will get derailed.
I'll work at the shop and climb
my way up.
Listen.
You won't climb back
up again, for good.
I'll cross that bridge...
when I get there.
You're going to quit?
Why don't you go
to trial instead?
Trial?
Against Yamagishi?
I'm alive.
That's good enough for me.
Well...
you were thought dead.
Somebody died on train tracks.
Let's wait and see what
his next move is.
I'll keep this for you.
I want something light.
I knew that was you,
Yama-chan.
Hey... Yama-chan.
Hey. On your way
home from work?
Confirming your order:
2 lemon sours...
Let me pitch in.
H-hey...
-Is he your friend?
-N-no... he's just a street barker.
You know, he barks to get
customers into the pub.
Is he with you?
He's not, can't you tell?
We're being harrassed.
So that's 2 lemon sours and the
karaage. Will that be all?
Thank you.
Sorry to barge in.
Enjoy.
Woops, excuse me.
Akane-chan?
So you're here at the
shop sometimes.
Nobody here knows we're
seeing each other.
Don't tell anyone.
What was that all about?
What? Sorry about that.
- The karaage are ready.
- Sakama-kun, Sakama-kun!
Welcome.
You know, Sakama-kun...
you're like Sakana-kun.
Gyo-gyo!
You're in good mood.
Yamaji-sensei. is there bullying
in your class?
Not yet.
I see.
But we have minor squabbles
all the time.
You're quite a bystander.
You must have lots of patience.
The kids tend to solve their
own problems, so...
Thank you for waiting.
Do you speak to the parents?
I sometimes send
them short notices.
I've read about methods to
stop classroom bullying...
T-toilet!
-But if there is bullying...
-Master, the dinner platter.
Got it.
Kids in class 2 of the 4th grade
are good kids for sure.
But I can tell they're stressed,
and they're all different.
Maybe some will be assailants,
and some will be their victims.
I think such cases should be
conceptually considered.
- Even if the effort proves futile.
- But...
- What?
- I'm just glad...
...that it wasn't an actual case of
bullying this time.
Wait a second...
what are you saying?
You want to assert
that you were right?
No, it's important to be wary...
but it's also important
to have trust.
You didn't trust those kids.
You didn't even notice
until she pointed it out.
Don't get self righteous!
What was that for?
Your conversation is stupid,
that's what I think.
H-hey...
Isn't it time for a strip tease?
Stop yammering stuff you don't
mean and speak the truth.
Otherwise it's a waste of
time and booze.
What's your problem?
Now now. Were we a little
too loud? Sorry.
Hey, I know...
you all were talking loudly so
everybody could hear you.
You want everyone to know that
people in public service
talk about education even when
they're out drinking booze.
We hear you loud and clear...
good job, everyone!
Step outside, now!
Hey, calm down.
What do you mean by
"speak the truth"?
Example: why are you always
om Yama-chan's case?
Are you attacking Yama-chan to
cover up something?
For example.
And you and you. You're
interested in this college grad,
but don't know what to do.
Yet, you don't want to leave,
so you just keep drinking.
Don't be ridiculous.
That chubby woman there and the
grey-hair comb-over...
are only interested
in the karaage.
And Yama-chan, he just can't wait
to be alone with you.
And you're not averse to that
idea either.
But bushy eyebrows there,
and the thin man here,
don't like that fact.
That's why I'm saying, start
the strip tease.
You bastard!
That's enough!
Sorry, everybody!
- Are you all right?
- I was being friendly, that's all.
Did you kick me?
I'm not trying to get anywhere
with Sakura-sensei.
I mean...
well...
you are the first intern I've
ever trained, and...
I was excited. It was a fresh,
new experience for me.
So I look forward to going to
school everyday.
I know I'm stuffy to someone
as young as you are.
You might have thought of me
as overbearing.
- Not at all...
- But the children genuinely...
love you.
I cannot win over that,
nor betray them.
So I want you to love those
kids back too.
I don't want you to view them
as "assailants" and "victims"...
I realize that yours is only a one
month internship, but still...
to those kids...
it could be a month that'll impact
the rest of their lives.
For that precious month, I didn't
want answers from the internet...
What I want to say is...
Never mind becoming
a good teacher.
Become a good human being.
Come on, say something.
Yes.
- You should've said something.
- I don't know him that well yet.
He's my age and he's still a
virgin. Can you believe it?
I believe it. And there he is,
flagging a taxi.
- He flagged it.
- He did.
- And you, sensei?
- Oh my.
I'm walking home.
Some how...
the things you said made
me glad.
Huh?
I feel I was reprimanded fairly.
You're right, I have
to be more aware.
Because this month will also
impact the rest of my life.
That's our Yamaji-kun.
Is that so?
Huh?
Look!
What was that?
I guess Akane-chan's
advice was effective.
I spoke to her as I
would to an adult.
And be sweet when appropriate.
That was her advice
to you, huh?
How much longer...
- Is the internship? Training?
- A little over two weeks more.
- No nudity till then, eh?
- Stop it, will you?
I partially appreciate
what you did, but...
I also partially despise you
for what you did.
- Oh my.
- Not "oh my".
Cheers.
- What's up?
- I was just thinking...
What you did was exactly what I
did to Yamagishi.
I feel I was reprimanded fairly.
Maybe it's a
generation-gap thing.
We were once reprimanded,
now we do the reprimanding.
But I got accused of
power harassment.
Power harassment?
That's scary.
Sakama-san is in the midst of
a dispute with a subordinate.
Seriously?
What's going on?
- I'll do him in!
- That's a little hasty, Maribu-kun.
All right then...
I'll get a law degree and
be your lawyer.
There's not enough
time for that.
In that case, I'll just do him in.
Then he'll shut up for good.
You should shut up for good.
What's with the "Akane-chan"?
Huh?
You said "Akane-chan".
Yamaji-kun, you mentioned her
by her first name.
You saw her only once and
you call her "Akane-chan"?
Oh...
I guess so.
Huh?
So that's all there is to it?
Well...
Yeah. Sorry about that.
That was a weird reaction.
Who is this, "Akane-chan"?
That's why, "Akane-chan"...
You guys! You're not
staying the night here.
Good job.
Thanks to you the
trial was cancelled.
As it should. Besides, how
could a weakling like you
power-harass anybody?
So you can officially go back
to work now?
The compensation suit wasn't
expensive, and...
the penalty is 50,000 yen,
and you're laid off for one week.
That's the company's decision
concerning your case.
Yes. And Yamagishi will take
my place starting today.
Mornin'...
I bet I'm flooded with emails.
What a hassle.
Hey, senpai.
Good job.
Good morning.
I see...
If that's the case,
I'll take your place,
and whip this guy into shape.
You better go easy on him.
Besides...
It won't count as power
harassment if I did it.
- Um, Nogami-san.
- This is really good.
This wasn't meant for you.
I see...
you persevered through this
ordeal, Sakama-san.
I know it's improper
for me to say this...
but I have your son to thank.
I think he'd be
happy to hear that.
But then again...
why would he be?
He didn't know you.
Yes, but I feel like
I know him.
Look.
I want you to see something.
This came from the company.
"Due to neglience of the
communicant's obligations,
"a consolation of 25 million yen
shall be paid.
"As to the funeral expenses..."
They said it'll go to trial if I'm
dissatisfied with this.
Who's to say if this
money is appropriate or not?
Luckily for you the suit
was settled at 50,000 yen.
Yes.
Is this wine your family's?
Yes, it is.
It's so nice.
Maybe I'll drink some now.
- Right now?
- Yeah.
I feel dissatisfied.
Me too.
Even if his power-harassment
accusation got dropped...
it still feels like a lost match.
Is he feeling down?
I haven't spoken with
him so I don't know.
Oh well.
If I called now I
might get a proposal.
Laid off for one week?
Why?
I heard he's disciplined for power
harassment, don't tell anyone.
I'm sorry. So I'll be working
the grill today.
- Cancel.
- But I taught Sakama how to grill.
Listen.
I don't come here because I want
to eat Yakitori.
Stop acting tipsy.
I'm out of breath.
You know, I...
- Hey, Yama-chan.
- Hey, Maribu-kun.
Did you hear? Sakama-kun
got disciplined.
Oh...
Thank you very much.
That pisses me off. I should've
done him in.
Hey, ugly!
You're an important person
aren't you? Do something.
What did you just call me?
- I called you ugly.
- Stop it, please.
Oh! She's Akane-chan?
This?
He meant to say "her".
Why are you wearing shades?
- I lifted them up.
- That's not the point.
It's impolite to wear shades
when speaking to people.
I see.
Good morning.
There he is. The
disciplined man.
Shut up. How long must you
sleep in, anyway?
It's Saturday, who cares?
- Where's mom?
- I dunno.
- Get it.
- You get it.
How many interviews did you do
before you got hired?
Seven or eight, I think.
Crap, I've already exceeded that.
I was told prospects were grim
after the Lehman scandal.
Like you, I had no goals.
I was unnoticeable.
So it didn't bother me when I
got rejected.
In the interview for my current
job, a woman was ahead of me.
She self-promoted herself with
great confidence, and then,
she started crying
at the interview.
I was like, "oh please".
On my turn, the interviewer
didn't hear a word I said.
So I winged it and went
"blah blah blah"...
and got accepted. That woman and I
were the only ones who did.
It was Akane-chan.
Did I already tell you all this?
Maybe it won't work out.
What's the matter?
Maybe...
- it won't work out for me.
- Are you crying?
I won't get hired anywhere.
Maybe I'm useless.
Don't say that. You're doing
your best.
I went to a coffee shop yesterday...
there was a girl my age
working there, happily.
She was smiling, and sparkling.
She was talking about Macchiato
and stuff...
she looked super happy to be
working at that shop.
I was envious.
Will I smile like her someday?
You will. Besides, she probably
wasn't smiling for real.
Probably.
You know, it's for show.
You know, putting on an
smiley face for customers.
- I can't take it anymore.
- Don't give up!
I don't know how many interviews
you've had, but don't give up.
For crying out loud...
Hello, Sakama Distillery.
- I'm so sorry...
- What's the matter?
They want a tour of our
liquor distillery.
- You saw our home page?
- That's right.
- I'm sorry, it's out of date.
- Oh my.
What? Yutori-chan, why are
you crying?
It's nothing.
I'm so sorry, but we stopped
the distillery tours
at the end of March.
Mom!
She's all right, Midori-san!
Anyway, I'm sorry, we got no
tour for you.
Ah...
but we're already here.
- Hello.
Well... our Sakama Distillery
has been around 151 years, since
the first year of the Keio period.
I am the sixth generation
distiller.
I will explain the
distillation process.
Thanks.
Sorry to barge in
on you like this.
I said let's not, but those guys
wouldn't back down.
At the end of the tour, you
can sample our wine.
It's okay. Just a little
surprised, that's all.
Ah...
Let me introduce her.
This is Miyashita Akane-san,
the area manager.
Don't you mean, "girlfriend"?
Well, yes, but...
This is my sister-in-law.
Nice to meet you.
I am Masakazu's mother.
I appreciate your coming
to visit us.
Should I give her my
business card or is that weird?
Why are you acting
so awkwardly?
- This is your first time?
- That's right.
That's why I didn't
want to do this.
What I mean by that is...
I wanted to meet you under
more formally settings.
What a lovely lady. Isn't she?
I'm Yutori, his younger sister.
Um...
should I continue?
Oh. Sorry to interrupt.
I'm his older brother.
The filtered wine matures
in this barrel.
It's filled with wine.
It's full!
Wow.
That's different from
your usual.
It's filled with it.
Now let us begin sampling.
First, note the color.
Then the fragrance.
And then the taste.
Never mind all that,
just let me drink.
This is the sampling cup.
Do you see the blue
double-circles inside?
You gauge the transparency
with respect to the circles.
Pour it, old hag.
He didn't mean to say that.
Second is fragrance, and
third is taste.
You breathe with
your mouth first...
and exhale through the nose...
then you spit it out.
But I already swallowed it.
Sure you can drink it, but
you spit it out because taste
buds numb if you're tipsy.
Oh...
I swallowed it again.
Crap...
Sensei, may I sit next to you?
They all taste so good,
so I drank too much.
- Are you all right?
- Sure.
It sure feels good.
Are we still in Tokyo?
It's still Tokyo, though it's
at the very edge of it.
Where are you from,
Miyashita-san?
- I'm from Saga.
- What do your folks do?
How many siblings do you have?
What number in line are you?
Say, Moms. You have to be more
natural about stuff like that.
Masakazu.
Hey Maribu-kun, where'd
you get that?
I got it from the fridge.
Want some?
Aw man...
We got a gift from
Miyashita-san.
You should go to the hot springs.
Is it co-ed bathing?
It's only a 10 minute
walk from here.
Onii-chan, you should
drive them there...
Oh, he's drinking.
It's actually drinkable!
It sure is.
What's going on?
This was my brother's home-made
beer. It was utterly horrible.
It tasted like dishwater
wrung from a rag.
Maybe you drank it
before it matured.
Right?
Yup.
I thought you'd be feeling low
because you got disciplined...
but it seems I didn't
have to worry.
I did feel low at first.
Living in a distillery
near a hot spring,...
you've got nothing
to complain about.
It's not that simple.
Besides, I can't drink rice wine.
But your mom is kind...
and your little sister is cute...
Your brother and his wife run the
biz. What more can you wish?
There are lots of things.
Oh boy.
I haven't spent time with friends
on a day off in years.
Friends?
- Are we friends now?
- I wasn't talking about you.
Friends would be
more thoughtful.
That's right. They won't call you
on a weekend to trouble you.
Or worry that you'd have to make
excuses for them turning down.
In the end, we just keep in
contact through Facebook,
and actually never
meet up for years.
But we meet each other
3 or 4 times a week.
We're not friends.
- But 3 or 4 weeks...
- We're not friends.
What shall we do after this?
- My Mom's making dinner.
- What shall we do after that?
How about you, Yama-chan?
What am I doing?
I'm going home.
You should spend the night
someplace around here.
- I can't do that.
- But this is your chance.
No...
She still has two
weeks to go.
So what? Is she going to change
two weeks from now?
Is she going to shed her skin
or something? No, she won't.
So the time is now.
Just be quiet afterward for 2 weeks,
then you'll have the same result.
Come to my rescue
here, Sakama-kun.
Hey, did you power-harass?
What?
Did you say
inappropriate things
to your subordinate, put him down
and drive him to despair?
You didn't, right?
So why did you pay a penalty
and get disciplined?
Your subordinate seems to be
doing just fine.
Well...
it was the company's decision.
But you and your subordinate...
are both a part of the company.
Maybe you should be
more assertive.
Woops, sorry.
Well, we're not friends,
so I just gave you a
piece of my mind.
Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch...
Are you okay?
What was that for,
Akane-chan?
That really hurt!
Got you!
Are you okay?
I just can't keep up physically.
Keep up physically?
Incredible.
You can drink it now.
Thank you.
Guess I'll be going.
Hey! Riff raff. Wake up!
- We're leaving.
- I'll see you to the station.
We'll go too.
Oh man...
We're doing this for you.
No, please don't.
- Thank you for everything.
- Please come again.
- Yeah.
Congrats for returning
to your job.
You weren't in the wrong.
Welcome.
The usual for me.
- Wait, make it a beer instead.
- Beer.
You should drink with us.
- It's a celebration.
- Thank you very much.
- Beer?
- The famous home-made brew.
Wow. Really?
"Sakama's Premium
Draft Beer"?
My older brother didn't heed the
instructions...
he had to let it sit a month before
cracking it open.
Thank you.
It's not that good, but if it's
chilled really cold it's drinkable.
Got it.
But you know, it's strange...
that my son and you
have become such
good friends.
We're not friends.
- Miyashita-kun.
- Yes?
Tell Sakama-kun to
pay a visit to the main office.
You two are dating,
aren't you?
- What?
- Was I wrong?
I heard you're
getting married...
Where did you hear that?
I don't remember...
What?
You go straight through here,
-then turn right at the first light.
-I see. Thank you.
Excuse me, sensei.
Which "sensei"?
Yamaji-sensei. No,
Sakura-sensei.
But first, Yamaji-sensei.
- "First"?
- Nevermind, come here.
Be quiet!
Hey, are you "Yamamichi"?
- Yes.
- Listen to me you old geezer.
You been messing
with my woman.
G-geezer?
A change of plans?
Yamamichi equals virgin.
I'm out of luck.
Are you jealous?
Get out of here, scumbag.
You know him?
I want to change.