Get up, Yutori-chan.
Come downstairs.
What is it?
Come on, Yutori-chan.
What?
What? What time is it?
One in the afternoon... no,
it's night?
Well, Masakazu...
has an important
announcement for us.
Well...
I was thinking of getting married.
What?
You should get married.
But there's one more thing.
Yeah...
I was wondering about continuing
the distillery with my brother...
that maybe I should.
What? Are you serious?
But you don't have to
quit your job for that.
That's right, you finally got back
to work and things are looking up.
But I thought it's perfect timing
to quit, without feeling bad.
My brother's having a tough time
running our business by himself.
No, I...
That's true.
You have better rapport with
the workers too.
That's right.
If Masakazu-san were to take on
succession of the business...
Wait a second here. I'm talking
about
working together with my brother.
No, no. Don't say that.
You should do it.
What do you mean "I" should do it?
What is this?
What are you two scheming?
Actually...
I have...
been thinking about this.
That I am no
company-president material.
You don't want to be one?
-That's not it...
-You want to quit?
I want to quit!
You quit, then what?
I want to...
leave home.
Is that your wife?
No.
Come on, shut up.
You were right about the shower.
The shower head was loose.
Right? It was like this.
Why are you in your shirt?
Oh, um...
I'm having a drink.
Sure.
Say, Miyashita...
this thing we're doing...
This is my first time
with a married man.
Oh... you just broke up with your
colleague, Sakama-kun...
and now you're with
your superior...
Say what you will, I don't care.
I'm going to Sendai anyway.
What?
Isn't that why you
brought me here?
Miyashita.
It'll only be once, right?
Be quiet.
Miyashita...
stop vocalizing
everything I'm feeling.
I want to become a farmer.
Specifically, a rice farmer.
After 3/11,
their whole family moved
to Hokkaido.
They learned it from scratch.
They started to grow rice.
Look at this land.
My friend cultivated all of it.
All in five years.
Property is cheap up there,
living is easy too.
I've heard enough.
I understand well now.
The both of you couldn't
handle anything:
the distillery, having a child,
and me...
That's not what I'm saying.
My obstetrician agreed
with the idea.
They said living in a
nice environment without
stress will stimulate pregnancy.
"Stimulate pregnancy,
Stimulate pregnancy..."
you make it sound as if
I'm pressuring you.
Did I ever say I wanted a
grandchild? I never did, not once.
I want a baby.
I don't want to fight, Midori-san...
I'm fine with it.
You're going to start a farm...
it's not going to be as
easy as it sounds.
Professional farmers have had
it tough all their lives.
That's okay by me. I'll take
over the business, mother.
No, "that's okay I'll do it"
isn't good enough.
It's: "Please allow me to run it!"
What a joke...
I'd rather shut the business down
than have you do it reluctantly.
I'm authorized to shut this
lousy distillery down.
"Perfect timing to quit
without feeling bad"?
I wasn't waiting for your timing.
This is the pits.
Morning, Miyashita-kun.
Good morning, division chief.
I saw May's balance report.
It's going well.
Yes. As each shop exuded its
own personality...
the favorable results finally
showed up in the figures.
But it seems the sales
on weekdays....
isn't rising very well.
Then maybe we should go
all out and start serving lunch!
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
-Good morning.
-Morning.
Oh, sorry.
Time to make rounds
to the shops, right?
Mind if we waited till the
afternoon? I'm swamped here.
-Morning, Miyashita-kun.
-Good morning, division chief.
I saw May's balance report.
It's going well.
Yes. As each shop exuded
its own personality...
the favorable results finally
showed up in the figures.
But it seems the sales on
weekdays isn't rising too well.
Then maybe we should go
all out and start serving lunch!
Lunch, eh? That's a good idea, it'll
help us beat our competition.
Okay, I need an estimate...
What?
Oh, um, I got your call
last night, so...
Oh.
I returned the call because
I thought it might be urgent, but...
Oh, sorry about that.
I fell asleep.
Lunch, eh...
That's a good idea.
I wonder about that.
-If it were a business district...
-Oyako-don,
karaage lunch,
and also chicken curry.
Those will never be profitable.
If we're open from 12 to 2, will you
have time to prepare for dinner?
-Easily.
-That's impossible.
So at the outset,
let's just go with a limit of 50
servings and see how it goes.
Okay.
By the way, I'm allergic to eggs.
Work instead of
flapping your mouth.
I'm sorry.
Which one is the
unsweetened coffee?
-This one?
-It's sugarless.
-Mildly sweetened.
-This one?
-That's got sugar.
I'm sorry, I wasn't sure what you
wanted so I bought one of each.
That's the trouble with
you millennials.
In the first place...
why are these all hot?
I'm sorry.
Kitazawa-san.
-I heard you're coming back.
-Starting next week.
I lost it all on horse races again.
-Again?
-Is he a newbie?
I'm Michigami.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Also, is Yamaji-sensei a virgin?
He's a virgin.
Erm... What?
Why did you ask that?
And why did you answer,
Ota-sensei?
Woops, sorry about that.
I thought it'd be better to
talk about it casually.
You know, there will be sex
education classes in the 4th grade.
It's about the birds
and the bees.
I know that.
Of course I know that.
Let me ask you casually...
-do you think you can teach it?
-He can't.
Why are you answering,
Ota-sensei?
-You'll teach in the 2nd semester.
-Oh, the 2nd semester.
-Can you do it?
-He can't.
-I can do it.
-You can do it.
Sex education eh?
Brings back memories.
Back in my day...
it was for girls only...
It was a secretive class held
in the audiovisual room.
But it's co-ed now, eh?
But there is a problem. Not just the
faculty, but students and guardians
all know the fact that
I am inexperienced.
Because of that Shizuma!
Shut up, virgin!
Well, there are only two
ways you can go.
One is to teach class at the same,
unknowledgeable level as the kids...
Impossible, the kids know a lot.
Possibly even more than me.
The other way is to throw
it all away.
No, I can't do that either.
You talk of it like it's
trash or something.
But I've come this far,
it's a treasure to me.
Remember that movie...
of tighrope walking from one
building to another?
It's like that movie.
I've only got a few more steps
before I reach the other building.
But if it were any other
one of you,
you would've already fallen.
Oh, I have to go now.
For crying out loud...
I feel foolish spending my money
here and raising my voice...
I think it's beautiful.
If my son had...
just one-tenth of your
virtuous spirit...
He'd never have illicit affairs...
Huh?
-What?
-Please don't tell Sakama-kun!
-Welcome!
-You're talking to him.
-Welcome.
That's right.
I'll do that over again.
What's it about?
Aso-san told me.
-About Maribu and Yutori-chan...
-Yamaji-san!
How'd you find a nice place?
Not bad for a millennial.
I heard you have a daughter,
Michigami-san.
-Oh, yes.
-You do?
-Can I try to guess her name?
-Sure.
She's the daughter of
"Maribu," so...
-"Rurubu"?
-No, even I wouldn't name her that.
-Wrong!
-Compliments of the proprietor.
-Seriously?
-Yes. Excuse me.
No, not this guy.
He's over there...
I'm sorry!
-I'm sorry.
-You apologized before bumping in.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
Hey, hey.
Are you sure?
-My sister?
-Yeah.
Forget about that.
Oh, sensei!
-Welcome.
-Here I am.
Welcome.
We have a new customer.
Please take the booth in the back.
You're still here?
Sorry, it's voluntary overtime.
Um,
that's not what I mean...
What?
Never mind.
Good job.
That was awkward.
The total is...
5,628,000 yen.
That's impossible, you idiot!
-Do it again.
-I'm sorry.
I hear you got promoted.
It wasn't a big deal.
I'm making an effort too.
How's your sister doing?
Huh?
Hey Maribu.
-Let's go to the next place.
-Okay.
Thank you very much.
The customers are leaving.
She can't reply, she's
working right now.
She can read it later.
-Excuse me.
-Yes, I'll be right there.
I heard you cheated on her?
-So what?
-Not "so what."
Thank you for waiting.
What can I do for you?
A refill of the draft...
just one...
-should do.
-Understood.
Why did you show up here,
where she's working?
-You trying to impress her?
-You know...
you sound like you've never
been dumped before.
-Never have.
-I see... so this was your first.
You go out, cheat, then cheat
again on your cheating partner.
-And you've never been dumped?
-Never have.
-I'm way poplar.
-"Popular."
Sorry.
I said "popular."
In any case, I wasn't dumped.
You were dumped.
No matter what...
you should feel down about it
like a normal person.
Listen...
you shouldn't obsess over it.
You have to face the facts.
You need to learn that...
there are some things
you just can't change
no matter how hard you try.
-Vir-...
-Virgins know a thing or two too.
Don't get so full of yourself,
"fashion glasses".
I'm sorry.
"Fashion glasses"...
Hey, when did they bring these?
Up to here is fine.
You sure?
If you feel worried call me,
I'll come walk you home.
I might call even if I don't
feel worried.
Etsuko-sensei...
J-just a second...
Oh...
Uh...
Oh!
Look there!
"Sex Education for Children"
-Look, it's Saito Takumi!
-No way!
Isn't that so?
Um...
I'm not sure if it is.
-Welcome home.
-I'm home.
Masakazu is far more stable.
Like I said...
I'll come back to train
the workers.
Don't bother.
I'm shutting down the distillery.
I can run the business
from Hokkaido too.
I can take internet orders
on my PC.
-Please tell her, Midori.
-Mother.
You haven't seen the accounting
book lately, have you?
I haven't since father died.
What about it?
If you look at this, you'll see that
he's unfit to do business.
I think you'll be convinced.
-Midori.
-Sorry, I had to say it.
Bro...
How much do you know about
my boyfriend?
Huh?
Well, it doesn't matter,
we broke up.
I see.
I wonder why.
Why do you wonder why?
It was my fault.
Yutori-chan, if you went to a
college that accepts you...
and get hired where they'd hire
you... is that good enough for you?
-I can't take it anymore.
-Don't give up!
I don't know how many
interviews you've had, but...
it'd be a waste to give up now.
But I passed the interview.
-And then, I dunno...
-You woke up.
-It's not as attractive anymore.
-That's not true.
That's not true...
at least I tell myself
that's not true.
I've been running away from
reality, then suddenly...
I realized how childish I've been.
Like the goofy things I've done;
childish words and actions...
I remember those things
whenever I see him.
And now even he seems goofy.
I think he's doing what he can...
to change; isn't that so?
It's not that I'm taking
your boyfriend's side,
but maybe he's realized
you've changed,
and has been trying to
match you.
That kind of thing...
I never expected him
to be normal.
He's certainly not normal.
-Huh?
-Oh, nothing.
As long as you know...
that it's your fault.
Yeah.
What about you?
What?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
We talked so much my
noodles got dry.
My dear...
Sorry, sorry sorry. Silly me...
I thought it was the
immigration bureau.
-Immigration bureau?
-Never mind.
Hey, Yama-chan.
-What are you doing here?
-Oh, this...
What? You working
part time?
No, I...
Collecting cans?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
That was my fault.
There we go.
I'm not staying long.
Sorry, I have to get up early.
Yama!
"How dare you disturb
us in the middle of the night!"
"You brought alcohol?
Have you no common sense?"
"Huh? You idiot."
She's totally welcoming you.
She is, really?
-What is it?
-Well, um...
I can't say it in front of her...
This is unthinkable.
Oh, well...
It's fine if you use something
other than Chinese or Japanese.
"Well, I happened to
hear something..."
"About you and..."
She already knows about
Yutori-chan.
But it ended before Yutori-chan
learned about them.
All over?
That's the promise I
made to Sakama.
And I was able to
fulfill my promise.
I even changed jobs while
I was at it.
Of course I never thought
I'd get dumped.
Oh...
He's awesome.
Sakama-kun?
He knows what's precious
to him.
He fights for it tooth and nail
in the trenches.
You know...
what I like about that shop...
is watching Sakama work.
Oh, at "Tori no Tami"?
I wanted to show that to my
coworkers today.
They say "millenial this" and
"millenial that," but...
you can be a millennial, and yet
be so unlike a millennial.
He tackles all kinds of things...
he breaks dishes...
he gets yelled at by his
part timers...
-What are you doing?
-I'm sorry, I'm changing the sauce.
He got the salt and sauce wrong
and tried to wash it in the sink.
Guys like that are rare.
He doesn't fit the mold.
That's true.
But he's awesome.
As I watched him...
I got inspired to do
something too.
It's no time for me to be
finding myself.
You've been trying to
find yourself?
All the while as I
barked at customers.
But I quit.
I sold all my self-help books.
I don't know if gardening is
something I want to pursue, but...
I enjoy the challenge.
And the beer and yakitori after
work at Sakama's are delicious.
There's no doubt about that.
There's no doubt, all right.
I have to make an effort.
For their sake too.
He's finally come back.
I thought you forgot about us.
Hey Yama. What are
you doing here, anyway?
At last...
my son...
has been released from the curse...
-...of the Michigami family.
-Curse?
You see...
He has a half-brother that's older.
He's an attorney.
They're like cats and dogs.
-It's my fault, of course.
-I'm sure it is.
He didn't give up on college
entrance exams because
he was competing with his
4 years older brother.
But now...
we no longer live in an academic-
degree oriented society.
Right? It's okay if he lives by
different values.
You too, Yamaji-san...
Me too what?
Oh, uh...
Don't try to distract me. What were
you going to say about my values?
-Isn't that heavy? I can carry it.
-I'm fine.
I'll do it.
It's okay, I'm fine.
Never mind.
-Never mind.
-It's okay.
Lunches are doing well.
Thank you very much.
I think the limited menu
was a good idea.
We're sold out before 1:00 PM
on consecutive days.
Can you increase it to 100
orders starting next week?
Yes.
We've been together all
day lately.
What?
Oh... you're right.
They're gossiping in the office
pantry that we're an item.
They don't know we're finished.
Right. We're here for work.
I wonder if I should go to Sendai.
It doesn't feel real at all.
Ignoring me, huh?
No...
you're going, aren't you?
Afterall, it's a promotion.
We have to get up early tomorrow.
Spend the night at my place.
You need instructions for
lunch, don't you?
-Yeah, but...
-"Yeah but"...
I'm fine. I'm confident nothing
will happen if you spent the night.
-Right?
-Not "right."
-This isn't good, we're lingering.
-No, even if we lingered,
nothing will become of it.
Yamaji said...
that women will change. Even
though if he's never done it.
But I won't change. I'll be as if
nothing happened tomorrow.
"Sakama-san, your placement of
revenue stamps is sloppy!"
I'm sorry.
See? I haven't changed.
What about me? Have I changed
since we broke up?
I dunno...
Parts of you I didn't want changed
didn't change.
-I see.
-That wasn't good enough?
No...
I thought maybe I've changed.
Because of the
Nogami-san situation.
If we concealed it, our company's
image would've been tarnished.
But Hayakawa-san decision...
to have a public apology
was praiseworthy.
I too...
for the first time, felt that I
wanted to protect the company.
It felt good to bow on
behalf of the company.
Dedication to the company?
I used to make fun of that.
But it was interesting. I felt
it was worth the effort.
I'll see if your dress shirt
and trousers are still here.
Oh...
Those ladies in the
office pantry...
Yeah?
"I think those two are an item."
"Isn't Miyashita having an affair
with division-chief Hayakawa?"
What? What?
The company. It's nothing but a
gathering of such people.
So don't change for the
company's sake, Masakazu.
Thank you very much.
What is it?
Nothing.
Masatoshi.
I'm counting on you.
Hey Maribu, stop
dilly-dallying.
What kind of driving was that?
"... the body becomes sturdy."
"In women..."
"...hair begins to
grow under the arms."
"The ches..."
"Ches...t... becomes fuller..."
"The hip area becomes larger..."
"The physique
becomes rounder."
What?
Nothing.
Oh.
Oh no, I made a mistake.
I blew it!
What is this? Is this all the
thigh meat we have left?
Are you for real, store manager?
I already chopped all the scallions.
-We have to cancel lunch!
-I'll go take the sign down.
Huh?
I brought thigh meat!
Here ya go!
Nogami-san? Why?
I ordered it. Thanks for the
fast delivery.
I can't turn Sakama-san down.
This box is on the house.
-Eggs.
-Yes.
Here you go.
Thanks.
-This is for you, Murai-san.
-Three customers.
Welcome.
-Ready to go.
-Okay.
-Here you go.
Nakamori-kun, man the
cash register.
Thank you very much.
Bill please.
Darn that's good.
Thank you very much.
Yikes. I'm sorry, we're sold out.
I'm so sorry.
Lunch has finished.
If I may have your attention
for a moment...
Yes sir.
I would to invite
Miyashita-senpai...
to say a few words!
Aw come on.
All right.
Well, today's job is done.
It was my last day
as area manager.
Good job.
Sorry. I already saw
this in the locker.
Why didn't you hide it
properly, Yamagishi?
Up till last year, the sales
in this shop...
was the worst in Suginami of
Setagaya.
But now, it's number-one
in the area.
Thanks to its fine staff, it's in
top 10 in all 23 districts of Tokyo.
Yay! That's splendid!
Senpai.
Oh. And...
For a year, starting in july,
I'm going to work on the Sendai
-branch project.
"Tori no Tami" will become
even more successful.
My hopes to get married will be
pushed further and further away.
So everybody,
pool your energies together,
-and run a solid business.
-Yes.
Well said!
Thank you very much.
Now my successor and new...
store manager will speak.
Go ahead.
Senpai?
-Oh. Let me finish this.
-You have to do that now?
Huh?
Huh? Well then...
I'm the new store manager.
The man who
will grow if he's showered
with praise.
I'm Yamagishi.
I know I've got some
problems, but...
thanks to my kind senpai...
here I stand.
What? Are you crying?
I think I struck a weird nerve.
Then Nogami-san,
you talk.
-Why me?
-Why you?
Because you're an elder.
Well said!
I've got nothing to do with this,
but...
okay...
Hello.
I'm Nogami, who caused
a public panic.
I've reopened my business.
I'm not going to improper
establishments anymore.
I'm not kidding.
I owe it all to Sakama-san.
We live in an age where
mistakes are never forgiven.
But he spared a geezer like me.
Don't, you'll make him cry.
You sure encouraged me,
didn't you?
He said he approved of me
as a human being.
That's why he said he'll
help me out.
What's the matter?
Everybody's making the
store manager cry.
Store manager! Thank you for
all you've done for us!
Thank you very much.
Okay new area manager,
pull yourself together.
Everyone still needs to prepare
for the night shift.
Come on.
Area manager.
He's still crying.
Uh...
When I was told to work
at the shop,
frankly...
I thought of quitting my job.
That's why I'm telling you to
pull yourself together.
But I'm so glad I didn't quit.
I've had good experiences
since then.
Seven dull years in the
workforce...
were redeemed in a matter
of months.
I have no regrets at all.
Nogami-san.
Yamagishi.
Murai-san.
Nakamori-kun.
Sakura-san.
I sincerely
thank you all.
What is this, are you quitting?
-Yes.
-What?
Miyashita-san.
I'm...
quitting my job
and getting married.
What?
-To whom?
-To Akane-chan.
Okay everybody. Let's get on
with the preparation!
Wait a second. Senpai,
don't leave us hanging.
You can't wrap it up like that.
I'm not saying it's immediate.
When you come back from Sendai.
I'll wait 3 years, 5 years.
I want to marry you.
I've had good work experience.
I have a sense of accomplishment.
All he did was serve 100
bowls of Oyako-don.
Speaking of which, it's
incredibly clean here.
-Is that why you cleaned?
-Yes.
-Thank you, everyone.
-Sakama-san, it's a waste.
-You're young; just getting started.
-Getting what started?
I don't know how to answer
that, but...
-Aiming higher, for example.
-Aiming higher than whom?
What are you saying?
You know...
that's what people do.
It's not as if I'm going to
become the company chairman.
I've had enough.
I was surrounded by all you
wonderful folks.
I've been trusted so fully.
How can anything make
me happier,
except to get married?
-No!
Don't cry. You should think
this over, senpai.
-Forget it.
-No, I can't.
Let's do it.
Let's get married.
Right now.
I'm so happy, Masakazu.
I'm so happy.
Hey, I've got a bouquet!
Toss!
Then...
-... Sendai?
-I'm not going.
I'm quitting my job since
I'm getting married.
I promised my father that.
Which means...
that I would...
have to work? What am
I going to do?
What am I going to do?
Don't think about it.
No. No, no, no...
I can do it. I can become the
company chairman.
I can do it!
Calm down, Masakazu.
Calm down.
First, we must report it
to the company.
I see...
I'm very sorry.
I know I was just allowed back to
management, but...
Well, it's Miyashita-kun
after all...
I know I could never make
her change her mind.
It's too bad.
Thank you for everything.
That went without a hitch.
That's how it is.
I thought he'd fight a little bit,
to keep us from leaving.
We have to tell your mother.
"Retirement Request"
"From Miyashita Akane
and Sakama Masakazu"
Their names are side-by-side.
Typical millennials.
You think so too?
You think it's the same as a
bicycle too, boss?
I think so. Of course it is.
There's no similarity at all.
Say, Michigami-kun.
Yes?
We've met before,
haven't we?
-Huh?
-Let's see...
It was at the bar district
of Koenji.
No way, you can't do that.
Kitazawa-san, you go to
Koenji for drinks?
Yeah. Although I'll
never go back there again.
You don't remember, Maribu?
I dunno...
I wonder if I should say it...
My junior and I were around there
when we were accosted by a
customer-barker.
-You wanna go, right?
-Let's go, let's go.
What?
That was too much!
We were billed 120,000 yen
for edamame beans and bear.
You were a swindler,
weren't you?
-No, I'm not. Give me a break.
-No, it was you!
Huh?
Don't lie.
I couldn't forget you,
even if I wanted to.
Afterall, it was only
2 or 3 months ago.
Kitazawa-san. He said that
it wasn't him.
Actually...
I had my junior confirm his
picture too.
That's right. That's correct.
-Yamaji. Yamaji.
-Hey, hey.
What's this dramatic entry,
Akane-chan?
What is this, a make out? Hey.
-I got proposed to.
-What?
What? What?
By Sakama-kun?
Of course. Who else
would it be?
Oh my!
Amazing. Amazing.
-Who's this? Who's this?
-Oh, this is...
Hello there...
my name is Wakayama.
He's a student in Yamaji-sensei's
class, and...
I quit my job!
You did it!
What's up?
Got a problem?
Why don't you bark
something at me?
Go ahead. "Come on in
for a round."
I can't hear you. Say it from
the bottom of your gut.
"Come on in for a round."
You're an idiot.
Con artist.
Hey...
Stop it.
Hey. Hey.
"Yamaji"
Hey bro.
Oh, hey!
-Maribu-san.
-What?
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
There've been a lot of police
searches lately.
Congrats.
"Congrats"?
Is that all?
I'm getting married, you know.
I've given it thought,
you know!
If I'm going to bow for
a company... We're one too...
So by becoming the successor
of Sakama Wine Distillery,
I should find job satisfaction.
You guys aren't giving a reaction.
Never mind.
That's how it is. I will become
the 6th generation successor.
So bro. Go to Hokkaido.
Hokkaido?
Oh yeah. Hokkaido.
-To go farm.
-Farm.
You only live once.
You lose out if you
don't do what you want to do.
Right?
What's the matter with
all of you?
Masa-kun...
you can forget about
that idea.
-Forget it?
-Forget about it.
-Why?
-Munetaka.
Apologize properly.
Thanks for the meal.
"Maternal Handbook"
-We've got good news too.
Just today...
we got the test results...
Sorry.
I can't go to Hokkaido
to start a farm.
Please have mercy.
What's so funny?
Pay up.
This is the standard price here.
Are you the manager?
Hey, who the heck are you guys?
What're you doing here?
-What's going on here?
-You're under arrest.
Maribu-kun. Anybody home?
It's me, Yamaji.
Um... huh?
Excuse me. What's your
relation to Michigami-san?
Um...
-I'm his friend.
-I'm from the Immigration Bureau.
Only you, his older brother,
can rescue Maribu-kun.
Congratulations on the marriage.
I look forward to
our future together.
-Oh, oh.
-What?
This is unbelievable.
What does "legit" mean?
-Who decides that?
-Why the apology?
Maribu-kun.