Is Yamamichi here?
Answer me.
Where's the teach'
called Yamamichi?
"Teach"?
"Teacher", you mean?
Don't give me that crap.
Bring Yamamichi here.
Yes! Yes!
Sensei, please.
Who are you?
No one without permission
is allowed in.
I got no business with you
guys. Where's the principal?
In the principal's office.
Hurry, hurry.
Who's the dean?
I am. What do you want?
My girlfriend is cheating on me...
with a teach' in this school
called Yamamichi.
They went to the hot springs
on Saturday.
What's going on?
Hey. Are you Yamamichi?
- Yes.
- Don't "yes" me, you geezer.
You laid a hand
on my woman...
G-geezer?
Shizuma.
You know him?
Be seated, please.
Why are you sitting next
to Yamamichi?
The name is written as
"Yama-michi", ...
but it's read as "Yamaji"!
Yes. I am Yamaji.
Why didn't you say so
sooner?
So you read my texts.
I read them. I saw them.
I have a right to read them.
Calm down. Come on.
What's your name?
Kogure Shizuma.
How old are you?
Nineteen.
He's a junior from my college.
In that case you should mind your
manners, Kogure-san.
No matter what the situation.
Who goes to his girlfriend's
- place of work and...
- What do you care?
I have to confront her in front of
this Yamaji bastard.
Or else she'll pretend to
not know what I'm saying.
When did you read them?
When did you look at
my cell phone?
While you were...
- taking a dump at the cafe.
- Stop that.
Shut up, virgin!
Did you hear me?
We're Millennials. Got a Problem?
Wait a second.
How does her younger
boyfriend
know that you're a virgin?
I'll explain it sooner
or later.
The only one who could have told
him is Etsuko-sensei, right?
So who was it that
told Etsuko-sensei, and when?
Can I, later?
Anyway,
according to Shizuma-kun,
while Etsuko-sensei went to
the powder room...
He unlocked the cell.
From '0000'?
He's an idiot, but he's obsessed
with her cell phone.
Etsuko-sensei was aware of
Shizuma-kun's jealousy.
That's why she changed
the lock code frequently, but...
on top of that...
she even deleted
all our texts to each other
frequently.
"Yamamichi"?
"I like... you, sensei."
Using the word prediction?
Thanks for waiting.
He restored her texts,
- one sentence at a time.
- Oh my, that's scary.
I can hear the theme song of
Mission Impossible.
It's incredible. I think only an
idiot could go that far.
While she slept, or while
she wasn't watching,
he'd repeatedly restore her
deleted text messages.
Then he reached a conclusion
that: "Yamamichi = virgin".
He's got abilities that are
comparable with an archeologist.
That would be more difficult than
decoding ancient tablets.
And yet why can't he read
the words 'Yamaji' correctly?
Because he's an idiot.
Anyway, Shizuma-kun
sat there till the end of school.
You can show me if you've
got nothing to hide, right?
Show me your cellphone.
You went to the hot springs
with her, didn't you?
We didn't go to the hot springs.
Our friend's home is a distillery.
- We all...
- Did you do it? With my woman?
Huh? Virgin teacher?
Whether he did it or not?
Is that the only possibility?
There's no other possibility.
What else could there be?
And if...
I did do her, then what?
Then it's obvious.
I'll make you sorry
you done did do it.
Your grammar is incorrect!
Let me say this...
I had no idea...
that you were in her life.
"You really don't mind?"
"No, I'm actually proud of you."
"I'm glad, I thought you might
think it was gross."
"I wouldn't, because I..."
- "What?"
- "I don't have experience either."
Huh?
You have no experience?
How could you say that?
Stop it.
She's experienced. She's
experienced plenty with me.
That's enough!
Do you understand now?
That means that Yamaji-sensei
did not lay his hands on
Sakura-sensei...
according to your words.
I guess so.
Then apologize.
You're on sacred ground: an
elementary school's faculty office.
You have profaned it with your
inferior emotional outbursts...
You've raised a fuss,
with utmost disrespect.
Apologize.
I am very...
sorry.
Etsuko-sensei.
Come on, bow your head.
Good job, Yamaji.
I'm proud of you.
You endured well.
Nah, nah.
Thanks. Thanks just the same.
But the dean scolded me
terribly after all that.
I never guessed you would come
out and tell her you're a virgin.
I figured I'd tell her first.
I thought I'd feel easier
if I did.
I wasn't ashamed of the
fact either, so...
The outcomes was
unexpected, though.
And it got announced to
the entire school.
Anyway, the word 'virgin' will
get trendy
in class 2 of fourth grade.
No doubt about that.
The kids might ask:
"Dad. What's a 'virgin'?"
How will parents answer them?
My dad said he's not
a virgin.
My mom's not a virgin either.
I heard it means you're not
fully grown up.
You can buy a movie ticket for
1,000 yen if you're a virgin.
Seriously?
That's awesome.
Okay everybody, be seated.
I think you all know,
but we in the 4th grade will
put on a play
at the Autumn Arts Festival.
So before we practice
for the preview,
we will announce the play
during Friday's parent-observation.
Okay, quiet.
Next, I shouldn't say this.
Huh?
Oh, yes.
Um...
What was I going to say?
I am in charge
of Sakura-sensei's
goodbye party.
Are you quitting, Sakura-sensei?
My promise was for
four weeks.
Stay one more week!
If I want to be a real teacher,
I have to first graduate
from college.
So I will go back to
college for a while.
Now...
regarding the play we'll
be announcing...
what would you like it to be?
- Star Wars.
- Death Note.
"Dangerous Cop".
We should do a play
kids can act in.
Then how about "Big Daddy"?
Quiet, everyone.
How about "Wizard of Oz"?
You want to play Dorothy,
don't you, Etsuko-sensei?
I will be in charge of the
musical accompaniment.
What about Yamaji?
The witch. You play the
witch because you're a virgin.
That's good.
Our relationship is out of the bag.
You know...
I'm interviewing with
Kotobuki Company.
Am I wrong?
I heard you were
getting married.
Yamagishi said that?
I think he's telling everybody.
That's when it was...
You sound glad. Why?
No, no.
This is a bad situation.
But I never had it under wraps
in the first place.
I think I've said it before,
but I'll say it again.
I want work and private matters
to be separate.
Sakama's girlfriend, Miyaji's
boyfriend, and so on...
I don't want to know such things
to bias my views of colleagues.
I don't want to know about
my weakness.
Weakness? Huh?
You mean to say that your
going out with me is a
weakness? Is it?
That's why!
If the store manager doesn't have
ambition, workers won't either!
Isn't that so, Murai-san?
Yes, I agree.
You have to show some
personality.
Or you'll never beat
your competition.
The number of stars in food blogs
aren't everything, but...
you need service that'll make
customers say:
- Koenji Tori-no-tami is different.
- I completely agree.
For example, ...
so customers will remember
our faces and names,
we could wear tags with nicknames
and individual message.
Like "Eternal work
leader: Murai".
"I can play the guitar."
Stuff like that.
Murai-san, please bring
Nakamori-kun here.
Oh. Yes.
Nakamori!
Anyway, let's let them think
we're just good friends.
What are we? Celebrities?
Is it more natural if we said
we've broken up?
Wait a second...
Thanks for waiting.
Sit! Sit!
What is it, area manager?
Are you frustrated?
Do you have a girlfriend,
Nakamori-kun?
Why are you asking me that,
store manager?
I'm not interested or anything,
I just...
We just broke up.
I see.
I said let's date over LINE, and
we were both excited, but
we had no time for each
other because of work.
Then she said:
"Let's break up" on LINE.
You haven't seen her since?
That's right.
You only dated on LINE?
Didn't you do "stuff" with her?
Oh. Yeah, we did
before we started dating.
"Stuff"...
You're funny.
Yikes!
- Sorry.
- That's fine.
- I...
- It's okay, really.
Give me the bill.
I've got a new job, I've
been so busy lately.
I've got to go to a meeting
now. See?
I'll leave a big tip; I won't be
here everyday anymore.
Is that so?
Will you miss me?
Not at all.
We had fun the other
day, didn't we?
How's your sister?
Store manager?
Same as you.
- Well, it's a girl's bar though.
- Huh?
But it's legit.
It's not a ripoff joint.
Come visit.
"Opening service:
40 minutes free of charge"
No way.
Welcome home.
You don't need to wave,
I know you're smoking.
You do?
Don't go in there.
Mother-in-law is depressed.
What, why?
She had a fight with
Yutori-chan.
The usual squabble; she says go to
interview and Yutori says no.
For goodness' sakes...
Hold it.
You can't go upstairs either.
Yutori-chan is crying up there.
Wait, wait, wait.
You can't go that way either.
What the heck?
My man is drunk.
He wanted to sell his
homemade beer...
but the workers weren't
interested.
He should've discussed it
with them first.
Hey.
Oh?
Thanks.
Are you in college?
I'm looking for work.
4th year in college?
Did you enjoy college?
So-so, I guess.
What about club activities?
I've been too busy
looking for work.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I've been swamped
looking for work...
so he dumped me.
I dunno...
sounds like you went to college
so you could go look for work.
Because what I asked you was:
How did you like college?
But all you talk about is
looking for work.
Everybody's like that.
That's only a part
of what goes on in college,
whereby if you don't look for
work, you won't find a job.
Anyway, thanks.
I'll wash this and
return it to you.
You're not crying.
I shouldn't have worried about you.
Go downstairs and apologize to her.
That man, Maribu; which college
does he go to?
Who is that guy?
Who is that guy...
a student on hiatus?
Seriously?
He said he's going to become a
doctor or a lawyer.
Although he's just a
storefront barker.
What? That's funny.
...and with child.
I forgot to say that.
Whatever the case, I think he's
had quite an impact on my sister.
Anyway, what's with
our area manager?
But you see...
isn't it more thrilling to see each
other covertly?
But the way she so thoroughly
keeps us a secret...
it makes me think:
"What am I to you? Am I
an embarassment to you?"
I'm not even sure we're
actually going out.
We don't have any
hobbies in common.
When we're together she plays
cellphone games,
and I'm watching videos.
People of Yutori's generation...
are lousy at dating.
She tells me not to
expect too much.
That's why, you see...
I don't feel like I'll lose to her.
What? Are you in
competition with her?
Of course I am.
My generation doesn't give up.
We're passionate.
You see...
my wife was seeing
another man.
He was the same age as you...
Yutori's generation.
And she told me that
he said to her:
"Let's wait till I get my accounting
license, to get married."
Now since I'm of the
passionate generation,
I took that opportunity
to use my money and time,
to get her back; so I went
all out.
Bouquets of roses.
A diamond ring hidden in
the bouquet.
A day trip to go eat
Shanghai crab.
It was one surprise
after another.
I got on my knees to her,
in the rain.
Wailed to her.
As a result, by the time the guy
would get his license...
she and I were with child.
If only Yamaji-kun had 1/100th
of your passion...
Speaking of...
it's a reservation from
Yamaji-san.
What, 4 hours?
- Yamaji-sensei.
- Sorry, I was checking something.
Regarding the choice of the
candidate to play Dorothy...
who made the decision?
I did.
I figured lots of kids
would want to play her.
Of course, it's the starring role.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying this because
my daughter wasn't chosen.
I told her myself.
To steal the spot light even
though you're playing side role.
But still...
How come the only part left for
her to play is the witch?
That's right.
She could have tried for the
fairy godmother role instead.
Why was Elen-chan
chosen for the lead?
Because her name sounds
like she's half caucasian?
No, it was a majority vote
on the 3 candidates.
That was the day Yudai-kun and
Asuka-chan were sick and absent.
No way.
Not everybody wasn't
there for it?
Ayaka-chan lost because
of 2 votes.
Well, well...
I don't want to suggest that
you do it all over again...
But can you call the two absent
kids and ask their vote?
They both agreed that
Elen-chan would be good.
Can you please reconsider?
What shall we do?
You chose the part yourself,
but you're going to turn it down?
I think she doesn't want to
act with Mori-kun, the bricks.
Why is my son playing bricks?
He's chubby, not flat.
Is it because my husband
works at a steel mill?
No, of course not.
- How funny.
- That's not it.
The Lion is far more chubby.
It's okay if my son plays
the Lion.
But can you change the name of the
play to "Lion King"?
He had the starring
role last year.
It's hard for him to
get motivated.
How come fairy 3 has more
lines than fairy 4?
Why is that?
There is no
particular reason...
In that case the line: "Defeat
the witch of the west!"
should be said by fairy 3.
Yes.
While we're at it, change: "That's
right, that's right", to fairy 2.
Why are you just sitting there
spacing out?
- Take notes.
- Oh. Yes. Yes.
Oh no. I feel like we're
monster parents.
We're not monster parents.
Real monster parents
aren't like us.
Anyway,
Yamaji-sensei and Sakura-sensei,
please do as you like.
How are we supposed to
do as we like?
You're right,
you're right.
If they wouldn't gripe so much,
I wouldn't be so vested.
I don't care if there are three
or four Dorothys.
I don't care if it's "Lion King"
or "Rip van Winkle".
I'm sorry about
the commotion.
Listen to me.
Their own child may look
the prettiest to them...
But objectively speaking, some of
them are downright ugly.
No, no, you can't say that.
- It's such a hassle.
- Here's your orange juice.
Why don't you play the witch
since you're like a witch?
Those monster parents...
Yamaji-san.
Let's change the subject
of conversation.
How's it going with
Etsuko-san after all that?
For now...
her internship is over.
All right. Go
take the last order.
From who?
I wish somebody would come.
I don't care even if it's Maribu.
"Sakama"
Welcome.
Why?
Did I give you my number?
I found this in my older
brother's pocket.
Seriously?
What the...?
Did I throw it away?
Can I shut off
the stove now?
Um...
Please do.
Welcome.
Such terrible timing.
Is it Maribu?
Welcome.
Hey there.
We're a party of four,
is that okay?
- We close at 11:00 PM.
- That's okay.
Sorry about this. We
were in the neighborhood.
I thought it'd be better to spend at
our own store rather than another.
We'll seat ourselves.
Welcome.
This is awkward.
He's the power-harasser?
Quiet, he'll hear you.
Let's just have a few
and leave.
Does your brother know
about this?
- No.
- Then you can't do this. Go home.
Do you have a resume?
Of course you have a resume.
You're looking for work.
Family background...
I know about that.
What you seek to accomplish...
"I aspire to contribute to the
new services and plans of
your company."
Thank you very much.
But you haven't made
any contributions yet.
What are you thinking?
I want to change.
At a girl's bar?
My pride...
my self-consciousness...
I have all kinds of people
telling me...
that I have no value
whatsoever in society.
I've lost my self confidence.
I want to put myself in a harsher
situation, and gain experience.
But just as you say,
Michigami-san...
all I've done the past 4
years is look for work.
Looking for work to work, then
get married, then have kids...
to live a life that is clearly
spelled out.
But I'm not even at the
starting line.
Even though I'm trying so hard.
Nobody gives me the
opportunity to work.
What kind of society
do we live in?
If I can't work, that means
they're telling me to die.
What gives them
the right?
All they did too was do internship
and get hired.
Whether that can determine if
they can function in society
Or whether they are
valuable human beings...
is a separate matter, isn't it?
Rather than having nothing,
exposing my chest
at a girls' bar
would be far cooler,
more valuable, and exciting.
I must say...
I don't get it.
But you're cute.
Of that there's no doubt.
Oh man, this is too much...
You're my friend's
younger sister so...
I should turn you down, but...
But Sakama-kun...
is not...
my friend...
therefore...
And bring me karaage.
Sorry, but that was the
last order just now.
Huh?
No one told me.
I'm sorry.
This is the last call
for alcohol too.
Why didn't you just
say that at the beginning?
I did say that we're
closing at 11:00 PM.
- Sorry about this.
- It's not your fault store manager.
Such bad attitudes nowadays.
How long's he been around?
I wanted to eat karaage.
He thinks he's rented the place
for his private party.
You can make stuff that don't
require a flame, like salad.
No... we can't.
Hey. We're having a private
party here.
I can't take it anymore.
Please. I'm really sorry.
Here's the check.
He's got something up
his sleeve.
The food was satisfying;
since it's from our company.
Thank you very much.
However,
you customer service...
needs improvement.
- Who the hell do you think...
- Thank you very much!
"Where are you now?"
Oh.
You're harsh.
Hey, thanks.
Oh...
- What's going on?
- Sorry, I just noticed the message.
I just saw that,
and texted you back.
I just saw it.
So you do it huh? Rock...
Rock...
Rock climbing.
- You haven't heard?
- I haven't.
- I didn't tell him.
- I see.
The height here is great.
Yes, the height here is great.
I never knew you did this.
Sure you wouldn't.
- But isn't it strange?
- What is?
You know...
weren't you with Aso-san?
Yeah, till 9:00. I wanted to
get some exercise, though.
That's right. So we just decided
to rock climb, right?
That's right, right?
That's what's strange!
Hey. Don't you think
it's strange?
Gosh you're stubborn.
That means you were seeing him
without letting me know.
- I wasn't hiding it from you.
- She just didn't tell you.
You've been exposed, but you
don't seem to care at all.
Want some?
Aren't you two being too friendly!
There's enough water
in there for two.
Huh? Huh?
Are you jealous or something?
No, no, no way.
Yamaji is out of the question.
Akane-chan is out of the question.
You can talk to me that way,
but aren't you being rude? Hey!
All I did was dicuss school matters
and my love interest, with her.
You can talk to Aso-san
directly about those things.
No, she is too radiant for me.
I get you! I too can talk
about anything if it's Yamaji.
Me too. I'm connected to
Akane-chan by friendship.
And Yamaji has a
feminine side to him.
Yet he's not female.
That's what's good about him.
Akane-chan you too. You're
masculine, but you're not male.
We could even take a bath
together without worries.
But that would be...
an unknown till we try.
I like you, Yamaji!
Are you two now beyond the
male-female distinction,
and best buddies that can talk
heart to heart?
You have a nice relationship now,
is that it?
What are we, celebrities?
"Witch of the west?"
"That's right. The
witch of the west."
"Defeat the witch of the west."
"That's right, that's right."
"I'll get you, Dorothy!"
"Who are you?"
Okay, rehearsal over. Get
ready for class.
- Let's do it after school again.
- Okay.
Studying switch: ON!
You're Yamaji's lackey.
As a person involved with
management...
I felt responsible to go see how
the shop was being managed.
As a supervisor...
I wanted to see how our business
is being run...
But that's the area manager's job.
- I'm sorry.
- You can't do whatever you want.
Yamagishi-kun.
I commend your initiative.
But let's stick to your own job.
You know, you had taken time off
because of you-know-what...
Were you planning on making
accusations again?
That's okay, Miyashita-kun.
You can get away with your
behavior
if you've proven yourself a valuable
employee; you haven't yet.
- Was that power harassment?
- No, a correct assessment.
That is all.
Get back to work.
Why don't you go and apologize
some time tonight?
Yes.
Welcome.
Did people at your office
talk to him?
I'm sorry.
- Can I kick him out?
- Please don't. I'm sorry.
Hey, Sakama-san.
Nogami-san.
This is a nice joint.
I invited him. He said he
wanted to come say hello.
Yamagishi-kun says he felt too
awkward to come here alone.
About yesterday...
I apologize.
Party of two, please.
Party of two!
I ... didn't...
What?
I ...
...didn't...
Sorry, I can't hear you
over the sewing machine.
Since that incident,
I haven't been in contact with him.
Oh. I see.
This once-in-a-lifetime
teaching internship...
I didn't want to let that turn it
into an unpleasant memory.
But it's too late.
I don't mind at all.
Even now, I like...
I'm glad you decided to be a teacher
and that I'm became a teacher.
I'm glad from the bottom
of my heart.
I'm sorry I deceived you.
I will not contact him until
my internship is over.
I don't know if I'll keep on
seeing him...
I'll think it over after the
internship.
Welcome. Party of two?
Party of two!
M-Maribu?
I'm going outside for a while.
She's a good girl,
so make sure she gets
on the last train home.
See you.
In a single night...
What?
I got sevice worth
500,000 yen.
Are you serious? That's
crazy amazing.
He's quite different from
yesterday.
Perhaps he's behaving himself
because he's with a client.
Or perhaps the area manager
chewed him out.
What do you say,
Sakama-san?
- Can you drink at work?
- Erm no...
- Just one cup.
- Atta boy.
Sorry. Thanks.
I was worried about you for a
while there...
thought you got fired
or something...
but you're doing splendid,
store manager.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
I don't know about the human
resources of a big organization.
But when you're drinking with me,
it's personal.
Sakama-san. About
Yamagishi-kun...
he is...
starting to understand
how it all works.
He wants approval, that's all.
We were that way too once,
weren't we?
But then again, you and I are
many years apart.
Only...
praising isn't the same as
giving approval.
You slap 'em.
You scold them. You
yell at them.
You punch 'em out. You make
them cry.
You apologize. You pick up their
check. You punch 'em out.
You lick their cheek.
All those things...
are part and parcel of
approving someone.
Isn't that how it is?
Yes.
I approve of him.
Leave him to me.
Hey there.
Give us another bottle.
One more bottle!
Can our store manager
drink rice wine?
- Yamagishi-kun.
- Yes. Yes.
- Has the last train left?
- The last train has gone.
- I see.
- No more trains.
Then I don't need my train pass.
We don't need the train pass.
Oh, I think we can get on that cab.
Excuse me.
Hey. It's gone.
Yamagishi-kun.
I can't find my shoe.
- Shoe?
- Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Got rid of that
old bastard.
Give me a freshly squeezed
lemon sour.
That guy went on and on
with his preaching.
What's your problem?
- Huh?
- Where you shown in?
To this seat?
You're supposed to sit down...
after you've been shown
to the seat.
And you place your order...
after they ask you
for your order.
Oh, Maribu-san,
he's a coworker, and...
You scumbag!
The world doesn't revolve
around your ego!
This shop is this man's
establishment.
There is such a thing as
social propriety.
Store manager!
Shimoyama-san.
Hello.
Sorry about today.
Don't mention it.
Yamaji-sensei.
A call from Inoue-san's mom;
absent due to a stomach ache.
What? Wait just a second...
Inoue-san...
- she was...
- A fairy.
Oh yes. The one with
increased dialogue.
- I need someone to take her part.
- Yamaji-sensei.
It's Saotome-san's mother.
I'm sorry, the doctor diagnosed
my daughter with a stomach ache.
What?
The witch? The witch
of the west has a stomach ache?
Goodbye, teacher.
We can't find somebody now,
there are too many lines.
Oh. I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- No, no.
I'm the one who
should apologize.
I heard a friend of mine
was rough with you yesterday.
- Was that guy your friend?
- My friend?
Friend. Yeah.
Yeah. He's a friend.
You'll sue me if
he's my friend?
You won't sue me?
You won't, for real?
I won't sue you.
Really?
Gosh, Yamagishi.
Your distancing is really off.
I want you to come with me.
I am Dorothy. I live with
uncle Henry
in Kansas in America...
Why did it start already?
Where's the witch?
Sensei. It's too late to
change anything now.
Tanoguchi
- Whose home is this?
- Whose home?
My mother's.
But the family name
is different.
- Then maybe she's your mother?
- Please don't kid around.
Her son dove onto the train
tracks and killed himself.
It was the morning you
ditched work.
What?
This isn't funny.
Yes.
It's this guy.
He's Yamagishi.
- Come in.
- What?
Come on.
We have come to see
the Wizard of Oz because we
want him to help us.
Please help me get back
to Kansas.
Please give me brains.
Please give me a heart.
Please give me courage.
Please make everyone's wish
come true.
All right, I will.
If you defeat the wicked,
wicked, witch of the west...
I shall grant you your wishes.
The witch of the west?
Woof!
That's right.
The witch of the west.
Defeat the witch of the west!
That's right, that's right!
It's the witch of the west.
Why you, Dorothy!
Give me your silver slippers.
That's the wicked,
wicked witch of the west.
She's a wicked witch who
bullies everybody.
Calling me 'wicked' is
to praise me.
I know! The witch can't
stand water!
Splash her with water!
Woops.
You're really going to...
I am glad...
that you are a good person,
Yamagishi-san.
Okay. Now I approve of you too.
What do you mean?
I don't understand.
It's nothing.
Let's go.
Come on. Eat something first.
Thank you.
- I'll help out too.
- Thank you.
Let's see...
Here's your apron.
I have a lot of food.
Okay, Dorothy.
Click the heels of your silver
slippers 3 times.
You will be able to go home
if you do.
Yes, so that's it.
The entirety of your internship
has now concluded.
Yes.
As of today...
we will say goodbye...
to Sakura Etsuko sensei.
All rise.
Ready...
One-two...
Sakura Etsuko sensei...
thank you for the month that
you had spent with us.
Thank you.
I'll take a look.
Thank you, everybody.
I promise to attend the
Autumn Arts Festival.
Until then, we will guard
Yamaji's virginity.
Okay, thanks. Thanks.
Yamaji-sensei.
I'm sorry I wasn't of
much assistance to you.
No, no, no.
I was truly lucky to have interned
in your class, sensei.
I look forward to working
together with you.
Well...
everybody in 4th grade,
class 2...
It's really goodbye to you all now.
What do you think
she meant by that?
She just meant she looks forward
to keeping professional distance.
But she said nothing about
professional distance.
How would I know?
Why don't you just phone her?
Shizuma-kun will get mad
and come to school.
In that case, forget about her.
Next!
Hey, what is this?
Are you crying?
I'm not crying.
You're crying.
I'm not. I'm...
No, no, no... it was chalk.
Chalk got in my eyes.
What am I going to do with
Ma-chan?
What?
Yutori came home later than
you last night, didn't she?
So what? Is that so?
It's been every night.
I hope she's all right.
Leave her be, she's not a kid.
Maybe I scolded her too much.
Maybe I put too much
pressure on her.
What? Is she asleep right now?
She's awake, you know.
Sister. Taste this for me.
Okay.
Yutori is helping with the house
chores; it's unheard of.
It's proof that she's lying to me.
This place is 7 yen
more expensive.
Let's buy from that other place.
Are you hungry?
No, no, no ...
what a lowly...
What college does Maribu go to?
Who is he?
Using the word prediction?
College...
Beer.
- Welcome.
- I'll have the usual, with salt.
How's your sister?
That's funny.
Your sister is cute...
Thank you for waiting.
Excuse me!
Oh yeah... I don't have it.
What?
Thank you.
Good job.
She's got a part-time job!
A part-time job!
You're super funny.
She's a good actor.
All answers
are correct.
Is she pretty?
That shop won't last long.
I've been seeing her.
I've been quiet about it because
I'm still uncertaint.
Maybe we should
break up.