You're dating my sister?
Are you?
Hey.
Yikes, sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
It's messy, but come in.
I'll introduce you.
That's my wife.
I can't talk with you here.
Can you go outside?
No, please stay here.
If you don't mind, that is.
Oh...
You want me to serve you drinks?
If so, go and buy it yourself!
Actually, I hadn't thought I'd
done anything wrong.
Besides, she was the one
who asked me out.
You'd go wouldn't you? If a meal
was laid before you, you eat.
She must've felt a little bad
for you.
And she did hesitate
momentarily.
What does your wife think?
I haven't given her
divorce papers yet.
That's where you and I differ.
Not filing for divorce...
is nothing to brag about.
You've done it so many times,
you've got no right to preach to me.
Hey.
Let's start from the beginning.
It was the distillery tour...
What about club activities?
I'm busy trying to
find employment.
I thought she was
aloof at first.
There was no vibe
between us.
She was dark and boring.
I asked her if she was millennial,
like her name implied.
It's like you went to college just
to look for employment.
- Huh?
- Because...
I was asking you about
college, but...
you just talk about finding
employment.
Everybody's like that.
And you, are a college
student on hiatus!
At your age, I don't care if you're
trying for Todai or Kyodai,
but don't act so proud when
you haven't even gotten in!
- She contacted me first.
- How?
- Remember the business card?
- Store manager?
Just like you.
It's a girls bar though...
- I found it in my brother's pocket.
- Seriously?
Your security is a little
too lax, isn't it?
Shut up!
Sorry.
Anyway...
She did the job interview.
- I want to change.
- At a girls bar?
Not worth a thing in society;
all I do is look for employment.
I didn't understand a word
of what she was talking about.
But she was totally cute.
She's the most popular too.
So...
- Did you lay a hand on her?
- Don't rush it, geezer.
There's an order to things.
Hey.
I laid a hand on her.
We're Millennials.
Got a Problem?
Sorry, I was just kidding.
But think about it,
Yutori-chan.
You just went to the university
that accepted you...
then just hope to get employed;
is that all you want?
In this world, there are people
who die unnoticed...
There are lots of
things you can't do,
places you can't go,
people you can't meet.
There are so lots and lots!
You and I are that way too.
Out of limitless choices, we
chose to be here, at this time.
That is why I want to have pride
and a sense of responsibility with
regard to the choice I've made.
I don't want my customers to
regret choosing to come in.
Out of all the pubs
they could've gone to...
I want customers to be glad
they chose our travel agency,
out of countless agencies; that
their trip was unforgettable.
That is the kind of service I
want to give the customers.
I think about it all the time.
Maribu-san.
You're an unexpectedly
serious person.
You are not a serious person!
I'm sorry.
I'm ashamed that she worked
at this guy's establishment.
So you apologize... you're
being strangely meek...
I betrayed you, Sakama.
Didn't you feel bad toward
your wife and child?
She's not my wife.
She expected me to cheat,
from the get go.
You said it's my disease, that
it was genetically passed on.
You do what you want.
Don't you think of wanting
to break up?
Mind your own business
you geezer!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Let go, ouch...
My visa has expired, I cannot go
to a government office anyway.
I came here on a tourist visa.
We have to keep quiet,
there's no choice.
You...
have you no common sense?
I don't. What the heck is
"common sense"?
Hey.
I'm a millennial, so I was never
taught about such things.
Is it common sense to marry
and divorce repeatedly?
Is it?
You airhead!
It depends on how
many times.
Um... four or five times.
Ouch...
You have an older half-brother?
He's four years older;
he's an attorney.
I followed in my older brother's
academical footsteps.
He was top of the class.
My mother was furious...
and she put a lot of
pressure on me.
She's not related to my brother,
so she got competitive;
she wanted me to win.
This guy here was also considered
a prodigy back in the day.
- My bro passed entrance exams.
- He had the highest scores.
I thought he'd been negligent.
Just when I thought things were
finally turning my way,
this guy here gets involved with
a subordinate at work...
She wasn't a subordinate. She
was just a part-time worker.
Shut up, who's asking you to
interrupt with your prattle?
I haven't talked about
your illicit affair yet.
Never mind.
- I've learned what I need to know.
- What's that?
At your age, you're acting like
boy who hasn't grown up.
- I am?
- Aren't you?
You blamed all of your goofups
on your parents.
So you got compared to your fine
brother; your mom pressured you...
your father had illicit affairs.
Those things are irrelevant.
There's plenty people like that.
Those things don't mean you
can lay a hand on my sister.
I'm here to talk about my sister.
I want to protect my sister,
that's all.
She doesn't know you
have wife and child.
- Go outside.
- Please stay.
What are you going to do?
- I'll break up.
- Darn right you will.
It goes without saying.
How will you do it?
- I'll say I have a wife and...
- Don't ever tell her that.
Don't tell that to my sister, my
mother, or others; it stays here.
It's a secret between the
four of us here.
Nobody else must know. Yamaji-kun,
Miyashita-san, Etsuko-sensei...
- I got it.
- You sure?
I won't do anything with
Yutori-chan anymore.
Sorry, I mean to say...
I'll never see her again.
However,
it's a very delicate time for her.
I don't want her to feel she's been
dumped, while she's seeking work.
So...
I want you to encourage her.
- I can meet her?
- Without meeting her.
By texting, or by phone.
I see.
- Good morning.
- Masakazu did you know?
Do you know about Yutori's
boyfriend?
Oh... you sure he's real?
He's real all right;
not 2-D, but 3-D!
You should bring him
here some time.
Sure...
It might come out later, but...
I want to tell you the truth...
I'm brushing my teeth now,
so wait a while.
Wait. Wait, wait.
Our oldest brother is
committing adultery.
What is wrong with everybody?
Don't worry. It looks like
it won't go any further.
- What's this?
- Yikes!
Let's have a look at the browsing
history. Look at all that!
The cat's out of the bag.
This is, um...
I was just browsing a little.
Of course. I'm working
on my fertility.
- Adultery is the worst.
- And today's my birthday.
I'm leaving now.
Oh boy...
What a terrible day!
"Kapibara Dumpling"
Uh... maybe you prefer tea?
- Oh, it's okay.
Thank you.
I'll explain in detail when the
division chief arrives.
But Nogami-san...
is in somewhat of trouble.
- Nogami-san?
- Yes. Please have a look at this.
The inventory we've been
supplying was cancelled.
Maybe he'll go out of business.
- Morning.
- Oh, good morning.
- Is your leg okay now?
- Yes.
What? What happened
to your leg?
But in essence transactions
have not cancelled?
- Yes.
- But sales was rising till March.
- No. The meats listed here...
are our main products.
The orders have been cancelled!
This month, two boxes of bean
sprouts, spaghetti salad...
Those minor items are still
in circulation.
- And the payments?
- They've creepily, easily...
- gone to another supplier.
- What?
- It's obvious.
We've been cut off.
Wait a second...
give me a break.
You should've known better.
Sorry... I...
thought I just needed to
hold down the dam...
I tried to do it alone...
I thought too highly of myself!
Your crying isn't going to
help our situation.
That's way I say you...
- What?
- Nothing.
I don't envy you, Sakama-san.
You're injured and you have
to deal with that subordinate.
So, how is Yamagishi?
He's working hard, with a renewed
attitude; lovable too.
He helps me when I'm swamped.
I see. The reason I ask is...
You've cancelled orders past
May; were you dissatisfied...
The season that follows May is
better for fish, rather than meat.
Especially the older generation,
they don't do well with fried foods.
Nogami-san, today's main order
was fried chicken cutlets right?
Yeah...
I'm not the chairman here, so...
I take orders from up top
sometimes.
But Nogami-san, you once said...
that you're a person-to-person
guy, not a company guy.
Did I say that?
I talk big when I'm drunk.
What?
Are you fault finding
or something?
No, it's just that you've been
our client for twenty years...
Don't assume you're entitled.
I'm sorry.
We make our decisions based on
tastes and prices.
Those are the
deciding factors.
- Ours tastes better.
- Ours tastes way better.
- Maybe they're cheaper.
- To purchase their inventory?
No. The difference is
probably negligible.
If it's neither taste nor
price, then...
Maybe it's customer service.
I had to go all over town
with the guy.
On company time?
He's crude when he's drunk,
despite his looks.
But he does look like that.
Depending on point of view.
He parlays from one
pub to the next...
Scandinavian pubs,
South American pubs...
and when we finally went
where they spoke Japanese...
we'd be at a buckwheat noodles
shop at 5:00 in the morning.
He'd be so drunk he'd talk to the
cook behind the counter,
trying to seduce her, telling her
she looks like Angelina Jolie.
Augh...
Makes me angry
just thinking about it.
I'll go there and act
sarcastically lovable.
It's grunt work. The kind of
work you don't like.
It's better than the grunt
work of customer-service.
I heard Miyashita-san's
promotion has been determined.
- Yeah.
- That's awesome.
If she's going to Sendai, it'll
be a long distance relationship.
We broke up.
What? Seriously?
You can spread the word for me.
Because of the shock of
breaking up...
I severed my Achilles' heel.
Mmm...
So this is what it tastes like.
Is there filling?
- Please take one.
- Yamaji-sensei.
Got a minute?
"Kapibara Dumpling"
That's a gift.
From who?
From me.
So this is what
Kapibara tastes like.
Don't say such gross things.
- You went to Izu?
- Yeah, to the cactus park.
- You spent the night?
- Yeah, one night.
Who did you go with?
A friend.
- Somebody I know?
- Yeah.
- I only know one person.
- Yamaji.
We have 3 complaints
on accomodating the
learning disorder student.
We just got a call saying...
their child's falling grades,
could be Daigo-kun's fault.
- That's not the case.
- Of course, they're just excuses.
They're parents afterall.
The kids in class are happy to
accomodate, but...
the parents anticipating junior-high
entrance exams are getting nervous.
Daigo has been concerned about
that as well.
He's worried he's holding his
classmates behind.
I've been telling him
it's not the case...
The class is proceeding at the
same pace as other classes.
Perhaps we should switch back
to separate tutoring.
I just don't know how to
explain it to Daigo.
May I speak to the students
about this?
- Don't you think that's strange?
- Please.
It's okay, but don't you think
it's strange?
A man and a woman staying in
the same room at an inn.
- Yamaji is my friend.
- How about the bath?
It was separate, right?
Not mixed bath, right?
The room had a shower,
so I don't know about the bath.
- You went in together...
- Be quiet.
I wasn't told about this
trip, Akane...
Area manager, neither you nor
Yamaji-kun told me.
Why must we tell you?
Because they're friends.
- What if I went on such a trip?
- With whom?
- I'm just saying, what if.
- Wait a second, with whom?
Okay, read out loud.
One-two...
"Millennium education"
Has anyone heard of this?
Nobody has?
It's not about cramming your head
with stuff to score high on a test.
It's about taking initiative to
learn what personally interests you.
It's about increasing time to
experience more things.
That's the concept of it.
I'm proud to say...
I was one of the 1st students who
received millennial education.
They call us "first generation
millennials."
For example...
All of you don't have school
on Saturday and Sunday, right?
However, adults older than me...
had to go to school...
even on Saturdays.
What!
Those poor people!
Okay, okay...
What do you think happened to the
children on millennial education?
They became stupid.
You are right.
Their academic abilities plummeted,
it became a societal problem.
After they became grownups...
they were incompetent; they were
apathetic; they were gutless...
they'd only do what they were told.
They had no sense of rivalry.
They could not sense danger, they
had no focus.
They were unable to respond
to unexpected things.
But those are all just excuses.
At their own convenience, they
made Saturday a no-school day,
and made textbooks thin, then
treat us like we're broken.
However, even the generation
of millennials...
has their good aspects.
They don't get in the way
of others.
They strive for what's best without
being influenced.
They revere individuality.
- Daigo-kun, stand up.
- Yes.
As you all know...
Daigo-kun is not good at math.
But he's good at everything else.
He got 100 in kanji, that's awesome.
However...
he has trouble calculating.
Who thinks their studies will get
negatively affected if they
were in the same class
as Daigo-kun?
Be honest and raise your hand.
Okay.
In that case...
What if we ignored Daigo,
- and proceeded without him?
- I'd feel sorry for Daigo.
Who agrees with him?
Okay, thank you.
Okay then...
- What should we do?
- Yes.
I think only Daigo should be allowed
to use an electronic calculator.
What? But that's not fair.
But kids who don't see well
wear glasses.
- So if a kid's not smart...
- You're wrong about that.
Daigo just has...
trouble calculating divisions,
that's all.
But I think yours is a good idea.
Glasses, calculators...
are tools necessary for all of us
to learn together.
However...
what if Daigo's grades go up...
and he surpasses all of you?
- That would make me mad.
- You'd be mad, then what?
I'll use a calculator too.
Okay, okay.
What do you say, Daigo?
What do you want to do?
I... want to learn along
with everybody.
Why is that?
Because when I get an
answer correct...
everybody is glad for me.
Which makes me even gladder.
I see.
- Do you like everybody?
- Yes.
Does everybody like him too?
Yes.
Thank you everybody. Thank you
Daigo. You may sit.
So, starting tomorrow,
Daigo-kun will
take only the math class
separately,
in the study room.
What? Why?
It's not what you think.
Listen.
I'm not doing this
so Daigo-kun will get left
behind; nor because
I want Daigo-kun to do
better than Mori-kun.
It is a necessary,
special measure...
so that he can learn along
with everybody...
so that he can become a
productive grownup,
together with you all.
A time will come when Daigo
is allowed to use a calculator.
That is true equality.
I believe that...
that is the true
millennial education.
Okay, and that...
wraps it up.
Get ready for class.
"Millennial"
I'm so sorry...
I couldn't quite reach a
good conclusion.
Not at all.
You spoke the words of a teacher.
- Even I was moved to tears.
- No, please.
Honestly...
when I first heard you were the
homeroom teacher,
I thought, "he's too young",
"he's a millennial",
"he's a virgin"!
Those were my thoughts.
- I'm sorry.
- Nah, nah... huh?
But after hearing you speak
today...
I thought, "this millennial
teacher is not bad".
- I appreciate all you do.
- Likewise, thank you.
How did she know?
Who told her? Akane-chan?
Sakama-kun?
I've never met that mother
in the first place.
The whole school knows about it,
no sense trying to hide it.
Oh yeah! Thank you
for the gift.
The one from Izu's
cactus garden.
You're still mad?
So anyway...
- listen, Akane-chan.
- She's working right now.
The supplementary study session
went on till 7:00 today.
His mother had to go to work
during the session.
So I had to take Daigo-kun
home, but...
the night job his mother was
talking about...
what do you think it was?
Something "adult"?
I'm sorry, sensei.
No, same here, sorry
to bother you at work.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to go home first?
I have the early night-shift so
I still have an hour more.
I'll study for tomorrow.
- I'm sorry.
- No problem.
She was an angel in
a white robe.
Nobody's listening?
She got divorced
three years ago...
she's having a tough time with
alimony for education only.
She's an outstanding parent...
she's with her son all day.
Your phone's ringing.
- Hello.
- Like I said...
Don't answer this number,
virgin "Yamamichi".
So that you'll never answer
this call again...
Shall I cut off your lips and
ears and set fire to them?
Huh? Salt or sauce?
Salt...
Etsuko-sensei
It's Yamaji, what do you want?
- I'm sorry. I'll hang up.
- No, no, I'm sorry about that.
What? Where are you?
Oh... just a second.
I guess Yamaji's finally
getting popular.
I'm one of those prospects
too, right?
Welcome.
Here's your draft beer.
I don't have a service
coupon so...
- I'll have green tea.
- But I already poured this.
I'm sorry.
What's he sorry about?
He just said "I'm sorry."
I was with some friends...
I thought you might be here...
Oh, I see.
Oh yeah, Maribu-kun
just showed up.
I see.
Huh?
Is Yutori-chan's interview with
the chairperson tomorrow?
- You're speaking to me politely?
- Well...
may I reply to her text?
Just act naturally. People will
suspect something's off.
Welcome.
Please come on in.
- Big brother!
- We met coincidentally downstairs.
I was in the neighbourhood, so...
Don't lie. You're never in
this neighbourhood.
Thanks for caring for my little
brother all the time.
They look alike.
- Maribu-kun.
- Oh, you're right.
You're one of the
members from that day.
You haven't told them
anything, right?
Huh? Oh...
I haven't.
Please sit at the private booth.
- You can't butter me up.
- No, I mean it.
Thank you very much.
You're stopping right there?
Come on over here.
Thank you very much.
- They're number one and three.
- I see.
- I want to see numer two too.
- We will, next time.
We'll go to one more pub...
I want to go somewhere
more, you know...
- somewhere rougher.
- Rougher? What do you mean?
These two are this year's
new products.
"Demon Bride's Tears"
dry taste and
"Little Sister-in-Law,"
sweet taste.
- Please try them cold first.
- Thank you.
Oh. It's got a clean finish.
My brother.
May I please respond
in this manner?
Take out the "I love you"
at the end.
You're right. I'm sorry.
You're calling me "my brother"?
This sake is good hot too.
- It's smooth.
- Thank you very much.
How much is each bottle?
What is this?
What does "thanks for the meal
yesterday" mean?
Well...
I told you not to see her.
Never to see her again,
Michigami Maribu-san.
It was just for dinner,
just for dinner.
You sure it was just dinner?
Look me in the
eyes and say it.
- I can't say it.
- You...
What the heck is
wrong with you...
- Store manager.
- What?
Oh...
I thought we could serving
this to the customers
and check their response.
But we've got a fixed supplier;
and this is a franchise.
Of course, I understand.
I'll leave the bottles here.
If you're pleased with the wines...
please let me know.
Even if it's an order of one or
two bottles, I'd appreciate it.
- Please think about it.
- Understood.
I will take them back to the
office for an assessment.
I was told to not return till
I could get an order.
Mother? Sister-in-law?
Both of them.
I get rejected everywhere I go.
And I've never been in sales.
I've never even bowed
my head to anyone.
I was thinking of quitting outright.
Then I remembered you.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
I know things are
tough for you.
It's tough all right, like being
in a pressure cooker.
I thought it would work if
I just did it. I was too naive.
Are you talking about fertility?
I have to be grateful.
About the fact that you were
born into this world.
You're overthinking things.
You've heard of gifts
from heaven.
- They come even when you forget.
- I won't ever forget.
Always...
I keep thinking.
So what's wrong that I surfed
the net for "adult" contents?
Well, that's another story...
I don't know about that.
Excuse me.
My name is Sakama Yutori.
Nice to meet all of you.
Looking good.
No, no.
Here.
Well, good seeing you.
- Here.
- Thank you very much.
- You've got style.
- Nah.
- Let's have coffee.
- Sounds good.
It's instant coffee, but...
Just as I...
thought.
Nogami-san was...
firmly locked on to Aiai Foods.
Aiai? The biggest
in the business?
Yes.
He's belittling us.
However...
there's no way we
can beat the competition.
So...
we should bow out
with dignity...
No.
I'll call you back in 5 minutes.
If you don't mind,
I know another place that
has good wine.
Wine, huh?
I'm not in the mood for wine.
Care to come in?
If it's not wine you want...
maybe you want something
more exciting.
It's not much, but here.
Nakamori-kun.
Bring me a draft beer.
One order of draft beer!
From my client...
I got...
a 6 month contract extension!
Make an immediate
delivery, please!
He thinks he's a hero now.
I hope payments won't
be a problem.
Nogami-san gets carried away,
we have to be careful.
So anyway, here.
It's unusual for you to use a
supplier like this.
Because I can't let Miyashita-san
always outperform me.
Oh... you're talking about
the Sendai thing?
It's currently pending.
What?
She said she wants to
think about it.
Well, she's getting
to be that age...
I finished. May I go play now?
You can, but did you double
check your answers?
I did, but the ones I don't
know, I just don't know.
- Hey.
- Me too.
Me too.
Hey, hey, wait a second.
We're going to play.
Are you guys serious? Hey!
- Are you really serious?
- It's okay.
Daigo.
Do your best, Daigo.
Hey, he's still studying.
Daigo!
This isn't correct, Daigo.
This one's correct.
Daigo, let's play soccer.
Hurry up.
Sensei, play soccer with us too.
Let's play, let's play.
Be careful.
Don't run in the hall!
Watch out, slow down.
Don't run.
Gosh...
I guess there was no point
in putting him in a separate room.
Truly...
it's all thanks to you,
Yamaji-sensei.
No, no...
Huh?
Yeah...
Oh...
Did you see that?
Did I stare that much?
You're wearing turtle neck,
you're fully covered.
Yama-chan, you're looking
for excitement, aren't you?
I think that sometimes too.
What?
What are you afraid of,
Yama-chan?
Women are not scary.
Maybe you need to be
a little afraid.
Well, you know, when you fall
in love it's like that...
It's just the natural
progression of things.
In my case, it so happens
that the one has not yet
appeared.
But it has not affected my life.
In fact, I'm not short on
female friends...
I have a good relationship
with all of them.
It sounds like a comment
made by an actor.
But I know they're
doing it for sure.
But you see...
I know you'll think I'm stupid
for saying this, but...
I already think that
so go ahead.
Women change after
their first time.
Yeah.
I'm sensitive to those things.
Because I've been an observer
for 29 years.
So I can tell who's doing it
with who.
I'm usually right.
And women's attitudes change.
They take advantage.
They become arrogant.
They become greedy.
They become moody.
They become happy.
I don't want the person
I really like...
to change right in front
of everyone.
On top of that, I'll change too,
just after doing it once.
There's no way to go back
after that.
You don't change.
I dunno...
You won't change that much.
If you do it once,
you'd want to do it again.
You do it again, you want
to do it with others. That's all.
You guys are on
different levels.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- You understand?
- Right?
-Right?
-That's right.
I feel like I want to try
all kinds of things...
but it's impossible to go out with
every woman in the world.
To choose one...
implies you reject all others.
If that's the case...
if I don't choose a single one...
I reject no one. No one's
feelings are hurt.
I won't get hurt either.
Am I wrong?
I...
want to go out...
with every woman in the world.
- Did you talk like that with Akane?
- We did.
What did she say?
- Bring it on!
- Huh?
I'll show you how we change.
- So come here!
- No, no.
You got me all wrong.
About what?
You want to change too,
don't you?
No, you're drunk.
And I don't want to hurt
Masakazu-kun.
He won't know if we
keep quiet about it.
Besides, we separated.
That's why I took this trip,
to allay my broken heart.
I understand, but...
But you see...
that's got nothing to do with...
- You're pathetic.
- Huh?
I thought you had more guts
than that.
No, no, don't get me wrong.
Well you see...
No, huh? Huh?
Huh?
You'll never become happy if
you're scared
to get your heart broken.
Guys who can never break
your heart...
can never make anybody happy.
You're talking about
Masakazu-kun.
Oh boy...
No...
No, that's not it.
This. You see.
Y-your foot was bare...
sticking outside
your gown...
You see...
Um, seriously...
Are you asleep?
Are you crying?
I didn't want to break up!
I realised it only after
breaking up.
That...
there were several
precarious times...
because...
he never made an effort.
He was awkward.
He's a millennial.
So...
I thought I'd ruin him if
we kept going out.
But...
I've never been asked by a man
to go separate ways.
Is that so?
That is so.
I dunno...
I panicked hearing about her
promotion and stuff...
I thought I better change,
or else I'm no good.
I didn't care...
if Masakazu was no good.
It's not like he'd ever become
the company chairman,
no matter how hard he works.
He's not the type to climb the
corporate ladder
by changing jobs.
So I didn't care if he
didn't change.
He didn't have to aim for the top.
That's what I wanted
to tell him, but...
I was his superior, so I
couldn't say that to him.
I guess not.
He's obnoxious...
he's a blockhead...
He's wishy-washy...
He has no self-confidence...
But that's who Masakazu is.
It'd be no fun if he changed.
If I wanted him to change, it
could've been anybody else.
It can be Yamaji.
Yeah... huh?
I'm quitting my job.
I'm not going to Sendai.
I want to be with the
no-good Masakazu.
But I can't tell him that.
I'm a boring woman.
That's not true.
You're a fine woman,
Akane-chan.
You'd be wasted on me.
Hand me the towel.
So...
Are you doing it?
Or not?
Stop kidding around.
We're having a serious talk.
Gosh...
I told Masakazu-kun...
that although I can be your
conversational companion...
I'm incapable of making
you happy.
The only person who
can make you happy...
And that was all.
I dunno...
maybe it's because
Yamaji told the story...
I felt like crying and yet
I couldn't.
What's that supposed to mean?
He's crying.
You see...
I should've gone...
on that trip with her.
I thought that too.
But if you guys went, you'd
sleep together and it'd be all over.
I'll zip it.
So...
are you going to ask her back?
No...
after hearing what you'd said...
I definitely can't ask her.
- Why?
- Because I want to change.
If...
I can't change...
it'd be unbearable.
I'm so glad, Yutori
got hired.
Ta-da.
Oh.
"Oh"? Is that all?
That's right, we must celebrate.
Your boyfriend will celebrate it
for you, won't he?
I got an order from
Masakazu's shop...
for "Demon Bride's
Tears" and
"Little Sister-in-Law", officially.
Oh. I see.
Sorry about the terrible names.
Here's the extra order of
"Little Sister-in-Law".
Thank you very much.
I think he's finally
getting serious.
I'll go lend a hand.
Come on, let's go eat.
You got hired?
Congratulations.
We should celebrate.
Yeah... that's true.
Yeah.
I'll fade out slowly.
Huh? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Right away, yes.
We'll break up right away.
Sorry, I'm at work now.
Let's talk later.
- Was it crowded?
- Not at all.
- It's a weekday.
- True.
It's kind of noisy here.
There's been a little problem.
- Sorry to interrupt...
- What?
Miyashita-san. Thank you,
regarding the rice wine.
Oh, sure. They decided the wines
give personality to the shops.
Where are you crutches?
Oh no. I forgot them.
Anyway...
go to Nogami-san's,
right away.
- Huh?
- He has food poisoning.
Huh?
Out of all the customers who
ate the shipped bento...
30 people were taken sick
to a nearby hospital.
According to investigation...
Isn't that Masakazu's...
client?
What?
They were expired?
They repackaged expired
bentos and sold them.
Sounds like something
Nogami-san would do.
Where's Yamagishi?
I cannot reach him.
That guy again...
Division chief Hayakawa is
there already.
You go there now too.
- Yes.
- But before you go...
I know the timing is odd, but...
This man here...
Yes.
- He's my father.
- What?
That's him?
Well now...
I am Miyashita Akane's father.
I have arrived from Saga,
just today.
- We are sorry.
- This is food poisoning.
Office workers are in a battle.
You have to be more ashamed.
You and me both.
Yamaji's here.
A gardener?
I do love Akane-san.
But I do not like her father.