-[shouts] Chowa!
-[student] He's a telekinetic.
-[pops]
-[Nanmaru] Just call me Nanmaru.
Minamimaru is hard to say.
[Emi] You probably
share a common ancestor
with Professor Marukami.
[Sachiko's grandma] Sachiko.
Did you have another dream?
[Emi] Professor Marukami
had acquired some kind of ability.
Maybe it's a skill only those
with Marukami blood can perform.
-[pops]
-[Emi] Professor Marukami
-never came back from Marukawa Town.
-[body thuds]
He's missing.
-The victim, 51-year-old Toshio Kuraishi…
-[Tagaya] A hole…
A hole?
Professor Emi.
Let's go.
To Marukami Village.
Previously on Land of Tanabata
[faucet squeaks]
[birds chirping]
[sizzling]
[Sachiko's grandma] You're good at that.
-[Sachiko] Thank you.
-[chuckles]
That should do it.
[Sachiko] See you later.
[♪ exciting music playing]
-[Sachiko] Good morning.
-[elder] Good morning.
[bystander 1] The media is here.
[bystander 2]
Wow. They're serious about this.
I am currently
in front of Kurone Construction
in Kurone District's Marukawa Town,
where the incident occurred.
The scene of the crime is over there.
[reporter]
A room on the second floor of this office
which is covered with a blue sheet.
It has also been reported that there is
a large round hole in the window.
Despite several days having passed
since the incident,
the police haven't identified
the perpetrator,
nor even the weapon used.
Autopsy results revealed the shocking news
that a part of Mr. Kuraishi's head
and right arm had vanished.
A round hole in the window glass
and something round
that gouged out Mr. Kuraishi's head.
How could these things be related?
[reporter on TV] Kurone Construction,
led by Mr. Kuraishi,
has been spearheading the development
of a golf course on Mount Marukami,
located in the heart of Marukawa Town,
and has frequently been involved
in disturbances with the local residents.
Recently, there was a large-scale protest
surrounding the office.
-Their reputation is--
-[remote clicks]
[♪ uneasy music playing]
[door lock clicks]
[keys jangling]
[♪ theme music playing]
Land of Tanabata
[train rumbling]
-[♪ tranquil music playing]
-[train horn whistles]
[birds chirping]
Downbound
[Nanmaru groans]
[Nanmaru] So this is it.
The place where my ancestors lived.
[Emi] First, we'll head to
the local history museum.
Professor Marukami
must have gone there too.
-[Tagaya] Okay.
-[student] Wait.
Shouldn't we try
some tasty local food first?
[Tagaya] Didn't you just eat on the train?
-[student] Huh?
-[Tagaya] What?
-[student] Is that enough?
-Of course. You had a whole boxed lunch.
[Nanmaru] Sorry. Let's let her pass.
-Sorry.
-Thank you very much.
-[student] Hello.
-Hello.
-Hello. Hello.
[elder grunts]
[Emi] Excuse me,
do you know if this person came here?
[receptionist] What's his name?
[Emi] It's Masami Marukami.
[receptionist] All right.
-Please hold on a second.
-[Emi] Okay.
Huh?
[Nanmaru] These holes…
-Nanmaru.
-Hmm?
That has been passed down
through generations
by this region's
prestigious Marukami family.
[Tagaya] The Kasasagi flag.
[Nanmaru] Cool…
[student] It's an unusual flag.
A Kasasagi, and a person's palm.
What's that circle in the middle?
Some people say it's a ball,
while others say
it represents the sun or a clump of blood.
[Tagaya]
But nobody really knows what it is.
Cool…
[receptionist] I checked,
but it seems he never visited the museum.
-Is that so?
-[receptionist] Yes.
-Thank you.
-[receptionist] Of course.
[luggage rattles]
We should be able to get
a full view of Marukami Village from here.
-[Tagaya] It's just like the model.
-[student sighs]
The jagged edges on the left
are the Seven Peaks,
and the thing ahead in the distance
that looks like a pudding
is Mount Marukami.
[Emi] Nanmaru, your ancestors,
the Marukami family,
lived near the foot of that mountain.
Right… But the person called Minamimaru
was killed, wasn't he?
Where does my surname,
Minamimaru, come from?
Tadayori Minamimaru had no children
when he was killed by Michiyasu Shimadera.
That's why his relative,
Masayori Marukami,
sent his youngest child to be adopted
by the Minamimaru family
to continue the family line.
Professor Marukami figured out
that you're a descendant
-of that very family.
-[Nanmaru exclaims]
I see!
[inhales sharply]
Wow, you've all really done your homework.
[Nanmaru] What?
[Tagaya sighs]
[Tagaya]
Which means this must be Mount Kurone.
Ah.
There's a bird.
[Emi] Excuse me.
-[villager 1] Yes.
-[Emi] Can we please ask you something?
[villager 1] Okay.
[Emi] We're looking for this person,
you see.
[villager 1] Huh?
Hmm…
I don't think I've seen him before.
-Please look closely.
-[villager 1 inhales sharply]
Maybe you've seen him around.
-[Tagaya] Excuse me.
-[Nanmaru] Sorry to bother you.
[Tagaya] We're looking for someone.
Do you know this person?
-[villager 2] I'm afraid not.
-I see.
-Okay. Sorry about that. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Let's try over there.
-Okay.
[Tagaya sighs]
Oh.
I saw that building on the news.
Kurone Construction
[Tagaya] Oh…
The place where the murder happened.
-Nanmaru.
-[Nanmaru] Hmm?
Could you open a hole there from here?
-What?
-You know…
"Chowa!"
[Nanmaru] No way. It's too far away.
I see…
What about Professor Marukami?
Huh?
I'm just saying it's a possibility.
Let's take a break somewhere.
All right.
Cafe Marukami
-[Tagaya] This place looks good.
-[Nanmaru] Yeah.
-[Tagaya] Right?
[Tagaya] All right!
[door bell chimes]
-[cafe owner] Welcome.
-Hello.
[♪ light music playing on radio]
[indistinct chatter on radio]
[exclaims]
Look.
[Nanmaru] A festival.
Marukawa Festival
[Nanmaru] "From June 18th… to June 24th."
That's seven days!
Wow, that's long.
-What kind of festival could it be?
-Good question.
[Sachiko] It's the Tanabata Festival.
[Tagaya] Huh?
Tanabata is usually in July,
or August on the old lunar calendar,
so June is a bit unusual, isn't it?
I suppose that's true.
[Sachiko]
It's always been held in June here.
[Tagaya] Interesting…
[Sachiko] What would you like to order?
-[Tagaya] What will you get?
-[Nanmaru] Hmm?
Um, iced coffee then.
-Two please.
-All right.
-[Sachiko] Two iced coffees.
-[cafe owner] Coming right up.
Hmm? What is it?
It's just, that girl…
-[Nanmaru] We might be closely related.
-[Tagaya] What?
It just kind of hit me.
-It hit you, huh?
-Mm.
So it's not because she's your type?
-That's not the reason.
-What?
-Really?
Yeah.
Sorry for the wait.
[Sachiko] Here's your milk.
[glass clanks]
-[Sachiko] Enjoy.
-Thank you.
[Tagaya] Thanks.
-[door bell chimes]
-[villager 1 sighs]
-[Sachiko] Welcome.
-Hey.
-Boss.
-[cafe owner] Hey.
[exhales deeply]
[grunts]
-[cafe owner] Here you go.
-Thanks.
[groans]
The police are being such a pain
because of the incident.
[villager 1] Why bother coming back
if you go and do something like that?
[cafe owner] You think it was that person?
[villager 1] Of course. Who else is there?
Who else can do that kind of thing?
-Right, Sachi?
-What?
[softly]
Hey. You're being too loud.
There are other customers here.
[villager 1] They won't understand.
Just stop.
It was murder, after all.
[villager 1 whispers]
Fine.
By the way, what about that professor?
[villager 1] Quite something.
You can tell they're a direct descendant.
This coming festival is shaping up
to be a pretty good one.
[cafe owner] It's like the revival
of Lord Marukami, huh?
-Right!
-Exactly.
-[laughter]
-[Tagaya] Excuse me.
The professor you mentioned just now.
Is that Professor Masami Marukami?
[all] Nope.
I see.
So, who might you two be?
Ah. We're students of Professor Marukami.
We lost touch with Professor Marukami
after he came to this town,
so we came to look for him.
Let's see.
Certainly, the name "Marukami" is the same
as the feudal lord who lived around here.
[villager 2] This Professor Marukami…
-Does he have family ties to this town?
-[Tagaya] Yes.
He said he had roots in this town.
Is that so?
So, you really don't know him?
I'm sorry to say,
but I have no idea who he is.
We were just discussing
preparations for the festival.
"Professor" and "lord"
are the names we give
for roles within the festival, you see.
Is that right? Sorry for my interruption.
Not at all.
[Tagaya] Let's go, Nanmaru.
[Nanmaru] Hang on.
Hey! Wait a second.
Excuse me for asking,
but did he just call you Nanmaru?
Ah… My last name is Minamimaru.
My ancestors also lived here.
I think his name was Masayori Marukami.
The same as Professor Marukami.
-Oh my!
-My goodness.
-How rude of us!
-What?
So that's who you are. Mr. Minamimaru!
-[Nanmaru] What?
-How young you are! How old are you?
-[Nanmaru] W-What?
-How about another coffee?
-[Nanmaru] Uh…
-Our cod roe spaghetti is delicious.
-[villager 1] Delicious!
-[villager 2] Right!
-But…
-Please, sit down.
[Emi] I'd like to ask you something.
Did this person come here?
No.
He never stayed here.
Did you come all the way from Tokyo
to search for this person?
[Emi] Yes.
Please contact me
if you discover anything.
-Here's my card.
-[receptionist] Certainly.
You must be terribly worried.
-Thank you.
-[receptionist] Of course.
[footsteps approaching]
-[student] Welcome back.
-Thanks.
It was no use. I didn't find anything out.
I see.
But several people
looked clearly flustered
when they saw
Professor Marukami's picture.
-You thought so too?
-[distant chatter]
Actually, me too…
[Tagaya] Mr. Minamimaru!
-Shall I carry that for you?
-Stop that impression.
-[student] Welcome home.
-[both] Hello.
-[student] How did it go?
-It was amazing.
Nanmaru is a lord.
-A lord?
-[Nanmaru] No, I'm not.
[Tagaya] Right this way. Please sit down.
How old are you?
-I'm 21.
-[Tagaya] Wow!
-Young and spunky!
-What are you saying?
[student] You're a lord for real!
-A real lord!
-[Tagaya] That's right.
They were acting really unfriendly,
but completely changed their tune
when they found out.
[Nanmaru and student laugh]
[Tagaya] You're laughing like a lord!
But a Tanabata in June,
that's unusual, isn't it?
That's true.
Do you know what the "Tanabata"
in Tanabata Festival refers to?
I do.
It's the story in which Altair and Vega,
envisioned as lovers,
cross the Milky Way
to meet once a year, isn't it?
[Nanmaru] Altair?
[splutters]
Vega?
[Tagaya] Mm. They're different names
for Hikoboshi and Orihime.
[exclaims]
-I get it.
-[Tagaya] Now you get it.
It is said
that for Altair and Vega to meet…
"Altair, Vega"
…this bridge
was made by laying out Kasasagi feathers.
Therefore, Kasasagis are said
to be mediators between men and women.
-Wow. I never knew that.
-Hmm.
But there are no Kasasagis
in the Tohoku region.
In Japan, they're only found in Kyushu.
Furthermore, it is said
that they came to Japan
after Toyotomi Hideyoshi's
invasions of Korea.
Then, it would be strange for Kasasagis
to be on flags from Tohoku
in the Sengoku period, right?
This means that the origin of the Kasasagi
depicted on the Marukami flag
must have been some kind of drawing
that came to this village
along with the Tanabata story.
The Kasasagi
must have gradually become symbolized
and further established
with each Tanabata Festival.
That's why they could draw it,
even with no Kasasagis.
[Emi] Exactly.
But… I still don't know
why they chose to have it on their flag.
[all] Hmm…
That's a difficult question.
-[receptionist] Excuse me.
-Yes?
There are some townspeople
waiting at the entrance.
Okay.
Are you Mr. Minamimaru?
[Nanmaru] Yes…
Welcome to the land of your ancestors,
Marukami Village!
[elder] Let me introduce myself.
I'm a member of the town council.
My name is Genichiro Hayano.
Having heard about your visit,
Mr. Minamimaru,
we decided to host a modest banquet
to welcome you all.
[♪ quirky music playing]
Actually…
we came to this town
with a specific purpose.
Yes. I've heard all about it.
I understand you have come here
out of concern
for Professor Marukami's whereabouts.
[inhales sharply]
We at Marukawa Town,
intend to help you
with all our resources--
Mr. Hayano, this isn't an election.
-[laughter]
-Right.
Please, come.
-Yes.
-[villager 1] Let's go.
-[villager 2] Come on.
-[villager 1] Let's head off.
[villager 3] Let's go.
Welcome Party
-Yoshie.
-[Yoshie] Yes!
-Eriko.
-[Eriko] Coming!
[indistinct murmuring]
-Hello.
-[Nanmaru] Hello.
Here you are, young master.
Thanks a lot.
-[glass clinks]
-[liquid pouring]
Now for the servants.
Thanks.
-Here you are.
-Servants?
[indistinct chatter]
Here you go.
Okay. Enjoy.
[villager 1 clears throat]
[silence]
[nervous chuckle]
[soft laughter]
So… cheers!
[all] Cheers!
[villager 2] Drink up!
[applause]
[indistinct chatter]
[cafe owner] Here you go.
Thank you.
-[cafe owner] By the way, Mr. Minamimaru…
-[liquid sloshing]
Yes?
How should I ask this?
Has it been passed down to you too,
Mr. Minamimaru?
You know.
-Do I?
-[soft chuckle]
-[silence]
-Huh?
[insects chirping]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Ah…
[awkward chuckle]
You mean the supernatural ability?
-Wow!
-That's it!
In that case,
how about a display for everyone--
Sorry to interrupt the fun.
But we'd like your cooperation.
I'm Kanemura from the prefectural police's
First Investigation Division.
I would like to ask a few questions
about the recent murder
of Mr. Toshio Kuraishi.
Detective, how can you
barge in here like this?
-Right.
-[villagers] Right!
Don't worry.
I won't take much of your time.
It appears the main opposition
to the golf course construction
are all gathered here.
You lot are from out of town though,
aren't you?
That's right.
-What are you here for?
-[♪ tense music playing]
Stop it already! You have no right
to interrogate our guests.
-[villagers] That's right!
-Come on. This isn't an interrogation.
However, I think they ought to know.
That recently,
a murder occurred in this town,
and the murderer is still at large.
And that the people
who were vehemently opposing
the victim's golf course construction
are gathered here right now.
[Mr. Hayano] Mr. Kanemura, was it?
If you continue to make such rude remarks,
we will have to take action as well.
-That's right!
-Leave already!
[sighs]
Excuse me. I'll come back another time.
[indistinct chatter]
-My apologies.
-I'm terribly sorry about that.
-It's fine.
-Oh dear! That completely ruined the mood.
-[laughter]
-[villager 1] You're not wrong.
Sorry about that.
-Don't worry.
-Please, keep on drinking!
-[villager 2] Yes, let's drink!
-[cafe owner] Here you are, young master.
Thank you.
[villager 3]
This alcohol is delicious, after all.
Thank you.
-[villager 4] Drink it in one go!
-[villager 5] Right.
-I'm sorry, we ended up drinking so much.
-[Mr. Hayano] Not at all!
-Thank you.
-[Nanmaru] Let's head to the next bar.
-No way!
-[laughter]
-We'll take our leave then.
-[Tagaya] I'm going!
[Mr. Hayano] Thank you so much.
-Take care.
-Goodnight.
-I'm stopping at the store on the way.
-They'll be fine.
Goodnight!
[chuckles]
[student] Careful.
-[Tagaya] You drank quite a bit.
-[Mr. Hayano sighs]
[birds chirping]
[Nanmaru groans]
[student] Nanmaru, feeling hung over?
[Nanmaru chuckles softly]
[Nanmaru] I think I might be.
[Tagaya] You'll be fine in no time
with a bit of mountain climbing.
[Nanmaru] Sounds tough.
[Tagaya]
Nanmaru, I made a model of this mountain!
[Nanmaru] Um…
-So what?
-Huh? So I'm telling you it's fine.
-[student] Fine?
-It's fine?
[Tagaya] It's fine! Keep going.
-[student] Really?
-[Tagaya] Yes. It's fine.
[Nanmaru] Have a little mercy.
[Tagaya pants]
I can't go on.
-[Nanmaru] Come on.
-[student] Keep going.
[Nanmaru] Hey, Tagaya.
-[Tagaya] What?
-You're going to get left behind.
-[student] I can't…
-[Tagaya] You know what…
-[Nanmaru] Keep going.
-[Tagaya] Just leave me.
[Nanmaru] Don't give up.
[Tagaya panting]
Hello.
I'm sorry, but…
the festival will be taking place
at the summit soon.
It's off-limits to the general public.
What? But we came all this way.
[villager] I'm terribly sorry.
[Mr. Hayano] Oh.
Mr. Minamimaru?
Hello there.
[Mr. Hayano] What's the problem?
[villager] It seems these people
would like to climb up Mount Marukami.
[Mr. Hayano] What?
This is a bit of a problem.
The festival is nearly here.
Are we free to climb the mountain
when the festival isn't on?
[Mr. Hayano] Well, of course.
I see.
In that case,
Professor Marukami
would have been able to enter last month.
Well, I'm not sure.
We weren't here last month, you see.
[chuckles]
Um…
-wouldn't I be allowed?
-[student] Wait…
What? In your case…
[inhales sharply]
-[Nanmaru] Yes.
-[exhales deeply]
[whispers]
Oh. He's thinking.
Understood.
[Mr. Hayano]
Technically, the festival hasn't started,
so I will grant you special permission.
However, please make it brief.
-[Emi] Okay.
-Thank you.
-[Emi and student] Thank you.
-[pats on arm]
Nothing can stop you, Mr. Minamimaru.
-Nothing at all.
-[Tagaya and student laugh]
-All right!
-Thank goodness.
-Mr. Hayano, are you sure about this?
-[Mr. Hayano] Huh?
It's Mr. Minamimaru, after all.
[Tagaya panting]
-Watch out.
-We made it.
[student exclaims]
-What is all this?
-This place is huge.
[exclaiming]
Wow!
[Tagaya panting]
All right. Just a bit farther.
-[Tagaya] A bit farther.
-[Nanmaru] Just a bit more.
[Tagaya] Hey. You're going too fast.
Professor!
[Tagaya panting]
-All right.
-[student] There are rocks in a line.
They look just like normal rocks.
[Emi] One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
Seven rocks.
There doesn't seem to be much else here.
[Tagaya exhales deeply]
[Tagaya] I knew it, that mountain…
Mount Kurone.
Because of that mountain, the sunset
comes early in this entire area.
[Nanmaru] But even after the sun sets,
it feels like it might reappear
from that opening at the base.
In the end,
we didn't find any clues here, huh?
Where could Professor Marukami be?
-[beeps]
-[can clattering]
-[vending machine tray clanks]
-[can pops open]
[Nanmaru chuckles softly]
Hello, Mr. Minamimaru.
Could it be… that it hit you too?
-[♪ quirky music playing]
-What?
Hit me?
Uh…
Never mind.
What is it?
[nervous grunt]
Um…
You are a person…
Within Reach, aren't you?
Um… what does that mean?
Well…
you have powers.
Right?
Ah!
My telekinetic ability?
[soft chuckle]
Wait a second.
[shouts]
Chowa!
[distant dog barking]
[shouting]
[pops]
-[panting]
-[hurried footsteps approaching]
[receptionist] Is something the matter?
No, sorry. It's fine.
[chuckles]
[Nanmaru] Here.
What's your name?
Sachiko Higashimaru.
So it is.
-[Sachiko] So it is?
-Hmm? Nothing.
[Sachiko] Um…
The people in this town
might say some strange things,
but please don't take them too seriously.
What? Okay…
[Sachiko] You seem like a normal person.
Since you're living a normal life,
I don't think
anyone has the right to interfere.
[Sachiko] Excuse me.
-Huh?
-[door slides close]
Dewa no Kuni Volume 1
Kurone District, Marukawa Town
"Marukami Village"
[knocks on door]
Come in.
[student] Excuse me.
-Excuse me.
-What is it, all of a sudden?
[Emi] Sit down.
-Okay.
I was just…
wondering what to do.
We didn't find any clues at all, did we?
Also, the people in this town
have gotten friendlier
thanks to that daft lord,
but something feels off.
I think that Professor Marukami…
might be being held prisoner
somewhere in this town.
If things go wrong…
You're overthinking it.
But we've been searching all over
and not gotten any witness information.
Isn't that odd?
[student] That's true, but…
Moreover, this town is hiding something…
and everyone is in on it.
[♪ unsettling music playing]
Hiding something?
There was that murder too.
It might be dangerous
to stay here for too long.
Understood.
Let's go back to Tokyo.
[Emi] Right.
But… I want to at least stay
for tomorrow's festival.
It feels like
everything up to now
has been leading up to this festival.
[Emi] In any case,
let's be very careful tomorrow.
We can't trust the townspeople.
-[phone ringing]
-Okay.
-[ringing continues]
I'm sure of it. He opened a hole.
Though only small.
He is Within Reach.
[receptionist] Yes.
Okay.
[Sachiko] I'm off now.
Hey.
Big brother…
[Sachiko's brother]
What? Are you heading out?
To my part-time job.
[♪ uneasy music playing]
We've not seen each other for a while,
so why not stay home?
It's not like you need the money.
Did you cause the recent disturbance
at my workplace?
Yeah. That's right.
There's no need for you to go out to work.
As for money,
we'll be getting plenty of it--
Stop!
Huh?
Don't mess with me.
-Do you want to be punished?
-Stop it!
[Sachiko's grandma] Takashi!
Leave.
I thought I told you to never come back.
What? You want to try it?
Go ahead and try it!
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[mutters]
-[♪ music fades]
You've spoiled my mood.
And on Tanabata too.
[Sachiko sobbing]
[door bell chimes]
[cafe owner] Welcome, Mr. Minamimaru.
-Thank you.
-[cafe owner] Sit where you like.
Okay.
-[glass clinks]
-[liquid sloshing]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Here you are.
-Thank you.
-Here.
I'll have an iced coffee please.
Certainly.
How long will you and your friends
be staying here?
We're going to head home
after seeing the festival today.
What about Professor Marukami?
Ah. Well… I think
the university needs us to head back.
I see…
I suppose that can't be helped then.
[soft chuckle]
What do you plan on doing
after graduation, Mr. Minamimaru?
Well, I still haven't got a job lined up.
Is that right?
You can come to me for advice, any time.
This is your true home, after all.
-Right…
-[cafe owner] Okay?
[both chuckle softly]
-[door opens]
-[door bell chimes]
Sorry I'm late.
It's not like you to be late.
Sorry for the wait.
Thank you.
Sorry about yesterday.
Hang on.
What did you mean yesterday,
about a "person Within Reach"?
What?
[Nanmaru] I've been wondering,
since we're going home tomorrow.
There's still so much I don't understand,
so I was hoping to figure
at least one thing out.
[Sachiko in soft voice]
Listen.
At the festival tonight,
there's the Black Flag Shrine,
just outside the shopping district.
Can we talk there, just the two of us?
Okay.
[♪ light music playing on radio]
-[vendor] Here you go. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-You got it.
-[student] Got it.
Great.
-This is a full-on festival, huh?
-[Nanmaru] Yeah.
Right. There are lots of people.
Look! Candy apples and chocolate bananas.
-I love it.
-So good.
-[student] Hotdogs.
-Huh? Look.
Hang on, what's a "squishy animal"?
Who knows?
-I've never seen it before. Wild, huh?
-[student] What is it?
-[Tagaya] Shall we check it out later?
-[student] For sure.
Sorry, I'm meeting somebody now.
[student] Really? Who?
[Tagaya] The girl from the cafe?
I sort of promised her.
-Huh?
-See you then.
[student] No way…
Sorry. Have you been looking for me?
-No, not at all.
-That's good.
Yes…
[student] Look at him.
He's in love.
Deep in love.
Yup.
[indistinct chatter]
[Nanmaru] It's refreshing to see people
wearing yukatas for once, isn't it?
Don't people normally wear yukatas
at summer festivals?
[Nanmaru] Ah.
[Nanmaru inhales sharply]
Oh yeah,
you can call me Nanmaru,
if Minamimaru is hard to say.
[soft chuckle]
Then that would make me Tomaru then.
[Sachiko]
Nanmaru, are you a university student?
[Nanmaru] That's right.
I'm a fourth-year student now.
But I still haven't found a job.
What about you?
[Sachiko] I never got a proper job
after high school.
I did have a job lined up,
but it didn't work out.
They rescinded the offer?
What a terrible company.
[Sachiko] Over here.
[insects chirping]
[wind gusting]
[Sachiko] Occasionally,
individuals with special qualities
are born into the old families
of this town.
There are two types.
One type is those "Within Reach."
The other type is the "Window Openers."
[♪ light music playing]
As far as I know,
there are six people Within Reach,
including you.
No…
There are only five.
Five telekinetics?
In addition, those who open the window…
and especially those Within Reach,
are the ones qualified to become
the priests of Mount Marukami.
[Nanmaru sighs]
Is it really that impressive?
What?
Certainly, I may be Within Reach.
But still, it's a rather boring ability.
[Nanmaru] Who cares about
such a tiny hole opening up?
Or could it be that…
it has some use I don't know of?
That would be great.
I could use it for my job hunting--
Stop it!
This is not a joke.
What?
Uh…
Forgive me.
I just wanted to say
that I agree with you.
It's useless for everyday life--
No. I wasn't being serious.
[breathes heavily]
Isn't it fine?
To just live normally.
[Sachiko] Normal is best.
[♪ pensive music playing]
Yeah, but…
don't you think
"normal" is difficult these days?
[Nanmaru]
I don't know how to obtain normalcy,
so I at least want something to rely on.
Like a supernatural ability, for example.
[Sachiko] Well,
if you became a priest,
you could make a living
by using your powers.
But you'd never be able
to leave this town.
[laughs]
What? I wouldn't want that.
[both chuckle]
That's a shame.
By the way,
what kind of powers
do Window Openers have?
Well, they don't really have any powers,
and there are lots of them.
I'm actually one of them.
Really?
But…
I can't really explain it.
All I can say is
I sometimes have nightmares.
Mm…
Nightmares…
[♪ festive music playing]
It should be starting soon.
I'm looking forward to it.
[chuckles]
[Takashi] Look at you two.
You both really love this festival.
Takashi? You've come back?
[Takashi] Hmm? Why?
Am I not allowed to come back?
[scoffs]
[inhales deeply, grunts]
Here we go.
-[can pops open]
-[soft grunt]
[exhales deeply]
[Takashi] By the way,
I heard another person Within Reach
besides the new priest
has come to this town.
[Yoshie] Who knows?
I haven't heard anything.
[Takashi] Is that the truth?
So that's how it is.
Whatever.
[Takashi sighs]
[sighs]
A small portion for Professor Emi.
-Here, a large portion.
-[Tagaya] Thanks.
What's that?
[Tagaya] What is it, Professor?
Professor?
-Come on.
-What?
Professor!
Professor! Wait!
Hmm?
[indistinct chatter]
[Takashi groans]
That hurt!
Hey! Wait there!
Look at what you did!
I'd like to have a few words with you,
young man.
[Tagaya] Professor.
Look, above Mount Marukami.
[Tagaya] What?
[student] It's glowing. Is it a bonfire?
[Tagaya] No. But I wonder what it is.
[Emi] I'm going to go check it out.
-Right now?
-Isn't it off-limits?
[Emi] It's fine.
You two wait at the inn.
We can't let you go alone.
[Emi] We can't all go.
All right, you come with me, Tagaya.
Sakuragi, you meet up with Nanmaru
back at the inn.
-Okay.
-[Emi] Let's go.
Okay.
[♪ unsettling music playing]
[Tagaya] Here we go.
[Tagaya pants]
All right.
[both panting]
A bit more.
Shush!
[distant thump]
Can you hear that?
Is that a drum?
[distant thump]
[Tagaya] Here we go.
-[distant thump]
-Nearly there.
[distant thump]
-Turn that off.
-Right.
[distant thump]
[loud thump]
-[distant chanting]
-[loud thump]
[followers chanting]
Come forth…
[villager 1] Hey, what's the matter? Huh?
[groaning]
Take this!
[chuckles]
This should teach you a lesson, jerk!
[villager 1] What's with this guy?
[scoffs]
He's stuck a jewel to his head.
No, it's embedded.
Disgusting.
[villager 1] Forget this guy.
Let's get back to drinking. Come on.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[groans]
You saw…
[Nanmaru grunts]
[Nanmaru]
Where are Professor Emi and Tagaya?
Mount Marukami.
Mount Marukami? At this time?
I thought it was off-limits.
Professor Emi said
she just had to go and see it.
Look at this.
[Nanmaru] What?
Marukawa Town Newsletter
Marukawa festival will be held!
[Sakuragi] Turn the page.
Protests Held
Against Golf Course Construction
Historic Mount Marukami
Don't defile our precious land
Outsiders leave our town
[♪ ominous music playing]
[distant chanting]
[chanting continues]
[loud pop]
[Tagaya] I thought they saw us.
Did you see the person in the middle?
[Tagaya] Yeah. Do you suppose
that person is the most important one?
[animal screeching]
[Tagaya]
There's nothing here but these rocks.
There are only six rocks.
[Tagaya] What?
I'm sure there were seven.
Now there's only six.
One,
two, three…
four, five, six.
You're right.
Does this mean one rock disappears
each day of the seven-day festival?
[Tagaya] Hmm…
[groans]
[♪ tense music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[villager 1] What about Akemi,
by the station?
It should be open.
-All right. Should we call and book--
-[pops]
-[popping]
-[both groan]
[panting]
-[all gasping]
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
[villager 2] What the…
-[groans]
-[breathing heavily]
[villager 3] My leg… My leg!
[villagers whimpering]
[wind gusting]
[♪ fast-paced dramatic music playing]
[♪ music intensifies]
[♪ music stops]
[♪ closing theme music playing]
Translated by Zak