[Sachiko] My brother
has always been pathetic,
just like his power.
[Yoriyuki]
There's somebody I can't forgive.
[Nanmaru] Was he murdered
by Yoriyuki Marukami?
[Sachiko] His dreams…
are scarier than anybody else's.
All of us…
We can't live away from the village.
[Aki] I want to know the truth.
So work with me.
[Oshita] Why did you decide
to become a cleaner?
[Nanmaru]
I feel like it relates to my ability.
Previously on Land of Tanabata
[rustling]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
No way…
[♪ suspenseful music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
-I see something.
-What is that?
[rustling]
Your eyes… You might want to close them.
[loud pop]
[wind howling, gusting]
-[citizen 1] Huh?
-[citizen 2] What just happened?
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ tense music playing]
[citizen 1] Look.
[indistinct chatter]
-[citizen 2] Terrorism?
-[citizen 3] This is crazy.
[citizen 4] An explosion?
-[citizen 5] Run.
-[citizen 6] Run!
[citizen 7] It's dangerous here.
[indistinct chatter]
[citizen 1] It's dangerous here!
[citizens clamoring]
[citizen 2] Hurry!
[citizen 3] Hurry! Just hurry!
[citizens screaming]
Where could it have…
-[citizen 4] No! Oh, no!
-[citizen 5] Come on!
[♪ ominous music playing]
[birds chirping]
[citizens clamoring]
[Takashi] Why go this far?
[Yoriyuki] Just a little more…
I will end the nightmares.
[♪ theme music playing]
Land of Tanabata
[anchor on TV]
A mysterious large explosion
caused the upper floors of
the Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building
in Shinjuku to disappear
as if they had been sliced off.
Rescue operations are ongoing,
and over 200 people are reported missing.
The government has hinted that…
Did…
Yoriyuki do this?
Of course not!
He was a priest who protected
this village. How could he?
Who else could it be?
Furthermore, numerous witnesses
reported seeing a giant black sphere
floating in the sky over the Shinjuku area
just before the explosion.
Investigations are ongoing to see
if this was connected to the explosion.
At the time of the explosion…
[panting]
[Sachiko breathing heavily]
Mom…
[♪ somber music playing]
[sobs]
[Sachiko] Please…
Help Yoriyuki.
Please.
[birds chirping]
In a press conference held by
Chief Cabinet Secretary Mochida earlier,
it was announced
that preparations are underway
to declare a state of emergency
for the Tokyo metropolitan area.
In response to the current situation,
Prime Minister Osanai stated that
in addition to police investigations,
the implementation of security measures
at Self-Defense Force facilities
is also being considered.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Nanmaru grunts]
[clicks tongue, groans]
[♪ light music playing]
[gasps]
[Sachiko] Don't come any closer!
You're about to go Beyond the Window!
[breathes heavily]
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
-[sirens wailing in distance]
-[helicopter whirring]
[clerk] Okay, everyone, due to the state
of emergency being declared,
there's going to be
a large-scale lockdown in Tokyo.
The government has issued a notice
for businesses to suspend operations.
We're really sorry,
but we'll have to stop business activities
and ask everyone to stay at home.
Stay at home?
[clerk chuckles]
But everything's going to be all right!
There's nothing to worry about, okay?
What is this? A war or something?
[Oshita] How are we supposed
to feed ourselves?
-[phone vibrates, chimes]
-[clerk clears throat]
[clerk] If anyone
is considering leaving Tokyo…
"Sachiko Higashimaru
Are you all right?"
…we'll handle your case separately,
so just let us know. Okay?
[chuckles]
Also…
we're planning prompt measures for work
starting tomorrow and beyond.
Please wait for further communication.
[phone keys clacking]
I can't believe it.
Why do such a thing?
The level of this power. It has to be…
[phone vibrates]
[cafe owner] No way.
Yoriyuki would never do such a thing.
There must be…
"I'm okay here."
…some kind of reason.
-[sighs]
-[villager] Yes.
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter]
[popping effect on phone]
[phone chimes]
[frustrated groan]
[clattering]
[phone clanks]
[Sato grunts, whimpers]
[grunts]
[Sato breathing heavily]
-[bone cracks]
-[screams]
[exhales softly]
[Sato groaning]
[Sato groans, breathing heavily]
[Sato breathing heavily]
She says she simply must talk to you.
Thank you for helping out
the Marukawa townspeople in Tokyo.
I appreciate them coming all this way.
As head of the Higashimaru family,
what do you think
about the recent incident in Tokyo?
Somebody has used their power
outside the village.
[Emi] Are you…
talking about Takashi Higashimaru?
No, not Takashi.
He's not capable of that.
Then who is it?
[line cuts]
Do you think they might be involved?
How could they not be involved?
Right now, we know about the ability
of those Within Reach in that village.
That means there must be
something we can do.
[Sakuragi] Something we can do…
Ms. Sayuri Emi
I'm going to Marukawa Town,
to search for clues.
You mustn't.
Why would you do something so dangerous?
Is it because you're a researcher?
Before that…
I'm a person living
in this society, aren't I?
You two go home.
I'll suspend this seminar for a while.
[zipper zips]
I'm coming too.
Me too.
I've come this far. I can't stop now.
[Sakuragi] I'll contact Nanmaru too.
[rain pattering]
[Nanmaru sighs]
What?
[♪ tense music playing]
Yo. Welcome home.
Sir…
[exhales sharply]
Money for the repairs.
I couldn't get in, you see. Sorry.
That's not the problem.
[panting]
That incident…
Yoriyuki Marukami was behind it,
wasn't he?
Perhaps.
[Nanmaru] Perhaps?
You were with him, weren't you?
Don't you understand what he did?
People have…
So many people have died!
[breathing heavily]
He says…
that he wants to put an end
to the gloom in his heart.
That he wants to end the nightmares.
Nightmares?
As for me…
I'm glad I'm not a Window Opener.
What do you mean?
How's Sachiko?
[Nanmaru] What?
I might not be able
to see her for a while.
[Takashi] I came here
to ask you for a favor.
Tell Sachiko…
when you next see her…
that I'm sorry.
Tell her I said that.
[sharp breath]
Sachiko too…
She said she wanted
to apologize to you too.
[Nanmaru] She said…
that you're not really a person
who can commit murder.
I see.
Oh, yeah. One more thing.
[plane engine whirring in distance]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Masumoto]
Why are you taking action by yourself?
Have you forgotten our deal?
[Yoriyuki] Boring.
[Masumoto] What was that?
[Yoriyuki] I've had enough.
I'm going to do as I please.
Tell me, what was it you wanted to do?
[Yoriyuki] I'm canceling our deal.
You crazy monster.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Aki has been kidnapped?
She was probably following me.
Serves her right.
Why are you telling me?
Because I felt gloom in my heart.
[Takashi] Here.
[door opens]
-[clanks in distance]
-[footsteps approaching]
They're around here
Warehouse, connected
What's with this awful map?
[paper rustling]
-[thwacks]
-[subordinate] Hey.
Wake up.
[Sato breathing shakily]
Did you do this?
[Sato gasps, whimpers]
[Sato breathing shakily]
[sighs]
Sorry about that.
Killing you two would be easy,
but there'd be a lot to handle afterward.
[Masumoto] With the weak yen,
we need to save money too.
Still though, the situation has changed.
[Sato whimpering]
[Sato breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[Masumoto]
We can't deal with the bodies here.
Kill the girl for now,
and help carry her body.
[Sato whimpering]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Sato breathing shakily]
[breathing shakily]
[Sato] N-No…
[Masumoto] Here. Aim properly.
[Sato breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
[phone ringing]
[Masumoto] Hello?
That man contacted you?
Yes.
He pulled out of the deal last night.
Okay. I'll be right there.
[grunts]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Masumoto] Leave them here.
We'll deal with them when we get back.
Let's go.
[car door opens, closes]
[car engine starts]
[restraint squeaking]
[breathes deeply]
[rustling]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[restraint squeaking]
[pops in distance]
What was that?
Aki!
[pants]
Nanmaru…
[subordinate 1] Hey!
Who are you?
[breathes nervously]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
Let go! Darn you!
[breathing heavily]
[both grunt]
Let go!
[chair clanks]
-[pops]
-[yelps]
[subordinate 1 gasps]
[screams]
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[grunts, groaning]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Nanmaru!
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[pops]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[Aki breathing heavily]
[Aki] Thank you.
[Aki and Nanmaru] One, two…
[grunt]
Are you all right?
[snips]
[breathing heavily]
-Are you okay?
-[shrieks, breathes shakily]
[♪ pensive music playing]
[subordinate 2 in distance]
Hey!
Has something happened?
[Aki] Can you stand?
-One, two…
-[Sato grunts]
[Aki grunts, panting]
[Sato] It hurts.
What's the matter?
[♪ pensive music continues]
I…
could have killed somebody.
That was…
It's my fault.
[Nanmaru] Back then…
if you hadn't stopped me…
[breathes shakily]
…I could have…
[elder] Masumoto told me.
That you pulled out of the deal.
These strange incidents
that have been occurring…
Are they your doing too?
[Yoriyuki] The recent one
was interesting, wasn't it?
What are you thinking?
-Tell me your goal!
-[cane thumps]
[Yoriyuki] I hardly ever get work
from you, and when I do, it's boring.
Surely not…
That's your reason?
[Yoriyuki] I needed to experiment.
Size, speed…
How much directional accuracy
I could maintain…
I thought you were
more sensible than this.
[Yoriyuki] I thought you might say that.
Anyway…
Thanks for everything.
However…
in a few minutes, you'll be thinking this…
"Once a person owns a pet,
they should bear responsibility
until the end."
[♪ ominous music playing]
Understood.
-Let's move fast.
-[subordinates] Yes, sir.
[elder] He's like a nuclear weapon now.
I must take action.
To the Prime Minister's office! Hurry!
[♪ music fades]
[loud pop]
[wind howling, gusting]
-[sirens wailing in distance]
-[helicopter whirring]
[♪ tense music rises]
[♪ closing theme music playing]
Translated by Zak