[melodic acoustic guitar playing]
♪ Love is all we need is what they say ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Mm… ♪
Saeko.
-Hi. Here you are.
-Thank you.
-See you next month?
-Yes, for sure.
-Have a good day.
-Bye.
Cheers.
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
-Hi.
-[man 1] Hey, Saeko.
Hiro's coffee is the best!
[Saeko] I know, right?
[man 2] Tell him.
♪ Hear the waves ♪
♪ The simple days ♪
♪ Thought it was a phase ♪
♪ But I'm still alive… ♪
-[man 1] Hey, welcome back!
-Hey, guys. I'm back.
How are you doing?
-By the way, I love the T-shirts.
-Good shirt. Good shirt.
-Good job.
-Nice work. They look great.
Hey, I'm back.
[Hiro] Oh. Good to see you.
You know what? [sighs]
I just can't get used to it.
Keep seeing my face
everywhere I go now.
[both laugh]
Ah, well, guess what?
I've got even more
Hiro merch coming real soon.
Oh. [laughs]
-[Saeko chuckles]
-[Hiro sighs]
How was the bank?
Good. You leave it to me.
I know my negotiations.
You're good.
When I go,
I just start yelling at everyone.
I always thought
that people are one of two things.
It's like they're either a person
you love to be around,
or they're a person
whose company you just can't stand.
And my next thought was,
"Hold on, that's not right."
That most people I know are neither.
You're good at calling stuff out.
Mm.
That's business, all right.
All right.
[sighs]
Will you be okay?
You know I'm not able
to stay here forever, right?
I'm gonna have to leave.
Oh, I'm aware.
I know you've gotta go
discover more coffee somewhere.
That's right, I do.
-[groans]
-The beans are calling me.
I smell 'em.
[laughs]
Are you doing okay, Saeko?
I'm told you overdo it on the drinking.
Sometimes you go nuts and start shouting,
then burst into tears.
-[chuckles]
-Who told you about that?
[Hiro] Hmm?
Everyone!
"Everyone"?
-[Hiro] Yeah.
-It was you.
-"Everyone"?
-No, Saeko. It was Joe.
-Saeko, it's Olivia.
-Joe, man.
-Sister, come on now.
-No way.
-You're always blaming me. You are.
-[Saeko] Mm.
-[Saeko chuckles]
-[Hiro] Okay.
[phone buzzing]
This is Saeko.
Can I ask who's calling?
[wistful music playing]
I knew it.
I have been here before.
That is, Yusuke's been here before.
What's going on?
Ah. Sorry, I just, uh, kinda showed up.
But I'd like it…
if I could stay with you a few days.
Huh?
This is a visit as Yusuke.
I'm not visiting as Kazumasa.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry, but what are you doing?
Okay, uh, the other day,
before you left, you and I had that talk.
Actually, you did most of the talking,
and I listened.
Yeah.
Well, there was something
that I didn't get to say.
Oh? Uh, sorry.
I kept talking about myself.
It's okay.
I, uh, got an update on my health.
Oh yeah?
Uh, no, it's not…
It's nothing bad.
It's a… It's a good update.
-It's good?
-Yeah.
I am healthy, yeah. And getting better.
Uh, my doctor said,
"Don't worry, you're doing so good."
I think I'm gonna live a nice long life.
This heart I got, it feels great.
-Hey! Okay, good.
-Mm.
They said the treatment
for the rejection's working.
So what that seems to mean is…
I think that I'll start
to lose Yusuke's memories.
Yusuke
really will disappear from this world.
Because of that, I…
I thought you'd want some time
to be with Yusuke… if this is it.
I'd really like you to enjoy
these last few days
with Yusuke still here.
Say goodbye to him
so that you won't be left
with any regrets.
[Hiro] Saeko.
[Saeko] Oh.
-You okay?
-[Saeko] Yeah.
Hiro, I'd like to introduce…
Got coffee inside.
Of course I believe you.
All of it.
Aren't you lucky, Saeko?
There's a lot of folks
who have the person they love
leave suddenly,
and they're left constantly thinking that
they would've liked
to say a proper goodbye.
Yep.
And it's the same
for… for those who've left
and those left behind.
All over the world,
people share this experience.
But Saeko, listen.
You've got a chance
to say goodbye properly.
Kazumasa's here, so you can do that.
That makes you lucky.
Yeah.
Thank you so much.
For the coffee too.
It's delicious.
Mm.
Saeko, you don't worry about work.
I've gotten quite enough work
out of you already.
Think about how you want
to spend your time and spend it well
for the sweet guy
who traveled to be with you
and also your boyfriend.
Okay?
Thank you very much.
Mm.
[Kazu sighs]
[Kazu chuckles]
[melodic acoustic guitar music playing]
[Kazu] There.
Hey.
-What?
-Really?
-Having trouble?
-This okay?
-Okay, this is done.
-Whoa.
-You're good.
-I know, right?
[silverware clatters]
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
[Kazu chuckles]
All right.
-Whoa! Didn't expect that!
-[gasps]
-That was scary.
-I got it. I'm okay.
-[Saeko] Okay, let's eat.
-[Kazu] Mm!
[Saeko] Smells good.
[Kazu] Oh.
I wonder if I'll ever be able
to have any alcohol one day.
Hmm?
[chuckles]
Like, what if I become,
like, an awful drunk?
Like always shouting, "I need a beer!"
You know, like some stereotypical bad boy.
[both laugh]
Your idea of what
a stereotypical bad boy is is interesting.
That's like what a kid might say.
-[Kazu] Really, you think so?
-Mm-hmm.
[Kazu] Maybe because
I've always wanted to be someone like that
since I was a kid.
[Saeko] Hmm?
[Kazu] Yeah, like a rebel, you know?
Maybe I haven't grown out of it.
[chuckles]
Oh, but really, mostly what I wanna be is…
a guy who does a lot of goofy things
and, mm, makes you wonder.
Someone who's fun.
Mm. Yeah, I see.
And I think it's because I'm so quiet
I always worry I'm being,
you know, a headache.
I worry people just by being alive.
Oh, I do think
it's a really good thing
I got Yusuke's heart.
'Cause I somehow became
a little more… more fun to hang out with.
His memories are all fun things.
Mm, it's great.
[chuckles]
But he's leaving,
and it's pretty sad.
I'll miss him.
Mm.
[emotional piano music playing]
Sorry.
I said I was here as Yusuke,
and I've just, um, been Kazumasa today.
But you can be you.
No "sorry" needed.
I'm enjoying you.
You really think this is interesting?
Mm-hmm. I'm enjoying it.
I think it's fun.
Okay.
Mm.
Well, I'm glad.
[Kazu] Oh no!
[Saeko] Ah!
[both laugh]
[emotional piano music continues]
[Kazu] Thanks.
-[Saeko giggles]
-What a mess.
[both laugh]
Whoa.
So this is what… you wanna do?
I never got to live with Yusuke, so…
Mm.
-Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
[chuckles]
Huh?
Can I…
Please?
[both giggle]
[emotional piano music continues]
[music fades]
This is Saeko.
Can I ask who's calling?
This is Miki Naruse.
Kazumasa's wife.
I'm sorry to just call you
out of the blue like this.
Kazumasa should be arriving there
anytime now.
What?
And this is what he's gonna say.
That he's in good health,
great physical condition.
And that means
that the memories of your fiancé
will disappear
for good.
And he's there for you to say goodbye.
That's why he flew there.
But… it's a lie.
The heart that he has…
is about to give out.
Kazumasa is dying.
He's getting weaker as we speak.
And still he… he just had to see you.
Even though he's about to die,
he said it was important.
He couldn't help himself.
He just wanted to see you
one last time before he dies.
That's what he said.
No, that's…
Why are you doing this?
'Cause I love Kazu.
The love I feel
is more than just an ordinary love.
So I've accepted it.
And if you're wondering
why I'm calling you right now…
it's because I want you to suffer too.
I want you to go along with this lie
that he has gambled his life on.
I want you to…
[melancholy piano music playing]
…to shoulder the burden
of that kind of pain too.
And I'm sure that
he's gonna act like he's recovered.
Don't believe what he's telling you.
He definitely has his limits.
There's a lot he can't do.
Too much exertion
could make him suddenly drop dead.
And I just couldn't bear
to have that happen, so…
First of all, he absolutely cannot
drink any alcohol.
And please don't let him run
or carry anything heavy.
And one more thing…
[breathes deeply]
[sobs]
…if he has…
if he has sex…
it would put his life in danger.
[sniffles]
[Miki] That's it.
Please take care of my husband.
[melancholy piano music continues]
[sobs]
[sniffles]
[music fades]
[exhales sharply]
-[Joe] We got the spare ribs there.
-[Kazu] Wow, that's amazing.
[Joe] Thanks, sister.
-Hey! Where are you going?
-[Olivia] No!
-Wait!
-[man] No, you're our guest, okay?
-Take a seat.
-[Joe] Sit down and relax.
-Come on. I love that stuff.
-[man] Gotta keep my eye on you.
-[Kazu] Thank you.
-[man] Enjoy yourself.
Cheers.
-[Joe] Cheers. Cheers.
-[man] Cheers. Cheers.
[melodic acoustic guitar music playing]
[Kazu] Oh, that looks really good.
-Is that spam?
-[man] Hmm?
-Ah, spam. Yeah, yeah.
-You want some?
-Oh, look at that.
-Looks great!
-Help yourself.
-Thank you. Thank you.
[man] Can you pass the plate?
[Kazu] Thank you.
[guitar player humming]
Will you dance with us? Come.
-[Kazu] Really?
-Yeah.
-You should do it.
-Come on. Let's go.
-Let's go.
-You can do it. Don't be shy.
-Come right over here.
-[Kazu laughs]
-You can dance?
-Yes.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Right here.
-Okay. One.
-One.
-Two. Yep.
-Two.
-[Olivia] Three. Four.
-[Kazu] Three. Four.
-Now your hands.
-Uh…
-[man] Ah yeah!
-Cool!
-This way.
-Hey! You get in here. Yeah, get Saeko.
-No, no, no, no.
-[Kazu] Come on, get over here.
Saeko, go on!
[giggles]
Come on, it's fun.
-[man] You got it, Saeko.
-It's fun.
Here we go. Right here. Ready?
Okay, so…
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
-Four.
Hands.
-One.
-Oh, like this?
Nice and slow. Beautiful.
[melodic acoustic guitar music continues]
[inaudible dialogue]
[music fades]
You sure?
Mm.
Can you hear it?
Mm-hmm.
Fall asleep listening to it.
The sound of Yusuke.
[Saeko] Mm.
[chuckles]
You know what?
It's a T, huh?
A "T"?
Mm-hmm.
The letter. We're in the shape of a T.
Ah.
[both chuckle]
T.
Good night, Kazumasa.
Sleep well, Saeko.
[wistful music playing]
[sniffles]
[chuckles]
Sorry about that.
[sniffles]
I'm sure you're wet from my tears.
Mm.
[sniffles]
[laughs]
[both laugh]
[Saeko] When you laugh, I can't hear it.
[Kazu] Sorry.
-[laughs]
-So don't do it.
Yeah, okay.
[wistful music continues]
[Saeko] Come to think of it,
what was that?
What was what?
The very first time I met Yusuke,
he played me a song,
"I Want You Back," here in the airport.
Though before that, he played this song
that was kinda strange.
Not a song, really, but a melody.
I wonder what it was he played.
When I was…
When he was…
having a beer,
seeing you for the first time.
[sighs]
[Kazu] You, uh,
seemed like you weren't doing great.
Or like you were upset.
You looked like
you didn't want to leave like that.
And you were crying.
[chuckles]
[Kazu] So I wondered
if there wasn't something I could do.
Then I saw the piano.
I wanted you to stop crying.
I wanted to cheer you up.
Because
not everything in this world is bad.
I wanted to tell you somehow,
so I…
Here, look.
I wanted to tell you a word…
so I thought I'd play it.
[piano continues playing]
[piano stops]
"Smile"?
Saeko.
Smile, okay?
[chuckles]
I want you to smile.
Always.
[laughs]
["Smile" playing]
[music stops]
["I Want You Back"
by The Jackson 5 playing]
[dissonant notes playing]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[Kazu sighs]
[emotional piano music playing]
Thank you
for doing this.
You're welcome, Saeko.
I'm so glad someone like you exists
on this earth.
[emotional piano music continues]
[Saeko laughs]
Hang in there.
[Kazu chuckles]
And the same to you.
[both chuckle]
[emotional piano music continues]
[truck engine starts]
[music fades]
[breathes deeply]
[sniffles]
It's all right, sweetie.
Mm. You look great.
[sniffles]
[breathes deeply]
[emotional string music playing]
[Miki sobs gently]
[Kazu sighs]
You're here.
Yeah, I'm here.
[emotional string music intensifies]
[emotional string music continues]
[music fades]
-[Yuma] That one!
-[man 1] Yeah.
[man 2] Careful, don't damage it.
Here. This one's perfect, right?
Thank you.
[woman 1] Ooh!
-[woman 2] Ah, look at him.
-[woman 1] So helpful!
[man 2] Okay.
[footsteps approaching]
[Kengo] Okay, here you go.
Thank you very much.
[sighs]
Hey, Kengo.
Listen. Sorry if I'm mistaken.
Hmm?
But from now on,
why don't we not
fall in love with the same guy?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
[chuckles]
Mm.
[Kengo] Mm!
It's that time.
Wanna give it some water?
Mm-hmm.
[gasps]
[sentimental music playing]
[woman 1 gasps] Saeko!
-Hi, Saeko.
[gasps]
Saeko!
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know,
just doing a couple things here.
Hoping I could come say hi to you.
[Midori] Aw!
[laughs]
Aw, you were?
-[Saeko] Oh!
-Huh?
What?
Huh?
I didn't just sit here
getting fat since you left.
[gasps, chuckles]
[laughs]
None of us knows where life's adventures
will take us, do we?
[Saeko gasps]
[Saeko exclaims happily]
Congratulations!
Aw, thank you.
[Midori laughs]
[feel-good music playing]
Shinoda!
Oh!
Here.
Smell that.
Hmm? What is it?
That's something new.
[Shinoda laughs]
Good, right?
[Saeko] Mm.
[feel-good music continues]
[conductor] Is there anyone
who doesn't have a passenger ticket
or is extending their ride
and needs to change their ticket?
[music fades]
THIS IS MIKI NARUSE.
WE'RE BUSY WITH APPLE PICKING
AND NEED MORE HANDS.
IT STARTS ON OCTOBER 6TH.
I WILL SEE YOU THEN.
What is she doing?
That's very strange.
NISEKO STATION
So…
Get in.
But are you…
[car door closes]
[car engine starting]
All right, I'm a bit lost.
What's happening?
What exactly are we doing?
What was the idea of having me come out?
Oh, uh, I texted you everything.
I need your help. It's our harvest season.
Yeah, I got that. I read what you wrote.
It's just that I don't understand
why you want me out here.
Well, you see, uh…
Mm, we really need a lot of workers,
so I thought, "Let's see."
"Is there anyone who owes me something
and needs to clear their debt
who might feel like
they owe me an apology?"
"If so, I'd get them to help me."
"Oh! I know who."
"Let me get Saeko."
There you go.
Okay.
And thanks for asking me.
[Miki] Mm.
This favor's actually an annual one.
-Hmm?
Well, once a year, I'd like to see you.
[chuckles]
All right, I understand.
[both laugh]
[rhythmic pop music playing]
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[music ends]