[gentle acoustic guitar music playing]
-[Kazu] If you'd like some.
-[man 3] Oh, thank you.
-For you too, sir.
-Oh, no. I shouldn't.
-Oh, no. Go ahead.
-Thank you very much for this.
-[woman 1] It's delicious.
-[woman 2] I know!
[indistinct chattering]
[Kazu sighs] Thanks for helping.
[Saeko] Sure.
Ah, for you.
-[Kazu] Thank you.
-Enjoy.
[Kazu sighs]
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Didn't know how beautiful it was out here.
I've taken this train a long time,
but I never noticed.
[Saeko] Me neither.
[Kazu] Yeah.
Though I suppose I never got off here.
You think that makes us lucky, then?
It stopped, and then we actually
discovered real beauty out here.
[sighs]
Now, uh…
[music fades]
we've met somewhere before, right?
Huh?
Uh, when was it that I met you?
I don't think we've met before.
Oh, really? This is the first time?
I could've sworn that we've met.
Oh, I'll take that from you.
That's okay.
[Kazu] Oh, no. Well, I'm sorry.
Well, um, I wasn't trying to, you know…
-I wasn't trying to--
-Do you have a towel for this?
Oh, the dish towel is in here.
-Got it, thanks.
-Yeah.
Well, thank you for the coffee. [chuckles]
Hey. But wait. I still wanted to talk.
[conductor] Thank you
for all your patience.
I sincerely, sincerely apologize
for taking up all of your valuable time
this morning.
We will depart soon.
Oh…
[conductor] I would also like
to give a big thank-you
to the passenger
who kindly shared his coffee with us.
I was actually moved to tears.
-Now, please be seated. We'll depart soon.
-Thanks!
[woman 1] Oh, hey. Thank you so much!
-[man 1] Thank you.
-Oh, don't.
-[man 2] Thank you for the coffee.
-[man 3] Thank you so much.
-[woman 2] Thank you so much.
-Of course. You're welcome.
[man 4] Thank you so much.
[train alert chimes]
[whimsical music playing]
Why don't we call them first and confirm?
[man 1] Oh, good morning.
[Saeko] Good morning!
[man 2] Okay. Yeah, I'll call them.
[man 1] But double-check the numbers
'cause last time…
I'm so sorry I'm late.
-Let's begin.
-[Saeko] Yes.
All right, let's start with dry aroma.
-Right, okay.
-[Saeko] Yes.
[sniffs]
[man 3] Please go ahead.
[man 4] I like the light roast
of number three.
It had a very refreshing aftertaste.
[woman 3] It was great
in terms of uniqueness,
but I think it's a touch too bright.
[woman 4] I prefer
the darker roast of number one.
[woman 5] I enjoyed
the syrupy sweetness of it.
Like brown sugar.
I also liked the dark roast of number one.
Although, is it missing something?
I thought it tasted flat,
so let's fine-tune its roast time
to give it more contrast?
[Saeko] This one is quite eccentric.
It's very spicy and complex,
yet it's quite delicious.
[Shinoda] You know,
there's the eccentricity
and there's also the thickness of it,
but it's difficult
to get them both in a cup together.
With your skills, you can make it work.
[chuckles] Well, look.
Just 'cause you flatter me
doesn't make it possible.
If we can figure this out,
we'll have another flagship product.
And just how are we supposed to do that?
-Hey!
-What?
-I think--
-Yeah?
Let's think this through once more, hmm?
-Shinoda.
-Yeah.
Number one or number two?
Which represents us better?
Hmm…
[music ends]
Number one, I'd say.
[woman 6] I see.
-[groans]
-[woman 6 laughs]
[Saeko] You know what?
On second thought,
I realize now that what he said wasn't
exactly the most groundbreaking statement.
So what if he and Yusuke
made the same observation once?
[sighs] I feel stupid.
What was I thinking?
[Kengo sighs]
And he seemed like
a really nice person too.
[inhales sharply]
Uh, I treated him terribly.
When he asked if we had met before,
I completely shut down.
I guess it could be just that
I looked like someone he knew.
I mean, we take the same train together.
I see.
That's it.
Sorry. I have nothing to add to that.
You're a good listener,
so that's already enough.
Are you serious? I'm just a listener?
You are! In this world,
everyone needs a good listener.
If everyone always said
every single thought…
If there were only people
like me walking around,
this world would be too noisy.
-Really.
-[laughs]
All right. I guess it works out.
Yeah.
Come to think of it,
I remember you were more of a listener
with Yusuke as well.
[Kengo chuckles]
Was it always like that
since you guys were little?
Basically.
Good to know.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
-What's that?
-[Kazu chuckles]
Wow!
-You know what?
-Hmm?
I'm glad you can drink coffee now,
especially since
you never liked it before.
But it seems like you didn't just
get over the dislike of coffee.
You really like it now.
Oh, you are right. I think you're right.
Mm-hmm.
So you… you like it, huh?
It's good to explore new passions in life.
-Mm.
-I think it's wonderful.
I just think I'll be sad if you start
disliking things you used to like.
What?
[chuckles softly]
No.
I won't.
I haven't really changed,
and the things I like won't change.
Like my favorite ramen is… still miso.
That won't change.
-I wasn't thinking of that.
-[chuckles]
-I like sauce over my fried eggs.
-That won't change either.
-[giggles]
I heard Miyazaki does too.
-What? Really?
-Yeah.
-Oh, who cares?
-[both laugh]
Let's see, what else?
[wistful music playing]
[Yusuke] Maru Coffee! [laughs]
-[Kengo] Maru Coffee!
-[Saeko] I thought it was cute.
[Yusuke] It's so chic and so stylish.
Who came up with this?
-[Saeko] Yeah, who?
-[Kengo] It was Yusuke!
[Saeko and Yusuke laugh]
[Yusuke] Maru means "round."
Or "a circle."
-Mm.
-'Cause the Earth is round.
Uh, so even if people end up separated,
they circle back to each other, you know?
That's where "Maru" came from.
Check this out.
[Yusuke laughs]
-[Saeko] What are you doing?
-Hey! What?
It's important that you do it slowly!
-[Kengo] See?
-No! This will improve it!
-I'm serious. And in circles.
-I told you!
-It turned out good!
-[Kengo] Guess it's not bad.
It's so good. It's so good, right?
You like it, don't you?
[Kengo and Yusuke] Oh yeah.
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
-[Saeko] No, no, no. You're not there yet.
-[Yusuke] Huh?
[Saeko] You're not!
[man 1] Whoa!
[man 2] All right! Here they come!
-[man 3] Woo-hoo!
-Look at that!
Whoa!
[Saeko] Look at it!
They're huge! So pretty!
We love fireworks!
[all] We love fireworks!
Tonight, Saeko, you look so beautiful!
[all cheering]
-[man 4] Here comes another one!
-Whoo!
[Saeko] You'll get sunburned
if you lie down there.
-That's okay. [laughs]
-[Saeko] You sure?
I wanna get a tan.
-Whoa. That's dangerous.
-[Saeko laughs] It is!
[Yusuke] Hey. Can I use it for a second?
The view from here is awesome.
-Look!
-[Kengo] Oh, this is awesome.
-Wow!
-[Yusuke] So cool.
We gotta get some photos by the water.
Come on.
[Kengo] Yusuke.
[Kengo laughs]
[Saeko] Yeah, the view is nice.
[Yusuke] So tell me…
Kengo.
[Saeko] My favorites?
[Kengo] Hmm?
[Saeko] Um, let me think.
Shake my hand.
Yeah? Here.
[Kengo chuckles]
[Saeko giggles]
[both chuckle]
Grow big.
I'm rooting for you.
[laughs]
I was just thinking.
If coffee cherries grow here…
[sighs] …I'll be ecstatic.
Think I'll cry. Yeah.
[laughs]
Ah… Look at it.
Isn't it so cute?
[wistful music continues]
[music fades]
-[child 1] Those ones are bright red!
-[child 2] Oh, you're right!
-Those ones look good.
-They're pretty.
-[child 2] There are centipedes!
-You see?
-[child 1] Awesome!
-[Kazu laughs]
-Centipedes?
-[child 2] Keep running!
-You guys are fast. Be careful!
-[child 3] We're gonna get bitten!
-Thank you for doing this again this year.
-Oh, hi!
-It's so generous of you.
-We love doing this.
-The kids were so excited to come today.
-That's great to hear.
-Hello. It's wonderful to have you here.
-Oh, hello. Thank you so much.
-[woman 1] Wow! Look at those apples!
-[woman 2] Try them.
-[woman 3] Beautiful.
-[woman 1] They look perfect.
-[child 3] I know!
-Yes!
Because the sunlight
doesn't reach this side.
-That's correct. Well done!
-[child 4] Wow. You're smart.
-Now, you take this…
-[child 5] That's so cool.
…and point it towards the sunlight
like that. That's great!
Let's clear this area out
so that plenty of sun will reach it.
-[woman 1] Sure. All right.
-[woman 2] Yeah?
[Kazu] Run! Run!
[children shouting playfully]
[Kazu shouting playfully]
[Kazu] Watch out! Watch out!
Oh, there you are! I'm coming for you!
[playful shouting continues]
[man 1] Watch out!
[ethereal music playing]
Miki!
[woman 1] Wow, you all run so fast!
Make sure you wash up before you eat.
[music fades]
Hello.
Yes? You need something?
Um…
Yes. Would you like to date
and get married eventually?
I would be honored.
What?
Uh, I could marry you right now.
I really like you!
[sighs]
I couldn't conceal how I feel any longer.
Yeah, but I don't think
I'm the right guy for you.
Well, I disagree.
It… it's very flattering.
-However…
-[moans]
Oh God!
No, uh…
Um… it's just that… Well, I'm so plain.
[chuckles] That's fine though.
I'll be the flashy one
when we're together.
-And boring.
-That's all right.
I have a good sense of humor.
You'll see. [giggles]
Yeah, but I'm unreliable,
and I look frail.
Look how little I eat,
even though I'm a man.
[chuckles] That's okay.
I'm tough, dependable,
and I always have a lot to eat.
[both laugh]
Well…
I don't know if you've been told or not…
I have a condition.
A heart condition.
That's okay. My heart is strong enough
for the two of us.
-[chuckles]
-Oh?
[Miki] Hmm?
[chuckles]
[Kazu] I guess I have
no excuse to turn you down.
Because for a long time…
Well, I've had feelings for you too.
Ever since you were Miss Apple.
[Miki] What?
What? Really?
I can't believe it.
I'd love for us to be together.
[chuckles]
I'd like that as well.
[both laugh]
So is it good?
[woman 1] Hey, guys!
Does anyone want more?
-[Kazu] I'll take that.
-[woman 1] You want some?
-[child 6] I do! I do!
-[woman 1] There's plenty to share.
-[Kazu] Here comes another plate.
-[woman 1] This one.
-[Kazu] There's plenty more.
-[child 6] Look! I'm a two-way player!
[Kazu] Two-sport style?
[Miki sighs]
Hey.
What is it?
Aren't you just so glad for Naruse?
What do you mean?
Oh, just look at him!
He's so cheerful and full of life.
Isn't he?
[Miki] Stop it.
What? What's wrong?
Of course it's a good thing
that he recovered.
What I mean is, don't say you're glad
he's becoming cheerful.
It sounds like he wasn't
good enough before.
What? Oh no, I'm not saying that.
Well, you might as well be saying that.
Saying that I fell in love and married him
when he wasn't good enough for you.
It's just insulting.
Oh, is that how that works?
Yes, it is!
Just stop acting so thrilled
that he's become a different person.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Well, I'm so glad
that Naruse's become so cheerful.
-Sorry, the teacher asked me…
-He's behaving like a different person.
…if they can come help us again in autumn.
-What?
-One other thing. The kids were saying…
[Kazu laughs]
-Mmm!
-You kids ate a lot.
-It's yummy! Yeah.
-Really? Yeah, good.
[feel-good music playing]
-[Kazu] Huh? Um--
-I wanna say…
I apologize for the other day.
Oh, don't… don't worry. I was a little--
No. I was the one at fault.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I couldn't bear to leave it
the way it ended.
I behaved like someone who thinks
everyone's hitting on her.
You didn't deserve that,
especially after you made coffee for us.
And so,
I'm really sorry I ruined everything.
Yeah. Still, I was--
Don't say you were also responsible.
I was the only one in the wrong.
Okay. I won't, then.
I apologize for how forceful I seem.
[chuckles] Uh, no…
Uh, if you'd like to…
Uh…
[chuckles]
[music fades]
Uh, so… my name is Naruse.
-Ah.
-It's nice to see you again.
And I live in Niseko.
My wife's family
has an apple orchard there.
Oh.
-Well, it's nice to meet you properly.
-Likewise.
I'm Sugawara.
I live near Rankoshi Station.
I actually moved there quite recently.
Oh, so you're actually from Otaru, then?
No. I was born and raised in Tokyo.
My parents are there.
But I went through a lot recently,
so I got a new job and moved here.
Oh, I see.
Uh, what do I do?
I'm dealing with so much.
-Hmm?
-Here's the thing.
I actually have been working
in the coffee business.
Oh!
Yeah.
Wait.
You're saying that you're
a coffee professional?
Uh, yep. You could say that.
Crap! You should've said that earlier
because I was lecturing you
like you were a novice or something.
Well, when would I have told you?
Well, that is true, I guess.
So you know about brewing coffee as well?
Uh, yes, I do.
Oh wow! Are you serious?
Just be honest with me. How did it taste?
Oh, yeah, it was awful.
[both laugh]
-[Kazu] I'm sure it was.
-Yeah.
-[Kazu] How embarrassing.
-[Saeko laughs]
-[Kazu] Sorry about that.
-[Saeko] Oh, that's all right.
I have one piece of advice
to brewing delicious coffee.
Yeah. Go ahead.
So let's say right here,
this is our dripper.
-Mm-hmm.
-Pour a little water slowly at first.
Then, once it's absorbed,
you can pour the rest,
starting from the center.
Huh…
-[Saeko] See you.
-[Kazu] So long.
-[Saeko] Have a good day.
-[Kazu] You too.
[feel-good music continues]
[student 1] Excuse me.
Uh, yes?
How can I help you?
-Um…
-Hmm?
-I had a question about this.
-Okay.
[student 2] Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Uh, yeah.
[feel-good music continues]
So I do it like that?
[music ends]
Hey, I have coffee for everyone.
-It's not from a cafe. I made it myself.
-Wait, what's that?
-Oh, he's got coffee!
-Wow! This is great.
-Go ahead. Enjoy.
-Thank you!
-Appreciate it.
-What? Coffee?
-Can I have one?
-Of course.
What's going on here?
-I wanted to try brewing some myself.
-This is so good.
-Is it really?
-I love it. Yeah.
-It's delicious, right? Isn't it?
-It's great.
-[man 1] This is good.
-[woman 1] It's relaxing.
-[woman 2] What a treat!
-[woman 3] Mmm. Wow, it's good!
-[woman 1] It calms you down, right?
-[woman 4] It really does.
[woman 1] It's nice to relax,
take a breather.
It's delicious. [chuckles]
[announcement] The local train
for Oshamambe
will soon be departing from Platform Two.
Please make sure to board in time.
Oh, hey there.
-Good evening.
What a nice coincidence
seeing you twice in one day.
It only comes once an hour, so… [giggles]
Well, that's true.
-Let's… [chuckles]
-Ah.
[conductor blows whistle]
[train alert chimes]
[melodic pop music playing]
I miss those days.
I wish I could go back. I'm jealous.
Sure, but college kids now
are having it really tough.
Like trying to find work.
So then, why did you want to work
at a coffee company?
[chuckles] It's a long story.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I wanna hear it.
It's an interesting company to work for.
Everybody who works there
has had their life changed by coffee
in some strange way.
Oh…
They owe their lives to coffee, huh?
-Huh…
-[laughs]
Now that I've started,
I kinda wanna tell you more.
What?
[Saeko] I was like, "Let's go farther,"
but they didn't listen to me
and kept saying, "Let's go back."
So I said, "Fine, but I'm going.
Which way is it?"
-Mm. Mm.
-And I started walking.
Then, the next thing I knew,
I was lost somewhere
in the mountains of Costa Rica.
But there was jungle everywhere.
-Wow. That's crazy.
-I was so lost.
It took a while to figure it all out.
[children giggling]
[child 1] Where do you wanna sit?
-[child 2] Over here!
-[Kazu] Here.
[child 1] Wow. This is cool!
They look like they're married.
[child 3] Ah! Ah! You guys are flirting!
-No, we're not.
-[child 4] Are they really?
-No, no. We're not.
-We're not. We're not.
Whoa, whoa. We're not. We're not.
-[children chanting] You're in love!
-Knock it off right now! I'm so sorry.
[panting]
[sighs]
[melodic pop music continues]
Huh?
Good evening.
I wanted to hear the rest of your story.
[laughs]
[music fades]
[sighs]
I accidentally found out
that they're planning to
have a surprise thing for my birthday.
Ah, I think I understand it all now.
When is it?
Well, it's tomorrow.
-Oh.
-But that's not the point of the story.
I overheard it when they were busy
preparing for the surprise.
Mm.
How should I respond to it?
Should I just act surprised, like, "Wow!"
Or something like that?
What would you do?
Mm…
You should act like you didn't know.
Just act excited about it
since that's what they're hoping for.
-Mm. That's what I thought.
-Mm.
Hold on.
Actually, though…
I shouldn't?
That would've been
my usual course of action.
-But you should have fun with it.
-What?
You act like you didn't know,
you're surprised,
you make everyone excited.
Then, when everyone is all excited,
you surprise them.
You reveal you knew all about it.
You can give small presents
to everyone after that.
That way, everyone has a fun time.
-Huh.
-Mm.
[chuckles]
Thank you very much.
I'll surprise them.
I hope it goes well.
Yes.
Oh. Then… let me say happy birth--
No, wait a second!
You're not supposed to say
those sorts of things in advance.
If you say it too early,
this whole thing is sure to fail.
[chuckles]
'Kay. I won't say it.
I'll say it tomorrow.
[laughs]
Thank you very much.
[wistful music playing]
Is something wrong?
Oh, no.
I have
a really strange feeling right now.
I'm not sure how to say it.
Uh, I'm sorry.
[music fades]
[Miki] Sorry for the short notice.
-You're sure it didn't affect work?
-Mm-hmm.
It'll be okay.
But how crazy is it that those two
are down with a fever now?
And I'm gonna be in the farm show
for the first time.
[Miki chuckles]
Thank you.
[sighs]
[pensive music playing]
Are you doing okay?
Mm. I'm feeling good.
I guess we haven't
driven this far in a while.
Mm.
[heart beating]
[pants]
[breathing heavily]
[screams]
[tires squeal]
-Kazu? Are you all right? Are you okay?
-[breathing heavily]
Can you breathe?
Kazu?
Just breathe.
Are you okay?
[announcement] The final train
for Oshamambe
will soon be departing from Platform Two.
Please make sure to get aboard in time.
The final train for Oshamambe
will soon be departing from Platform Two.
Please make sure to get aboard in time.
[footsteps rapidly approaching]
[chuckles]
[conductor blows whistle]
[train crossing alert chiming]
[tender piano music playing]
[heart beating]
[conductor] Ma'am?
Ma'am?
It's your station.
Oh, I'll be going.
[music fades]
RANKOSHI STATION
[phone buzzing]
[chuckles]
[Hiro] What? Hmm, am I doing this right?
-Is this okay?
-It's good to see you.
Like this? Oh, this way.
Ah.
-Hey, Saeko.
-[Saeko chuckles]
How are you?
[Saeko laughs]
You don't look so good. What's going on?
Really?
Out for a walk?
I guess.
Yes, I am walking.
How are you doing, Hiro?
What is it?
Oh, I just got the sense that
maybe you were feeling down.
I was right, huh?
What can I say?
I can just sense it.
Look at this face.
I know these kinds of things.
Hmm? [laughs]
Well,
thank you though.
[Hiro laughs]
Whenever I think of someone
who passed away,
I believe there's a reason for it.
It's that that person wants to visit me.
It's a sign that they're coming to see me.
[poignant piano music playing]
It's been eight years since my wife died.
Yet she visits me every single day.
She must really like me. [laughs]
The point is, you should think of him
as often as you want.
And one more thing, Saeko.
You said that it was difficult
for you to look forward.
Don't worry.
Humans aren't… aren't built
like automobiles.
We aren't made to walk backward.
Okay?
So as long as you're walking
each and every day, that means
you're moving forward.
You're walking towards the future.
Right?
Follow your heart.
All right, Saeko?
Mm.
Look at that. Huh?
See that?
It's the Hawaiian sky.
You're going to be okay.
[music intensifies]
[chuckles]
Everything will work out fine, Saeko.
[music fades]
The memories of the person
who donated their heart…
[gentle string music playing]
they all belong to me now.
Isn't that what's happening?
Scientifically speaking--
It's not scientifically proven.
However, there have been
several cases reported, correct?
Am I wrong? Aren't there?
These experiences…
these thoughts,
I don't know where they're coming from
except from this heart.
I need to understand…
what their spirit is after.
When I think…
of what's going to happen to me though…
I'm scared.
[music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
[Yuma] Uncle! Play with me!
Sure.
What do you wanna play?
-[Yuma] Let's play tops!
-Tops?
[Kazu] Go!
-[Yuma] Oh?
-[Kazu] Oh crap!
-Yay! I win!
-Oh! You're too good.
-Hey, if I win again…
-Yeah?
…will you do what I say?
What? Sure.
-You ready?
-Mm.
[both] Ready and…
Eh. Ah.
-Yay!
-You're good!
Now you do what I say.
All right.
-Okay, so…
-Mm-hmm.
With the surgery,
it's like you're in your second form?
Hmm?
Can you show me the scar?
Uh…
Hey, you promised, so you have to show me.
It's pretty… scary though.
You sure you want to?
No. Don't worry. I won't cry.
You promised.
So it's okay, right? Show it! Show it!
It's okay.
-Hmm.
-Really!
I won't cry, okay?
-You sure?
-Mm.
Hmm.
-You ready?
-Yeah.
Wow! That looks so cool!
-What?
-It's super cool.
[chuckles]
-Are you sure?
-Yeah!
-You think so?
All right.
-[rhythmic pop music playing]
-Hey. Let's go see the apples.
Hmm? Right now?
-Yeah.
-Eh, uh…
-Hurry. Let's go! Let's go!
-Wait, just--
Wait. Wait, wait. Wait, wait.
-[Yuma] Come on! Hurry!
-I'm coming.
Careful, Yuma.
You're so fast.
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[music ends]