[hair dryer whirring]
[gentle piano music playing]
[breathing anxiously]
[sighs]
[gentle piano music continues]
[groaning]
Damn it!
He isn't Yusuke.
You're falling for this guy, aren't you?
[sobs] Why couldn't it just be an affair?
[Kazu] When you were down,
what would Yusuke do?
What does everyone want me to do now?
[yelps]
[wistful music playing]
[Kazu] How long do you think
I'll be able to go…
till my heart gives out?
From now on, think in terms of months
or in weeks.
Less than a year.
Consider that as you plan for the future.
[shaky breathing]
I… I'm sorry.
I just…
I'm kinda panicking.
I'm sorry.
[shaky breathing]
I'm sorry. I just… I'm sorry.
[music fades]
This
hurts.
[sighs]
[groans]
Huh?!
[low snarling]
[uneasy music playing]
[low snarl]
[music intensifies]
-[phone ringing]
-[gasps]
[growls]
[phone continues ringing]
[ringing stops]
[relieved sigh]
That was scary.
[sighs]
[groans] That was awful.
So scary.
[sighs]
That was so scary!
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
[exhales]
Why am I struggling with this?
How uncool.
[laughs]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[phone line ringing]
[connect tone plays]
Yo, Saeko!
[chuckles] Are you serious?
You're like a guardian angel or something!
Huh?
Oh, you figured it out.
-Now you know.
-Listen to this.
-I have to tell you. What?
-This is embarrassing.
I guess you caught a glimpse
of these wings right here.
I've been hiding these things.
[laughs] You got me!
-Wait a minute.
-[Hiro clears throat]
Are you there?
-[Hiro grunts]
-You hearing me?
You there?
[chuckles, groans] My back.
I threw it out the other day.
Oh. Uh, are you all right?
[groans] I'm too old. I hate it.
[chuckles]
When you're old,
stuff like this is a real pain in the ass.
I got the blues when I thought about
the future of my farm.
So I wanted to see your face.
[laughs]
But now that I've seen it,
I am all better. Mm.
Actually, you're the angel.
[siren wailing]
[Hiro] Huh?
What's that?
Is something wrong?
What's going on?
Saeko? What's the matter?
[rhythmic electronic music playing]
[phone chimes]
DID YOU SEE THIS?
Now let's hear what happened
from the woman
who actually encountered the bear.
Thank you for speaking with us.
Are you all right?
-Yes. I'm okay.
-Great.
Tell us about the situation.
It was pretty dark out
when I actually saw it.
But I locked eyes with it,
and I immediately started panicking.
[reporter] You locked eyes with it?
How far away were you?
[Saeko] I think it was somewhere
over there,
so I'd say it was about three meters away?
[reporter gasps] Only three meters?
That sounds really close.
And it's incredible that you warded it off
with just your gaze.
-[Yuma] So cool.
-How did you do it?
The bear was scared of her!
-[Saeko] I don't know. I was terrified.
-Yuma! Come on! School!
I mean, my whole body froze in fear.
Naturally.
And just how big was this bear?
-[Saeko] Well, it was like…
-Uh…
Okay, let's go.
-You're going to be late!
-[Yuma] What?
-[woman] Hey, hey, Midori!
-What is it?
-[woman] Quick, quick, quick.
-[man] Come here. Look at the TV.
[reporter] Is this a safe neighborhood?
-[Saeko] Uh, I couldn't say.
-[gasps] Saeko?
[man] Yeah.
[Saeko] I think this was the first time.
Certainly for me, it was.
But honestly, I'm not quite sure.
-[reporter] Okay.
-Saeko.
Why did you pick those track pants?
-Well, uh…
-[man] She seems…
-Is everything okay with her?
-Jogging?
[phone chimes]
SAEKO
CAN I SEE YOU FOR A BIT TODAY?
Was that all? I kinda need to…
How are you?
Oh.
Nice to see you.
Are you feeling all right?
Ah. Guess you heard about the bear.
Right. Well… yes.
About the bear.
I was really worried.
For the bear?
Yes.
Oh, no. [chuckles]
I meant to say I was worried for you.
[laughs]
You know,
I'm kind of relieved.
"Relieved"?
Well, you know, I figured
there's a pretty good chance
this would be awkward.
It was only yesterday
that we had that thing.
You must've thought about it as well?
How to act next time we saw each other?
You have this look when you're thinking.
[chuckles]
Anyways…
Yeah? [chuckles]
Well… [clears throat] …yes.
Well, I guess
I was too surprised to even be awkward.
[sighs]
Were you distracted
by the track pants I had on?
No. Uh, I wasn't paying attention to that.
I really thought right there,
in the middle of the street
with that bear,
that was gonna be my end.
Right.
And I didn't wanna die
in those awful pants
or go to a hospital in them. Nasty.
I've spent so much money
on being fashionable,
and this is my last outfit?
No! No way! I can't do it!
[chuckles]
[sighs]
Actually, the two of us,
we have met before.
We just didn't realize it.
Yes.
That's true. We definitely have.
I was surprised seeing those rain boots.
What does it all mean?
Even if all this was fate,
it's tough to say how we'll end up
or where this fate is leading us.
That's true.
Everything all right?
Uh… yes.
I feel fine, actually.
That's good.
Yeah. [clears throat]
I have
made the decision to stop seeing you
going forward.
What?
Dealing with all this
is too much for me now.
I'm not gonna lie.
It's left me feeling really confused
about us.
'Cause I've never fallen in love
with anyone as much as I did with Yusuke.
I was so in love.
I'm still in love too. Even now.
I know.
It's true that he's dead.
However, he's still alive inside of you.
And he's not just alive.
It's his memories and his mind too.
Yusuke lives on inside you.
I just wanted to see him again.
I had to see him again.
Who wouldn't take that chance?
But…
now I'm really confused.
Do I wanna see Yusuke,
or do I really wanna see you?
Is it Yusuke I love? Or do I love you?
We kissed, and I almost had sex with you,
but I couldn't.
I apologize.
But I just
feel like I can't take this.
Like I can't handle it anymore.
And it's driving me crazy.
And I wanna be fair to you.
If I keep seeing you,
I'll start wanting to spend
all my time with you.
And that's not fair to you, is it?
You have your own life
and your own family.
And I don't wanna screw that up for you.
However, I do wonder where your head's at.
I'm curious how you're feeling.
Is Yusuke's heart the reason why
you've been so nice to me?
Or do you yourself actually feel this way?
I don't know.
But when I consider that possibility,
I… feel like I'm going insane.
Then my head starts spinning.
It's overwhelming.
That bear made things even worse.
I was going…
to lie to you about how I felt
until I came here.
"I only love Yusuke."
"I don't have any feelings for you."
"We can't be together."
I was going to say that
and then never see you again.
But it just isn't true.
I wanted you to know
how I really felt inside.
[emotional piano music playing]
We had this strange connection.
It was quite fun,
and I'm grateful to you.
I'd never want…
to disrespect any of that with a lie.
[chuckles]
This is all your fault.
You're easy to talk to,
and you're kind of cute.
Anyway,
it's time for me to stop.
I know I'm not making sense right now.
I'm sorry.
No, I understand what you're saying.
That being said,
I'm grateful for our time together.
Bye now, Yusuke.
[chuckles]
Will you…
please take care of him?
[emotional piano music continues]
[music fades]
-Sorry to interrupt, Midori.
-Hmm?
I was hoping to discuss something
with you. Do you have a minute?
What's up?
Ah…
You say you wanna discuss,
but the look on your face says
you've already decided.
What?
I love when women have that look.
It's beautiful.
However, as president,
I don't think I'm looking forward
to hearing this.
All right.
So what now?
Do you wanna treat me to lunch, hmm?
That sounds nice.
Well, then.
I accept.
Thank you very much.
[emotional piano music resumes]
[man] We should be all set.
What do you feel like?
Shinoda.
Oh.
Hey. Which would you choose?
[music fades]
Mm. I'd go with this one.
I thought so.
-Hey.
-[man] Yes.
-[Shinoda] Let's roast them.
-[man] I'll get it ready.
[sighs]
[brakes squeal]
[whistle blowing]
[melancholy music playing]
[woman] Hi there. I'm your new contact.
My name is Kashiwagi.
Akane Inc. sent me. It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too. I'm Naruse.
This is a nice café space you've got.
[Kazu] Thank you.
We couldn't have done it without you all.
I, uh…
Yes?
Oh, nothing.
-I look forward to working with you.
-Likewise.
Hi, nice to meet you. I'm Kashiwagi.
I'll be taking over for Saeko.
-Nice to meet you.
-[Kashiwagi] Nice to meet you.
What have you got here? It's gorgeous!
I know, right? It's fantastic.
[Saeko gasps]
-[Kazu] Huh?
-Huh?
-[melancholy music continues]
-[inaudible dialogue]
[melancholy music continues]
Even your heart isn't enough
to keep me alive.
I'm sorry.
What do I…
What do you think I should do?
What would you like me to do, Yusuke…
with the time I have?
[music fades]
[sighs] Okay.
[footsteps approaching]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[Kengo] Oh.
Welcome.
Do you know where Saeko's off to?
No.
What is it?
Oh, uh…
There's something
I need to discuss with her.
It's urgent.
Oh, I see.
Can you please tell me?
Please.
There's something
I really need to tell her.
You should… stop worrying about Saeko.
She already decided
to end things with you.
Yes.
Well, there's your answer.
You should leave her be.
For her sake, at least.
No, I need to know.
I think of what you said the other day.
You felt like you were
making things difficult for everyone.
You don't need to
think of yourself like that.
Let me rephrase.
You should stop thinking like that.
Just your being here,
it goes a long way to making folks happy.
Lots of people.
So,
just relax and live your life.
I really appreciate it.
But…
I can't afford to do that now.
[sighs]
[sniffles]
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[Kengo] Hey.
[man on PA] The train
will soon be arriving at Platform Five.
Please stand clear.
The train will soon be arriving
at Platform Five.
[panting]
[grunts]
[man on PA] The train
bound for New Chitose…
[panting]
…New Chitose Airport
will soon be arriving at Platform Five.
[panting]
[man on PA] Please stand clear.
The train bound for New Chitose Airport
will soon be arriving at…
[panting]
[grunting]
-[music ends]
-[groaning]
[grunting]
[grunts, pants]
[rhythmic pop music resumes]
[woman on PA] This train
is bound for Oshamambe.
It will soon be departing,
so please find a seat
and stand clear of the closing doors.
[grunts, pants]
[panting]
[man on PA] The train
bound for New Chitose Airport
will soon be departing.
Please make sure to board
in a timely fashion.
[whistle blowing]
Please stand clear of the closing doors.
[panting]
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[sobs]
[sniffles]
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[music ends]
[poignant piano music playing]
[music fades]