♪ Can I have the day with you? ♪
[Saeko panting]
♪ Nothing more that I would choose ♪
Ah! [pants]
♪ Nothing more that I could use… ♪
[sighs]
Unbelievable. Why on earth is it raining?
[Saeko sighs]
Pretty sure the weather forecast
didn't mention rain.
Did they?
They didn't, right?
[sighs]
♪ Nothing more that I would choose ♪
♪ Nothing more that I could use… ♪
[Saeko sighs]
My poor shoes.
[Yusuke pants] Hey.
Ah, you made it!
Huh? What's wrong? Your shoes are off.
'Cause I don't want 'em getting all wet.
I really like these shoes.
They're my Louboutins. I love these shoes.
They're proof that I've been working hard.
Where's your umbrella?
My umbrella?
What? You being serious right now?
I texted to come over here and get me
'cause I was stuck in the rain.
-I did, right?
-Uh, yeah.
I got that.
So I sent you that… that text and said
I'd rush over here.
Obviously, I need an umbrella
if I'm stuck in the rain.
Oh yeah. I don't even have an umbrella.
Oh my God. Really?
You really didn't think about that?
[Saeko groans]
Why did you even come over there, then?
[Yusuke] Hmm…
I guess I came to keep you company.
[laughs]
-Huh?
-Yeah. I did, yeah.
Think it's more fun
waiting together than alone?
Hey, I got an idea.
How about we dance together in the rain?
-[Saeko] Huh?
-Come dance with me!
-[Saeko] Are you serious?
-Ah! [laughs]
Let's dance!
No, this is silly.
-Really, let's do it!
-I will not dance!
-[Yusuke] Why not?
-Hurry up. Come here! You're getting wet!
-[Yusuke] You coming or not?
-No, stop it!
-[Yusuke] Really?
-Just come back.
Get out of the street! Here.
-You're getting soaked.
-[Miki] Sorry! Sorry you had to wait.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm fine. Thank you.
-Hey, Miki, can you stop a second?
-Sure.
[Yusuke] Man, it's really coming down.
It's not stopping, is it?
[Saeko] We could be waiting here
for a long time.
-[Yusuke] I know.
-[Saeko] You're gonna catch a cold.
Here! You guys can use this.
-And these too.
-[Saeko] Huh?
This stuff's pretty worn out,
so just toss it when you're done.
-[Saeko] Uh…
-Bye.
-Thanks. That was very sweet!
-Thanks so much, man.
-Huh!
-[chuckles] Wow.
[Yusuke laughs]
[gentle piano music playing]
[Yusuke chuckles]
Yes, I get to share an umbrella with you.
It's classic, like in a movie. [laughs]
That's why you should've brought one.
[Yusuke] Right.
[gentle piano music continues]
[Kazu chuckles softly]
What's up?
I was thinking…
[Miki] Hmm?
I think I'll go for it.
Have the surgery.
[door opens]
[music fades]
NISEKO STATION
[Kazu] Thank you.
-I'll see you tonight.
-Take care, okay?
-See you later.
-Mm.
[inhales sharply]
[exhales]
-[truck horn honks]
-[tires squeal]
[breathing heavily]
[Kazu breathing heavily]
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
[wistful music playing]
[phone chimes]
[sighs]
SAEKO SUGAWARA:
KENGO, CAN I ASK A FAVOR?
TELL ME SOME OF YOUR MEMORIES WITH YUSUKE
[chuckles softly]
All right.
What do you know?
I'm a decent guy.
Thank you.
Sorry to drag you out here.
I was curious
what Yusuke's hometown was like.
Yeah. Happy to join.
I've actually never been here either.
[Kazu] There's something
I have to tell you.
[Saeko] Hmm?
[Kazu] I have never done this before.
Played hooky.
[Kazu chuckles]
Uh, I did take a lot of time off, though,
because of my health.
There were a lot of times when,
all of a sudden, I wouldn't be able to
go to work or school.
So, unlike other people,
skipping always seemed to me
like a waste of an opportunity
since I missed it so much,
so I'd never dream of doing it.
I'd never done it before.
But I'm enjoying it.
Oh yeah?
Skipping for the first time?
-Yes.
-[laughs]
If Yusuke's here now…
or, at least, his heart,
I wonder
if that's why I wanna be free?
-Mm…
-Mm.
[Saeko laughs]
[sentimental acoustic guitar
music playing]
[Saeko] This is it.
YUSUKE'S FAVORITE PLACES
[Kazu] Wow!
THE SHRINE WE ALWAYS PLAYED AT TOGETHER
The big chestnut tree
should still be there.
Yusuke was such an expert
at climbing trees,
especially the big chestnut tree.
His favorite.
-Wonder where it is?
-Mm.
A big chestnut…
[Saeko] Maybe this is it?
[Kazu chuckles]
Mm. It's a big one.
[laughs]
No. No, don't!
Be careful, don't overdo it, okay?
It's dangerous.
-I'm serious! That's high enough!
-[groans] Hold on.
Kazumasa.
[chuckles] I climbed it!
[laughs]
[music fades]
Well, I climbed up, but, uh…
-Just be careful.
-[grunts]
Here we go.
Slowly.
-[Kazu] Oh!
-Whoa!
-Hey, easy.
-[laughs] I'm okay.
Whoa.
-You could get hurt jumping like that.
-Oh, thank you.
[sighs]
[exhales]
[Saeko chuckles]
[both laugh]
[melodic acoustic guitar music playing]
♪ Love is all we need is what they say ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh… ♪
MT. MANMARU
[Kazu] Oh…
It feels great out here.
I think I can do this. Hup.
Aw, but this one's kind of…
[Saeko] Looks tough, huh?
[Kazu] Yeah, this part's hard.
They're too far apart.
I think if I could…
[grunts]
[both] Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
-[Kazu] Argh!
-Yes!
[both laugh]
This part is difficult!
[Saeko giggles]
What is she gonna play?
Ah!
Oh yeah!
-Okay.
-Yeah, here we go. I'm not sure… Oh!
[both laugh]
[waitress] Thanks for waiting.
Here's your extra-large portion.
-Good luck.
-[Kazu] Thank you very…
Whoa! [chuckles]
That's a lot!
So I guess that's it.
He always ordered the biggest portion.
Do you think you can eat all that?
Of course.
[both in Japanese] Let's eat.
[in English] Mmm. It's so good.
-Mmm. Yeah, it really is!
-[laughs] Mm.
[employee] Of course.
Thank you for coming.
Have a good one.
[Saeko] Mmm!
[music ends]
That was delicious. [clears throat]
[Kazu] That was so good.
[laughs]
Oh, and then two jumbo okonomiyaki mixed.
What? No!
Which he
never actually ate.
[laughs]
I had you going, didn't I?
I like teasing you. It's fun.
Yeah, yeah.
MEMORIES CAN BE TRANSFERRED
FROM AN ORGAN TRANSPLANT
MOUNTAIN BUS ACCIDENT
[wistful music playing]
[parking brake clicks]
[gasps]
[music fades]
THE CAFÉ IN THE NEXT TOWN OVER
[Kengo] The café you're heading to now
is run by Yusuke's mother.
She moved a long time ago
when he was still really little.
But she lived in the next town over,
so I'd go there with Yusuke a lot.
He'd say that's where my mom is.
But he never went inside.
I gotta think that
he really wanted to see her.
Let's go in…
and see what it's like.
[woman] Hello. Come in.
Are you open?
Yes, have a seat.
[Saeko] Coffee okay?
Oh.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Excuse me.
Uh, can we get two coffees, please?
Coming right up.
["I Want You Back"
by The Jackson 5 playing]
[music stops]
[shaky breathing]
Sorry. That was great. Thank you.
[Saeko sighs]
[shaky breath]
-[wind whistling]
-[ocean waves crashing]
"This is the last place."
"This is the spot
that Yusuke liked the most."
"Where the wind blows in from the sea."
[Kazu] Ah…
I feel like I kind of understand…
why he liked it here.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you for today.
I have had… a wonderful time.
My pleasure. Thank you for inviting me.
I realized that
there's a lot I didn't know about Yusuke.
[sentimental music playing]
I've always wondered why
he would try hard
to entertain people so often.
He always noticed
if someone was struggling.
He said his role was
to act as a softener in the world.
He must've been
such a sad and lonely kid himself
that he didn't want others
to experience that.
He hated how much sadness
was in the world.
[breathes deeply]
That's why he was like that.
Yeah, I see that.
-It's a little embarrassing.
-[both laugh]
Praising him this much to you.
He could also go overboard sometimes.
-Mm…
-Sometimes it was like, "Get a grip."
I'm sorry.
[Saeko] Hmm?
I guess… [sniffles]
…it's a weird moment to say sorry.
[both laugh]
Hey, you know what?
We should take a picture.
And show Kengo.
Uh…
-So…
-I can take it if you want.
-That'd be great. Here.
-Okay.
[Kazu] Mm…
Hmm? You wanna go this way a little?
-This way?
-Yeah.
No, uh, uh, go a little more…
Mm, is this good?
Uh, no. I think the other way was better.
-Here. Move this way a little. That's it.
-Little lower.
THANK YOU FOR TODAY
I'LL TELL YOU MORE WHEN I VISIT NEXT TIME
[music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
Ah, thank you so much.
Uh, Guatemalan.
And that will be 800 yen, please.
[phone buzzes]
[wistful music playing]
Uh, with a card? You can tap.
[phone dings]
Come back again soon.
[door opens]
-A hundred and eighty.
-Now take away 30?
-A hundred and fifty.
-Oh!
-Ooh!
That's correct.
[Yuma] What about this one here, Uncle?
[Kazu] Hmm? Okay, let's look at this one.
[music fades]
[Miki] You're Saeko Sugawara, right?
Huh?
May I ask who you are?
Your name is Saeko. You were engaged to
Yusuke Nakamachi, weren't you?
Who are you?
My name is Miki Naruse.
[Saeko] What?
And Kazumasa's my husband.
Oh.
I'm sorry… for surprising you like this.
It's okay. But…
I do want to thank you.
Thanks to Yusuke Nakamachi,
thanks to him offering his heart to us,
my husband can go on living.
I'm really… very grateful for that.
You don't need to…
It's not me who you should be thanking.
Can you please stop doing this?
Sorry?
I know how you must be feeling.
I know it's true your boyfriend's heart
is now beating inside Kazumasa.
However, he's still the guy he is.
He isn't your boyfriend.
So stop it, trying to get closer
to my husband like this.
Get closer?
-What are you saying? You think that--
-But that's what's going on.
Look at his point of view.
He can't just brush you to the side
'cause he still owes you.
And now…
he's finally…
he's finally healthy, and…
and he can enjoy his life,
spend time with his family
like a normal person.
Please don't destroy that.
Listen, I know that your boyfriend's heart
is keeping him alive,
but he's still Kazu, and that's it.
Kazumasa is not Yusuke.
Hold on a minute, okay?
Did he
mention anything, any of this to you?
That he feels sorry for me,
that's why we talk?
Did he tell you that?
No, he didn't.
[Saeko breathes deeply]
The two of us don't have
a relationship like that.
It's not romantic between us.
I think he would agree with me too.
Maybe you should actually
talk to him about all this.
You think…
you got some idea about
what I've experienced.
How could you ever understand?
Don't be so hasty
in assuming you know how I feel.
Isn't Kazumasa still alive?
The one person you love most.
He is, right?
The love of your life.
Please don't act like this.
You know how I'm feeling.
[breathes deeply]
I'm not gonna quit.
I don't want to.
-I wanna see him.
-[poignant music playing]
It is, after all, Yusuke's heart in there.
It holds memories of us inside it.
Now here you are insisting that…
that I can't see him?
How would that make you feel?
There's an accident. Kazumasa dies.
His heart's still alive, though,
inside someone else.
Is he actually dead?
And this has nothing to do with you?
And what if that heart
still knew who you were?
What if it still had memories
of you and him?
What would you do?
Would it still have nothing
to do with you?
Is that all you feel for him?
That's not the way I'm built.
[whimpers]
[sobs]
[sobs] What did I…
What did I do to deserve all of this?
Why…
[sniffles]
[crying]
Why is this…
Why couldn't it just be an affair?
[crying continues]
I'm sorry.
[music fades]
[groans]
[labored breathing]
-[woman 1] Oh, are you all right?
-[woman 2] Are you okay?
Yes.
[groans]
[ethereal music playing]
[woman] Saeko.
Hello.
The sample of the Guatemala beans.
Thanks so much.
I'll be sending it for testing
and cupping preparation.
Thank you very much.
Yep.
How long do you think I'll be able to go…
till my heart gives out?
[music fades]
-[nurse] Mr. Hara?
-Yes.
-[nurse] Room five, please.
-All right.
[sighs]
Whoa!
[groans]
Ow. Ow!
[sighs]
[groans]
Oh man, I thought that was you.
[gasps]
Huh?
You're here?
Oh…
Hop on.
What?
You can't walk barefoot.
Come on.
It's okay.
Okay.
I appreciate it.
It's fine.
[grunts]
[gentle piano music playing]
So why are you over here?
Uh…
Just wandering around.
Then found a house that I recognized.
The house had blue walls.
I knew it was your house.
And then I…
I got this happy feeling.
It was actually kinda weird.
Just knowing that
that was where you lived, I felt happy.
[Kazu sniffles]
Am I heavy?
[chuckles]
Not, eh…
You're not exactly light.
[both laugh]
-Sorry. [sniffles]
-It's okay.
Oh my goodness.
[Saeko] Hmm?
It's, um…
another first. I've never given a…
piggyback ride to a woman.
Really?
Yusuke did this for you, though, I'm sure.
I bet he would do this a lot.
[gentle piano music continues]
[Yusuke] Ooh.
[Yusuke and Saeko laugh]
Careful, don't fall.
-And what if I do?
-Then you get a penalty.
[Saeko laughing]
Come on! Ah! Don't do that!
[both laughing]
Hey, I got it. Getting there.
-[Saeko] Yeah, you're good.
-Mm. Yeah.
[both laugh]
Not exactly.
[Kazu chuckles]
[music fades]
[Kazu sighs]
Well, we're back.
[emotional piano music playing]
[music fades]
[umbrella rattles]
[gasps]
[wistful piano music playing]
[wistful piano music continues]
I was thinking…
Hmm?
I think I'll go for it.
Have the surgery.
What?
Are you serious?
Mm-hmm.
Because if it works, and I get well, then…
we can annoy each other.
I'll have an idea, like, um…
mm, not too dumb,
but, you know, kinda goofy.
And you can be like,
"You're so dumb!
What was going through your head?"
[Miki chuckles]
I think that would…
-That'd feel like I was healthy.
-Mm.
I would really feel like I was alive.
Uh-huh.
But
this thing's not gonna be easy.
Getting a heart transplant
means that you live, but in a way,
the donor, he also gets to keep on living,
you know?
[Kazu] I'll be living a new life.
A new life together with the donor.
[uplifting music playing]
[Saeko] This is indeed the first time
we've shared an umbrella.
Yeah, that's right. Hmm.
I'm actually glad it's raining.
-[chuckles]
-[sniffles]
You can look at something you think's bad,
but if you let go,
it can actually turn out great.
Oh my goodness.
You really are one of a kind, Yusuke.
All I do is get super angry all the time.
But I think we'd have a lot of fun
if we spent our lives together.
Huh?
You proposing to me right now?
-No!
-Oh yes, you are!
-Not what I'm saying.
-All right, all right.
So… so right now,
if… if I proposed to you,
what would you say?
-I'd say no.
-You serious?
-You'd really say no?
-[laughs]
[Yusuke] No way.
-[Saeko] Did I say that?
-Uh-huh.
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[music ends]