["Such Great Heights"
by Iron &amp; Wine playing]
OTARU GENERAL HOSPITAL
♪ I am thinking it's a sign ♪
♪ That the freckles in our eyes ♪
♪ Are mirror images ♪
♪ And when we kiss they're perfectly… ♪
Kazu.
♪ I… ♪
There's fireworks through the window.
[Kazu] Really?
-There.
-Wow.
-Oh, yeah.
-[laughs]
-Those are kinda outta nowhere.
-Mm. They are, aren't they?
They're far away and… kinda little.
I wonder where they're coming from?
-Could be Mt. Misato?
-Oh yeah. Could be.
I just love fireworks.
They're pretty, aren't they?
Maybe people are celebrating
something good that happened?
Maybe they are.
That's gotta be what's going on, right?
Way to go!
[both laugh]
I wanna see the summer fireworks again
with you, okay?
[music fades]
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry.
All right, what are you apologizing for?
I don't think I'll make it
to the summer fireworks.
I know I won't.
Well, I think you will.
I just know you will.
You'll live.
And you'll see the fireworks with me.
[chuckles]
All right then, I guess I will.
Mm-hmm. You're going.
And now, guess what. I brought you apples.
Want one? I'm gonna have one too.
No, uh, not right now.
[woman] Hmm?
You know what? I will, uh, have one.
I was just thinking
an apple would be good.
-So thanks.
-[giggles]
Yes, I win.
[chuckles]
So what should we do when you're all well?
Here.
Mm…
[tender piano music playing]
Scuba dive,
skydive, or, uh, bungee jumping.
Mm, kinda rough on your heart, isn't it?
[both laugh]
I was hoping you'd say
we'd go on a trip together.
Oh yeah.
And where should we go together?
Mm,
someplace nice and warm, maybe.
Mm, sounds good.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm! These are great.
Yeah, right? I got the best ones for you.
The former Miss Apple
knows her stuff, huh?
[woman chuckles]
-Mm!
-Mm.
-Oh!
-[laughs]
[sighs]
[sniffles]
[sobs]
[breathes deeply]
[sniffles]
[helicopter engine roars overhead]
MISS APPLE
[woman 1] Ah, it smells so good. Yummy.
I'm back!
-[man 1] There's my girl.
-[woman 2] Hi, sweetie!
[boy] Hey, how do I solve this?
And how is Kazumasa doing, hmm?
So handsome. Cute, as always.
Strange answer, but okay.
[woman 1] Really?
Well, I'm glad to hear it. It's so sweet.
Yeah. Ah, he's so good-looking.
[laughter]
When's Uncle Kazumasa coming home?
Mm, we're not sure. Why?
Because he is the best tutor there is.
Other than him, no one else in this house
is able to tutor me better.
What?
Oh man, did you hear?
We're a bunch of idiots.
[man 2] I'm sorry
that we're all too stupid.
I'll tell him that if he's not out soon,
your brain just might turn to jelly.
-Thank you!
-[man 2] That's right.
You should beg for his help.
[woman 2] Oh, I'm so sorry.
[woman 1] No, it's okay. It's our fault.
[laughs]
The color's really good this year.
-[man 1] Yeah, good thing, huh?
-Mm-hmm.
[phone ringing]
[gasps]
Yes, this is her.
[footsteps rapidly approaching]
[panting]
Mm-hmm.
You can do this.
God is telling you… to live.
[ethereal music playing]
[sighs]
[tender piano music playing]
[inhales]
[exhales]
Mm.
[monitors beeping]
-[coordinator] It's here.
-[surgeon] Let's start trimming.
-[assistant] Yes, sir.
-[surgeon] Ischemic time?
-[coordinator] One hour and forty minutes.
-[surgeon] Okay.
[tender piano music continues]
[ethereal music playing]
Kazu. [echoes]
[waves crashing]
[reverse-sounding piano playing]
[ethereal music continues]
[rescuers] Can you hear me?
[music fades]
[woman] Kazu?
Kazu.
[emotional music playing]
Hello…
again.
[sobs]
[emotional music continues]
[woman] Everything okay?
[Kazu] Fine, thanks.
I feel comfortable. My body feels good.
I feel much lighter.
[woman] I see.
[Kazu] Ah…
[emotional music continues]
[man 1] They're back. Hey, Dad!
[man 2] Huh? Oh!
Hey!
Oh!
-[Kazu] I'm back!
-[man 1] Welcome home!
[man 2] Welcome home!
-Uncle Kazumasa!
-Hey, Yuma! [laughs]
-Wow, you got taller, didn't you?
-Yeah, I did.
-Welcome home!
-[Kazu] Right?
I'm sorry I made you guys
worry about me for so long.
[woman 1 laughs]
-[Yuma] Let's go!
-[woman 1] Come on in.
-[Kazu] Okay, yeah.
-[woman 2] Come in!
-[Kazu] My bags.
-[man 2] I'll get 'em!
-Tomo, help me out?
-[man 1] Just give them to me.
-Dad, are you sure?
-Here. Oh, it's fine.
-This is heavy.
-What is in here?
-You are old!
-Hey, you take this.
-[Yuma] I'll do it!
-[Tomo] Are you sure?
[Yuma] It's okay.
-Be careful.
-[man 2] Give me a second.
[woman 1] Hurry, the food's coming.
-Ta-da!
-Wow! This all looks so good!
Let me get this out of the way.
[woman 2] Okay, guys!
It's ready! Let's eat!
All right, everyone tell me
what you wanna drink.
Who here wants coffee?
-Me.
-[man 2] Oh, I do.
-I do.
-Here.
[man 2] What?
I thought you didn't like coffee.
That's… right. Yeah.
I don't know. [chuckles]
I just felt like having a little.
What did the doctor say?
I… I guess it's okay.
All they said was not to have any alcohol.
-I want coffee too! I'll have some!
-Here.
-[woman 1] What?
-[man 2] Now he wants some.
-Might wanna wait till you're older.
-[Yuma] I wanna try it.
[woman 3] Okay, I'll pour you some.
-Ew!
-[all laugh]
-See, we told you.
-I knew you wouldn't like it.
All right, Yuma. Here.
I got some juice for you.
-[Yuma] Yay!
-Yeah, you'll like this better.
[woman 3] Coffee is kinda bitter, huh?
-[man 2 laughs]
-[woman 3 laughs]
I like this.
[all exclaim]
[Kazu] It's really good.
-[chuckles] Yeah?
-[Kazu laughs] Yeah.
[Kazu sighs]
You okay? Are you tired?
-No. I'm okay, thanks.
-[chuckles]
I feel so good
that I'm surprised at myself.
But
it does feel a little strange.
It almost feels like my body
hasn't really accepted this heart yet.
Or, actually, it's like the opposite.
This heart hasn't accepted my body.
It's as if there's someone here with me.
It really is a strange feeling.
Mm. Yeah, that is strange.
[Kazu] Mm.
But I can't believe how great I feel.
Like… I can do anything.
[laughs]
-That's good to hear.
-Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you for everything.
[woman] Mm-hmm.
As soon as the doctor says okay,
I can start working again.
Mm-hmm.
It's great, isn't it?
I'm glad you took sick leave
instead of quitting.
So optimistic.
Mm-hmm.
I wanna thank you.
[both laugh]
-And I thought before that…
-Hmm?
-…let's go somewhere. All right?
-[gasps]
Yeah! Yay!
[both laugh]
[woman moans happily]
I also thought…
that we, uh,
could have a few kids one day.
[breathes deeply]
[indistinct chattering]
-[woman] It's really busy here.
-Mm.
I'm gonna go in here a second.
[Kazu] Okay. I'll wait upstairs.
Mm-hmm.
[airplane engine roaring]
[child 1] Tag! [giggles]
[note plays]
[poignant piano music playing]
[music fades]
["I Want You Back"
by The Jackson 5 playing]
[man 1] This guy's good.
Beautiful.
-[music ends]
-[crowd cheering]
[exhales sharply]
That was amazing.
You play the piano?
Kazu.
Let's go. Okay?
Let's go.
-Mm.
-[woman chuckles]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
["Beauty All Around" by Hush Kids playing]
Are you nervous?
It's been a while.
[chuckles softly] Yes, it has.
Mm.
♪ With a hundred million flowers ♪
♪ I'm looking for a clock… ♪
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
♪ That doesn't count the hours… ♪
Hmm.
NISEKO STATION
-[Kazu] Thanks.
-[woman] Okay.
-[Kazu] Here I go.
-[woman] Okay, good luck!
Take breaks, okay? Call when you're done.
Mm. I'll see you.
See you later!
[laughs]
♪ I'm looking for a stone ♪
♪ That's a perfect skipper ♪
♪ I'm looking for a boat ♪
♪ That'll take me down this river ♪
♪ I'm looking for a light ♪
♪ That will not break till dawn ♪
♪ Till all the drunks and prayers
Have been ♪
♪ Carried home ♪
♪ Oh, oh, there's beauty ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Beauty all around ♪
[brakes squeal]
♪ I'm looking for a home ♪
♪ Sitting on the water… ♪
[conductor] I hope you have
a wonderful rest of your day.
To those passengers who have just finished
their day's work, welcome home to you.
And if you're just passing through,
thanks for traveling with us today.
[announcement on PA] Otaru, Otaru.
♪ Full of riches ♪
♪ Oh, oh, there's beauty ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh… ♪
OTARU UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION
♪ All around ♪
♪ Oh, oh… ♪
Use this as a reference.
Okay, thank you.
Here.
That's great. Thank you.
-Hello.
-[students] Hi.
-[woman] Hi.
-How's it going?
That's fine. I'm on my way.
It's building four? Right.
[music fades]
-I'll go check.
-Great.
-Okay, thank you.
-Thanks.
[indistinct chattering]
-[woman 1] Yeah, who's next?
-[woman 2] What would you like?
[woman 1] Come on forward.
[woman 2] Thank you for waiting.
Large, right?
[woman 1] Okay, next person, please.
-Uh, katsu sandwich, please.
-Katsu sandwich? Okay.
-[student 1] Mayuka!
-[student 2] Oh, hey!
Hey, guys!
Kazumasa!
-Ah.
-[man] Come sit down.
-[Kazu] Thank you.
-Right here.
So
sorry to cause
such a headache for you guys.
You didn't.
We're glad you're back, really.
[man] Mm-hmm.
Huh? Is that coffee? Is that yours?
[man] Oh yeah.
Oh. I like it now for some reason.
-[man] Really?
-Huh. How interesting.
Mm.
[man] Mm, you know,
we've been receiving
a lot of requests from the students
to turn that space into a café.
[woman] They've asked Student Affairs
to look into it.
A café, huh?
[woman] Mm-hmm.
That's a good idea.
-[woman] Mm-hmm.
-[man] Yeah.
MARU COFFEE
[Saeko] Hello. Akane delivery.
-How's it going?
-[man] Oh.
Whoa!
Uh, these are the Guatemala Antigua
washed beans.
And then, these are the natural beans.
Oh wow. Thank you very much.
Any good?
They're wonderful.
-I guarantee it.
-[laughs]
So I'm running through
the airport screaming, "Yusuke!"
[laughs]
[chuckles] Wow.
And, obviously, it's not him.
[man chuckles]
I have this feeling
he's still out there somehow.
-Mm?
-Just 'cause it's Yusuke.
[Saeko laughs] I know.
[sighs]
I wonder what that was.
-How about you, Kengo?
-Hmm?
[Saeko] How are you holding up?
[Kengo] I'm just trying to get by.
All we can do is go on
living without Yusuke.
It's pretty boring though. [chuckles]
[Saeko] Mm.
-Oh, uh…
-[Kengo] Hmm?
So I received a thank-you letter.
The person who got Yusuke's heart
wrote me this thank-you note.
Wow, didn't know they did that.
Yeah. Neither of us know who the other is.
It was a really nice letter
he sent me though.
He sounds like a nice person. Really good.
Well, that's great.
Yeah.
So that, uh…
that made me feel really glad.
Mm.
I mean, you know,
you want it to go to a good person,
don't you?
I guess you do, yeah.
[Saeko] Yeah.
The fact that he sounded so nice,
that really makes me happy.
[Kengo] I bet it does.
Mm-hmm.
[Kengo] Oh. [groans]
You mind, uh, giving it a little drink?
Of course not. I'd love to.
You're used to getting rain
in the afternoon in Hawaii, huh?
That looks good.
Hmm.
The café owner
who's that dead guy's best friend…
Huh?
He says that the best way to forget love
is to go out and fall in love again.
You're such a cliché.
-Oh?
-[laughs]
Go fall in love. Why not?
I mean, it's not like I'm determined never
to fall in love again.
Really?
All right, then.
What kind of guy would you like?
Hmm…
Someone who looks for fun everywhere.
Someone who's optimistic because
that's something I struggle with myself.
And someone who's a little bit goofy
in a loveable way.
Someone who's not afraid to talk about
the important things in life.
And someone who is madly in love with me.
You just described Yusuke.
[giggles] Yeah, I did.
[both laugh]
-Oh no!
-What are we going to do with you?
[tender piano music playing]
[Saeko] To the person
who sent me the letter,
I was told it was okay to send a reply,
so I decided to write to you.
Thank you for your letter.
It made me very happy.
I read it over and over again every day.
TO THE ONE WHO READS THIS LETTER
It cheers me up every time.
Reading it gives me strength.
Thank you.
Your letter is very precious to me.
How are you doing healthwise?
Is the heart of the person I loved so much
still beating the way it should?
Maybe I shouldn't be
writing things like this…
but I always thought
his heart was a little mischievous.
I hope it's not getting you into trouble.
I truly
and sincerely wish you well
from the bottom of my heart.
I know that we will probably never meet.
Let's both do our best to get through it.
Stay well.
Take care.
[tender piano music continues]
Welcome back.
-[Kazu] Thanks.
-Mm.
[music fades]
And I'm back.
Well, good job, babe.
What's going on?
[chuckles]
I was just thinking…
that I'm so, uh, happy.
[chuckles] Hmm?
[both laugh]
When I got off the train
at the station today,
your car was there,
and you gave me a smile and everything.
And you told me that I'd done well.
Your face was…
[chuckles]
…just so pretty.
[laughs]
I thought, "God, I love that woman."
Just thinking how happy I am right now.
I also thought,
"I'm really glad I got better."
Mm. I was thinking that.
All right, then. That's great.
Mm.
It really is.
[wistful music playing]
What if we… drove around a while?
What?
Mm-hmm.
[both laugh]
[wistful music continues]
[conductor] Folks, we've received word
that the line ahead is blocked,
so we'll be stopped here for a while.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
[man 1] What? We can't get through?
-[man 2] I can't believe this.
-[woman 1] We're stuck here?
-[man 3] What happened?
-[man 2] I don't know.
[man 4] Seriously?
[man 2] Who knows for how long.
-[woman 1] Oh dear.
-[man 1] This isn't good.
Sorry, ladies and gentlemen.
I need to ask for your patience.
It seems we can't get through up ahead.
I'm sorry about this.
And please feel free
to wait on the platform if you prefer.
[man 4] How long you think it'll be?
[conductor] I think crews are
on their way, but I don't know yet. Sorry.
-[man 1] Can't you tell us anything?
-I'll let you know as soon as I find out.
-[man 1] What do you mean you don't know?
-Sorry about that.
-[man 2] This is gonna take forever.
-Sorry, ma'am.
It's not a problem.
What?
[grunts]
[sighs]
[indistinct chattering]
[man 1] The signal's weak out here too.
[Kazu] Oh, I thought I'd make some coffee.
[woman 1] Hello?
Hello?
[indistinct chattering]
You mind if I help with that?
Huh?
Oh, thank you.
Uh, okay,
so I think we'll use these for the--
Oh, it's fine, I got it.
Okay, thank you.
This is nice.
I know, right?
Actually, I just
bought all of this yesterday.
I knew it was good.
I wanted it the minute I saw it.
Didn't think I'd use it
in this kind of situation though.
I feel like coffee's nice
on difficult days like this.
Hmm.
Like right now,
everyone seems a little on edge.
[Saeko] Oh?
Yeah.
A cup of coffee is not gonna
solve your problems or anything.
But
if you can take a time-out
and look at your situation differently,
from a slightly different perspective,
you may realize this isn't so bad.
It could allow you
to find beauty in things.
Things that you didn't even notice before.
Hmm.
[wistful music playing]
Coffee really does… have
the… the power to do that.
Coffee has that power.
It really does. Did you know that?
Don't you think?
Mm. Oh, you might be right, actually.
-[Kazu] Mm.
-[chuckles]
[Kazu] I think so.
[heart beating]
[music soars]
[music fades]
[rhythmic pop music playing]
[music ends]