[blows]
[gentle ethereal music playing]
No.
Why are you just watching me sleep?
Good morning.
Don't "good morning" me.
Huh?
What?
Were you out?
Mm. I was out connecting with nature.
-[Saeko] Hmm?
-[chuckles] You know what?
You're really adorable
whenever you're asleep.
[both laugh]
When you love a person's sleeping face,
they say that's the sign of true love.
[laughs] Really?
No! It's the truth!
[laughs] It is!
And when you're asleep, you're so cute.
It's like, I don't know, you look
even prettier when you're resting.
-Huh?
-[chuckles]
Sorry, I'm just kidding. That's not true.
-[laughs]
-Here I come!
[Saeko laughing] Whoa! Hold on!
Hey, wait! The sand!
-[Yusuke] Come on. It's totally fine!
-The sand!
[Yusuke sighs joyfully]
Listen.
Can you feel
the joy you bring to my heart?
Listen.
No, I can't.
[Yusuke breathes deeply]
Well, that's strange.
All right. Try this.
Listen to the sound of my heart right now.
Just feel this heartbeat.
Such a peaceful rhythm.
[both laugh]
Isn't it comforting?
Uh, where does this leave us?
'Cause I know that Yusuke…
said exactly what you're saying now.
Yusuke?
He was the man I loved.
[wistful music playing]
He died.
Yusuke Nakamachi.
His name was…
Yusuke…
Do you think that…
[music fades]
Oh. Hey, you!
Shinoda!
-[Shinoda] Uh…
-Uh, what is it now?
[Shinoda] Well, nothing now.
Um, wasn't your phone ringing?
[Saeko] Huh? Oh, I'm sorry.
Well, it's okay. It's just…
Just what?
[Shinoda chuckles]
Uh, wait a sec.
Is it working now?
[Shinoda] Well, yeah.
[Saeko gasps]
You're kidding! That's great!
[machine whirring]
Whoa!
[laughing]
[Shinoda laughs]
What's this?
Listen to it work.
Mm. It sounds good.
-Didn't I tell you? Just plain fate.
-[Saeko giggles]
I knew exactly
how to get it running again.
Look. The sun's come out
as if to celebrate our fateful meeting.
[rhythmic electronic music playing]
EMERGENCY BLANKETS
[Kazu] Okay, thank you.
Sure, just leave them there.
-I'll leave these here too.
-Thank you very much.
YUSUKE NAKAMACHI
[pensive music playing]
TRANSIT BUS CAUGHT IN AN AVALANCHE
FALLS OFF A CLIFF IN OTARU, HOKKAIDO
[inaudible]
[music fades]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
It's annoying how gorgeous the view is.
[wind whistling]
[Saeko breathes deeply]
[Saeko] I'm still in shock.
[Kazu] Yeah.
[Saeko] Yusuke is…
His spirit continues…
to live on
as the heart that beats in you.
[Kazu] Yes.
Thanks to the transplant from him…
I'm alive and well.
At that point, my heart
had reached its limit.
I'm very grateful.
I can't thank him enough, in fact.
That's nice of you.
So you and your family…
you're happy… now that you're healed?
Yes.
[laughs]
He really is wonderful.
Yusuke is still spreading joy,
even after his death.
What an angel.
Is it really true though?
We don't have evidence
since they'll never give us
the information
about who the donor was
or who received the transplant.
Is this just a coincidence,
and we're pretending like it's something?
There was a letter.
Did you receive it?
A thank-you letter.
Huh?
I wrote these words for you.
"If there's anything I can do…
to ensure your happiness, I would do it."
"I know I'm far away…
and I know it's not up to me."
-"Still, I can't--"
-"I can't help it
if that's how I really feel."
I also wrote a reply letter.
"Is the heart of the person I loved…"
"Is that heart still beating"?
"'Cause I always thought that
his heart was a little mischiev--"
[Kazu] "…a little mischievous."
"I hope it's not… getting you
into trouble."
[gentle piano music playing]
This is all real.
[Saeko sighs]
So you and I…
We never should have met, should we?
Well, I'm glad either way…
that I got to see you.
Uh, that's very kind of you.
Still, it's weird.
I can't wrap my head around
what's happening.
But I'm also glad…
that we found each other.
[music intensifies]
Uh, can I show you something?
There, that's him.
Yusuke.
[chuckles]
I like him.
He looks nice.
[Kazu chuckles]
[music fades]
Ah! Uh…
The next one won't come for a while!
What? Uh…
-[Saeko] Hey, um…
-Oh!
[Saeko] Yusuke, see you later.
[Kazu] I'll come again.
Hey. Hurry! Let's go!
Ah! No!
-[Kazu] You're fast. Whoa!
-Whoa! Hey! You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
[Saeko] I'll hail the bus.
[both panting]
[Kazu] Oh no.
[both continue panting]
[gentle guitar music playing]
[Kazu] Thank you.
-Itadakimasu.
Wow.
[laughs] I know, right?
[chuckles] Yeah.
Can I… say something?
It's just you never hesitate
to be the center of attention.
You and Shinoda are so passionate.
Are you all like that?
[chuckles] Where I work?
[both laughing]
You might be right.
We're not needlessly humble,
that's for sure.
"Amazing work." "Yes, I did my best."
"Everyone's doing great."
-Yeah. We're all like that.
-Mm.
That's why I like working there, I guess.
I see.
[music fades]
Well, I guess you want to know
what I've been going through.
I mean, how it feels to have
Yusuke's heart beating inside of me.
-[Saeko] If it's all right.
-Yeah, it's fine.
I'm not sure
if I can explain it very well, but…
I believe it has his memories.
It's the only explanation I can think of.
Memories?
Yes.
His heart
carries his memories…
like a brain, almost.
I still live my own life
as Naruse every day.
But… occasionally,
Yusuke's memories come alive.
And the memories don't feel like
they belong to me either.
No. Yusuke is here inside
but as a separate part of my body.
Like, I play piano now,
even though I've never played before.
What?
It goes like…
[humming "I Want You Back"
by The Jackson 5]
Something like that.
The island of Hawaii…
Have you ever been there
recently?
Did you play it at the airport?
Yes.
In May with my wife.
[wistful piano music playing]
[inhales sharply]
So you were
there?
Yes.
Well, now I don't know what to say.
Hey…
Yes?
Can I listen to…
his heartbeat right now?
[music fades]
Yes.
[wind whistling]
[sobs]
[emotional music playing]
[Saeko sniffles]
I'm sorry.
[emotional music continues]
[music fades]
So I found out.
Hmm? What's that?
I found the person who owned this heart.
Who they were.
Like when we were driving the other day--
I don't wanna hear it.
What?
Don't say anything.
I know you wanna find out who they were.
I don't wanna know though.
So don't tell me anything.
I'm sorry.
I'm thankful to the person
who let you live.
Truly.
[Kazu] Mm.
I also know that what they had
in their life… their memories,
all of it remains inside you.
[Miki sighs]
However,
I've decided to accept that
as a part of you.
All of it.
And to love you regardless.
But… I don't wanna know.
I'm sorry.
I just don't need to know
who this other person was.
[Kazu] Mm.
I'm so sorry.
It's all right.
[wistful music playing]
I understand.
It's fine.
Miki?
Thank you.
Mm.
-[woman 1] Oh, look.
-[Kazu] It's ready!
[Miki] Is it all done?
-[woman 2] Wow!
-Whoa!
-[Yuma] Wow!
-Come over here, Yuma.
-Looks great, Naruse!
-It's finally ready.
-[Yuma] It looks so good! Ooh!
-[Tomo] That looks delicious!
Wow!
-It's so good. Yeah.
-Is it?
-That's great!
-That's great.
-[woman 1] He's right.
-Mmm. So good.
-You sure? I'm so glad.
-Mm!
I'm glad he's done.
He was making a mess all over the floor.
[sentimental music playing]
[indistinct chattering]
They say they need more chairs.
I'll contact the supplier
and see how soon they can get them ready.
-Go for it.
-Okay.
-I've got this.
-Thank you so much.
-[Saeko] Oh wow! This one is really chic.
-[student 1] Yeah.
[Saeko] Oh, this is nice too though.
-[student 2] Right, right.
-Yeah.
-[student 3] It's a very pleasant design.
-It really is.
[students 1 and 3] Naruse.
-[student 2] Should we leave it to him?
-[student 3] Let's have him pick.
-'Cause we can't seem to decide.
-[Kazu] What's this?
-But they're all so cute.
-Naruse, we need you to choose one.
-Oh, are these all the logo designs?
-It's hard to pick just one, right?
-To you, which one is the best?
-Oh, well…
Hmm. This is a hard one.
[rhythmic electronic music playing]
[woman] I think there's one more.
[woman 2] Yeah, yeah.
[chuckles]
You ready now?
Yep.
Wait! A little longer.
[Kazu] Hm.
Hmm.
All right.
-Three, two…
-Two…
-Oh!
-Oh! Yes!
[Saeko laughs]
I was right.
Let's have this one be
the main coffee, then.
Yep.
It's very crowded at the moment.
Please wait a little longer.
Here's a menu for you to look at
while you wait.
CAFÉ RUN BY UNIVERSITY STUDENTS OPEN
Now, pour the beans in like this…
And then…
Keep going.
Don't shake it a bunch like that.
-Okay. Got it.
-Do it in one go.
Eh… Yup. Looks great!
[Shinoda] And later,
we'll add another bag.
-[student 3] Here. I brought a new one.
-[Shinoda] Oh, keep pouring, then.
How is it?
Oh, please. Don't bother.
We're doing great.
Yeah, I figured.
Are we all like this?
-Huh?
-Hmm? Oh, it's nothing. Never mind.
Hawaiian Kona, is it?
Yeah.
-These beans are great.
-Mm.
[sniffs]
-[student 6] Hi, Naruse.
-Hi there.
Huh? Hey there.
This is amazing, isn't it?
It's a huge hit.
Naturally.
Oh, of course.
[quietly] We are all like that.
Huh?
Ah… Right. Oh, nothing.
[ethereal music playing]
Isn't this whole situation crazy?
It's all for real.
Yusuke's heart continues to live on
in Naruse's body, along with his memories.
That's incredible, don't you think?
[sighs]
So, what's he like?
He's nice.
He's a really good guy. Very kind.
You'll meet him and see.
Oh. Is that right?
[Saeko] Hmm?
His heart, huh?
What is it?
Well, I… I don't wanna meet this guy.
Why not?
You should probably stop seeing him too.
You may be right.
Yusuke's heart
could carry his memories somehow.
Still, he's not the same guy.
He isn't Yusuke.
It's not like Yusuke's really there.
I know that.
[sighs]
Why would you say that?
It's not just 'cause Yusuke's
somewhere inside.
You're falling for this guy, aren't you?
[laughs]
What are you talking about, Kengo?
Well, are you?
I swear it isn't like that.
I personally think you should stop this.
Right now.
I can't.
Because Yusuke's in there.
I can listen and hear his heart beating.
It knows I'm there too. I swear.
So Yusuke hasn't totally left this world.
I have to keep going. I won't stop.
[groans]
Well, do whatever you want,
but I'll pass.
How can you pass on this?
[wistful music playing]
Good night.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Kengo] I'm sorry.
[music fades]
Welcome.
[Kazu] Oh.
[gasps]
What?
Uh, sorry about that.
Hold on. Are you
Naruse?
What?
Oh. Thank you so much.
So you heard about me
from Sugawara, right?
Yes.
Ah.
When I searched for Nakamachi,
this café popped up.
Ah… I understand.
I found my way here…
as if I'd been to your café before.
Oh, really?
This is a really nice café you've got.
It was Yusuke.
Excuse me?
It was Yusuke who took care of the plant.
I told him there's no way a coffee tree
would grow in Hokkaido.
Still, he was confident
it would thrive here.
Oh, really?
When you came in and you saw me,
it looked like you recognized me.
Oh.
I did. I'm sorry.
So you really… You really remember me?
Yes.
[breathes shakily, sobs]
Seriously? What the hell?
[sniffles]
I apologize.
I can't help but feel…
[breathes shakily]
…like I'm making things difficult
for everyone.
[wistful piano music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[train brakes squeal]
[wistful music continues]
-[Kazu] Saeko.
-Huh?
Oh.
When you were down…
what would Yusuke do…
to help you feel better?
[music fades]
Please tell me.
No, I'm all right.
[Kazu] I'd really like to know.
Hey.
[Saeko] He would start dancing.
What?
But he was good. Breakdancing, especially.
You're lying. [laughs]
No, I'm not.
He'd dance like crazy.
Spinning on his head,
jumping high, flipping around.
Well, um…
-Really?
-Dance for me.
Well, I wonder…
if his heart remembers how.
It could.
Like… like this?
[grunting]
[Saeko] I lied.
[Kazu] Huh?
I apologize, but I lied.
[chuckles]
[laughs] What? Really?
Are you serious? That's not fair.
I was attempting to do it.
I thought I would start breakdancing
if I tried.
[chuckles]
Come on. That was really mean.
That could've been a disaster.
What if I fell?
[laughs] That's why I stopped you
before you started.
[Kazu] No, no.
Sure, that's true, still…
[Saeko giggles]
Maybe I should've waited a little longer.
[both laughing]
No matter how absurd,
he'd do anything for you.
That's how he was.
If you could listen to his heart…
until the next train arrives…
would that ease your pain?
[melancholy music playing]
[Kazu] At this point, I don't know
where my own feelings lie.
I love my wife more than anything.
And that's never going to change.
However…
I can't help
but keep thinking about Saeko.
I truly want her to find
peace in this world.
And I wanna make her happy.
It's overwhelming.
[breathes shakily]
How can I trust these myself?
Do these feelings belong to me,
or do they belong to Yusuke?
I wanna see her.
I believe these feelings are mine,
but I don't know.
Why can't I figure this out?
[sniffles]
What should I do?
I just don't know.
Why can't I decide?
[sniffles]
I can't go on like this.
[melancholy music continues]
RANKOSHI STATION
[music fades]
[sighs]
[rhythmic pop music playing]
[sighs happily]
[Miki] You're back!
I wondered where you were.
-Well, I'm back.
-[Miki chuckles]
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[music ends]