[tender piano music playing]
[Yusuke] Okay. There you go.
[Saeko] Thank you.
Today, around the world,
we should all be celebrating you.
Mm-hmm. Honoring the birth of Saeko.
-[chuckles] Come on.
-[laughs] Yeah, yeah.
The world's brighter now
because Saeko's here in it.
It's a happier world just
having you exist at all.
I'm serious.
Thank you
for being in this world.
Thank you.
Happy birthday, Saeko.
[softly] Thank you.
[giggles] Ugh! I might cry.
-Just kidding.
-[both laugh]
You're kidding?
-You're not crying?
-No.
You have tears in your eyes.
Stop giving me that face.
[both laugh]
[music fades]
[Kazu] I'm sorry about…
Oh.
I'm sorry… about the other day.
I told you I'd be here
to wish you a happy birthday, but I, uh…
[chuckles]
Honestly, I was, uh…
I was kinda looking forward to seeing you.
Oh. I'm really sorry.
I re… I really am… really, really sorry
I didn't make it that day.
It's fine.
You don't have to keep saying sorry.
I wanted you to come,
though, technically,
it wasn't you I wanted to see.
Can I explain something to you?
Okay.
It's strange. Sometimes you…
you say things exactly how he would.
A guy I was in love with.
You don't look alike or anything.
You've got different faces.
Although… it shocked me
'cause, in some ways, you're so alike.
It's like
I started seeing him in you a little.
It was fun for a while.
I could look forward to… to
us spending time here on the train.
He really was the love of my life.
I'm sure it's better if I stop doing this.
I probably should.
So I'm sorry.
Oh, no. That's…
Why'd you apologize?
You haven't done anything wrong.
I don't like it though.
I do like to think back. All the memories.
But it also makes me sad.
And what if I started
confusing you with him?
And I end up falling for you, huh?
That wouldn't be very good.
It'd be wrong,
and it'd cause problems for you.
And for me too.
And besides,
you're not even my type at all.
[laughs]
[Kazu] Oh… I see.
I'm sorry.
That was really rude of me to say.
That's okay. It's…
Yeah, I guess it was.
To be honest, I was thinking
I'd start taking a different train
so we wouldn't see each other.
It wouldn't work, though,
'cause there aren't many
other trains to take.
So we'll just have to make do.
We both can say hi and stuff and be nice
and leave it there.
And nothing else. Just being polite.
Anyway,
thank you for everything.
Uh, hold on.
So this guy…
I, uh…
That's all right.
[chuckles]
[wistful music playing]
Yeah. So that was it.
[music fades]
Like a mini-love story taking place
over rides on a train
with a guy who kind of reminds the girl
of her late fiancé.
[Kengo laughs]
A love story between you and that guy?
No. No way. It's not like that at all.
-Are you sure?
-Yeah, of course.
So he was really that much like Yusuke.
Oh.
Would you wanna meet him?
No.
No, I wouldn't.
He's not Yusuke.
No, I guess not. He isn't.
You're right about that.
You gonna be okay?
Hmm? Mm-hmm. I'm fine.
You know,
I just don't want you getting hurt.
You went through a lot.
Mm. Thank you.
[chuckles]
-[Yuma] He's coming. Hurry up!
-[man 1] Hurry, let's go.
-[Kazu] Okay.
-[man 1] We'll get stuck in traffic.
-[Yuma] Come on, hurry!
-Sorry I'm late.
[Yuma] We're gonna miss
the beginning of the fireworks!
[Kazu sighs]
We're really gonna see 'em, aren't we?
[Miki] Mm.
Just like you said we would.
You said I'd see the fireworks.
Yeah, I did.
[both laugh]
-I thank you, ma'am.
-[laughs] You're silly.
[both laugh]
[Yuma] Uncle! Auntie!
[Kazu] Hi!
You know…
[Miki] Hmm?
I told you that
the doctor said that, medically,
there's no explanation for it, right?
[Miki] Mm-hmm.
But I'm still feeling…
feeling someone,
like, inside, this strange feeling.
It hasn't gone away.
I…
Well, I wonder if this someone is
the one who gave his heart to me.
The reason that I'm still here.
[emotional music playing]
Because it's like…
I really think
I've got memories of his in my head.
Organ transplant is
still kind of… a mystery.
No one knows what's possible for sure.
The doctor said
there's so much we don't know.
So,
I just gotta keep living like this.
Living with his memories.
And that's it.
[Miki] Hmm.
[Kazu] I'm sorry.
[Miki] Mm.
[chuckles]
There's nothing to apologize for, okay?
Mm.
[Miki] What can you do? You know me.
I'm ready. You need me,
you know I'm here for whatever it is.
Thanks, sweetie,
for your support here.
Mm-hmm. You got it.
Hmm.
-[Miki] Anyway…
-Hmm?
How do I look in this? Huh?
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's just you're so beautiful
I didn't know what to say.
[both laugh]
-What? Well, you better figure it out.
-[laughs] Sorry, sorry.
[man 2] Miki! Thanks for waiting!
Come on!
-Let's go.
-Mm.
[crowd chanting]
[announcement] The fireworks show
is about to begin.
The fireworks show…
[Kengo] Ah, finally.
[man 3] Is it starting soon?
[Saeko] Yusuke loved fireworks, didn't he?
[laughs]
Oh man, he was the "fireworks are my life"
kind of guy. You know how he was.
[laughs] He was so funny.
Uh-huh. He was like…
When he was making his plan
for his proposal…
[laughs]
"Oh my God!
I need fireworks when I propose."
"I gotta do it like, 'Will you marry me?'"
Then, after a beat, just…
"Swoosh! That's the way to go!"
[laughs]
[Kengo] Man, that sure was
a hell of a lot of work. Right, guys?
[all laughing]
[Saeko] Thank you.
Yusuke looked happy too.
The last thing I saw him do was smile
as he watched the fireworks.
That's good though.
Thanks for having me over tonight.
The firework festivals happen every year.
Gotta get used to it.
[sentimental music playing]
[crowd oohing]
[Kazu] Wow! Look at that!
-[Kazu] Aren't they great?
-[Miki] Amazing!
-[woman 1] So pretty!
-[Kazu] Yeah.
[man 4] There they go. Still going.
[Kazu] Here they go! Whoo!
[all exclaim excitedly]
[Miki] Look at the colors!
They're so beautiful!
-[boy] They're so bright!
-[Kazu] Yeah!
[boy] Wow!
[Miki] It's incredible, right?
How many they do.
-[fireworks explode]
-[crowd exclaims]
[crowd oohing]
[boy] Wow!
[crowd exclaims]
[boy] So cool!
[sentimental music continues]
[crowd exclaiming]
Oh! Ah! There they go!
Okay!
Here they go! Here they go! Here they go!
Look! Bang!
[all cheering]
[Yusuke] Fireworks are the best!
Otaru is the best!
[all cheering]
Yukata Saeko is the best! That's right!
Saeko!
[man 5] Oh, look, there's more!
Fireworks are the best!
[all cheering]
[man 5] Otaru is the best!
[man 5] Fireworks are the best!
[all cheering]
[crowd exclaiming]
[music fades]
It was so cool. Oh, no, no, Yuma! Hey!
Yuma, get back here!
[Kazu] And he's gone.
So, I've, uh, been thinking a bit.
[Kazu] Hmm?
Mm, I don't like to think about it…
Hmm… [laughs]
…but I thought
if our situations were reversed…
-If what?
-Um…
Ugh, how should I put this?
Um… Well, let's say, for instance,
if the donor of your new heart was
in love in their life,
if they were married,
or if they had a partner…
Mm-hmm.
…then they died,
leaving that loved one behind…
If that person…
If their heart is still beating,
alive inside someone else,
do you think all of their memories
would still exist of their love in life?
-Mm.
If they do,
do you think the bereaved…
would wanna meet that heart?
If I were her…
I think I'd want to.
Something to think about.
[ship horn blaring in distance]
-Midori.
-[Midori crying]
Hey.
Are you… Oh.
[inhales sharply]
Oh… I'm sorry. [sniffles]
You wanna talk about work
and forget you saw this?
Or do you… [sniffles]
…wanna know why
I'm sitting in here crying?
Uh, well…
Tell me?
Thank you. [sobs]
Let's talk while we eat.
Yeah, just sit down.
I'm gonna eat.
[Saeko] Mm.
Ooh, I got eel!
[Midori sobbing]
[Midori sniffles]
[whimsical music playing]
Long story short,
it's always been
my fate to have success in career,
but not when it comes to love. [sniffles]
Seriously. I'm so unlucky
that all I can think is it must be fate.
Something always ends up going wrong
whenever I fall in love.
There's no hope for me.
[sniffles]
Mm! I know it's fate.
It's my fate.
From the way I'm learning to see things,
sometimes the word fate is used
when someone thinks
that something's been decided already.
I don't really believe that.
I mean, don't you feel like
fate's actually up to us?
[Midori] Hmm?
[Saeko] Yeah, like,
while we're here, alive,
we're constantly making choices
all day long.
It's just one decision after another.
And what determines our futures
is… is connected to those decisions.
I feel like you make your own path
in the world.
You harness it yourself.
I get that.
So I feel like good choices
bring good things to us,
and bad choices bring bad things.
And it's no one else's fault.
That's how we should
think about the world.
That should go for both
our work lives and love lives.
It's not fate or anything like that.
-[Midori] Mm.
-Midori.
Let's consider the choices we make
and stop thinking our lives
have been decided.
If we keep trying, none of us know where
life's adventures will take us, do we?
[Midori] Mm-hmm.
[laughs]
Mm. That's true.
[Midori chuckles]
What's going on with you?
So all you needed was to cry and then put
food in your mouth, and you're better now?
Ah, I'm sorry. But thanks.
[both laugh]
[Saeko laughs] It's okay.
What am I doing lecturing you on fate?
[Midori] Mm.
Huh? Didn't you wanna talk about work?
Okay. So I've got two projects
that I need help with.
I'll let you choose. Or should I choose?
Do you wanna pick which one?
Since you just explained to me
your thoughts on fate, you wanna choose?
Mm… Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Do you wanna make a presentation
opposite a competitor?
Challenging, exciting…
Or something smaller and easier,
but it doesn't pay as well
as the first one does.
Although it does seem like
a good investment for the future.
What'll it be?
Hmm…
Mm…
[muffled] Uh, well…
[whimsical music playing]
[student] Good morning.
Hey, buddy.
What are you looking at?
I heard today's gonna be….
One, two, three, four,
five, and six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five…
[indistinct shouting]
A lot of our students
are into good coffee.
We've had several requests
to have it here.
Oh, I see.
Is this it here?
Yep, we've just been using it for storage.
[Saeko] Really?
[gasps] What have you got here?
It's gorgeous!
I know, right? It's fantastic!
-[Saeko gasps]
-Huh?
Huh? What are you doing here?
I, uh…
I think I should be asking you
the same question.
Huh? I'm here for work.
Ah! For the coffee thing we're doing?
I'm Saeko Sugawara. I work for Akane.
Oh…
Kazumasa Naruse from Student Affairs.
[woman] Looks like you know each other.
[Saeko chuckles]
So what happened?
-Huh? What do you mean?
-With this!
Oh! I think it was just left here
from before. They said to throw it out.
Really?
It's a coffee roaster of some sort?
Yeah, that's right.
Wow, that's cool.
Oh, it's great!
And it's quite old from the looks of it.
I think I saw a picture of one of these
same machines while doing research.
Ah, is that right?
I don't think you get it.
It's like finding something
off the Titanic.
[chuckles] What?
It's really that old, huh?
So I went a little overboard,
but it's really great.
Oh, I see. All right.
I'm sorry. Um…
-You mind if I send the office a photo?
-Yeah, that's fine.
Go ahead.
-All right. Well, I gotta get back.
-Okay.
-I'll leave you to it.
-Thank you so much.
It's great.
[phone camera clicks]
[Saeko] Ah…
-[phone camera clicks]
-Wow.
[Saeko sighs]
Wait.
Did you say you were getting rid of it?
Yeah. They said to throw it out
so we can store more potatoes.
No, no, no, no!
That cannot happen. You can't do that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Saeko sighs]
It's weird, huh?
What's going on here?
Huh?
Oh, forget it.
[phone buzzing]
Ah, excuse me a sec.
Hello.
Yes, that's right.
Yeah, I know! It's an amazing discovery.
Yeah. Right.
[excited] Seriously?
Yes.
Ah! Okay, I understand.
Yeah, I'll check back in later.
All right, I'll let 'em know.
Thank you.
So here's the thing.
Apparently, what you have here
is an old PROBAT machine.
There are only a few people in Japan
who know how to repair them.
And one of these guys
is a craftsman where I work
and is an expert on these old things.
Oh yeah?
The man's on his way over now.
He said that he got emotional seeing it.
[both laugh]
So this thing… Ah!
So it's… it's really great, isn't it?
Mm-hmm.
It's fate, I guess you could say.
Yeah.
Right?
Huh?
-Ah…
-Oh.
Or…
Or a… a coincidence. A random event.
I think sometimes we use the word fate
when, actually, it's just a coincidence.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I guess you're right. Coincidence.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[feel-good music playing]
-[Kazu] Miss Sugawara.
-Hmm? Oh.
I, uh… I wasn't sure if I should
offer our coffee to such an expert.
However, you might wanna see
what we've been working with
as a starting point.
-Here you go.
-Ah, well, thank you so much.
-Looks great.
-Enjoy.
-Here we go.
-Okay.
Hmm…
This kind of coffee
makes you wanna be quiet.
Oh, it does?
-Yeah.
-Sorry.
No, it's okay. It does have potential.
This is a really great space.
I like it.
It's nice.
Mm.
Well, thanks. Glad you like it.
In this kind of setting,
the coffee should make people wanna
talk and connect with each other.
[Kazu] Mm.
Mm. So I think
we should go for something a bit lighter.
I'm sorry.
I never used to like drinking it,
so I'm new to it.
I've just now gotten interested.
Mm. Is that right?
Yeah.
I had a pretty large operation.
And after that,
I had lots of changes going on.
I started to like coffee, for example.
[Saeko] Mm.
I've never heard of that before.
[Kazu] Mm.
[gentle piano music playing]
Welcome to my obsession.
[both laugh]
Ah, thank you.
My personality changed too, a little.
[Saeko] Mm.
So…
Yeah.
[chuckles] What is it? Tell me what?
I wondered how I reminded you of
the person you were in love with.
-Oh.
-Oh, I'm sorry.
No, that's okay.
Uh…
What was he like? Was he fun to be around?
[chuckles]
Yeah. So much fun.
-[laughs]
-Really?
So maybe I reminded you of him
'cause I changed.
Originally, I was kinda boring.
I wasn't really
the life-of-the-party kind of guy.
[Saeko] Mm.
Was he a big coffee fan?
Oh yeah.
I mean, so much so, he even had a café.
Really? Wow.
But I brewed coffee
better than he did. [laughs]
Is that right?
I really did love him, you know?
He died though.
What?
[music fades]
-Ah.
-Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, no. I'm sorry. We're working.
I shouldn't have mentioned it.
No, no. I shouldn't have asked you.
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
So…
I wanna do this right.
To do a good job.
Of course.
Looking forward to it.
-[Shinoda] Hey. Where is it?
-Ah!
-Show me!
-Shinoda. Over here.
-Where is it?
-[Kazu] What?
-This way?
-Uh…
Uh… [splutters]
Ooh…
Ah…
Yeah.
[laughing]
You can find one if you really want to.
This is fate, right?
[feel-good music playing]
Was it you?
[Kazu] Huh?
This.
[Kazu] Oh! Yes.
Ah…
Thank you.
Oh, no. That's all right.
[Shinoda] I can't thank you enough.
Now let's get started.
Don't worry. I'll get you running.
[wind whistling]
[woman] Looks like it's going to be
a pretty big one.
Do you think the trains will be okay?
[man] I think it'd be better
if we went home early.
[reporter] It is currently moving
northeast over the Sea of Japan
at 20 kilometers per hour
and is expected to make landfall
in Hokkaido soon.
With the typhoon bearing down,
Hokkaido is now in the storm zone.
Hey, where's Shinoda?
Oh. He just left for the university.
[woman] Said he was worried about
the coffee roaster.
Huh?
Is he gonna be okay?
-[man 1] I got this one!
-[man 2] Okay, okay!
[man 1] There.
-We need to take this off!
-Yeah! Wait, wait, wait!
-It should be easy!
-[man 2] Wait a sec!
[man 1]You got it?
-[man 2] I got it!
-Okay! Good!
[man 1] All right, now the other one!
-Okay!
-[man 2] All right!
That's it!
[man 1] Hand it to me!
[phone line ringing]
[Kazu] Hello.
Oh my God, sweetie, hi.
You okay over there?
-Mm. How are things where you are?
-[student 1] Here they are, Kazumasa.
-Ah, in the back.
-We're bringing the apples in right now.
I think we got here just in time.
That's good.
They've stopped all the trains.
We opened the lounge
to students who are stuck.
I think I'm staying
till we're all able to go home.
[student 2] Pass out the extras!
-Mm. Be careful, all right?
-[student 2] Thank you!
And take care of your mom and dad.
-[knocking at door]
-[guard] Come in.
Hello.
-[guard] Hi.
-How's it going?
Good. Nothing too major.
Okay, that's good.
I hope it calms down soon.
Well, looks like
the storm will last quite a while.
Tonight's gonna be a long one.
Yeah, I guess so.
The rain really is coming down.
[guard] Mm.
[Kazu] Hmm?
[uplifting music playing]
Oh!
I'll bring it back!
[thunder rumbling]
[Kazu] What are you…
What are you doing out here in all this?
[Saeko] What? Ah! The wind was so strong
when I got out of the taxi!
I couldn't move.
But I'm fine. Really.
I don't want you to worry about it!
-No! You're not fine at all!
-Huh?
It's only gonna get worse.
Here! Put this on!
I'll take that.
Thank you for coming.
Mr. Shinoda… Is he all right?
He's okay. He's here.
Oh really? Thank goodness.
Are you okay?
Yes.
-Let's go.
-Uh…
[both panting]
[both laugh]
[uplifting music continues]
[tender music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[tender music continues]
[music fades]
[thunder rumbles]
[Shinoda] Ah. Ah, ah.
Shinoda.
Oh. You came.
Yes. I was worried about you.
Thought you'd get blown away.
[chuckles] No way. Not me.
[Saeko chuckles]
Looks like we'll be up all night.
Yeah.
It's a little exciting, huh?
Uh, staying at the college all night.
Anything could happen.
[chuckles]
POTATOES
[indistinct chattering]
[woman 1] We've got baked potatoes
with butter coming out.
-We ready?
-[Saeko] Yes, coming right up.
[crowd cheering]
You think we should get some coffee going?
Don't you think that'd be nice?
-[man] Good work today.
-Thank you.
[woman 1] It's pretty good. Pretty good.
[Saeko] Okay, here you go.
-[woman 3] Do we have any coffee?
-[woman 4] No…
-[Saeko] We have coffee.
-[student] Thank you.
[woman 3] Here you go.
Take some butter too.
[Saeko] There you go.
-Sorry. I can help out.
-[woman 3] Oh, welcome back.
[Saeko] Here you go.
Okay, great.
There's another pot right over there.
[Kazu] Ah, yeah, okay.
-[Saeko] Here you go, enjoy.
-Can I squeeze in?
I'll move this. I'll move this.
-Ah… Enjoy.
-Thank you so much.
[Saeko] Of course. Enjoy.
[woman 3] I got hot baked potatoes
with butter just for you.
-[Kazu] Nice and hot.
-Thanks.
-[Kazu] No problem.
-Thanks again.
-Here. Take care. It's hot.
-Great. Thanks.
Sure.
-Here.
-Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Careful, it's hot.
-Yeah, go ahead.
-[student 1] Thank you.
[woman 3] Here you go.
-[student 2] Thank you.
-[Kazu] Sure.
-Here you go.
-[student 3] Thank you.
Do you guys need a blanket?
-[student 4] Yes, please.
-Okay.
Excuse me. Is there any water left?
Water? I'll get some for you.
It's downstairs.
[both] Thank you.
Oh, I just love libraries.
Whoa. I don't know this one.
[wistful music playing]
[tender piano music playing]
[heart beating]
[moans]
What? No…
Why are you just watching me sleep?
[Saeko] Yusuke, come on, stop it.
I told you not to watch me sleep.
[gasps]
[music fades]
Uh…
Oh… Uh…
Sorry.
It's okay.
Um…
Yes?
There was…
There's something
that just now occurred to me.
Okay.
Do you mind if I tell you?
Go ahead.
I couldn't say it…
on your birthday.
I wanted to say…
happy birthday.
Today…
we should… be celebrating…
celebrating around the world…
honoring the birth of Saeko.
The world's brighter now because…
Saeko's here in it.
It's a happier world…
just having you exist at all.
Thank you…
for being in this world.
Thank you.
Happy birthday, Saeko.
What is this?
Why are you… doing this?
Yusuke?
[rhythmic pop music continues]
[music ends]